<Game>
	<Name>Aoi Blink (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This is an excellent little platform game. Well, it's pretty decent anyways. It's the same old story you've heard before: boy finds magical blue donkey-horse, boy's father goes missing, boy joins up with two convicted felons, a princess, and a bus driver to find boy's father. Yaaaawn.So you run around with a couple of your new-found friends and shoot things and jump on other things. Each has their own abilities, so you can switch between them all by pushing Select. The princess can jump really high, for instance, but she can't shoot. Whenever you fall into a pit, or lose all your life, Blink the magical flying blue donkey-horse comes along and saves you. Weird? Absolutely. But then, what did you expect from a TurboGrafx game?Translation Description:This translation also suffers from the affliction known as Disturbing Lack of an Apostrophe, but it won't really get in the way of enjoying the game. It's a platformer for God's sake. And the translation's complete, so enjoy it. Be prepared to sit at the title screen for about ten minutes if you want to read the back story.Reviewer: Spinner 8http://romhacking.net/trans/504/</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>West One</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>rJMk0Eb1NQo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20230</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588904-blue-blink</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/aoi-blink</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20230-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539367-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539368-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-map-of-the-first-area.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539369-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-start.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539370-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-first-stage.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539371-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-take-this.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539372-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-short-advice.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/539373-aoi-blink-turbografx-16-screenshot-second-stage.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/8/2/gfs_4304_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/5/2/gfs_4304_1_2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/2/gfs_4304_1_3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PsEmGic.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Based on a TV anime series (from the grandfather of manga Osamu Tezuka), Blue Blink is a cute platformer that manages to find its place among the crowd. The game is divided up into different areas, each represented by a map screen. Within these areas, you can choose your route to the end (by exiting levels at certain points). Throughout each area you have to find a 'master key' allowing you access to the boss - this can be hard to locate at times and requires lots of shooting at blank areas of screen just in case. Control of your character is original - on each stage you have three characters which you can choose between, with the CPU controlled ones following behind you like some bizarre congo line. The characters are preset and vary from stage to stage, and each one has different attributes. For example, some have very high jumping ability, whereas others are poor at jumping but have spread-shot weapons. Once you have found the master key and reached the final level in the area, you are entered into a boss battle, where you sit astride the titular donkey and attempt to fight your way to the next area.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>QwZbCGPvayA</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f052d83-9d1c-45d8-805b-73052d3192f7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1384d0b1-2c2f-4012-a38c-e7c715dd9e0e.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/afe6d2fa-9993-422c-a246-1c61d86c9f6b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aab09867-74f7-4e16-a7b4-a05422a3d7fa.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>