<Game>
	<Name>Bloody Wolf (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Snake and Eagle, two commandos of the Bloody Wolf special forces, receive instructions from their commander to destroy the enemy's heavily armed base to rescue the President and any allies who have been reported as MIA.Based off the 1988 arcade game, this single-player, top-down, run and gun shooter takes a nod to Contra-style gameplay, allowing one of the two mercenaries to blast their way through eight levels of enemy opposition armed with only a knife and a machine gun.  Along the way, new weapons such as shotguns, bazookas, flash bombs and grenades grenades can be added to the arsenal, as well as health and defensive power-ups.  Players can even find a motorcycle to ride in some areas, or swim through certain parts of a level.The President and your fellow soldiers need you!Cheat: Cheat CodesAt the title screen, press Up, I, Down, II, Left, I, Right, II. A sound will be heard if entered correctly.Cheat: Cheat CodesPress II, I, I, II, I, II, II, I at the title screen. Then press the following for the appropriate level:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Technologies, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>V3i4bdPzQjc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8190</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588903-bloody-wolf</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/bloody-wolf</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bloody-wolf/3030-2432/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/8190-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/6/3/51563_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251494-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251495-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-character-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251496-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-give-yourself-a-code.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251497-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-your-mission.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251498-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-stage-1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251499-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-free-the-hostages-from.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251500-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-dialogue.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251501-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-riding-a-motorcycle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251502-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-say-hello-to-shotgun.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/251503-bloody-wolf-turbografx-16-screenshot-inside-a-jeep.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/w90KfGX.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Snake and Eagle, two commandos of the Bloody Wolf special forces, receive instructions from their commander to destroy the enemy's heavily armed base to rescue the President and any allies who have been reported as MIA. Based off the 1988 arcade game, this single-player, top-down, run and gun shooter takes a nod to Contra-style gameplay, allowing one of the two mercenaries to blast their way through eight levels of enemy opposition armed with only a knife and a machine gun.  Along the way, new weapons such as shotguns, bazookas, flash bombs and grenades grenades can be added to the arsenal, as well as health and defensive power-ups. Players can even find a motorcycle to ride in some areas, or swim through certain parts of a level. The President and your fellow soldiers need you!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a88126d-317a-4eb6-bae6-fb9c20cc0dd3.JPG</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e86d85a-defb-4400-ac07-c9ad131041b1.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c9e3a404-bf5c-4993-bbd0-4296e0cba60f.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0facba54-f91e-4e5e-98ea-fafc8e0d71a6.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75ed90bd-46e3-4b8a-8686-90a29f621dd1.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/793b908a-d5d1-4a14-bb50-a494b01814ae.PNG</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>NEC</Publisher>
</game>