<Game>
	<Name>Bomberman (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bomberman is a maze-based arcade game, developed by Hudson Soft. The first in the Bomberman series, it unfortunately didn't contain any multiplayer. At the time it was well-received and today it is considered as a genre-defining video game. There has since been countless iterations on its blueprint and huge multiplayer communities around them.Story:Bomberman is a robot working at a bomb factory who gets bored of making bombs. He hears a rumor that anyone that makes it out from the underground factory gets a wish. Bomberman, desperate to escape, sets out on a journey to the surface. The only thing standing in his way is the factory security guards who will do anything to stop him. Spoiler alert: Bomberman will turn into Runner when he reaches the surface.Other VersionsThe Famicom version differed slightly from the MSX original, so the Famicom version was ported back to the MSX under the title "Bomber Man Special".European versions were released under the names "Eric and the Floaters" (MSX/Spectrum) and Dyna Blaster (Amiga, Atari ST, and PC)Cheat: Stage and Item SelectStart a new game and get 300 points as your Hi Score. Lose all your lives and select "End" to go back to the title screen. Now, wait until the Demo screen appears and once it ends, as the title screen unfolds, hold Down + Button 1 + Button 2 + Select and press Run to start the game. When the intro is shown, press Run again (while still holding the buttons) and you'll enter the Stage and Item select screen.Cheat: Hidden Bonus Point ItemsThese items award you large amounts of points upon collection, but are all very difficult to find.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Technologies, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>reKN7IBUakY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5658</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588906-bomberman</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/bomberman</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bomberman/3030-20589/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5658-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5658-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45924-bomberman-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97724-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97725-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97726-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-map.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97727-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-first-round.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97728-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-just-laid-a-bomb.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97729-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-destroyed-an-enemy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97730-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-get-into-the-exit.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97731-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-dead.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97746-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-when-time-runs-out-these.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97747-bomberman-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-power-up.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5mmcSeC.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5658.png</clearlogo1>
</game>