<Game>
	<Name>City Hunter (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>City Hunter is based on the eponymous manga by Tsukasa Hojo. The story focuses on Ryo Saeba, a young man with a mysterious past, who founds the City Hunter team in Shinjuku, Tokyo. The City Hunter is an underground private detective agency, which takes care of particularly dangerous cases. In the game, the player is able to play through three of such cases, which are unrelated to each other and can be played in any order. The gameplay is essentially that of a side-scrolling shooter. The player navigates Ryo through the stages, dispatching of the frequently appearing enemies with his gun. The gameplay system is rather simple, without power-ups or different weapons, and with one items possible to carry at a time. The levels are usually designed as vast indoor areas, with many rooms Ryo can enter. The structure of the game also reveals mild adventure elements: often it is necessary to speak to a character, receive an item (such as a key), back-track to a previous area in order to reach a previously inaccessible room, etc.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/3/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>kCNDVh21UiQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18402</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588927-city-hunter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/city-hunter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/city-hunter/3030-51973/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18402-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807261-cityhunter001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807260-city_hunter_%28j%29-008.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807259-city_hunter_%28j%29-007.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807258-city_hunter_%28j%29-006.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807257-city_hunter_%28j%29-005.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807255-city_hunter_%28j%29-003.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807254-city_hunter_%28j%29-002.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807253-city_hunter_%28j%29-001.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/4/gfs_5027_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/8/9/gfs_5027_2_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KI16LxM.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Ryo Saeba - a "Sweeper", bodyguard for hire, handsome, talented and the finest shot in Shinjuku. He's also a monumental lecher who only accepts beautiful female clients and will do anything to get a peek at their bodies. But keeping watch on him is his partner Kaori, sister to his ex-partner who was killed on one fateful night. Kaori has talents herself, being able to produce enormous mallets seemingly from thin air whenever Ryo is acting up around the ladies - and she isn't afraid to use them. City Hunter is based on the very popular manga/anime by Tsukasa Hojo. The game itself is a kind of action/adventure split into several different 'stories', of which you can choose in any order (with the exception of the final chapter). Gameplay mostly involves running around buildings, shooting the bad guys that constantly appear ahead of you and trying out the doorways scattered around. These doors often lead to separate rooms, sometimes with that essential character in that you need to talk to to progress the story. Aside from armed mobsters, you'll also have to navigate around laser beams, crushing machines and spikes that shoot from the ground. Around each level you will also find a nurse to heal you - although stumbling into a room with a semi-naked gal inside has pretty much the same effect. As you progress through the levels, you also gain extra weaponry - the bazooka being particularly useful in a crowded room.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ca93980-d27e-45c6-912c-e9955e40f6cd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d94aff0a-8dbc-40b2-a1cd-e8a61b503c68.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1455d3b-bee5-4221-b308-9839f00fa10e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9390fb8e-5b0a-4f6d-9292-52a7df52e793.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>