<Game>
	<Name>Cross Wiber - Cyber Combat Police (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>An upgrade to the previous Cyber Cross, Cross Wiber provides similar platform fighting gameplay with various Power Rangers style transformations, but also throws in some side scrolling shoot 'em up action for a change of pace.http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Cross_Wiber.htmCheat: Cheat CodesEnter the following codes at the title screen:Cheat: Cheat CodesAll of the below cheats are to be entered on the Title Screen. You will hear a confirmation sound upon successful entry.Cheat: Reach the Mirrored Ninja BossFollow these steps to reach the Mirrored Ninja Boss:Cheat: Reach the Mirrored Ninja Boss-On scene 9, enter the elevator (first door) and go up to the 9th floor.-On the 9th floor go right and enter the first door you see, it will send you to the 7th floor.-On the 7th floor go right and enter the second door you see, it will send you to the 3rd floor.-On the 3rd floor go left and enter the first door you see, it will send you to the 2nd floor.-On the 2nd floor go left and enter the first door you see, it will send you to the 13th floor.-On the 13th floor go right to face the mirrored Ninja boss.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Face</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>dPgZxghWPFE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>31728</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/579914-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/31728-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/254941-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/574757-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/574758-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-being.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/574759-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-bow.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651746-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-animated.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651747-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-chapter.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651748-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-pink.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651750-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-flying.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651749-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-life.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651751-cross-wiber-cyber-combat-police-turbografx-16-screenshot-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/b/2/gfs_19747_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Cross Wiber: Cyber-Combat-Police is a sequel to Cyber Cross and follows the adventures of Cross Wiber, an special inspector of the cyber combat police. Several years after the happenings in Cyber Cross, a new threat threatens Earth: Duma and his alien forces. Wiber now starts his counter-attack on Duma. This game is a side-scrolling action game with emphasis on combat, but also with some platforming sequences. The player has the ability to switch between four forms: human and three robot suits. All those forms have different abilities, e.g. one robot has a special gun and the human can only kick to attack but is the only form which has a special attack taking up a bit of life energy. The power-ups which can be collected during play have different effects depending on the used form, e.g. as human everything gives life energy and as robots there are weapon and armor upgrades as well as ammo.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d9f2c3a5-59cd-4ed3-88d2-f43cf1f5e0c8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ec5605db-7e6d-4cb4-ab39-35e33007c291.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9af19289-66c1-4f0c-bfe4-f14cf2303ff4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/277abeae-7d22-4fe0-8179-d869311e564b.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sankindo</Publisher>
</game>