<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Egg! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A decent platform game. If you like these runny-jumpy affairs, this is a pretty good one. You're a teenage girl, and your grandpa (? some old guy) puts a dragon egg in your backpack and sends you on your way.As you acquire powerups, the egg starts to develop into a dragon. Instead of clubbing enemies with your silly mushroom stick, the fire button will make you swing the backpack with the now-hatched egg in it, and the baby dragon will breathe a little flame at the enemies. Eventually the dragon gets big enough where YOU ride IT, instead of you lugging it around. Fully powered-up, the dragon even has limited flying ability.You can buy health and items to make the flame breath longer and other junk, at shops along the way.http://baetzler.de/vidgames/Hu-reviews.varCheat: Cheat CodesAt the title screen, press the following buttons:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NCS</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>rgBDaveAXDM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18443</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588950-dragon-egg</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-egg/3030-36191/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18443-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/9/3/51693_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/1866366-4.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/1866365-3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/1866364-2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/1866363-1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/f/2/gfs_4984_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/2/2/gfs_4984_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/6/f/gfs_4984_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/b/f/gfs_4984_2_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/d/b/gfs_4984_3_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jSuyUlA.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>A girl and her egg, all alone in the cruel world. But this is not just an ordinary egg, collect or buy power-ups (from handy local stores) and out pops a little dragon's head, ready to swing round and breathe fire at anything that dares to get in your way. Collect enough of them and the dragon hatches fully, allowing you to ride on its back, spraying enemies with fire balls. All this is done over scenery ranging from woodlands to strangely un-fantasy like hi-tech fortresses.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/308d1406-e32c-4d62-b59c-8d75fe55cce0.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a0f5bf8-c2ad-4b1c-be22-f69386b096fc.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/68eb6adc-063d-4b25-b6d1-e5f0f0fdc74e.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60043eda-c08b-4c4e-90ea-897f3f391442.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>NCS</Publisher>
</game>