<Game>
	<Name>Energy (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Energy is a sci-fi themed action/shooter game exclusive to the PC Engine in which the goal is to save various people in a dilapidated city crawling with mutated monsters. The game has something of a Metroid feel to it - not only in the weird and occasionally disgusting monster design, but also in that Energy will often require a bit of backtracking for necessary items before progress can be made.The game is based on a PC-88 game from Quasar Soft named Ashe. Besides the big improvements to graphic and audio quality, the games seem functionally identical.Energy was widely regarded by critics at the time as being one of the worst PC Engine games. The game is plagued with coding issues (such as very slow transitions between screens) and the requirements to proceed are often inscrutable. It does have something of a cult following to this day, however. Cheat: Password for full weapons, shields and powerAs a password, enter:</plot>
	<releasedate>19/4/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Masaya</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>x2AkmF8b0wQ</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/579437-energy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/energy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/energy/3030-42797/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490852-energy_pce.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482893-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482894-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482895-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-go-hero-i-can-t-go-because.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482896-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-fighting-slimes-on-the-streets.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482897-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-don-t-worry-little-girl-i.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482898-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-wow-hanging-on-vines-and-contemplating.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482899-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-tough-situation-see-how-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482900-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-those-guys-are-kinda-cute.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482901-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-aww.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482902-energy-turbografx-16-screenshot-wee-i-m-afraid-of-water.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Energy is a side scrolling platform game by NCS/Masaya. It is based on Ashe, an obscure PC-8801 Japanese game originally released by Quasar Soft in 1988.  A powerful earthquake has released an army of mutant monsters all over the city of Tokyo. A small group of humans survived and from their underground hideout they decide to send a team to investigate and fight the threat. The player takes control of a young fighter with psionic powers (called 'ESP'), the only known of his kind. He can use these unique phsychic powers to also fire balls of energy, his only means of defense against the various mutants and monsters that crawl around the levels. The player also meets many supportive characters throughout the game that offer clues about the overall story.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>SAm4ZD5tsKs</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dab03a63-cee6-43da-8a14-f4b91d15b418.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94687a9a-c291-45c1-8d3d-c10439cafd04.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df16b5a3-58ac-47e7-8592-2bcee5d568ec.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9150ea3-ef3a-493e-9131-c7fb33db7de1.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Masaya</Publisher>
</game>