<Game>
	<Name>Fire Pro Wrestling 2 - 2nd Bout (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Fire ProWrestling 2nd Bout is an Action game, published by Human Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1991.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerPress the following buttons to choose the same wrestlers in Excite Series or Elimination Match:Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerIn World Championship Mode, after you've used up the 3 continues, wait until the words "Game Over" are on the screen, hold Button 2 and press Down, Left 3 times, Up 5 times, Right 4 times. If done right, you'll get 3 more continues.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the Super Tournament number of players select screen, hold Button 2 and press Up 5 times, Right 7 times, Down 3 times and Left 6 times. If done right, the 4 hidden wrestlers will also participate in the tournament.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the Elimination Match character selection screen, hold the following buttons to select between 4 hidden wrestlers:Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the Excite Series character selection screen, hold the following buttons to select between 4 hidden wrestlers:Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerWhile playing, press Select to pause the game and then press any of the following buttons:Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the title screen, hold Button 1 and press Right 2 times, Left, Down 5 times and Up. If done right, the title logo will change from red to blue.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the title screen, hold Button 1 + 2 and press Left, Up 3 times, Right, Down 6 times. If done right, the ending will start right away. In addition, do the Pro Mode code first and then do the ending code to see the 2nd loop ending.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the title screen, hold Right + Down and press Select. If done right, the music will stop. Now, press Select to cycle between the songs.Cheat: Choose The Same WrestlerAt the Excite Series mode, select the 1Player vs 2Players mode. Then select your characters and at the "Round # Start" screen, hold Right + Button 2 + Select and press Button 1. If done right, both players will be controller by the computer.Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesTo fight against the hidden Bosses, complete "World Championship Series" in either the Singles or Tag team division while under "Pro Mode". Once all the selectable wrestlers have been defeated, a special series of "Lumber Jack" matches will start with the hidden Bosses as your newest opponents.Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesTo unlock the very last match ...the "Special Bout", complete the "World Champion Series"  under Pro Mode in either the Singles or Tag Team division. Once all of the hidden Bosses have been defeated and the ending credits have finished, the "Special Bout" will start.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/8/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>31940</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588972-fire-prowrestling-2nd-bout</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/fire-pro-wrestling-2nd-bout</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/31940-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/4/f/gfs_4563_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/d/2/gfs_4563_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
</game>