<Game>
	<Name>Fire Pro Wrestling - Combination Tag (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Fire Pro Wrestling Combination Tag is a wrestling game and the first in the venerable Fire Pro Wrestling series from Human Entertainment (and later Spike). As with the games to follow, FPWCT allows the player to select from a range of fictional wrestlers (based on real wrestlers of the era) and compete in an isometric wrestling ring. The gameplay emphasizes timing and precision over hammering the button in order to land attacks and finishers and to get out of holds and pins.WrestlersThe following wrestlers are available. In every case there is a real life counterpart.Victory Musashi (Antonio Inoki)Akira Saeha (Akira Maeda)Tommy Bomber (Jumbo Tsuruta)Thunder Ryu (Genichiro Tenryu) Hurricane Rikimaru (Riki Choushou)Zombie Masa (Masa Saito)Pirate Number 1 (Billy Gasper) Pirate Number 2 (Barry Gasper)Star Bison (Stan Hanson)Big the Great Bull (Bruiser Brody)Mascara Condor (Mil M&#225;scaras)Mascara Eagle (Dos Caras)Bloody Allen (Bad News Allen)Mad Tiger (Tiger Jeet Singh) Knight Blaster (Road Warrior Hawk)Iron Blaster (Road Warrior Animal)Cheat: Hard ModeAt the title screen, hold I and press Right, Left 5 times, Down 2 times, Up. If done right, the screen will change from yellow to green.Cheat: Hard ModeYou need a multi tap for this to work. At the title screen, on Controller 5, hold Up + Right + I and press Select to cycle through the songs.Cheat: Hard ModeAt the title screen, select Single or TAG match. Then select "1P vs 2P" and choose your fighters. Now, at the "Round Start" screen, hold Up + II and press I. If done right, the computer will take over.Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesTo fight against the hidden Bosses R.J. Phase and Carlos Krauser, complete either the second singles or tag team tournament on "Hard Mode". Once all the selectable characters have been defeated, a special series of "Lumberjack Death Match" fights will  start with R.J. Phase and Carlos Krauser as your final opponents.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>31939</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588971-fire-prowrestling-combination-tag</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/fire-pro-wrestling-combination-tag</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fire-pro-wrestling-combination-tag/3030-42802/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/31939-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802432-fireprocombotag001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490998-fire_pro_wrestling_combination_tag_%28j%29-004.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490997-fire_pro_wrestling_combination_tag_%28j%29-003.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490996-fire_pro_wrestling_combination_tag_%28j%29-002.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490995-fire_pro_wrestling_combination_tag_%28j%29-001.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/0/c/gfs_4562_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/9/1/gfs_4562_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<Notes>The first in the critically acclaimed Fire Pro Wrestling series, allowing for rapid wrestling action with unprecedented number of moves and a large roster inspired by wrestling legends from around the world.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37a1e54f-ae37-4d83-bb93-f5f4b005fefd.JPG</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce13b5bd-b0bf-4b68-a18c-8cb0863bc56c.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be507529-fab9-4a16-ba55-dd5bb7faffc9.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84bf47ef-ecef-483a-9837-3383ddcd7759.png</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>Human</Publisher>
</game>