<Game>
	<Name>Galaga '88 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A slight evolution from Space Invaders, Galaga differs in that the enemy craft fly in from the sides of the screen to form up in groups ahead of you. Then, various craft will attack you in different ways - some will spin around as they get close, others will join together to perform super-craft.Each defeated wave moves you along a stage, which are split up by the regular appearance of scrolling levels with multiple encounters and bonus rounds. These bonus rounds are 'Galactic Dancing' and feature the enemies moving around the screen in time to a piece of music. Destroy them all for a huge bonus score. You ship itself has a simple single shot laser, but by strategically letting it be captured and rescued by alien flies, you can power it up into a double, then a super-triple ship for greater firepower, although it is easier to get hit.HINTS:- Galactic bonus -Just stand still (don't move) and don't shoot in the bonus stage.- Red capsule -Hold Up and press Run at the title screen. The capsule on the ship will turn red instead of blue to confirm code entry. Shoot the last target on the first level to capture the red capsule and power-up to a triple ship.http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Galaga_88.htmCheat: Hard ModeAt the title screen, hold Up and press Run.Cheat: Galactic bonusJust stand still (don't move) and don't shoot in the bonus stage.Cheat: Galactic bonusHold Up and press Run at the title screen. The capsule on the ship will turn red instead of blue to confirm code entry. Shoot the last target on the first level to capture the red capsule and power-up to a triple ship.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>L_E1nrbtQEE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5671</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588979-galaga-90</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/galaga-88</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/galaga-88/3030-14593/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5671-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5671-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79183-galaga-88-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323532-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323533-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-select-a-ship-single-or.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323534-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-stage-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323555-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-last-ship-attacks.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323556-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-bonus-round-galactic-dancing.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323557-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-stage-3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323558-galaga-88-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-screen-s-filling-up.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712422-galaga88001.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712421-galaga_%2788_%28j%29-001.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17245/569621-galaga__90__u__009.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0xpKmWX.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Galaga '88 (ギャラガ'88, Gyaraga 'Eiti Eito) is a 1987 fixed shooter arcade game by Namco. It is the third sequel for Galaxian (following Galaga, and Gaplus). It features significantly improved graphics over the previous games in the series, including detailed backgrounds, larger enemies and greater ship details. Although it was well received, fewer cabinets of this game were produced than of Galaga and Gaplus. The game runs on Namco System 1 hardware. First ported on the NEC PC Engine, it was later released on the North American TurboGrafx-16 under the name Galaga '90 and the Sega Game Gear in Japan under the name of Galaga'91 (ギャラガ'91, Gyaraga 'Nainti Wan), and in Europe under the name of Galaga 2.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d267e17-4a18-4b9c-8727-bbd0fdb0e8ac.jpg</boxart2>
</game>