<Game>
	<Name>Galaga '90 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A slight evolution from Space Invaders, Galaga differs in that the enemy craft fly in from the sides of the screen to form up in groups ahead of you. Then, various craft will attack you in different ways - some will spin around as they get close, others will join together to perform super-craft.Each defeated wave moves you along a stage, which are split up by the regular appearance of scrolling levels with multiple encounters and bonus rounds. These bonus rounds are 'Galactic Dancing' and feature the enemies moving around the screen in time to a piece of music. Destroy them all for a huge bonus score. You ship itself has a simple single shot laser, but by strategically letting it be captured and rescued by alien flies, you can power it up into a double, then a super-triple ship for greater firepower, although it is easier to get hit.HINTS:- Galactic bonus -Just stand still (don't move) and don't shoot in the bonus stage.- Red capsule -Hold Up and press Run at the title screen. The capsule on the ship will turn red instead of blue to confirm code entry. Shoot the last target on the first level to capture the red capsule and power-up to a triple ship.http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Galaga_88.htmCheat: Hard ModeAt the title screen, hold Up and press Run.Cheat: Galactic bonusJust stand still (don't move) and don't shoot in the bonus stage.Cheat: Galactic bonusHold Up and press Run at the title screen. The capsule on the ship will turn red instead of blue to confirm code entry. Shoot the last target on the first level to capture the red capsule and power-up to a triple ship.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Technologies, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>L_E1nrbtQEE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5671</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588979-galaga-90</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/galaga-90</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/galaga-88/3030-14593/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2365540-tg16_galaga90.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5671-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27484-galaga-atari-7800-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800299-galaga-arcade-screenshot-they-re-coming-to-take-you-away-haha.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800300-galaga-arcade-screenshot-being-suckered-away.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800301-galaga-arcade-screenshot-captured.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800302-galaga-arcade-screenshot-feeling-whole-again.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800303-galaga-arcade-screenshot-challenge-accepted.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800304-galaga-arcade-screenshot-nothing-less.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/800305-galaga-arcade-screenshot-yet-another-wave.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/665762-galaga-arcade-screenshot-score.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/665763-galaga-arcade-screenshot-push-start-button.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/665764-galaga-arcade-screenshot-aliens-appears.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QZuZj3P.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Galaga is a smouldering planet that often erupts with angry mutants and misfits. As Galactic commander of the Federal Army, you have the job of making them dead. Not easy! Because they come at you in clusters like swarms of killer bees. This time, you will be flying the awesome Triple Proton Fighter that warps to new dimensions and increased firepower. Galaga goons, your graveyard awaits.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a5e9209-a5c3-4359-bd2e-c821ffda4bfb.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7efdb7fd-7b69-4aeb-a26d-daefc709c037.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c7c0100-b813-434b-beb9-ea4375cf8764.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4628baf-7253-48f9-bc86-e52f36fa8e7c.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c657866e-9acb-4bdd-8fc4-d19b7587c603.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e2a6ebc-2497-494c-ab58-f82844465ee0.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a9e81fd-c770-42e8-a0d4-2d1016ac8400.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03bfdadd-b228-44d9-beab-a282b75a8535.PNG</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>NEC</Publisher>
</game>