<Game>
	<Name>Gomola Speed (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Gomola Speed is an action game featuring a robot snake. You must find the pieces of your body strewn about each maze-like stage, which increase your size, and use your length to surround items, food, and enemies in order to eliminate them. You can also use bombs to stun more dangerous enemies.Different stages may have different goals -- for example, you may have to find a key, or use your surround ability on floor tiles to reveal items or enemies. Only your snake's head is vulnerable; if an enemy hits your body it will scatter all the pieces and you'll have to collect them again. After completing set conditions on each stage, a door will open that leads to the next stage, at which point you'll be just a head again, and will have to hunt for your body once more.The game has the same unique UPL style that will be familiar to fans of games such as Atomic Robo-Kid and Mutant Night.Cheat: Debug MenuAt the title screen, quickly press Up, Down, Left, Right, I, II, I, II, Up, Down, Left, Right, I, II, II, I, I, I, II, II, I, II, I, II, Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Left, Right, Right, Select. Once inside the debug menu, enter the options to enable more cheats.Cheat: Debug MenuAt the title screen, quickly enter any of the following codes:Cheat: Last Levels PasswordsThe game doesn't normally allow you to enter these passwords. To enable them, input the Debug Menu code. Then enter the debug's option mode and turn On the entry named "Full Command". Then exit the debug mode and enter the passwords.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/9/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>UPL Co., Ltd</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>kOzYLSVNayU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>31080</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/588985-gomola-speed</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/gomola-speed</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/31080-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/130899-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/130900-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383841-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383842-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-first-level.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383844-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-every-time-you-do-something.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383845-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-i-ve-placed-a-bomb-in.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383847-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-time-to-leave-for-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383848-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-bonus-item-and-a-key.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383849-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-ate-some-food.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383851-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-i-got-to-uncover-the.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383852-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-new-type-of-food.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383853-gomola-speed-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-long-level.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/G4OZ21D.png</banner1>
	<Notes>You play a segmented caterpillar-like creature that has to surround food to open the exit to each level. As you work your way around each area, you pick up new body segments which make you longer, and have the ability drop little bombs that attract the enemy bugs. There is a password system to avoid replaying all the levels every time.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/64ff5d1f-4425-4312-a803-55aec9030364.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08138a64-2793-4cc1-a8e7-6600ff836a2a.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/afa78db5-3456-4f9e-901c-d710cd4cb842.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f2b22fb-46dd-4d35-ad3f-66a918d243a7.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>UPL</Publisher>
</game>