<Game>
	<Name>Hisou Kihei - Xserd (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Hisou Kihei X-Serd ("Flying Mounted Cavalry X-Serd") is a strategy game where the majority of the units are mecha, or robot suits. The game was exclusive to the PC Engine and was released soon after another mecha strategy game from Masaya: Gaiflame.In each scenario, the Serds - a league of specialized attack mecha - are deployed from their HQ ship Altea. The Serds all have single-letter code-names and different specializations: for example, the G-Serd wields a laser sword for devastating melee attacks and can move quickly, while the B-Serd is capable of long-range mortar attacks but has limited movement. The eponymous X-Serd is the most powerful of the team.Cheat: Cheat CodesEnter these cheats while it's your turn during game play.Cheat: Cheat CodesDuring the player's turn enter the follwing 2 codes.NB the clear stage code must be entered and then the player must end their turn for it to work.Cheat: 1st &amp;amp; Last Stage and EndingEnter the passwords at the start screen (you must press select to choose the password entry if you have back-up memory plugged in from your Duo or other means).</plot>
	<releasedate>23/2/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>NCS</Developer>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>WE0gSjNTw8g</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589175-x-serd</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hisou-kihei-xserd/3030-51882/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805902-5264338736-51975.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805918-hisoukiheiserd002.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805917-hisoukiheiserd001.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805916-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-012.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805915-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-011.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805914-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-010.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805913-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-009.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805912-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-008.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805911-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-007.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805910-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-006.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2805909-hisou_kihei_serd_%28j%29-005.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Hisou Kihei X-Serd ("Flying Mounted Cavalry X-Serd") is a strategy game where the majority of the units are mecha, or robot suits. The game was exclusive to the PC Engine and was released soon after another mecha strategy game from Masaya: Gaiflame. In each scenario, the Serds - a league of specialized attack mecha - are deployed from their HQ ship Altea. The Serds all have single-letter code-names and different specializations: for example, the G-Serd wields a laser sword for devastating melee attacks and can move quickly, while the B-Serd is capable of long-range mortar attacks but has limited movement. The eponymous X-Serd is the most powerful of the team.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>7KTRQ3kwM40</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/beb6e681-0682-4b74-8cac-3c665b904157.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2603a702-c66e-432b-ac38-4a335d53ace2.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1fa9c38f-0ac8-4711-bcfe-1c992915513c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26e3cd7c-0944-4a3f-a750-29a7bcafe07f.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>NCS</Publisher>
</game>