<Game>
	<Name>Jack Nicklaus' Turbo Golf (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The basic game play of this game is a lot like any other golf game, believe it or not. You have this object called a club. You can use the club to whack various balls into the holes conviently located around the 18 holes or so of golf action. This game likes to piss you off by refusing to recognize you hitting the ball, however. I swear I would spend many minutes trying to hit the damn ball, and the damn ball would not move. Then, you have this little meter, but it does not mean anything because the chances are when the meter fills up and you swing you're going to miss the damn ball anyways.And there is the basic problem I have with most golf games. I can never quite figure out how to play them, because I always miss the damn ball. Unfortunately for Jack Nicklaus and his little game, it was released for the Turbografx 16, which sucks because the Turbografx 16 controller provides little help when it comes to playing this game. In fact, the controller will make you end up hating the game even more than you already will. Golf games almost always suck, and this game is no exception. And yes, that is bias, I am biased against Turbografx games.The graphics in the game are nothing extraordinary, I would have expected a little more effort been put into the graphics of the game, because the game seems an awful lot, graphically, like some of the golf games released on NES, and that is not supposed to happen because the Turbografx is the more powerful system, dammit! The cool part of the graphics is the title screen, which shows a nice picture of that cheery guy Jack Nicklaus swinging at air, which is proof that this game forces you to miss the ball.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/turbo16/review/R17513.html</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>8212</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/turbocd/916054-jack-nicklaus-world-golf-tour</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-champions/3030-15139/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/1122277-jack_nicklaus___greatest_18_holes_of_major_championship_golf___front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/8212-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115374-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115376-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115377-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115378-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115383-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115379-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115380-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115384-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115381-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/115382-jack-nicklaus-greatest-18-holes-of-major-championship-golf.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/8212.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Jack Nicklaus: Turbo Golf is a 3D golf simulation featuring an 18 Hole course created by Jack Nicklaus himself. Each of the 18 holes are from famous courses around the world and include number 8 at Pebble Beach, number 18 from Muirfield, number 12 from St. Andrews, number 12 from Augusta, number 10 at Riviera, and more. Gameplay is for one to four players and can be either stroke play or a skins game.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9dfc5436-5879-4670-bdcd-a2ffded45af1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/020e07e5-1f26-4340-bd4e-49d642a3b5ae.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/939fa711-134a-4c68-a3b7-318489fa5eea.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/19e5a6d4-e0fc-48da-8d95-c4750bf2b0f1.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a51cd23-e3be-472c-8e0f-8f7fd8c5eed9.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5915d86-72e6-465b-a71f-0a8d198bcfef.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8dab548a-335e-4e62-bc4e-906ea6371575.PNG</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85395a1e-c29e-4b5e-b825-24021dd58eb2.png</snapshot13>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Accolade</Publisher>
</game>