<Game>
	<Name>KickBall (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A baseball style game with elements of football and dodgeball thrown in. Chose from a selection of bizarre teams, from seals to sumos to Schbibin Men!HINTS:- Ending -After the team select screen, choose 'password' 0080http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Kick_Ball.htmCheat: Hidden CharacterEnter the 2 player mode and at the character selection screen, hold Up + II and press Run to select your player. After Player 2 picks his character, you'll be able to play with a hidden character.Cheat: Hidden CharacterEnter the 1 player mode and at the character selection screen, hold Up + II and press I two times.Cheat: Hidden CharacterEnter the 2 player mode and at the character selection screen, hold Select while moving the cursor and you'll be able to pick the same characters.Cheat: Hidden CharacterEnter the 1 player mode, pick your character and at the "Playball" screen, hold Select and press Run. If done right, the screen will go black. Now press Left, Up or Right to start on different stadiums.Cheat: EndingAfter the team select screen, choose 'password'Cheat: EndingSelect your Team, and enter the following password to start on the corresponding Match. If you enter the Next Season passwords, you will start the game against the CPU in alternate costumes.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NCS</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589004-kickball</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/7/5/51775_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/6/gfs_4988_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/7/b/gfs_4988_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<Notes>A baseball style game with elements of football and dodgeball thrown in. Chose from a selection of bizarre teams, from seals to sumos to Schbibin Men!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>9o522mpBLRc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80b575d3-c5e3-454c-a5d6-089a2589c645.JPG</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84d23fe2-3599-4c77-80ce-23776e20383d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7471252-3d48-4fc4-9e12-78d4488e67bd.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bfedb80-e048-4cb6-b1ea-9b76d67d3c5c.png</snapshot4>
	<Publisher>NCS</Publisher>
</game>