<Game>
	<Name>Kyuukyoku Tiger (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A vertically scrolling helicopter shoot 'em up, Ky?kyoku Tiger bears more than a passing resemblance to games like Raiden and Daisenpu. The gameplay is familiar enough, with smart bombs and coloured power-ups that give a variety of weapons.COMMENT:Great graphics, awesome soundtrack and tough but fair gameplay makes this game a winner. Enemy patterns are devious, making you move into dangerous positions if you don't have your wits about you, and power-up pods taunt you as they float just out of reach...but the gameplay is rock solid and although you won't be completing this as fast as the 'Soldier' games, it's certainly worth the effort trying. But the best bit is the sound effect of the chopper taking off - it'll have you looking out the window!HINTS:- Extra credits -Switch on rapid fire and hold RIGHT + II when the title screen is displayed.- Extra lives -As soon as the game begins, move to the bottom left of the screen and drop a bomb.http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Kyukyoku_Tiger.htmCheat: Get 9 creditsWhile playing, first lose all your lives and continues. Then, when the words "Game Over" appears and before it goes back to the title screen, press II, I, II, II, I, I, II, I, II, I, Select. If done right, the credits will appear instead of the title screen.Cheat: Get two extra lives on level oneAs soon as you start on level one, fly to the bottom left corner of the screen and drop a bomb.  You should hear a chime, indicating that you now have two extra lives.Cheat: Get two extra lives on level oneWhen you see the Yellow Weapon Powerup, hold Select and pick it up. If done right, your weapon will have homing abilities.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>dh_qFWoahZE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22393</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/579425-kyuukyoku-tiger</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/twin-cobra/3030-11930/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/22393-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/0/6/41706_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606551-twin+cobra+%28u%29-0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606550-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-6.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606549-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-5.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606548-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-4.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606547-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-3.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606546-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606545-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2606544-kyuukyoku+tiger+%28j%29-0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2382464-kyuukyoku_tiger__ultimate_tiger___j__001.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2382463-kyuukyoku_tiger__ultimate_tiger___j__002.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YmRWwjh.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>A vertically scrolling helicopter shoot 'em up, Kyukyoku Tiger bears more than a passing resemblance to games like Raiden and Daisenpu. The gameplay is familiar enough, with smart bombs and coloured power-ups that give a variety of weapons.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34ff6edf-0e15-4a55-8346-604765228b3a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a906ad2b-739c-4600-8876-38e8e45f016a.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/00053984-28e4-4629-8593-a3ee02422b3d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/459977c3-c423-452e-8a42-c5f4fa2aed49.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Taito Corporation</Publisher>
</game>