<Game>
	<Name>Mahjong Gakuen Mild - Touma Soushirou Toujou (Japan) (Alt 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mahjong Gakuen Touma Soushirou Toujou is a mahjong game for the PC Engine that features pixellated nudity. When playing female opponents, winning subsequent hands of mahjong causes them to undress, similar to strip poker. The game also has male opponents which the player simply beats up instead after every successful game.Touma Soushirou Toujou is the follow-up to the original 1988 Arcade game Mahjong Gakuen. Outcry over its salacious content forced Face to reconfigure the game as Mahjong Gakuen Touma Shoushirou Toujou Mild the subsequent year, which removed the nudity and replaced it with skimpy swimwear.Cheat: Increase ContinuesOn the continue screen (where it shows you the face of a Japanese girl), wait 1 minute and then, starting from Up, do a clockwise motion with the control pad. If done right, a sound will be heard. You now have 1 extra continue. To get 3 more continues, just wait 3 minutes or more on the same screen and then press Up 10 times. If done right, a sound will be heard.Cheat: Increase ContinuesAt the main menu, press the following buttons:Cheat: Increase ContinuesAt the main menu, press Left, Right, I, II, Left, Right, I, II. A sound will be heard if done right. Now, hit button 1 the same number of times of the stage you want to start in and then press Run.Cheat: Increase ContinuesAt the main menu, press Left, Left, Right, Right, I, II, I, II. If done right, the Visual Test will start. Now, to cycle through each image, you have to press the following buttons: I, Left, Right, II, Up, Up, Left, II, Down, Right, II, I, Down, Up, Down, Run, II, I, Up, Run, I, Left, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up, Down, I, Left, Down, II, Run, Right, Down, Left, Right, I, Run. In addition, if you press Select at any time, you'll get a screen with a boat and an island.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/11/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Sankindo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589025-mahjong-gakuen-toumasou-shirou-toujou</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mahjong-gakuen-touma-soushirou-toujou/3030-51720/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802467-1184526632-31820.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802473-mahjonggakuen001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802472-mahjong_gakuen_touma_shiro_tojo_%28j%29-004.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802471-mahjong_gakuen_touma_shiro_tojo_%28j%29-003.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802470-mahjong_gakuen_touma_shiro_tojo_%28j%29-002.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2802469-mahjong_gakuen_touma_shiro_tojo_%28j%29-001.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/0/9/gfs_4002_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/9/4/gfs_4002_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a3b3a634-7384-4e35-8d26-a40f8ec5a5ed.JPG</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30eae661-3bf7-4358-8aed-7ecdd7bd81fd.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96ddbdfb-5fa6-4371-b912-58a1cfd364b1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/650a8b05-351b-4345-8bc4-d0337441e033.png</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>FACE</Publisher>
</game>