<Game>
	<Name>Maison Ikkoku (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Maison Ikkoku, based on the serial manga and anime of the same name, is an adventure game set in a boarding house in the 1980s. The protagonist Yusaku Godai is a struggling student staying at the titular boarding house. When the young widow Kyoko Otonashi arrives as Maison Ikkoku's new manager, Godai is instantly smitten and seeks a way to win her heart. Much of the game's storyline concerns the burgeoning relationship between Godai and Kyoko, and the antics of Maison Ikkoku's other tenants who tend to take advantage of Godai's doormat nature.The game adaptation was originally released for the PC98-01 and MSX in 1986 before being ported to various other Japanese home computers, including also the Nintendo Famicom in 1988 and the PC Engine (TurboGrafx-16) in 1989. It plays similarly to other Japanese adventure games of the era: the player is given a selection of commands that often changes depending on the player's location, and must determine the correct series of commands necessary to continue the story.No version of the game was ever officially localized into English, though the PC Engine version received a fan translation in 2008.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Micro Cabin</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>33507</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589029-maison-ikkoku</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/maison-ikkoku/3030-33733/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/33507-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/33507-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797197-maisonikkoku001.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797196-maison_ikkoku_%28j%29-004.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797195-maison_ikkoku_%28j%29-003.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797194-maison_ikkoku_%28j%29-002.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797193-maison_ikkoku_%28j%29-001.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/6/f/gfs_4448_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/f/2/gfs_4448_2_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Maison Ikkoku (めぞん一刻?) is a graphical text-adventure game developed by Micro Cabin and published on multiple popular Japanese home computer systems towards the end of 1986. It was ported to the Famicom by Bothtec in 1988. Micro Cabin then ported the game one final time to the PC Engine in 1989. The game is based on the popular manga and anime series of the same name, Maison Ikkoku. The story is a bitter-sweet comedic romance involving a group of madcap people who live in a boarding house in 1980s Tokyo. The story focuses primarily on the gradual developing relationships between Yusaku Godai, a poor student down on his luck, and Kyoko Otonashi, a young, recently-widowed boarding house manager. In the game, you take the role of Godai performing various missions that deal with the storyline of Maison Ikkoku. You have to avoid Yotsuya's pranks, save money to throw a party, proclaim your love for Kyoko and other things. The action takes place all over Tokeizaka and not just the boarding house. Players can visit Soichiro's grave, Chachamaru, the train station and many other familiar locales.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6d070350-b57e-4dfb-9617-aa57fdcbb047.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1b1421a-7383-483e-8879-7da737588cbd.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7845b2f9-c2fc-431c-9bd2-c27d6b49e235.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bd1e024-b542-4d96-9783-711163889c18.jpg</snapshot10>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Micro Cabin</Publisher>
</game>