<Game>
	<Name>Makai Hakkenden Shada (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Makai Hakkenden Shada is an action-RPG from Data East that was released on the PC Engine (the Japanese TurboGrafx-16) in 1989. The game bears more than a close resemblance to Falcom's Ys: specifically the first game in the series, The Vanished Omens, which was a huge success for the PC Engine a few months prior as well as being a generally well-regarded computer RPG before then. As well as having a similar nude female figure in the opening intro, the game also borrows Ys's combat system: fighting occurs by walking into enemies at a slight angle, causing them to collide with the player character's weapon (which hurts them) rather than the player character himself (which hurts the player character). The various gauges for health and experience are also similar.Makai Hakkenden Shada is based on a centuries-old Japanese novel series called Nansou Satomi Hakkenden, or "Eight Dog Chronicles", that features eight half-brother samurai who are all descended from the same dog and have the Japanese word for "dog" somewhere in their names. While these books have been referenced or adapted many times in other media such as manga and film, Makai Hakkenden Shada and the Famicom RPGs Satomi Hakkenden and Shin Satomi Hakkenden: Hikari to Yami no Tatakai are the only direct video game adaptations. Okami also contained an oblique reference to the novels.Unlike Satomi Hakkenden, which eventually allowed the player to recruit all eight of the central characters of the novel series, Makai Hakkenden Shada only has the one playable character. Instead, other characters from the novels occasionally appear to help the player.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/4/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Data East Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589099-makai-hakkenden-shada</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/makai-hakkenden-shada</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/makai-hakkenden-shada/3030-42796/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2490775-makai_hakkenden_shada_pce.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482516-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-this-very-short.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482517-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482518-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-starting-in.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482519-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-equipment-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482520-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-buying-stuff.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482521-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-chatting-with.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482522-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-what-s-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482523-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-these-baboons.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482524-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-hmm-how-to.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482525-makai-hakkenden-shada-turbografx-16-screenshot-meeting-in.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The story of this game is loosely based on the 19th century Japanese epic novel Nanso Satomi Hakkenden ("Tale of Eight Dogs") by Kyokutei Bakin. In the game, the player controls a young warrior named Shin. The elder of his home village tells him that a magical artifact known as the Statue of the Four Gods has been stolen. This artifact was sealing away the spirit of the evil Tamazusa. To prevent Tamazusa's resurrection, Shin must find seven other warriors. Only when they are united can the evil be defeated once and for all... Despite the premise of eight warriors, Makai Hakkenden Shada is an action RPG in which the player controls only Shin. The game is similar to the better-known Ys games in many ways. As in Ys, the hero fights enemies simply by "bumping" into them. Defeated enemies produce money, which can be spent in villages to purchase weapons and various types of armor, and experience points. Once a set amount of those is accumulated, the hero gains a level. Later in the game Shin receives spells and special techniques, which must be executed actively, by pressing a button. There is also a "search" command in the game, which is required to use to solve certain situations.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ee9cc38-be7f-40b2-a378-d52a737e9e43.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eda734ee-ce71-48a1-9c48-dc27b11740dc.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/54954030-9295-4d91-b135-0fc577c61971.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc2845ad-d8b7-4d95-91ff-1df3deb8ede7.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Data East Corporation</Publisher>
</game>