<Game>
	<Name>Military Madness (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Military Madness, known as Nectaris in Japan, is a turn-based strategy game that uses a hex map and zoomed-in cutaways whenever two units meet in combat, similar to the Famicom/Advance Wars series. It is the first in Hudson's long-running Nectaris series, which was still seeing new entries when Hudson finally folded in 2012, after which the rights got passed to Konami.The game was originally released on the TurboGrafx-16, where it saw a US and Japan release. The game was later added to the Wii's Virtual Console in 2006, where it saw its European debut.Story:From the opening of the game:&#8230; The 21st Century &#8230;The Earth has become all too small for man's insatiable needs. However, the moon has offered vast resources for Earth's greatest countries.The most powerful nations staked their claims for the moon's riches and much fighting has occurred. The evil Axis Empire has been behind much of this terror.Finally, on april 6, 2089, the Axis Empire's army launches an all out attack and captures most of the moon. All innocent people must now fight or perish.The Axis army now occupies most of the moon's factories where they are continually producing new weapons for their secret assault on the planet Earth.The Axis secret police have rounded up many members of the Allied Powers and put them in prisons. Without their key people, the Allied Powers stands little chance.Meanwhile, the Axis Empire draws closer to launching their "S.A.M." or Supreme Atomic Missile&#8230;the weapon they will use to destroy the Earth.The Allied Powers know they must free their prisoners if they stand a chance to stop the S.A.M. before launch time.You must free the prisoners and stop this military madness before the Axis Empire and their secret weapon S.A.M. destroy the Earth and all its people!!!Gameplay:The goal of Military Madness is to destroy all enemy units or capture the enemy base in each of the game's 16 levels. The player starts the first level with basic units. As they progress through the levels more units become available. A turn consists of moving and/or attacking with each unit one by one. Units can be restored in factories. Only infantry units can take over factories and the enemy base. Attackers and defenders get bonuses for certain formations with nearby units (or the "Zone of Control"), such as the surround effect. The type of terrain a unit is on affects the possible distance it can travel as well as its defensive ability. Units become more powerful by gaining experience for each battle they survive.UnitsA variety of units allow for many strategic possibilities. They are divided up as follows:Foot Soldiers- Weak units that can capture bases and factories.Charlie GX-77Kilroy GX-87Panther CBX-1Tanks- The most common ground unit, with varied power and range.Bison S-61Lenet TT-1Polar PT-6Grizzly T-79Slagger GS-81Titan GT-86Giant HMB-2Lightweight Armored Vehicles- Weaker units that can move, attack, and move again in one turn.Rabbit MB-5Lynx MB-4Combat Aircraft- Very long ranged. They are not affected by terrain. Only specific units can attack aircraft.Falcon FX-1Eagle AX-87Hunter EF-88Artillery- Guns that can attack long distance.Hadrian SG-4Octopus MR-22Seeker AAG-4Hawkeye MM-107Atlas SS-80Land Mine- Can't move or attack. Used as support for other units or as a roadblock.Trigger M-77Transport- Weak, long-ranging units that can carry slower units.Mule MC-1Pelican C-41Cheat: Level Passwords (JP version)Note: unlisted levels have the same password as the US versionCheat: Alternate colorsPower on the system, and hold Select to reset. While continuing to hold Select, choose the one player continue option and enter a map name.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Technologies, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>T-fo515wMNc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5676</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589030-military-madness</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/military-madness</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/military-madness/3030-4152/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5676-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5676-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/97150-military-madness-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/133823-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/133824-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro-1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/133825-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro-2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/133826-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/133827-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-round-1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651324-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro-japanese-version.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651325-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-enemy-tanks-have.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651326-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-we-must-defeat-enemies.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651327-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-enemies-are-annihilated.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/651328-military-madness-turbografx-16-screenshot-bison-tank-s-stats.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lPAYyrA.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Space on Earth has become limited, and mankind has looked to colonize the moon. A group known as the Axis Powers has seized control over most of the lunar surface, and it's up to you as a member of the Allied Powers to fight against them. As you move around the map (shown in a top-down 2D perspective), enemy combatants will try and stop you from achieving your goal. Once encountered, the screen shifts view points to a close-up view of the skirmish at hand.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>F4Z8bSwy01I</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d09f441-2579-41dd-bc38-9599bef50062.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2144b3a9-de5d-4e4a-8d61-19d742d76f6d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6a034f4-58a3-4623-93a7-c8a3a24d5bd3.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b8ec4800-9a36-4465-936e-88b3cd7ce28c.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8ab98656-6f6d-4a44-a145-0e260805408d.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/32b7b0a1-e4ae-4236-9110-a57aef4cecf0.PNG</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34ea2cd7-1598-41c1-a512-f62b31861b44.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>