<Game>
	<Name>Nectaris (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Tactical combat games were not unheard of on consoles; the Famicom in Japan had Daisenryaku. Nectaris, however, gave war games an interesting twist. Nectaris takes place in the future, with Allied forces battling Axis forces (interesting WWII reference) for the moon and its resources. Your forces, the Allies, and the enemy Axis forces maneuver on a new hex map each level, but the game switches to a side view when your forces engage in battle, letting you admire your success or lament your failure.Graphically the game is fairly straightforward, and the few music tracks are nothing particularly impressive. Don't let that fool you, however, as you will become addicted. I won't go into too much detail because describing tactical war games can sometimes get messy, but Military Madness really isn't difficult to learn to play and yet it retains a modicum of complexity.It's also ass hard and will kick you around quite a bit once you make it past the first few levels. But boy is it nice when you get your HMB-2 Giant unit up to max experience and it becomes nearly indestructible. Mind you, I said NEARLY indestructible. Just remember not to break your TV from hurled game controllers. The sad part is you'll be running back for more.HINTS:- Play as Axis -Select the new game or one player continue option on the title screen, then hold Select and press I- Switch sides -Hold Select and press Run before choosing the one player continue option- Sound test -ONGAKU- Alternate colors -Power on the system, and hold Select to reset. While continuing to hold Select, choose the one player continue option and enter a map name.http://www.racketboy.com/retro/turbografx-16/2007/06/the-games-that-defined-the-turbografx-16.htmlCheat: Level Passwords (JP version)Note: unlisted levels have the same password as the US versionCheat: Alternate colorsPower on the system, and hold Select to reset. While continuing to hold Select, choose the one player continue option and enter a map name.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>T-fo515wMNc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5676</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589030-military-madness</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/military-madness/3030-4152/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5676-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5676-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712443-nectaris_%28j%29-001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712442-militarymadness001.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712441-military_madness_%28u%29-001.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/84171/1459877-bisonandcharlie.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/84171/1459875-battle.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/84171/1459866-surround.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/84171/1458921-story.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/c/3/gfs_40553_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/5/e/gfs_40553_2_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/e/gfs_40553_2_2.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>