<Game>
	<Name>Neutopia II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Some years have passed since the brave hero Jazeta destroyed Dirth, the Emperor of Darkness. Peace has returned to the land of Neutopia. But there are still monsters roaming the countryside, and some of them were spotted near Yurius Shrine. Jazeta went there to find out what exactly had happened. But he didn't return... You are Jazeta's son, and you must first of all find your missing father! Can it be that the shadow of Emperor of Darkness threatens the peaceful land again?..The sequel to "Neutopia" is similar to the predecessor in every way. Navigating your hero from a top-down view, you explore the vast countryside, fighting monsters in real time combat. The game is not a true RPG, but an action adventure: you don't gain any experience points from combat, only collect money to buy supplies. In dungeons, you must use bombs on walls to reveal secret passages, push stones, and fight many regular enemies and bosses.Cheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAt the name entry screen, type KOALA as your name and the main character will have a radically different look.Cheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAt the name entry screen, enter the following Japanese characters as your name (format is Row #, Column #): - 2,5 - 1,1 - 4,6 -. If entered correctly, the main character will have a radically different look.Cheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAt the password screen enter the following password:Cheat: Alternate Main Character Spritel(lowercase L)bnoBJt$  AyUkJ7Wa  XACpGDjmq1j1uR1Q  M8ozNO(letter)Qa  cPUM&amp;XcXCheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteIt will put you in the Town of Oasis ready to tackle the last dungeon, The Atra Labyrinth.Cheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAll passwords are case-sensitive! There is only the letter O, there are no zeros in the passwords. From the Main Menu select Continue and enter all passwords in the File Cabinet screenCheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #.Cheat: Alternate Main Character SpriteAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>yqXbmHe5v6k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8218</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589048-neutopia-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/neutopia-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/neutopia-ii/3030-19420/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2720389-5372533851-51836.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79164-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79167-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94367-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94348-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-naming-the-hero-jazeta.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94349-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-hero-dreams.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94350-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-come-to-me-baby.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94351-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-inventory-menu.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94352-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-peaceful-area.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94353-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-kill-the-old-man-and-get.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94354-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-what-s-the-password.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94355-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-fearsome-slimes.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94356-neutopia-ii-turbografx-16-screenshot-lonely-boy-in-a-lonely.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PGxiIU4.png</banner1>
</game>