<Game>
	<Name>Out Live (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A very important discovery was recently made on the planet Laffra - ancient ruins at an excavation site, containing relics of another civilization, with technique that would surely benefit the great intergalactic Empire. But a mysterious organization that calls itself "Mars" began to stir unrest on the planet. The head of Imperial Scouts sends the hero, piloting a combat robot known as "FW", into the depths of the ruins, to face the enemies and retrieve the precious knowledge...Out Live is a solo dungeon crawler; unlike most representatives of this genre, it is set in a sci-fi environment, and the player controls a giant robot rather than a medieval warrior. Most of the enemies are also machines and robots of different kinds. Before venturing into the dungeon, the player has access to various shops, where it is possible to repair the robot, buy weapons, protective shields, and items that restore the robot's energy. Most of the gameplay takes place in pseudo-3D, maze like underground complexes (without an auto-map, but with a compass feature). There, the game plays similarly to other dungeon crawlers: random enemies must be fought in turn-based fashion; they drop money and award the player character with experience points.A somewhat unusual feature is "double leveling": the robot has two independent levels, for attack and for defense. The experience points the robot receives after battles also come in two different flavors. Depending on the enemy type and outcome of the battle, the robot receives different amounts of experience. The leveling-up itself is automatic, increasing maximum energy, attack and defense parameters.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/3/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589060-out-live</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/out-live</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/out-live/3030-40761/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2382368-out_live_pce.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482580-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482581-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-lots-of-text-not-a-single.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482582-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-main-pre-dungeon-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482583-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-welcome-to-the-shop.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482584-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-we-need-guns.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482585-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-hitting-the-bar-hearing.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482586-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-it-s-time-to-go.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482588-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-enemy-encounter-battle-menu.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482589-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-status-screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482590-out-live-turbografx-16-screenshot-enemy-is-defeated-getting.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A very important discovery was recently made on the planet Laffra - ancient ruins at an excavation site, containing relics of another civilization, with technique that would surely benefit the great intergalactic Empire. But a mysterious organization that calls itself Mars began to stir unrest on the planet. The head of Imperial Scouts sends the hero, piloting a combat robot known as FW, into the depths of the ruins, to face the enemies and retrieve the precious knowledge... Out Live is a solo dungeon crawler; unlike most representatives of this genre, it is set in a sci-fi environment, and the player controls a giant robot rather than a medieval warrior. Most of the enemies are also machines and robots of different kinds. Before venturing into the dungeon, the player has access to various shops, where it is possible to repair the robot, buy weapons, protective shields, and items that restore the robot's energy. Most of the gameplay takes place in pseudo-3D, maze like underground complexes (without an auto-map, but with a compass feature). There, the game plays similarly to other dungeon crawlers: random enemies must be fought in turn-based fashion; they drop money and award the player character with experience points. A somewhat unusual feature is double leveling: the robot has two independent levels, for attack and for defense. The experience points the robot receives after battles also come in two different flavors. Depending on the enemy type and outcome of the battle, the robot receives different amounts of experience. The leveling-up itself is automatic, increasing maximum energy, attack and defense parameters.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>0m2yYPQlk8M</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a64b4f24-c78b-4ef6-b255-9a8038924836.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fdbd440b-ba88-48f2-a0b9-b4b78aa586b5.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d81d4a9b-a979-4b0c-8ec3-33a720a1201f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a47c6b28-af4d-4b4d-a219-c9bdc02b575f.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sun Electronics</Publisher>
</game>