<Game>
	<Name>P-47 - The Freedom Fighter (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The P-47 was one of the toughest planes in use in World War 2, and this side-scrolling shoot 'em up puts you in control of one as you take on hordes of Nazis. 16-bit versions have a simultaneous 2-player mode, as well as the ability to wrap-around the game with increased difficulty up to 4 times.You are initially armed with a machine gun, but can also pick up bombs, spray missiles and multi-missiles by picking up the appropriate letter. Each weapon can be upgraded by picking up further tokens of the same type. Tokens offering extra lives and speed-ups are also on offer.http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/p-47-thunderbolt-the-freedom-fighterCheat: 8 ContinuesAt the title screen, hold I + Select. Keep holding the buttons while the demo of planes pass through the title screen. When the demo is over and the 10 blue planes come from the left again, release Select and press Run. If done right, you'll have 8 continues instead of 2.Cheat: 8 ContinuesAt the title screen, push II, II, II, II, II, I, I, I, I, I, I, select, select. This will activate the level select option. Then push the following button combinations to start on the desired level:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Aicom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>9y2-HlY1TMs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>31081</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589063-p-47</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/31081-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/7/0/311570_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/d/2/gfs_5014_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/4/f/gfs_5014_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/f/b/gfs_5014_3_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jBZhN1b.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>P-47: The Freedom Fighter, usually simply P-47, is a horizontal shoot 'em up from NMK and Aicom. NMK would develop the original 1988 Arcade version of the game, which was published by Jaleco, while Aicom developed and published the subsequent 1989 PC Engine port. The PCE port pared down a lot the game's bosses and cutscenes to fit the game onto a 2MB HuCard. It was also ported to numerous home computers by Firebird.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>pz8SVzubzL8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b99aa46b-96cd-4e07-b5fa-1ecb8467594d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/868d512f-4e76-498e-9d2d-6722797b86bf.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8dfbc967-c2a5-494b-88b5-da5df5331fce.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f94b108-4567-43bc-8300-b1558b3a3045.png</snapshot5>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Aicom</Publisher>
</game>