<Game>
	<Name>Pac-Land (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pac-Land was created by Namco and released into arcades in 1984. It was also ported to many consoles and in 1996 was included in Namco Museum Vol 4 for the PlayStation. The arcade game used the Namco Pac-Land system board, which was also used in Dragon Buster, Metro-Cross, Baraduke and Sky Kid. Pac-Land also featured parallax scrolling for some of its backgrounds, which was not commonplace until the 16-bit era.Gameplay:The game centers around getting a fairy to the end of the stage and eventually back to the Queen Fairy in Fairyland. Since there were the five ghosts (Pinky, Inky, Blinky, Clyde and Sue) that kept chasing Pac-Man, the fairy was tucked away safely under the hat that Pac-Man was wearing. Together they venture right and left, completing levels and avoiding dangerous obstacles like quicksand, water and the ghosts themselves.For bonus points, the player can collect cherries and other items. Also, there is an power pellet on each stage that Pac-Man can collect. That turns the ghosts blue. Then the ghost consuming can begin...When the player has made it to the end of the final stage, they are awarded with a pair of magical boots. Those are helpful, as they allow continuous jumps in the air as Pac-Man returns home. Once he is home, he is greeted by Ms. Pac-Man and Baby Pac-Man. If playing the US release, Pac-Man is also greeted by Sourpuss and Chomp-Chomp (from the Pac-Man cartoon).Then, if the player chooses, Pac-Man starts another journey with the same objective but with increased difficulty.Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectAt the title screen, hold Button 1 + Button 2 and press Run. You'll enter the secret Game Options where you can increase your lives and turn "Skip" (level select) on. If you press Run again, you'll access the Sound Test. Press Run one last time to go back to the title screen. To enable the Stage Select, turn "Skip" on, go back to the title screen and start the game. You'll now see the words "Skip 1" on the screen, press Button 1 or 2 to select from any level.Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectAt the title screen, hold Button 1 + Button 2 and press Run. If done right, you'll get a hidden Pac Man scene. On this scree, hold I + II again and press Run to access the hidden options screen just like the USA version.Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectFirst enable the Level Select code. Then, at the "Skip 1" screen, press the following buttons to enable the cheats:Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectAccessed in 2 ways:1) Using the Level Select cheat enter the following code at the level select screen2) press start during the game's endingCheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectStaff IntroAt the title screen enter the following code. (only in Japanese version)Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectOptions Mode (appears in place of Staff Intro in USA version)At the Staff Intro screen, enter the following code. Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectSound TestAt the Options Mode screen, enter the following code.Cheat: Game Options, Sound Test and Stage SelectLevel SelectTurn 'Skip' to on in the options mode, start a game and use I &amp; II buttons to select the starting level.Cheat: Floating Hat TrickWhen you enter Break Time, hit Run and Select to reset the game just as Pac-Man's hat rises, revealing the fairy.  When you start the game, Pac-Man's hat will be floating over his head for the entire game.Cheat: Floating Hat TrickIn Round 2, find a stump that you can move. Move it a little, stop, and then continue moving it as far as it'll go and Pac-Man will be upside down. Move the stump all the way without stopping and Pac-Man will walk backwards. Move the stump most of the way, stop, then finish moving the stump and Pac-Man will both be upside down and walk backwards (All of this works in the Turbo Grafx 16 version only). </plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Technologies, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>aYJ0CD3R7iw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5679</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589066-pac-land</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/pac-land</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-land/3030-8575/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2365563-tg16_pacland.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5679-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/40298-pac-land-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98110-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen-us-version.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98111-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-coming-down-the-mountain.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98113-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-i-ve-encountered-a-magical.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98115-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-you-can-stand-on-ghosts.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98116-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-returning-home.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98119-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-later-levels-bring-different.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98124-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-round-1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98125-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-power-pellet.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98126-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-break-time.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98128-pac-land-turbografx-16-screenshot-tiny-cacti.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DFPvmIV.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5679.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Pac-Land, our friend Pac-Man is facing more daring adventures than ever before! In his new contest, Pac-Man comes face-to-face with ghosts on their own turf. In this 2D platforming adventure, his quiet day at home is disturbed by those nasty specters. A fairy princess has been kidnapped, and Pac-Man must leap over rivers, avoid dangerous water spouts, fly in magic shoes, dodge the Hoppers from the bushes, skip past the skulls aiming to drag you to Sand Prison -- all in the aims of reaching Monster Mansion and rescuing the princess to restore peace in Pac-Land!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>zxxWuN6Xztc</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80522f64-686e-4e11-a0d8-6f3bf23cda52.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c2fdf07-80a4-4634-94c7-857abc3af0aa.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83c7517f-5dce-4b05-b6c2-e3ac9f678e34.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/859036c8-3684-4635-97ad-0f5f10016e9f.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93124119-7804-46e5-a2b0-fc81cd6d3843.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d306c046-bed8-442f-9a3f-e5c1f1c1559f.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df8dc667-02c7-4e16-9b36-deb32de36247.PNG</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>