<Game>
	<Name>Parodius Da! - Shinwa kara Owarai e (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>One day, our octopus friend gets into a fight to the death with his old rival, the bug. Our octopus wins and people start to call him Mr. Parodius. On his paid vacation he goes to the countryside to enjoy a little farming. Returning to our ready-made octopus pot, he reads the 'People of the Universe' newspaper and nearly falls off his chopping board in surprise. There now is a picture of the mysterious Great Octopus with the Earth in his arms. 'F... father?,' he stutters. It was his father, who had disappeared just two years before, never to return home. So Octopus sets out on a search for the truth and with his companions begins to travel the world!Cheat: Secret Bosses3 secret bosses are hidden in the Special score attack mode. They are appear according to your final score, prior to reaching the boss.Cheat: Secret Bosses~30,000 Kaitou Midori Mantou (The Mysterious Green Cloak)900,000~1,000,000Shokutsuu Daiou Manjiri-kun (The Great Gourmet King Manjiri-kun)1,000,000+Super DX Koutei Penguin (Super Deluxe Emperor Penguin)Cheat: Secret BossesScores outside these ranges mean you will see an in game boss instead.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/2/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>u381OCQb7y4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18872</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589069-parodius-da</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18872-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/18872-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/f/gfs_3937_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/2/gfs_3937_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/2/gfs_3937_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/6/gfs_3937_3_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/O8SSmGY.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Konami's imaginative parody on the Gradius series. It plays just like Gradius, with the same power-up system, but features a far more bizarre and imaginative series of levels and characters. This game was released in Japan for the PC Engine and is a port of the Arcade original with a couple of differences: it doesn't have the arcade Stages 5 and 8, but features a stage titled SPECIAL and a new introduction that features several strange-looking Japanese characters. This is in contrast to the arcade intro, which chronicles the Gradius legacy up until the time of release.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>s3FS_VWakpo</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/727d04fe-982e-48c3-822c-32eb550e2673.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f755dcb0-499b-4f6a-8cec-977282de80e5.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9560133c-a2ff-4e4a-9dab-59c2b4264c02.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98d9489c-2052-4c05-a1f0-19da2163e74c.png</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>