<Game>
	<Name>Power Eleven (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Power Soccer has four main modes:Hudson Cup - single-player mode where series of games are played against computer-controlled teamsVersus mode - two players can face off in a match or one can compete against the computerWatch mode - observe a simulated game between two user-selected teamsPenalty Kick mode - similar to Versus mode in terms of player options (1 player vs computer or 2 player) but different in that no teams are selected.There are 12 playable teams in the game:ArgentinaBrazilColombiaEnglandFranceHollandItalyJapanSoviet UnionSpainUruguayWest GermanyCheat: Stage SelectYou need a second controller for this code to work. Select "Hudson Cup" and at the Team Selection screen, highlight your team, hold Select + I on Controller 2 and press I on Controller 1. Keep holding the buttons and when the black screen with the #1 appears, press Up or Down on Controller 2 to select stages.Cheat: Last Game PasswordAt the Hudson Cup Password screen, enter the following Japanese characters (format is Row #, Column #): - 1,1 - 3,14 - 1,14 - 2,14 - 4,6 - 3,2 - 5,5 - 2,12 - 1,11 - 2,14 -</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>93f9Oa_dMwk</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589073-power-eleven</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/power-eleven</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/power-eleven/3030-46766/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7135/2649349-powereleven.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/550809-power-eleven-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/550810-power-eleven-turbografx-16-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/d/gfs_4330_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/0/gfs_4330_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/c/0/gfs_4330_2_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/0/gfs_4330_2_3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/6/0/gfs_4330_2_4.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/d/0/gfs_4330_2_5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/0/0/gfs_4330_2_6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/b/0/gfs_4330_2_7.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Power Eleven is a top-down soccer game with three playing modes: multiplayer, penalty kicks (shown from the back of the transparent goalkeeper) and a tournament mode. The latter is the main mode for solo players and features twelve national soccer teams. Then the player needs to defeat the other teams with rising difficulty to win the Hudson Cup. Regarding rules, the game features no fouls or off-sides. Each athlete has a rating in the five statistics (run, dribble, kick, technique and power) which influences his performance on the field. The player can also choose between different formations and after successful matches athletes can be substituted. The most unusual aspect of the game is the power rating which is lowered when using the power mode which allows faster movement and forceful shots. However, the power does only get completely refilled after a match so it needs to be used with care. Because the activation of this mode takes up a button, there is no dedicated passing button to be found. The distance of a shot is chosen by pressing the fire button quickly or holding it.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>-02q4CEfwU4</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a8619361-82ae-43cc-a166-7ff2b7fe7a2e.JPG</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc4e3975-56ff-4f3a-ae48-94eed730a9fb.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1be7459-cd48-450c-a5e8-b6386534e6f2.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9ea3e88-39ac-4b75-b3d4-334568b4f370.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>