<Game>
	<Name>Power League (Japan) (All Star Version)</Name>
	<plot>World Class Baseball is a Sports game, developed and published by Hudson,which was released in Japan in 1988.Cheat: Hidden TeamAt the Vs Mode or Edit Mode team selection screen, hold Select and press I to pick your team. If done right, you'll play as the Champs.Cheat: Hidden TeamAt the Open or Watch Mode, after choosing your Team and the CPU's Team, press Left or Right to change who pitches first.Cheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwordsCheat: Pennant Mode Apples PasswordsFrom the Main Menu select Pennant Mode. Select the team you want to play as and enter the following passwords</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>10.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>8245</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/578600-world-class-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/power-league-4</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/power-league-ii/3030-51475/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/8245-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/1/1/40911_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797215-powerleagueii001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797214-power_league_ii_%28j%29-009.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797213-power_league_ii_%28j%29-008.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797212-power_league_ii_%28j%29-007.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797211-power_league_ii_%28j%29-006.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797210-power_league_ii_%28j%29-005.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797209-power_league_ii_%28j%29-004.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797208-power_league_ii_%28j%29-003.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797207-power_league_ii_%28j%29-002.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/f/e/gfs_97635_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>