<Game>
	<Name>Power Drift (Japan) (Alt 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Designed by Yu Suzuki and developed by Sega AM2 for the Arcades in 1988, Power Drift was the first kart racer, setting the template for more popular kart racers such as the Mario Kart series. The Sonic Drift series is, in many ways, a spiritual successor to Power Drift.The game was notable for its sprite-scaling graphics, which Yu Suzuki and Sega had used to great success with earlier racers like Hang-On and OutRun. It used them to create elaborate, surreal courses that seemed to rise and fall rapidly like rollercoasters.Power Drift was later ported to multiple home computers by Activision and to the PC Engine exclusively in Japan by Asmik Entertainment. It would later make its way onto Sega Arcade compilations for the Saturn and Dreamcast.Cheat: CheatsAt the title screen, hold Down + Right + I + Select and press Run. At the character selection screen, perform any of the following tasks. You can enable multiple cheats by pressing II on one character and then on another one before you select a player.Cheat: Hidden TrackSuccessfully beat all 9 tracks in first place (gold trophy) without continuing to access a hidden 10th track where you play as a fighter jet.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/4/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>fgAo9WR0_RI</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589072-power-drift</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/power-drift</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/power-drift/3030-7440/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2579/1741426-power_drift.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110289-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110290-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-driver-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110291-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-prepare-to-race.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110292-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-driving-through-the-desert.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110294-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-yeah.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110293-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-watch-that-corner.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110295-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-spinning-out-of-control.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110296-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-results.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110297-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-stage-2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/110298-power-drift-turbografx-16-screenshot-stage-3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/n24OW0w.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Choose from wacky drivers, like Jason the Skinhead or Jeronimo the Mohican and rev your way through all the stomach-churning circuits! Watch the dust fly and the wheels spin as you screech over a roller coaster track and wave goodbye to your opponents. Roar over mounds of mud, drive through the desert, slip 'n' slide on snow-covered tarmac and race your way through the night to face the final lap! CAREFUL! Power Drift is no easy ride! If you're heading for a collision hold on to your seat and enjoy those 360 degree spins before you bump back down to earth!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>3aZL2eEz4eU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74bc010f-269b-48b1-85c8-90278291a8c5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84e080cb-220a-46cc-a070-37f126d3d741.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e376dee-24a7-41bd-9050-4cb54af88138.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f260917c-5d54-4fd2-af84-340131330bad.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc</Publisher>
</game>