<Game>
	<Name>Power Tennis (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>World Court Tennis is handily the best tennis game for Turbografx. No question. It's also an extremely underappreciated game by any standard, and one that deserves a second look, as time has apparently turned its back on Namco's classy TG-16 library.STORY:Can I put negatives here? Play tennis! Yes! (Clutches fist in the pose of "the Thinker") You can win tournaments or exhibition games... or, you can take on the Evil Tennis King to save the treasures of the King of Chicago! The really messed up thing here is that I'm not kidding at all. Personally, I find the game all the more awesome for having such a ridiculous farce of an attempted story, but I'm really easy to please.GAMEPLAY:Good tennis play by any standard. The ability to customize equipment actually does affect player performance abilities, and the pacing of the game is almost identical to Super Tennis for the Super NES. There are only four types of shot, but they're really all you need. Sometimes you feel a little slow, and the diving is erratic at best, but on the whole it's fast paced, enjoyable, strategic tennis, and what more can you ask for in a tennis game?GRAPHICS:Not particularly good graphics here. World Court Tennis uses NES style character models with just a hint of shading to give them that "almost 16 bit" look that plagues most TG-16 games. Still, at least they're not off-putting, and they do have some nice little oddities, such as animating the audience clapping and the line judge actually pointing for a ball that's out. Not good, but more than acceptable.SOUND:Umm, it's bad enough to make you notice, but not bad enough to make you turn the sound down. It's like that itch that you can't quite reach on your back that you're not quite sure if it's bad enough to try to contort your body enough to scratch it. Just not a lot of effort was put into it by all appearances.HINTS:- Password -MNRKNHAAFFFFnPW : Tennis King- Faster gameplay -Enter the symbol on the bottom of the D column- Four-way split screen -Enter the cone symbol in all spaceshttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/turbo16/review/R80028.html</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<rating>6</rating>
	<VideoURL>mKE0VGsUkeY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18445</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589076-power-tennis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/power-tennis</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18445-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796122-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796123-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-selecting-the-player.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796125-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-3-court-surface-types.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796127-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-serving-in-hard-court.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796128-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-pressing-the-start-button.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796130-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-select-button-brings.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796131-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-won-the-match.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796133-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-sports-news.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796134-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-where-match-stats-are.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796136-power-tennis-turbografx-16-screenshot-grass-court-score-has.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Power Tennis is a tennis game for the PC Engine that supports up to four human players in its doubles mode. The game has options for singles and doubles with various options for players including an option to watch CPU opponents compete, three possible court types, and a World Tour mode that allows to player to create their own tennis star - male or female - and compete in Open competitions across the globe.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>qR5fPQ4OCus</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a353696f-3138-4837-bb02-fb265be9bdcf.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2503fd6e-512a-43a3-b58b-98b7bf1fcf6d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/969a16b0-83f2-4362-8de0-b81622a8068d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49f07e9d-3ac0-48f5-8fd0-52e5ef6992d6.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson</Publisher>
</game>