<Game>
	<Name>Psychosis (USA)</Name>
	<plot>There is something wrong with your brain. It is being taken over by the Devil Ugar himself! Your only recourse is to fight back against this hostile invasion. Thankfully your mind has created the ultimate weapon: a ship with which you can navigate the five causes (stages) and blast back the Devil's evil minions. It is your only hope, your one last chance to free your mind from this evil influence.Psychosis is a side-scrolling shooter where each level is meant to represent a different location within your mind. One looks like the sky, another filled with aquatic plants, one with what resemble tetris blocks. It is within these stages that you must blast everything in sight while collecting power ups to upgrade your weapon and shield. You can gain two floating balls that resemble mechanical eyes and can be directed 360 degrees around your ship to either act as a shield or to direct your weapon. Battle your way through each stage and defeat the boss at the end and eventually you'll do battle against the very DEVIL himself.Cheat: Level SelectAt the title screen, press Run to start the game. While the screen is fading to black, hold Button 2. The screen will stay black as long as you hold the button. Now, press the Run button 5 times to go to level 2, 45 times for level 3, 25 times for level 4 and 100 times for level 5.Cheat: Turtle ShieldRight near the start of the first stage, you should see two enemies chasing and trying to kill a caterpillar near the bottom of the screen. Try shooting the enemies without shooting the caterpillar itself. If you did it right, you'll see a cocoon near the middle of the level and a bunch of butterflies will fly away when you reach the boss. Now, get to level 4 without losing a life, and a giant turtle will appear and act as your shield.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Home Electronics (U.S.A.) Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>_11XA8nfHNQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8224</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/917248-psychosis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/psychosis</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/psychosis/3030-10833/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/8224-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/8224-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324361-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324362-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-cause-01.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324363-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-only-the-brown-larva-can.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324364-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-after-collecting-a-power.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324365-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324366-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-cause-02.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/324367-psychosis-turbografx-16-screenshot-shooting-at-a-masked-devil.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2716633-psychosis002.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2716632-psychosis001.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2716631-psychosis_%28u%29-003.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ziVm08r.png</banner1>
	<Notes>This is a side-scrolling shooter played in a world created from the mind of a twisted demon. Your soul has suddenly wandered into that evil world that exists in every person's heart. The only way out is to blast your way past the grotesque creatures that block your path in five "causes" (stages). You must face the dangers of this psychedelic world by making full use of three shot types and the satellite option. With power-ups, you can change your shots to a wide-coverage beam, a satellite-generated laser and more. Each shot type can be powered up to three levels. You can also block enemy fire by rotating the satellites to a desired position. How you use these features will be the key to successfully escaping this strange and surreal world</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Wu6ARUMpVdA</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37417783-2032-4655-b70a-649b5aff060b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5e29ec9-36c6-4fce-977e-8258cf1adbb1.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d029de34-c978-4799-8bce-895d83c7534d.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9cbd7bff-7ce6-4ebd-889b-b7269dff9496.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c785e2a8-c688-4386-9273-896cdb1cae3f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4168d58-92fe-4d95-9995-3203e73c1692.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30240bee-5247-4ba7-981f-1a2b82ee5893.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60e9b429-fc10-4985-ab9b-cc02d01cf0d5.PNG</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>NEC</Publisher>
</game>