<Game>
	<Name>Psycho Chaser (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Psycho Chaser is a vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up that features an android protagonist who strides up the screen. It was Sting Entertainment's first video game: the developer would later be better known for their JRPGs like Baroque and Yggdra Union. The player character, the eponymous Psycho Chaser, is a sophisticated android warrior with multiple built-in weapons that was designed to combat an AI that has gone out of control.The game was a PC Engine exclusive for almost two decades until it was added to the Wii's Virtual Console in 2008. Neither version of the game was released outside of Japan.Gameplay:The Psycho Chaser has four weapons that it can switch between at any point which offers different amounts of screen coverage: Fire, Multiway, Blaster and Thunder. Each can be upgraded up to three times between levels by collecting and spending "Psycho Energy".Fire is a straight vertical shot with a high level of power. Upgrades make it more powerful.Multiway fires in three directions: diagonally forward left, diagonally forward right and behind. It's a weaker weapon, but capable of hitting multiple targets in awkward positions. As it is upgraded, it adds additional directions.Blaster is a circular wave beam that attacks enemies directly to the left and right of Psycho Chaser. Upgrades increases the size of the waves.Thunder is a homing attack that automatically targets and chases whichever enemy is closest after being fired. It remains on the screen for a while, preventing the player from firing until it has vanished. Upgrades make it stronger, allowing it to destroy enemies faster.In addition, the player can collect power-ups which fire additional missiles with every shot. They spread out from Psycho Chaser and then fly up the screen.Cheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; EndingFirst reset the game 35 times.Cheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; EndingFull PowerAt the weapon status screen enter the code belowCheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; Ending4 way split screenAt the title screen enter the code belowCheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; EndingEndingAt the level select screen (see separate cheat) enter the code belowCheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; EndingLevel SelectAt the Sound Test screen (see separate cheat), select '1F' and enter the code below. You will hear an explosion if it worked.Cheat: Full Power &amp;amp; 4 way split screen &amp;amp; EndingInvincibilityChoose the level you want to start at and enter the code below</plot>
	<releasedate>6/4/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Naxat Soft</Developer>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>YfAb08DqvwU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22394</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589082-psycho-chaser</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/psycho-chaser</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/psycho-chaser/3030-51978/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/22394-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/150895-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/150896-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383855-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383856-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-at-first-you-don-t.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383857-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-time-for-level-one.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383858-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-incoming-enemies.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383860-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-mid-level-boss.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383861-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-incoming-missile.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383862-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-target-seeking-ammunition.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383863-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-side-ways-shooting.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/383864-psycho-chaser-turbografx-16-screenshot-game-over.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2807373-psycho_chaser_%28j%29-013.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gZQ937I.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Psycho Chaser is a vertically-scrolling sci-fi shooter. The player takes control of the titular battle android. There are multiple weapons which can be picked up and freely switched between, and also power-ups which allow for weapon and energy upgrades between stages.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>dQJ2wRlJ4vA</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d51107c1-3a6a-45c6-9238-c015c34770c8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e1da143-7cc7-4f83-b9e3-9ee3d355b49e.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40508f3b-5248-4592-aac9-c3e8d2c12222.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f539949-e26f-45fe-809d-b1087532b5d4.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Naxat Soft</Publisher>
</game>