<Game>
	<Name>Racing Damashii (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Racing Spirits is a Racing game, published by Irem, which was released in Japan in 1991.HINTS:- Sound test -At the title screen, press Selecthttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/turbo16/home/589086.htmlCheat: Extra Endurance TimesAt the title screen, quickly press Right, Down, Down, Down, Right, Down, Down, Right, Down, Right, Right (hold it) and press either I, II or Select. If done right, a sound will be heard. Now start the Endurance mode and you'll see new endurance times added for each track.Cheat: Extra Endurance TimesAt the title screen, quickly press Right, Down, Down, Down, Right, Down, Down, Right, Down, Right, Right (hold it) and press Run. If done right, a sound will be heard. Now the music will be Off during races.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Irem</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>eRAATxPuoP0</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589086-racing-spirits</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/racing-damashii</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/6/8/51868_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/6/8/51868_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/594727-racing-damashii-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/594728-racing-damashii-turbografx-16-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/594729-racing-damashii-turbografx-16-screenshot-bike-setup.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/594730-racing-damashii-turbografx-16-screenshot-ready-to-start-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/5/f/gfs_5043_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/c/2/gfs_5043_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<Notes>Racing Damashii is a motorcycle racing game with six courses. It is basically action-oriented, but the player needs to watch the damage of the motorcycle (decreases with crashes) and the tire condition (decreases when leaving the road). If one of the two bars runs out, the race is over, but repairs are conducted during pit stops. The two playing modes for single-player are training races and a championship in which points are awarded for good end positions. Those can be reinvested into motorcycle upgrades. The perspective is 3D with the camera fixed behind the player's vehicle.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>1fBc1jjDFGo</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af60212a-b76b-434f-8cc5-6f5d79395e52.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/677572eb-fbd8-477f-bf90-c2f6727b901d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/902c1cbd-29fb-4fdd-b2bb-34b77d928778.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aae46142-25e1-4a71-a88e-34e13ebe835d.png</snapshot8>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Irem</Publisher>
</game>