<Game>
	<Name>Rock-On (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Rock On, likely intended to be "Lock On" (or possibly intended to be different, to avoid confusion with a different Lock On) is a simple horizontal shoot 'em up for the PC Engine. The player controls a small and odd looking ship named the "Macmillan MP4" as they battle through a variety of enemies looking to get rich. The "Macmillan MP4" is capable of holding three types of weapons which the player can cycle through as they choose by pressing the run button. The "I" button is a standard shot type which the Macmillan is always equipped with; the II button is whatever special weapon the player currently has equipped. Both shot types can be fired simultaneously.Story:The game's fast-scrolling intro details the game's basic scenario: People have become bored with everyday life so some have started to search for the treasure (the FISA) of a lost civilization, termed the "ancient people". These bounty hunters are called "busters". The player-controlled protagonist is the buster most likely to succeed, a man named "Mr. Zella". Of course, this future society craves dangerous entertainment, so the whole thing has apparently been turned into some sort of television show for the entertainment of the masses; most of the enemies are likely placed by the makers of the show to increase the entertainment value for viewers. Prize money is apparently awarded for an exciting performance (although this has no effect on gameplay).ItemsThere are a variety of items to be picked up; most are alternate weapons for the player's ship.Speed Up: Increases the ship's speed, up to 6 levels.Laser: Shoots powerful shots straight forward.2 way: Shoot bullets in two directions at an angle above and below the basic shot.3 way: Shoot bullets in three different directions.8 way: Shoot shots in eight different directions.Front fire: Shoots a powerful jet of flame from the front of the ship.Back fire: Shoots a powerful jet of flame from the rear of the ship.Fire ball: Shoots a powerful fireball.Crack: Shots which burst when they hit the enemy, resulting in large damage.Napalm: Shoots missiles that explode in a fiery burst.Lock On Missile: Perhaps this should be "rock on missile"? It destroys even the most powerful of enemies with a single shot, but it's also single-use.Twins: Twin missiles fired from the front of the ship.Froncrash: Turns the Macmillan itself in to a projectile. Dangerous!Snake: Fires a strong snaking chain of shots. Slow rate of fire, but powerful.Barrier: Creates a barrier around the ship which can absorb some damage.Warp: Pick this up to move to the next part of the stage.Reverse warp: Moves the player to an earlier point in the stage. Look out!1up: An extra life.Stages:The game has 4 "zones" which the player advances through in his search for the FISA and for the entertainment of the mindless masses.The Space Zone's boss.SPACE ZONE: The first zone is in space. The second half of the stage takes place in an asteroid field; the stage boss is a giant battleship the player repeatedly circles, ala R-Type's stage 3.DEJA-VU ZONE: This oddly named zone takes place over a cityscape as the sun sets. It is incredibly short; the boss is a small sphere which does very little.The Labyrinth Zone, filled with "FISA".LABYRINTH ZONE: No relation to the identically named area from Sonic, this zone begins in a cave-like environment. The player must maneuver carefully at points to avoid colliding with the terrain. Parts of the stage resemble a mechanized base, complete with pounding piston trips, and other parts are volcanic in nature. Eventually, the player arrives in an ancient temple; the boss is a large mechanical dragon.EXIT ZONE: The final zone. The player continues to advance through mostly cave-like environments, with some variations; the are accelerates progressively, similar to some of the Gradius high-speed stages. Eventually the protagonist escapes back in to space, only for enemies to continue to assault him. The final boss is a resilient blue robot. The player should attempt to grab as much of the treasure as they can at the beginning, as it is the goal of the protagonist's journey.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Big Club</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>d68s6CgOHsE</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589089-rock-on</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/rock-on</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rock-on/3030-33688/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1674295-rockonfront.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/254824-rock-on-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/577195-rock-on-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-story.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/577196-rock-on-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/577197-rock-on-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/577198-rock-on-turbografx-16-screenshot-let-s-go.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/577199-rock-on-turbografx-16-screenshot-blasting-action.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797264-rockon002.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797263-rock_on_%28j%29-015.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797262-rock_on_%28j%29-014.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797261-rock_on_%28j%29-013.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2797260-rock_on_%28j%29-012.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Jjj4nQu.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>You are a buster and you are on a journey to find fortune and the legendary FISA ("mysterious fortune hidden by the ancient people" as the introduction sequence says). Furthermore, the whole world is watching you on TV and looking for your success. Your space ships starts will really low resources, single laser and slow speed. Destroyed enemies will drop icons : 2 (2 ways), 3 (3 ways), 8 (8 ways), S (speed), gun (laser), T (twin lasers), B (Back fire), flame (Fire ball) and infinite (send you back to the beginning of the stage). You can carry up to 3 weapons (items) and they can be selected by pressing Start. Get hit and you will lose all of them.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>QqsuXlDzB54</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b978cb93-0818-43b4-8cc6-cba7310376b1.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7e0b853-d1b0-4d2b-966e-2cfbdd90814b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cb5843f3-e380-4581-ae8d-8d0353062459.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f17a175-8564-4e37-b2bf-5b2039746243.png</snapshot12>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Big Club</Publisher>
</game>