<Game>
	<Name>Shiryou Sensen - War of the Dead (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>You explore towns, dungeons, the countryside, etc. Pretty much your standard RPG except for the modern days setting, and the battle system. It's very similar to Zelda II on the NES, only Zelda II is impossibly awesome and War of the Dead sucks.You play as a girl who... actually I don't know what's going on, everything is completely in Japanese. The only English I could find is the name of the guns! I, being the gun expert that I am, didn't need that translated. What I need translated is the part about who's responsible for the save system, so If I ever go to Japan I can be sure to drop by his house and congratulate him with a louisville slugger upside the head.The graphics are pretty good for how old the game is, they're a little better than NES, but not quite Genesis. It's pretty typical of old PC Engine games, it has that look to it. The one thing I wish PCEngine games had more of is parallax scrolling. It wouldn't do much for this game, but it would definitely make the battle scene graphics much better.REVIEWER: ArmamentArmedArmhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/turbo16/review/R26421.htmlCheat: Debug MenuTo access the debug menu, at the title screen, press Up, Left, Down, Right, I, II, II, I, Right, Down, Left, Up, Run.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Victor Interactive Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589161-war-of-the-dead</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/shiry-sensen-war-of-the-dead-</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/5/3/51953_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/5/3/51953_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/205928-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482631-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482613-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482614-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-it.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482615-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-on.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482616-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-status.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482617-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-i-ve.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482618-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-battle.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482619-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-killed.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482620-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/482621-shiryo-sensen-war-of-the-dead-turbografx-16-screenshot-you.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Shiryou Sensen: War of the Dead (1987) is considered by many to be the first true survival horror game. Designed by Katsuya Iwamoto, it was developed by Fun Factory and published by Victor Music Industries for the MSX2, PC-88 and PC Engine platforms. It also featured open-world gameplay and RPG elements. This horror action RPG revolves around a female SWAT member named Lila who must rescue survivors in an isolated monster-infested town. As the plot unfolds, it is later revealed that the monsters have come from a portal to another world and the family that has secretly protected it for generations.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>VdQ5ZCqOWb4</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90a58233-743a-4328-9865-089a69295da2.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ec28f3ac-4fe9-48a1-81c9-4b2df1052c2d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7000527c-6948-4965-968c-c74135240308.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22cab44f-73f2-4b72-9a9a-2fe5f202069e.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Victor Musical Industries</Publisher>
</game>