<Game>
	<Name>Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Street Fighter II': Champion Edition is a 2D fighting game developed and distributed by Capcom for arcades (running CPS-1 hardware) in March 1992.The first derivative (hence the "dash" in the title) of Street Fighter II, Street Fighter II': Champion Edition tweaked various gameplay elements (changing the speed, damage, priority, and other characteristics of normal and special moves) while allowing players to pick the same character (each player character sporting a different color scheme) and making the four boss characters (Balrog, Vega, Sagat, and M. Bison) playable.In the early '90s, the game received main ports for three platforms: the TurboGrafx-16 (released by NEC Interchannel on June 12, 1993, originally exclusive to Japan), the Genesis (released on September 27, 1993) and the Sharp X68000 (released November 26, 1993, exclusive to Japan). The Genesis version (released as Street Fighter II': Special Champion Edition in North America and Europe and as Street Fighter II' Plus: Champion Edition in Japan) is unique, as it also includes some of the updated content from the SNES version of Street Fighter II Turbo (which also has a Champion Edition mode). The TurboGrafx-16 version was digitally re-released worldwide for the Wii Virtual Console on November 16, 2009 (the Japanese version released by Hudson). An obscure port of the game was released for the Sega Master System by Tec Toy in 1997 (for Brazil only).The game was also ported to the PlayStation in a compilation including World Warrior and Hyper Fighting, released in October 31, 1998 (in North America as Street Fighter Collection 2), December 3, 1998 (in Japan as Capcom Generations 5), and May 1999 (in Europe, published by Virgin, same name as NA). This port includes a Versus and Training Mode, optional arranged soundtracks, and a "Super Vs. Mode" (which allows players to fight with different character versions, later expanded on in Hyper Street Fighter II: The Anniversary Edition). This version was also used in the Saturn release (released in Japan only at the same release date), the Capcom Classics Collection compilation (released on September 27, 2005 for the PlayStation 2 and Xbox), and the Capcom Classics Collection Reloaded compilation (released on October 24, 2006 for the PlayStation Portable).Special Champion EditionSpecial Champion Edition was the console version of both Champion Edition and Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting for the Sega Genesis, it had the following features.ArcadeKen Masters beats up a car.Titled simply Game Start in the in-game menu, arcade mode allows the player to choose from one of the 12 available characters to do battle against and AI opponent. The player would face all of the normal characters in random order followed by the boss characters, also in random order save for M. Bison who is always last. At set intervals during the arcade mode the player would be given a specific task to accomplish against the clock. These included destroying a car, a pile of bricks, and falling barrels.V.S. BattleV.S. Battle the player versus player mode.Group BattleThe Group Battle character select screen.Group battle is also a player versus player mode further broken into two separate variants.Match PlayIn match play both players first choose up to six characters to use. The players then fight with their selected characters in order until one side has been completely wiped out.EliminationElimination is identical to match play save for each player gets to choose how many characters they wish to use.HyperHyper offers all the same modes and options and the standard Champion option except the player gets to choose the hyper level for the game. The hyper level, 0 through 9, increases the speed of the game. Zero hyper being normal speed and nine being somewhere in the vicinity of 5 times speed. Also when in hyper mode the characters default to their alternate color scheme.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Interchannel</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>18873</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/575572-street-fighter-ii-champion-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/street-fighter-ii-champion-edition/3030-1096/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18873-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1614/785117-sf2sce_gen_uk_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18873-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2723132-2201888471-MJ60H.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2722459-7780017099-APr08.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2722458-6311784432-K7r3h.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2722457-3882864292-6TFdQ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3715/701302-sfcemg009.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3715/701300-sfcemg013.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3715/701298-sfcemg004.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3715/701296-sfcemg006.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3715/701295-sfcemg007.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8ORXlw1.png</banner1>
	<Notes>From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Bison's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as Vega, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ArfdKNLtOzw</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/de650688-46e2-46df-844b-75e99df23636.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f08b845c-afbf-401e-baea-812ccb4fcacb.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bdf3648f-dcd2-4a85-bafb-b2733fcb50a4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98d2664a-3525-45a6-a927-f41ebade947c.jpg</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>