<Game>
	<Name>Tatsujin (Japan) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Power on! All systems go! Takeoff! Meet the alien attack head-on in your Super Fighter! Before the Gidans overrun your planet, destroy them in an explosive scramble in space. You are the one pilot alive with the guts to do it! The Gidans have blown up your planet's cargo barge and are on their way to Borogo with a swarm of flying fortresses - asteroids loaded with tanks, guns, and explosives for an all-points takeover! Attack them face-to-face in your Super Fighter, the most powerful assault ship in the universe. Blast them to kingdom come with Power Shots. Fire the incredible Truxton Beam to disintegrate their speeding onslaught. And when there's no escape through their force fields, surprise them with the devastating Rainbow Circle Shot! You CAN save the planet!Cheat: EndingPlay the game until you have scored 7100 points. Reset. Enter the code at the title screenCheat: EndingAt the title screen, press the following buttons to enter the Options Screen. In addition, play the game, score 7100 points, reset and do the same code to get a more advanced Options Screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>2qjEPHqrrNY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>32833</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589146-tatsujin</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/truxton/3030-7598/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/32833-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1614/1294832-truxton_md_uk_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399310-truxton_gen_screenshot2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399291-truxton_gen_screenshot1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399290-truxton_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399289-truxton.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399288-truxton_gen_screenshot4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/8/0/gfs_4256_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/d/gfs_4256_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/a/9/gfs_4256_3_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AK3h4pY.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Tatsujin is a vertical shooter by Taito and conversion of Toaplan arcade game originally released in 1988. The evil Gidans are about to invade the Borogo system, their armada of giant asteroids are approaching and they have to be stopped. The player must infiltrate and destroy no less than five large enemy facilities and take down swarms of alien ships and all kind of ground units. The space fighter comes equipped with a default Vulcan gun (Power shots) and two more weapons are available for the taking - the blue lock-on lasers (Thunder Laser) and green blasts of energy (Tatsujin Beam). The only way to increase the active weapon's firepower is to collect Power Boosters special flying pods leave behind. Although five boosters are necessary to trigger a power-up upgrade and boost up the strength of the current weapon, special red flashing power icons bring it up to maximum power in no time. Each weapon can be powered up to three times for maximum collateral damage and smart bombs in the shape of monstrous skull-faced energy blasts can be unleashed to kill most enemies on screen. Finally, speed boosters are strategically placed throughout the game to help the player dodge enemy fire more efficiently.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>qeLhcTs1NfY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1920b13e-495b-40fd-a834-6086196b7022.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/684417bb-b040-4156-8a5a-d0038d704732.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84dee30a-a394-4788-8973-54d16eb95e92.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/520370d2-8cbc-4cc5-87e2-e8c0052d171f.png</snapshot10>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>