<Game>
	<Name>Tatsujin (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Power on! All systems go! Takeoff! Meet the alien attack head-on in your Super Fighter! Before the Gidans overrun your planet, destroy them in an explosive scramble in space. You are the one pilot alive with the guts to do it! The Gidans have blown up your planet's cargo barge and are on their way to Borogo with a swarm of flying fortresses - asteroids loaded with tanks, guns, and explosives for an all-points takeover! Attack them face-to-face in your Super Fighter, the most powerful assault ship in the universe. Blast them to kingdom come with Power Shots. Fire the incredible Truxton Beam to disintegrate their speeding onslaught. And when there's no escape through their force fields, surprise them with the devastating Rainbow Circle Shot! You CAN save the planet!Cheat: EndingPlay the game until you have scored 7100 points. Reset. Enter the code at the title screenCheat: EndingAt the title screen, press the following buttons to enter the Options Screen. In addition, play the game, score 7100 points, reset and do the same code to get a more advanced Options Screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>2qjEPHqrrNY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>32833</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589146-tatsujin</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/truxton/3030-7598/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TDJ3SvU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1614/1294832-truxton_md_uk_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399310-truxton_gen_screenshot2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399291-truxton_gen_screenshot1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399290-truxton_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399289-truxton.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7192/399288-truxton_gen_screenshot4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/8/0/gfs_4256_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/d/gfs_4256_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/a/9/gfs_4256_3_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AK3h4pY.jpg</banner1>
</game>