<Game>
	<Name>Tenseiryuu - Saint Dragon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Shoot 'em up where you play as a robotic dragon with the ability to use your tail to deflect bullets and harm enemies.COMMENT:This is by far the worst TG-16 game I have ever seen. Everything about this game sucks. Too bad since the arcade game was a real classic and this is the only known port of it.http://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Saint_Dragon.htmCheat: InvincibilityAt the title screen, hold Up and reset the system. If done right, when you start the game, you'll be invincible.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Aicom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>sifQbh9u8eQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18415</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589095-saint-dragon</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18415-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/9/6/gfs_5044_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/0/b/gfs_5044_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/b/f/gfs_5044_3_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PbQSRMw.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Cyborg Monsters have taken over the galaxy, reducing race after race into slavery. Being designed by man these beings have superior firepower and attack capabilities, and can only really be beaten by one of their own. St. Dragon the Cyborg Warrior chooses to fight back against this tyranny, and that is the role you take in this horizontally scrolling shoot 'em up. Five R-Type-style levels await, with a wide variety of weapons on offer. When you lose a life (even your last life; there are continues on offer as well) you don't lose any of your power-up weaponry, but the restart points are quite far apart. The game's main unique feature is the armoured tail you have, which can be used to ward off attackers and can do considerable damage on its own if well-used.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>uxOlFSwpgGE</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50154b61-091e-4a3d-9ed9-8b36b01504bb.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48e978bd-0441-4b06-914b-afd3ba267c09.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8b17495-5c92-4c30-bdb4-eac5553d99aa.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41963df2-b176-4120-9026-0d96e1b190bd.png</snapshot5>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Aicom</Publisher>
</game>