<Game>
	<Name>Terra Cresta II - Mandoraa no Gyakushuu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Vertically scrolling shoot 'em up where you collect modules that can either combine with your ship or fly in formation with you to alter their effectiveness.HINTS:(Pause the game and enter the following)- Bonus ships -Hold Up and press II, I, I, II, then hold Down and press I, II, II, I- Full power -Up, Down, Left, Right, Up, Down, Left, Right, Up, Down, Left, Right, II, Ihttp://www.pcengine.co.uk/HTML_Games/Terra_Cresta_II.htmCheat: Full Power and Bonus ShipsPause the game and enter the following:Cheat: Full Power and Bonus ShipsWhile playing, you can increase your F power anytime by holding Run + I + II (it should pause the game) and pressing Left or Right to increase or decrease it.Cheat: Level SelectAt the 'Formation Design/Game Start' screen, enter the following code. Then press Left or Right to change stages.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Nichibutsu</Developer>
	<VideoURL>rVu2_SL--zc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18418</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589135-terra-cresta-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18418-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/2/1/51921_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/b/f/gfs_5068_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/2/2/gfs_5068_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/2/gfs_5068_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/9/6/gfs_5068_3_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RyaxWAP.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Vertically scrolling shoot 'em up where you collect modules that can either combine with your ship or fly in formation with you to alter their effectiveness. A nice lesser known gem. Typical vertical shooter that uses a system of power ups in the form of different numbered 'armor' that attach to the ship. The armor serves as power ups, but also as 'hit points' as you loose a piece of armor when hit. Each power up can be used in a formation that can be set up at the start of the game for a large variety of options and firing directions. Instead of the secondary button being a 'kill all' bomb, it sends the 'armor' out into the formation. Some combinations of power ups have different weapon outcomes also, as in 'orbiting' protection options and lasers, etc. When all 5 power ups are collected, the ship becomes a 'flaming phoenix' that shoots in all directions and gives temporary invincibility. While not as polished as more popular shooters, the backgrounds (ground) are very detailed. The music is not 'legendary', but I find myself humming the tunes later, as they are quite catchy. The pace of the game is not as frenetic as some, but certainly not boring or slow. The game does suffer from the old 'loose your power ups and you're screwed' syndrome if you lose a ship, as the later enemies take a good bit of damage before defeat... but there are codes for full power ups and extra lives if you choose.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>maOscKaFKVM</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/838db391-24cf-4689-bd42-4233500ed7eb.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d9386d2-e1ed-4ab1-85cf-4e64aada411e.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4766254b-3499-423b-9097-38b6cecd32ff.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be3cf669-4400-4949-91a4-4004711fbcb0.png</snapshot6>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nichibutsu</Publisher>
</game>