<Game>
	<Name>Valkyrie no Densetsu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Legend of Valkyrie puts you in the shoes of a young Valkyrie of Norse mythology as she sets out to reclaim the fabled golden seed, which has been stolen by an evil god.The game plays as a top-down action/adventure title with some RPG and platformer elements. You must navigate the many levels that compose Valhalla and defeat all the enemies in your path while sorting out chasms and other platformer-styled obstacles.You can also find several NPCs in each stage, who offer gameplay hints, clues and items to buy with the gold stolen from fallen enemies. You can buy health power-ups, improved weapons and even magic spells for added fire-power.Cheat: Sound TestPause the game during game play by pressing Run.  Press Up, I, and II at the same time.  The number "00" will appear next to "Magic".  Press Left/Right to change the sound number and press I to play the sound.Cheat: Start Fully Powered Up PasswordAt the password screen, enter the following characters. Format is Row #, Column #.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/8/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>vvFVjUsAIsk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22396</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589154-valkyrie-no-densetsu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/valkyrie-no-densetsu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/legend-of-valkyrie/3030-17440/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/22396-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323703-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323704-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323705-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-game-start-these.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323706-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-jumping-over.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323707-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-boss-fight.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323708-valkyrie-no-densetsu-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-valkyrie.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/238/520955-valk0004.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/238/520920-valkyrie.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/238/520919-valk0022.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/238/520918-valk0019.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Overhead action game. Traverse swamps, canyons, castles and caves armed with your sword that fires upgrade able bolts of energy from its tip. The action also includes a few puzzles and there are some original ideas (like the level where you have to catapult yourself from one place to another). The PC Engine version of the game sports a big number of differences that almost make it a new game; the stage design has been changed, new stages have been added, the players are given passwords to save their progress, there is a new extra boss battle before the players fight the last boss (Kamuzu), and the ending is completely different from that of the arcade version (however, like many other Namco PC Engine conversions, the graphics and sound are inferior to that of the arcade version due to the fact that it is an 8-bit console).</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>vvFVjUsAIsk</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa8b830d-07e3-4b0a-a4e9-868aec4dcc81.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e3ce63d-6d06-4f58-9667-5980efd787aa.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d34b3cc2-27e4-446a-83db-fabe530e90b4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60491f13-ff99-4aa7-81ee-ca7af1a00b79.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>