<Game>
	<Name>Volfied (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Volfied is an Arcade title released by  Taito in 1989 as the sequel to QIX II. As well as ports for the PC Engine, Genesis and the home computers Atari ST, Amiga and PC, Volfied was also released on the 2005 PS2 compilation Taito Legends and as a Java mobile game in Europe in 2007.On home consoles in North America, it was marketed under the more familiar QIX brand. It was known as The Jintori ~Volfied 1500 (Japan) and Neo QIX (US) for its PlayStation port, which was part of the Simple budget series. For its North American Sega Genesis release, it was known as Ultimate QIX.Gameplay:As with QIX, the goal is to carve out pieces of the playing field by drawing a box that encapsulates a certain percentage of the screen. While drawing these boxes, the player's vehicle is vulnerable to the various enemy craft patrolling the playing field. Areas within the drawn squares turn inert and are inaccessible by enemies. Once the player turns enough of the playing field inert, which is a minimum of 80% for Volfied (up from the 70% needed for QIX), the level is complete and the player earns a bonus based on how far over the minimum percentage amount they managed to achieve. Each screen has one large enemy that cannot be defeated: if the player cuts the field in half with one maneuver, the "active" playing field will be whichever side holds the large enemy. Smaller enemies, however, will be destroyed if they are inside the inert area.Volfied introduces small bonus pods that, once enveloped in a box, confer bonuses and power-ups to the player. The type of power-up they earn is based on the letter on the power-up.Cheat: ContinueAfter getting a game over, press Start at the title screen and when the opening demo is begins, press Left 4 times. If done right, you should start on the last level you were in instead of the first stage.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>Azjuves7lyg</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589158-volfied</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/volfied</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/volfied/3030-19732/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/2246230-volfied_cover.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/97170-volfied-turbografx-16-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/97171-volfied-turbografx-16-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210417-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210418-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-short-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210420-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-first-easy-level.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210419-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-score-calculation.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210422-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-pc-engine-version-doesn.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210424-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-famous-bug-known-from.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210425-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-she-folds-out-her-wings-and.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210426-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-a-centipede-like-enemy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210427-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-the-cricket-level-difficult.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210429-volfied-turbografx-16-screenshot-boss-of-the-first-world.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1ZMSMc6.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The space ship Monotros has returned after receiving an SOS call to save his home world (Volfied) from alien invaders and has to defeat a different boss and his minions in each level. Volfied is very similar to Qix -- the player takes control of an ship/object whose purpose is to roam the screen, forming shapes and removing them from the play field. By way of reward, a picture is gradually revealed in the removed areas of the screen. The borders of the area which the player has not cleared become the border of the area the player's pointer can move along. When not cutting the ship is protected by a shield the shield decreases over time and when it hits zero the enemies can also kill you when not cutting. The player's object must avoid contact with any of the enemies which float around the screen, as this will weaken and eventually destroy it. Barriers limit which parts of the border boxes can be formed through. The goal is to clear 80% or more of the screen, and each additional percent adds bonus points. Most levels contain power-up blocks these power-ups can be claimed when the area around it is removed. Possible power-ups are increased speed (S), time frees for the enemies (T), pause you shield from counting down (P), a laser to shoot the smaller enemies (L), all smaller enemies are killed instantly (C) and a weapon to kill the boss (a red tomato only found in blocks with the red light). This game allows for one or two player games in three difficulty levels, but offers no passwords or saved games across its numerous levels.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>firsRUHuIFo</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d363a436-497d-451a-99e8-93798960f546.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3cdfef95-399a-4d53-8cfb-c4292eecfc98.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a89ccb74-6656-49de-8f84-ad86771be902.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/834f6e41-75f1-466f-8028-674546108bd5.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/58f92208-d827-4c8f-8187-1c5d004a7346.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1c5d0326-9f92-41a2-a210-5afec229418a.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>