<Game>
	<Name>Xevious - Fardraut Saga (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Xevious: Fardraut Saga is a vertically scrolling shooter and another installment in the Xevious series which started in 1982 when Xevious was introduced in arcade halls.The story of Xevious: FS is that a large number of UFOs have been reported above the South American continent. The player's duty is to reconnoiter the identity of the unidentified objects and the underground building located at 72.26.The Recon squadron has been mashed up to the last Solvalou. Moreover, we succeeded in developing a transformed type named "Gampmission". That is basically a combination of three fighters which are Solvalou, Solgrado and Zeodalley. By introducing this new machine we obtained the sinews of war which is needed in order to counteract increased enemy power. Now the battlefield of the Xevious army has been extended. Thus, we are in a critical condition.We will start operation of mash the Xevious army. Good Luck.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/6/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>mTlY6-BECPQ</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/tg16/589174-xevious-fardraut-densetsu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/turbo-grafx/xevious-fardraut-saga</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/xevious-fardraut-saga/3030-13357/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14206/971585-xjp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80261-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/226359-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135223-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-namco-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135224-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135225-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-scramble-jet.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135226-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-your-mission.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135227-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-known-object.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135228-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-identified-object.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135229-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-another-object.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135230-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-underground-objects-not.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135231-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-solvalou.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/135232-xevious-fardraut-saga-msx-screenshot-zeodalley.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Xevious: Fardraut Densetsu, despite sharing its name with Xevious: Fardraut Saga (Fardraut Densetsu in Japanese), can be considered a sequel to that game. The humans' battle against the bio-computer GAMP continues, with new pilots rising to the challenge and doing their best to protect the Earth. The game consists of two modes, entitled Arcade and Fardraut. The Arcade mode is the same as the Recon mode in Xevious: Fardraut Saga, being a port of the original arcade Xevious. The Fardraut mode is composed of four stages, featuring familiar South American backgrounds. Unlike most Xevious games, the player takes control of the aircraft Solvalou only in the third stage; the first two ones are played controlling two different, smaller ships, each possessing properties similar to the Solvalou: rapid fire against air enemies, and bombs dropped on ground structures.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>hWNVzQ-ddHM</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/517bd98b-3e41-4eb2-bdea-9117f01d98a5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da875676-0f0b-4763-92ab-87a11fcb03ed.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42f88d03-a488-409c-ac38-c0dbfc2d3250.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d63d3b5-dd39-498e-81df-0eef23b18001.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>