<Game>
	<Name>Blue Dragon Plus</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2009-02-24T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Unleash The Power Within! One year has passed since Shu and his companions defeated the tyrannical remnant of the Ancients, Nene. In the midst of the battle, the world split in two and now consists of a myriad of “cubes” that exploded from its depths. In one of these cubes, King Jibral stands on the balcony of Neo Jibral Castle and surveys the scene before him. He notices a mysterious cube in the distance suddenly start to move violently, and from it he sees the Shadow of a Balaur, a three-headed dragon, emerge. The enormous and sinister Shadow is just the beginning of the new turmoil and devastation to come. Features:  • Single Player Campaign With Over 30 Hours of Game Play  • Control up to 16 humans and Mecha Robos to fight against a horde of enemies  • Equip your units with items and alter their composition to bolster their strength  • Take Advantage of Your DS Features Through Exciting Real-Time Battles and Shadow  • High Quality Dual Screen FMV’s Showcasing More Than an Hour of Story Events!  • Exciting RPG Elements Such As Item Collection, Character Progression and Robot</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67c1f88b-1906-46f8-b180-4cfb01c5b869.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4f29439d-e730-463e-9422-5a37ec3f6261.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6ba205a-d4d6-43fc-8a68-83e0b2b1e1a1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5ad3fe78-318d-4536-9fef-017264368e42.jpg</boxart3>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eaa5f1cb-8b48-489f-b430-490ba9ed2604.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1831fe5e-ae78-4a55-bc53-824cd0bb97ce.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50b9eb09-b062-4b68-866b-8e704d6eaaa6.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c9d4c5d-7f5f-4e4f-b99b-33de6f6a6ae1.jpg</fanart4>
	<Rating>3.5</Rating>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Dragon_Plus</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Role-Playing; Strategy</Genre>
	<Developer>Ignition Entertainment</Developer>
	<Publisher>Feel Plus</Publisher>
</game>