<Game>
	<Name>Contra 4</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2007-11-13T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Battle to save the world. The action franchise that started it all is celebrating its 20th anniversary with an all-new adventure on Nintendo DS! Set after the events of Contra III: Alien Wars, the game follows mercenaries Bill Rizer and Lance Bean as they battle to save the world from a new extraterrestrial threat. Contra 4 takes advantage of the dual screens of the Nintendo DS to deliver larger than life action, with massive enemies, detailed platform gaming and mind-blowing set pieces. Using a variety of upgradable weapons, take the fight to the alien army of the Black Viper and reclaim Earth for mankind in single-player action or 2-player co-op mode. • Fast-paced 2D side-scrolling action from the franchise that defined the genre • Collect multiple power-ups to create new and explosive weapon combinations • Unique dual-screen presentation allows for frantic action and massive boss encounters • New grappling hook accessory lets you access hard to reach areas and dodge enemies • 2-player cooperative action lets you take on the enemy with twice the firepower</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9cb48dd-b3e7-43f2-9941-a2720be4f389.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e6a71bb-1dfe-4753-9656-690be43afbca.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dff34cbf-5853-424b-ae34-09b26efc14c5.png</clearlogo1>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b31f3c85-a0af-4b9c-9a5b-e9effacf12fe.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9097a539-33a0-49e4-b5eb-bc2d3bebff0a.jpg</fanart2>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b350fbd3-bdbd-42ef-bc4b-45237f5d4cd5.JPG</snapshot1>
	<Rating>4.0625</Rating>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Contra_4</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action; Platform; Shooter</Genre>
	<Developer>WayForward Technologies</Developer>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>