<Game>
	<Name>Diddy Kong Racing DS</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2007-02-07T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>The legendary game that single-handedly invented a genre is back and jam-packed with all-new enhancements. Trouble in Tropical Paradise After years of living in peace and harmony, the inhabitants of Timber's Island are shocked when their tropical paradise is invaded by a giant, hideous space pig! To thwart Wizpig’s nefarious plans, explore the sprawling island, unlock hidden racetracks, and drive, hover and fly against colorful characters in high-octane competitions! Your host, a gregarious elephant named Taj, greets you in a grassy meadow. Drive over bridges, through sparkling surf and around volcanoes. Start racing. You'll have to speed through a huge variety of racing challenges if you want to unlock all the island’s secrets, complete the adventure and save your friends from the parlous pig. Diddy Kong Racing DS boasts a huge number of courses, including several all-new ones! Diddy Kong Racing DS offers three types of vehicles: karts, hovercraft and airplanes. The drivers range from the quick and the small to heavyweights who specialize in bashing rivals off the course. Duel with classic DKR power-ups like oil slicks, gas clouds, land mines, super shields, speed boosts, homing missiles and magnets. In Diddy Kong Racing DS, you’d better be ready for anything under the sun!</Plot>
	<nPlayers>8</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d5fd900-dfbc-4e12-baba-72bea97b831d.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0bc55f7-c6ac-4eb0-bb6e-073f082ab189.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fbfd4f3-7cc7-48e9-a2ce-8863f0ad075b.png</clearlogo1>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38d4633e-f940-4125-afcb-e3f93f5dc819.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c29106ad-7c7b-42f3-a4c8-0bc62de8ad2b.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6e772c8-9f70-42e1-a9ae-31d1fd41093c.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cada37d4-2ed3-4110-8f8b-fc1daf0b098c.jpg</fanart4>
	<Rating>2.875</Rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Adventure; Racing</Genre>
	<Developer>Rare</Developer>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>