<Game>
	<Name>LEGO Rock Band</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2009-11-03T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Forget becoming the biggest Rock Band in the world... become the biggest Rock Band in the universe! LEGO style and humor take Rock Band to an all new level; experience fun for the whole family on a wild journey to rock stardom culminating in the ultimate rock gig that will take you out of this world! The game, which will allow families, tweens and teens to experience a wild journey to rock stardom where they can "Build a Band and Rock the Universe," will be available for the Xbox 360® video game and entertainment system from Microsoft, PLAYSTATION®3 computer entertainment system and Wii home videogame console. LEGO Rock Band for Nintendo DS will be developed by TT Games in partnership with Backbone Entertainment, a Foundation 9 Entertainment studio. All versions are scheduled for release holiday 2009. LEGO Rock Band combines the multiplayer music experience of Rock Band® with the fun, customization and humor of the LEGO videogame franchise packed with brilliant chart-topping songs and classic favorites suitable for younger audiences, including: Blur: "Song 2" Carl Douglas: "Kung Fu Fighting" Europe: "The Final Countdown" Good Charlotte: "Boys and Girls" Pink: "So What" Forget becoming the biggest Rock Band in the world... become the biggest Rock Band in the universe! LEGO style and humor take Rock Band to an all-new level; experience fun for the whole family on a wild journey to rock stardom culminating in the ultimate rock gig that will take you out of this world! Songs You Know and Love - rock out to everything from current radio hits to past favorites the whole family will enjoy. LEGO Themed Rock Challenges - play killer riffs to destroy a giant robot, summon a storm and demolish a skyscraper using the power of rock! Enhanced Customizer - don't stop with your avatar, customize your whole entourage! Design the band, roadies, and manager just the way you want! Build fame LEGO style - Collect LEGO bricks after each song to build cooler vehicles and move to new venues. LEGO Rock Den - buy furniture, decorate the walls and customize your band's hang-out as you climb the ladder to rock success. An easier skill set option for budding musicians. The announced song list is as follows: Pink: So What Europe: The Final Countdown Good Charlotte: Boys and Girls Blur: Song 2 Carl Douglas: Kung Fu Fighting Jackson 5: I Want You Back Vampire Weekend: A-Punk Foo Fighters: Breakout Bon Jovi - "You Give Love A Bad Name" Counting Crows - "Accidentally in Love" Sum 41 - "In Too Deep" Blink 182 - "Aliens Exist" The Hives - "Tick Tick Boom!" - Gamestop.com</Plot>
	<VideoURL>_RjG0PnKI2M</VideoURL>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b3e6046b-4583-4c86-89d0-affa383c53e7.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57aca590-bcf0-483f-afd0-7d74725fd912.png</clearlogo1>
	<Rating>2.5</Rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Music</Genre>
	<Developer>Backbone Entertainment, TT Games</Developer>
	<Publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</Publisher>
</game>