<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 09</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2008-08-12T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Madden NFL 09 is an American football video game based on the NFL that was published by EA Sports and developed by EA Tiburon. It is the 20th annual installment in the Madden NFL video game franchise. The game was released for the Nintendo DS, PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable, Wii, Xbox, Xbox 360, and Mobile phone.[1] It was also the last video game for the Xbox produced and released in North America and the last Madden game released for the Nintendo DS. A GameCube version was cancelled due to the system's discontinuation in 2007.[2] Unlike previous versions, the game was not released for the PC. EA Sports has said that they are "retooling the PC version" after not making 09. Despite these claims of 'retooling', PC users were again ignored the following year as no Windows version of Madden NFL 10 were released. In June 2009, EA Sports announced that for the year 2010, the Madden NFL, NCAA Football, NASCAR, NHL, NBA Live, and Tiger Woods PGA Tour series would not be shipped for Microsoft Windows.[3][4] The Wii version of the game is titled Madden NFL 09 All-Play and was launched under EA Sports' new All-Play brand exclusive to the platform, taking a slightly different approach to the game and taking advantage of the motion controls.[5] The 20th Anniversary Collector's Edition of Madden NFL 09 includes NFL Head Coach 09, an alternative case, an exclusive version of John Madden Football '93 with updated teams and rosters and bonus video content and clips. A demo of the game was released on Xbox Live Marketplace and PlayStation Network. The standard version and the anniversary package were released on August 12, 2008. As of August 12, 2008, the game was the last title released for the original Xbox. A Spanish-language version of the game was released on September 17, 2008 for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 platforms.[6]</Plot>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/589fe8b1-b9f0-48f0-96b5-304de316275f.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5f7e56d-3500-4aa7-a5d8-aea737c9cdea.png</clearlogo1>
	<Rating>5</Rating>
	<Genre>Sports</Genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts</Developer>
	<Publisher>Ele</Publisher>
</game>