<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 08</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2007-08-14T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Shrewdly judging talent is a key to success. Feel what it's like to be a field general making key personnel decisions on both sides of the ball during the game’s biggest moments in Madden NFL 08. Quickly identify your strongest players on the field before every snap, then move them into position to make game-changing momentum-altering plays. Play to your team’s strengths by immediately reading your opponent’s schemes and reacting to the action as soon as the ball is snapped. Create mismatches and exploit weaknesses as you read and react with Madden NFL 08. As of May 20, 2014, the Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection service for Nintendo DSi and Wii systems has been retired. Online features of this game are no longer available after this date but this game still provides an entertaining experience in offline mode. To learn more about this service change, please visit To learn more about this service change, please visit support.nintendo.com/servicesupdate. Features All-new look and feel — A redesigned Touch Screen menu system makes it easier to find and play all modes. Use all-new Touch Screen controls to score touchdowns and kick field goals in Paper Football, an old-time classic exclusively for the Nintendo DS. All-new Read &amp; React system — New player skill icons identify on-field strengths and weaknesses, providing an immediate read on what your opponent is giving you. Quickly react, create mismatches, and exploit opponent weaknesses before every play. Spectacular Catch Receiver — These receivers perform amazing catches that no other receiver can complete. Big Hitter Shutdown Corner — Spectacular catches will often leave the receiver vulnerable to big hitters. Read the field — Smart safeties read the offense and reveal all their playart. Aiming Arrow — Clutch kickers hardly ever miss, plain and simple.</Plot>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7079f329-f0b1-41f7-80b0-fc92c8af1019.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b0a8a87f-676d-4331-8015-df8f7d620dca.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Sports</Genre>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>