<Game>
	<Name>Phoenix Wright- Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2007-10-23T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Players star as a defense attorney, who must prove a seemingly guilty client's innocence no matter how dire the circumstances may seem. Phoenix faces the toughest prosecutor yet as the mysterious hard-boiled "Godot" tries to take him down at any cost. Players must collect evidence, survey crime scenes, weed through inconsistent testimonies, and overcome corrupt agendas to ensure that justice prevails. With the return of the popular "psyche-lock" interrogation tool from the previous title, "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Justice for All," players have to overcome even more intense courtroom standoffs in order to close the case. Maya Fey is a bright young girl that aids Phoenix in his trials; she harnesses her psychic powers which are useful in a pinch. Godot - the mysterious, hard-boiled prosecutor makes his appearance. Play as two lawyers - relive Mia's rookie days from the past and Phoenix's current cases in the present. Two distinct gameplay segments: Investigation phase - survey crime scenes, interview witnesses and gather evidence that will be used in court; Court phase - present findings from the investigation to support your case, listen to testimonies and examine witnesses. "Psyche-Lock" system - break down tough witnesses with a series of correct questions or catch them</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7ddf626-560f-4a55-abc7-35805e433b0d.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d17e89dc-2cbf-41c5-8c87-29c3613c2be5.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/732ed4c2-62d9-499a-9ea7-9094c8252d7f.png</clearlogo1>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e958d66-b6f1-44e6-b9c3-a0bddc29114d.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d59be2bc-8974-4a50-a56e-bdab99d84757.jpg</fanart2>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/91b7d544-fa85-4816-ad29-d6b4d89d9556.JPG</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4b329b7-4789-4424-8090-01a1508f1fd8.jpg</snapshot2>
	<Rating>4.25</Rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Genre>Adventure; Visual Novel</Genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>