<Game>
	<Name>Sonic Classic Collection</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2010-03-03T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Sonic Classic Collection is a video game compilation for the Nintendo DS developed by The Creative Assembly Australia, under supervision by Sega Australia and Sega of Europe.[3] It is a collection of: Sonic The Hedgehog Sonic the Hedgehog 2 Sonic the Hedgehog 3 Sonic &amp; Knuckles (With Sonic 3 and Knuckles, and Knuckles in Sonic 2) This compilation was officially announced on December 2, 2009 by Sega of America and was released March 2, 2010, although news of this compilation first broke when it was classified by the Australian Government's OFLC.[4] It features two extra lock-on modes from the originals, which allows the player to play as Knuckles in Sonic 2 and to play the complete version of Sonic 3 (titled "Knuckles in Sonic 3" as opposed to the original "Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles" title).[5] The games receive the addition of a save option; while players can "save anywhere" as billed, they must restart the act in which they saved - they are, however, allowed to keep their score and Chaos Emeralds from when they saved, as well as any extra lives and continues earned. The collection also includes a gallery of images.[6] It was originally supposed to also include Sonic Spinball, Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine, and Sonic 3D Blast but none of those three games made it into the final product.[7] The game was met with mixed to positive reactions from critics, receiving a 70 out of 100 on Metacritic. Praise was directed at the quality of the games included, but was criticized for its lack of a multiplayer mode and how the artwork included was the only extras included.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94c65b9f-c6dd-40c4-8fca-f137ff1d5113.png</1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80cbef82-b4fa-42fc-b5ef-587c0d9a68bd.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f6a2925-fd31-4d11-bf6e-24b7aa4c07a5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Rating>3.25</Rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action; Adventure</Genre>
	<Developer>Sonic Team</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>