<Game>
	<Name>SpongeBob SquarePants- The Yellow Avenger</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2005-11-07T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>SpongeBob acquires Mermaid Man's powers when he wears his belt. Unfortunately SpongeBob accidentally puts the Dirty Bubble into a washing machine with the belt, which causes him to split into countless dirty bubbles. SpongeBob has to stop villains such as Manray, The Sinister Slug, The Jumbo Shrimp, Atomic Flounder, and Dirty Bubble, using Mermaid Man's powers to save Bikini Bottom. The story is divided into Acts, each with a different villain trying to wreak havoc on Bikini Bottom: Manray wants to flood Goo Lagoon; Sinister Slug has an evil plan to stop the talent show; Jumbo Shrimp, with the help of Plankton, creates a machine to shrink people; The Atomic Flounder causes chaos in Industrial Park; and The Dirty Bubble returns with the machine the Jumbo Shrimp used in the third act. He plans to hit SpongeBob with more Little Dirty Bubbles. On the review-aggregating website Metacritic, the DS version has a 67 percent score, indicating "Mixed or average reviews",[1] while the PSP version has a 48 percent, indicating "Generally unfavorable reviews".[2] Ed Lewis of IGN praised the graphics and music of the PSP version, but criticized its "sparse and uninspired" sound effects, as well as, "Confusing menus, lack of guidance, and the creepiest loading screen that's been seen in a long, long while." Lewis also criticized the repetitive game play, writing, "If the levels were linear and you went through the game once these would be a fun challenge, but there's lots and lots and lots of backtracking involved and much of it can't be skipped.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL>2Vuywu4V9Xo</VideoURL>
	<banner1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23662bcc-9cad-4a3e-a13a-a5f95ac25339.png</banner1>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3066cab1-57d4-426a-a38e-bdd5ebbb8c54.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3bfb071-f034-4772-ad1e-9b193b2745d7.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8718844-47ef-4f7f-bc97-3bb8150a2134.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d27d34d-eca2-450c-92c6-8e6a70b8c5c6.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a84f14a7-e9ce-4095-a5bc-b4843f307d33.jpg</snapshot2>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SpongeBob_SquarePants:_The_Yellow_Avenger</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Adventure</Genre>
	<Developer>Tantalus Media</Developer>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>