<Game>
	<Name>Daimakaimura</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1990-07-27T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Daimakaimura is a platform game by Capcom and is the SuperGrafx port of the classic arcade game known outside of Japan as Ghouls'n Ghosts. The brave Arthur, infamous for wearing red hearted boxers under his piece of armor, is back. His beloved princess Prin-Prin has been captured by the great demon king Loki and he has now, once again, the daunting task of rescuing her. His journey gets him through six long stages from a creepy cemetery infested with Grim Reapers and Vultures, to a abandoned windmills full of deadly stone turtles. Arthur starts the game equipped with a short joust spear that he can throw at his enemies. Treasure chests appear from time to time (usually triggered by jumping over specific spots of the scenery) and Arthur can crack them open to reveal new weapons, brand new piece of armors or, if already equipped with one, the almighty Golden Armor. But treasure chests can also reveal mean sorcerers who won't hesitate to turn our hero into an elderly man with a walking stick, or a cute but particularly vulnerable duck. Finally, the Golden Armor can be charged up and unleash powerful attacks from the equipped weapon. For instance, the spear can trigger a lighting spell and daggers a mirror-image of Arthur. The game is vast and mean guardians keep the gates leading to Loki's lair.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL>rVzRe3LQnUc</VideoURL>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d327fe83-9e01-4458-a73c-16cace1080a5.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63789032-83aa-4d3f-b77a-dede6ca366d3.jpg</boxart1>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed350304-c6af-4f68-9b2a-e6a5cfd55bf3.jpg</media1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67d92b01-426f-42e1-8e7b-f1117372b8d6.png</clearlogo1>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b0c9e08b-9e48-429d-8d6c-7ef00e16e13e.jpg</fanart1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b18aaf9-7d39-43e8-b4b5-1154b259b719.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/849e0063-4d45-406c-b754-3b8f1318f864.png</snapshot2>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ghouls_%27n_Ghosts</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action</Genre>
	<Developer>Alfa System</Developer>
	<Publisher>NEC Avenue</Publisher>
</game>