<Game>
	<Name>Madou King Granzort</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1990-04-06T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Madou King Granzort is a side-scrolling action/platform game for the SuperGrafx system and based on a Japanese anime series originally aired in 1989. An atmosphere started to rise on the Moon after a powerful earthquake. Seeing that it could now support life, humans decide to colonize the newly terraformed satellite and settle there. But soon they realize they are not alone and find themselves in the middle of a raging war between two alien species. The player takes control of an armored robot able to transform into three different warriors. Each one of them comes with its own style of play and abilities - the Red Warrior uses a powerful laser sword and can trigger earthquake attacks, the Green Warrior uses a laser bow and can fly, and finally the Blue Warrior uses a spear and can raise an impenetrable power shield. Special items are dotted around each level - their range from extra lives to the one-hit silver shield (S) and the temporary invincibility gold shield (G). Along with the special items found on the playfield, little rabbits also sometimes appear and drop power-ups when killed. These upgrade the player's main weapons up to three times, increasing their overall range or shooting speed. Granzort features seven large maze-like stages and each one of them lead to a deep pit where the level's boss hides.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL>-N6YxGVsams</VideoURL>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74e2edce-89ae-4f0b-93cd-3bbba4bc4afa.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cadb093-f11b-4035-a4cf-c49a07ae8ab8.jpg</boxart1>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d145e197-ad74-4267-bbe7-c2513e93cfdd.jpg</media1>
	<media2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8762e8c9-cd9a-460e-afdd-8e93ae2824a6.jpg</media2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/943dedcc-9aab-4752-a6ab-3e51fc7243ef.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14c86dc1-6b83-4561-a102-e93398b32b9f.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20af403f-f672-4b46-9e2a-77a70a83c5e4.png</snapshot2>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mad%C5%8D_King_Granzort</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action</Genre>
	<Developer>Mutech</Developer>
	<Publisher>Hudson</Publisher>
</game>