<Game>
	<Name>Alchemist Marie & Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In the city of Salburg, there has always been a long tradition of alchemy - a magical science that dealt with combining various materials and turning metals into gold. You play as two young girls, Marlone and Elvira, who have to study at the Academy of alchemy, make powerful items, and prove to their masters they are worthy to be real alchemists.The game is a combination of role-playing and simulation. You have to read books and talk to people in order to learn more about items, and then to buy these items or to to find them somewhere. You must combine powerful items in order to impress your teachers. You also develop your characters in a standard RPG fashion. You can equip weapons and armor on them, and fight random enemies in wilderness areas. You gain levels and become stronger the more enemies you fight. The battles are automatic, and you can only assign a general strategy to your characters.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/7/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Gust Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>Lka9vUiIJ0M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>27693</thegamesdb_id>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/wonderswan-color/alchemist-marie-elie-futari-no-atelier</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alchemist-marie-elie-futari-no-atelier/3030-273/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/27693-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan%20Color/Named_Titles/Alchemist%20Marie%20%26%20Elie%20-%20Futari%20no%20Atelier%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<Notes>Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie: Futari no Atelier is a Strategy game, developed by Gust and published by E3 Staff, which was released in Japan in 2001.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Lka9vUiIJ0M</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4feee2eb-871b-4ffc-89df-6d677f7dba58.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/867048fb-e9d3-4636-a757-f9adadeb0639.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b23b1e37-12ec-4e8e-b89c-638be609cfbc.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/68b5732c-ed78-46d5-bee0-22ed287a9abc.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d189da7a-5c9a-4a96-9d95-8cba3c0542de.png</snapshot3>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>E3 Staff</Publisher>
</game>