<Game>
	<Name>Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:KeroricanRhyme Rider Kerorican is a rhythm game designed by the famed Masaya Matsuura (founder of NanaOn-Sha and credited with the creation of the music game genre). Rhyme Rider Kerorican is very similar to another one of Masaya Matsuura's games, Vib Ribbon. Rhyme Rider Kerorican was released for the WonderSwan Color on December 9, 2000 (only in Japan) and was published by Bandai. Rhyme Rider Kerorican was criticized for its very difficult gameplay, including its difficulty of timing and hard button combinations (in addition, if the player makes one error, it is instant death for Kerorican). Despite this, there is a "one-button" easy mode, in which there are no difficult button combinations.Gameplay:Kerorican flies over several obstacles.The game stars Kerorican, the titular female astronaut of the game. She walks along to techno music. The player must guide her as she encounters enemies and obstacles (jumping, kicking, or dodging these to the music). As she does so, more notes are added to the song. The more obstacles that Kerorican clears, the higher her combo meter goes. If this combo meter goes high enough, she can skip over certain obstacles (by flying over them). This happens more when there are harder button combos. The game is four levels long, for which it was criticized.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/12/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>27747</thegamesdb_id>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/wonderswan-color/rhyme-rider-kerorican</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rhyme-rider-kerorican/3030-18629/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/27747-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/307481-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/307480-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-media.jpg</media1>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan%20Color/Named_Titles/Raku%20Jongg%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267086-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-rhyme-rider.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267177-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-opening.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267087-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-menu-stage.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267088-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-intro-with.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267089-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-hopping.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267090-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-blue-armadillo.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267091-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-three-cones.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267161-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-learn-to.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267162-rhyme-rider-kerorican-wonderswan-color-screenshot-selecting.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Rhyme Rider Kerorican (ライムライダー・ケロリカン?) is a music video game in the style of Vib-Ribbon, an earlier game developed by the same studio. The game's plot is quite simple involving the adventures of Kerorican, a female astronaut wearing kemonomimi-style frog-helmet, as she walks along accompanied by jazzy techno music. As Kerorican continues her walk, she encounters more and more enemies and obstacles. Kerorican must jump, duck, kick aside, or otherwise dodge these obstacles to progress and as she does so, the actions she takes add notes to the song such that the player's actions results in a generative melody. By successfully clearing strings of obstacles, Kerorican's combo count increases and this can result in a reward to the player of a crown that acts to skip the player over obstacles. This game is played with the WonderSwan Color held diagonally, the only game on the system to do so. This is why all text in the game is oblique. The game has been criticized for difficulty of gameplay as timing and tricky button combinations often result in the player's death. The game also only contains 4 levels so replayability-value has also been considered a negative factor.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33b32ffd-fd19-42a5-b390-f0d5ac0634b5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1860a224-0971-4d3b-9301-97ddd6c99394.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd804061-bbea-47a3-8c60-828220efdee8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dcce5dad-2576-4449-b48b-6802e729a02d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df823499-65cf-4a37-ad5a-400fe4dd4dbe.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>