<Game>
	<Name>Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Story:With the brewing conflict between Oldtypes and Newtypes, Dr. Souzou Haran decided to usher in the next step in human evolution by way of the Meganoids. However, his experiment went terribly wrong, as two Meganoids (Zauser and Koros) destroyed Dr. Haran's Martian laboratory. Seeking to expand the Meganoid project, the two declared war on Earth. At the same time, the Muge Empire would stage an invasion, resulting in mass chaos. Luckily, the White Base (with cooperation from the Photon Power Plant, Saotome Research Institute, and Dancougar) would push back the invaders, causing them to scatter across space.One year later, just as Dr. Haran predicted, conflict between Earth Federation and the space-based Principality of Zeon broke out, resulting in the One Year War. The members of the White Base team would be renamed Londo Bell, and would be given the task of defending the Earth.Elsewhere, the aliens from Planet Barm have lost their homeland, and now plot to make the Earth their own...Featured SeriesA list of the anime series which are featured in the game. Super Robot Wars Compact introduced no new series.Mobile Suit Gundam Mobile Suit Gundam 0080: War in the Pocket Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ Mobile Suit Gundam: Char's Counterattack Mobile Suit Gundam F91 New Mobile Report Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Mazinger Z Great Mazinger Getter Robo Getter Robo G Shin Getter Robo (manga version) Brave Raideen Brave Leader Daimos Invincible Steel Man Daitarn 3 Aura Battler Dunbine Heavy Metal L-Gaim Super Beast Machine God Dancougar  New FeaturesSelect Scenario System. Instead of going through the missions in a predetermined path, the game is set up into several chapters. Each chapter has 3-5 missions that can be chosen in any order, before taking on a final mission that closes out that chapter. This is used in all other Compact games, Impact, and MX.End of Mission Bonus. The game rewards the player a skill based on how many turns it took to clear the stage.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/12/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27763</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-robot-wars-compact/3030-23090/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/27763-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan%20Color/Named_Titles/Super%20Robot%20Taisen%20Compact%20for%20WonderSwan%20Color%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<Notes>Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color is a Strategy game, developed by TOSE and published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 2001.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/518645fa-b0f1-45b5-af5e-93b8c61cf4b8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7bd3e72e-6c55-4a8f-a512-be3ffa07c3e8.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4e1fe496-bcce-4732-bc6c-d9bdc487706a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a7657c5-69a3-4640-abb5-a7c6745f6158.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/007623d4-b8b7-4bc6-9b75-b49f34fd0c0d.png</snapshot3>
	<Developer>TOSE</Developer>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>