<Game>
<Name>Bio Force Ape (Japan) (En) (Proto)</Name>
				<plot>Overview:The Bio Force Ape title screen.Bio Force Ape is an unreleased NES title that was in development at SETA before its cancellation. The game is an action platformer that puts the player in the role of a primate infused with power that makes him more humanoid and imparts him with superhuman strength. It was profiled in a preview article in the the August 1991 issue of Nintendo Power, but it was subsequently announced that the game was cancelled in the April 1992 issue.After its cancellation, the game vanished for close to two decades, though fake ROMs that pranksters claimed were the actual game did enter circulation through the internet. However, a copy of the real game, or rather, a functional prerelease build, surfaced in 2010.</plot>
				<releasedate>Canceled</releasedate>
				<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
				<Developer>Seta Corporation</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<VideoURL>BmSgbhAxZ_k</VideoURL>
				<thegamesdb_id>26413</thegamesdb_id>
				<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/995391-bio-force-ape</gamefaqs_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bio-force-ape/3030-35402/</giantbomb_url>
				
				<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AP2Kswn.jpg</boxart1>
				<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TMioIGL.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sAojFgi.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ImGDBoO.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/L35H7WY.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lIS3TcF.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lx5WIdK.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/iVemis7.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/U8X8fMI.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qzrkrNs.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8rGENkz.jpg</snapshot10>
				<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/XClv3n6.jpg</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/pQyqege.png</clearlogo1>

<Notes>Originally slated for release in 1991, Bio Force Ape allows you to play as a pet chimpanzee who must rescue his family by taking the mysterious Bio Force serum and mutating into a pro wrestler. It was the recipient of an extremely positive profile in Nintendo Power — “extremely positive” being NP‘s default setting back in the day — but then vanished, presumably never to be seen again. The archivists at Lost Levels not only acquired the long-lost prototype cartridge, but uploaded a playable version of it to the Internet.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5fe2e0f-c146-4a46-b2fb-743c5d99a0ce.jpg</banner2>
<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b80fd548-9d8b-4b0a-a282-1d4fa44192a2.jpg</boxart2>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/321eff94-dfa3-44c8-96a7-3118e134fd4e.png</clearlogo2>
<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8368c3e3-ec60-4890-8f88-9072b0511fcf.png</snapshot11>
<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e91f59d2-dd48-4647-87c2-9af7e60dee17.png</snapshot12>
<rating>2.8333333333333335</rating>
<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
</game>