<Game>
	<Name>Salamander (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>You've saved the innocent people of Gradius from the vile Bacterions. But now an even deadlier plague has slimed into the neighborhood. It's Zelos, an all-engulfing, planet-eating alien who's hungering to take a bite out of you! Only this time you don't have to rescue the millions of Gradians alone. You can call on a starfighter friend from the planet Latis, who'll fight beside you in his RoadBritish space destroyer. You'll both be gunning for max power-ups, with ripple lasers, plutonic missiles and impregnable force fields. But you better be on target. For this isn't your ordinary space scum. And to crush him you've gotta soar through his guts, blast past his death traps and ultimately blow out his heart. Good luck, Commander. The galaxy's counting on you!Cheat: 255 livesThis glitch might be a bit difficult to pull off, but rest assured that it works. Start a 2 players game. Bring the first player's lives to 0 and the second player's lives to 1. Now position your ships right on top of each other. They have to basically look like 1 ship. Now let yourself be killed and rapidly press the A button on controller 1 to try to steal a life from the 2nd player. If done right, both players will come back to life and the second player will have 255 lives to spare.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>AeQRlSfylp8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1480</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587413-life-force</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/life-force/3030-13960/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/2HwF50k.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/07AR1vf.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/etnGWSS.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/h54lJ8s.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/kQrjuPD.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZiEDV5s.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/uR4e8vq.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zuwQjZ4.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2vE343N.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/UMbGHcv.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Ww1eeOE.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4UaPhfV.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Lma3Wt8.jpg</fanart1>
</game>