<Game>
	<Name>Sanma no Mei Tantei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The player controls a facsimile of Sanma in a detective outfit as he tracks down clues behind a grisly murder that is depicted in the opening cutscene. In spite of the macabre death that begins the game it is full of Japanese comedic touches, such as absurd non-sequitur mini-games and an instance of perverted humor where the protagonist can search a girl's bedroom and find undergarments.It is also full of unique additions to the genre, presumably suggested by Sanma Akashiya himself in much the same way Beat Takeshi directed some of Takeshi's Challenge's odder design decisions. These include a little crab as a cursor for selecting items to interact with as well as the strange designs for some of the NPCs.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/2/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27264</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578397-sanma-no-meitantei</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sanma-no-meitantei</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sanma-no-meitantei/3030-39249/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/S0HHbMW.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/S0HHbMW.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/h2Gwa3y.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/tJbg1Up.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RcPgoCH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tdmLMRb.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/KSHHLgD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1gRakqJ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hNWQsRq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/p5ZxFTl.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/j3syoTW.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yLrDwzQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RiJRpZf.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Sanma no Meitantei (さんまの名探偵 Sanma no Meitantei?, lit. "Great Detective Sanma") is a murder mystery detective adventure game developed and published by Namco for the Famicom in 1987. In the vein of Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken, the player must visit several locations associated with the murder victim, to discover clues which will open up more locations in order to find more clues until ultimately, the identity of the murderer can be confirmed. The game is played entirely in Japanese and was never translated into English. The summary of the story is that while the president Yoshimoto held a party at his villa, Katsura Buntin was found to have been killed in the vault. On top of that, the "Star of Africa" diamond that was stolen from the vault. As detective Sanma Akashiya's assistant, you must help him determine the perpetrators of the incident. The game features a mini game which is a parody of Galaxian, and contains sound effects from other Namco hits such as Dig Dug and Xevious</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/522324d3-36e9-4444-bb6a-e2f812fe5b66.jpg</boxart4>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>