<Game>
	<Name>Seicross (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Seicross is a side-scrolling shoot-em-up/racing game in which a player-controlled racer must collect friendly Petras on a track, while avoiding or destroying the Basrah. The 1984 arcade game lead to ports for Nintendo consoles.Story:The planet Colura is home to two separate peoples: the friendly Petras, of which the player is a member, and the genocidal Basrah. Pacifists all, the Petras have succumbed to a Basrah attack and were driven underground where the Basrah could not attack. Some Petras remain on the surface: Seicross takes place above ground, where the Gilgitt Petras, a "rescue bike" must save the remaining Petras.Gameplay:Gameplay: on the arcade and console versions is identical. The player controls the Gilgitt Petras over multiple lanes. Shooting enemies and collecting Petras accumulates the point total. Avoiding obstacles and collecting fuel are mandatory. There are three stages with different obstacles and visuals, as well as a "dinosaur tank" boss. The game does not have an ending; proceeding through the various stages results in repeating them at a higher difficulty until lives are depleted.Cheat: CodesAt the title screen press and hold Left, A, and B buttons all at once on controller two. Then input the following codes on controller one:</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>FCI|Pony Canyon, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>W6AZnngo_ck</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2061</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587601-seicross</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/seicross</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/seicross/3030-17616/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zUPvoAP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zUPvoAP.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/GiXxkuQ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/qXASWvC.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/oRvp7Mp.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kcNTSJR.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tJhZtqN.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4DnTlHI.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IRKoDJ9.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/j1e2eys.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LQggaYB.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yV9UKkf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9xwlOj0.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/lwfTbRj.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DoZqxPN.png</banner1>
</game>