<Game>
	<Name>Seirei Gari (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The boy Michimune and the girl Miu happily live in a small house together with their wise old grandfather. One day, just when they were about to celebrate Miu's birthday, the room suddenly became dark, and an evil demonic figure appeared out of nowhere. Ironically, the dark being addressed your grandfather, saying it's been a long time. Apparently, grandfather also knew who or what this figure was, since he called him by the name Rosenkreuz. Rosenkreuz explains that he has waited a hundred years, but now it is possible to bring back the God of Evil, and to control the world! But for an unknown reason, he needs Miu. Rosenkreuz strikes your grandfather, and kidnaps Miu! Before grandfather dies, he could only whisper: "Save... Miu...". And thus, Michimune embarks on a dangerous journey to the land of evil, to save Miu from the clutches of Rosenkreuz."Seirei Gari" is a horror-themed adventure game along the lines of the more known  Uninvited or  Deja Vu. Every action is performed by choosing a command from the menu. You should examine every location before objects become "visible" and possible to interact with. Sometimes you'll also have companions at your side who will help you on your quest.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/8/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27267</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579516-seirei-gari</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/seirei-gari</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/seirei-gari/3030-5475/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/6ccWCT7.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/XAQ01BP.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KOoU3kM.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uNcjOkC.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xN2gJO0.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zju9bXs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/xPQRPhW.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/B7v7PaQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/sf5GHYT.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JmDsolx.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/FkDJZlS.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Seirei Gari is an Adventure game, developed by Advance Communication Company and published by Hudson, which was released in Japan in 1989.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0eadba0-f3eb-4d9c-8202-6df9c6053cf5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db463197-d36e-4c8b-a125-daf5656d3a79.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson</Publisher>
</game>