<Game>
	<Name>Sesame Street 123 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This math-based learning title for Ages 3 to 6 featuring Sesame Street characters. Sesame Street 1 2 3 includes a compilation of 2 previously released games:- Astro-Grover: Children play with Grover and the Zips from planet Zap by counting, adding, and subtracting Zips to help improve basic math skills.- Ernie's Magic Shapes: Children work with Ernie to practice matching shapes and colors in the problems he presents to them.http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sesame-street-1-2-3</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<Developer>NewKidCo.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2064</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587602-sesame-street-123</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sesame-street-1-2-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sesame-street-1-2-3/3030-40563/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/FHuA5O2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9QoOFqW.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/BfjoP49.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZmYm7ft.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PJcXRRV.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/m1J5k84.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Jqen0rP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LtF6Ykj.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VDKekCA.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FU65vUj.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/pDpeaLv.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/a8vruA3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/KqwWqxp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/qj6OcI4.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iUCJdzH.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Based on Sesame Street, the long-running PBS children's television show, Sesame Street 123 for the NES stars Bert's best friend and roommate Ernie and the lovable blue muppet Grover. "Ernie's Magic Shapes" consists of six different magic show-themed games that help teach children colors, shapes and pattern recognition. Children are asked to match simple shapes and colors and to choose specific shapes to form things like rocket ships, wheelbarrows, and birds. Astro-Grover features five different outer space-themed games that help teach children simple arithmetic. Children can add, count and subtract little green aliens called "Zips." When a child gets an answer wrong, he or she is gently informed and allowed to try again.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82e4f5ef-cd39-40ce-a6f4-08e90bfdad00.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/006a33a2-d12b-4229-9add-1909db57f8b7.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hi-Tech</Publisher>
</game>