<Game>
	<Name>Shatterhand (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Shatterhand is a side-scrolling action-platforming game. Levels have horizontal and vertical progression, designed with multiple platforms, ledges and even fences on which to grab. Levels are generally capped off with a boss battle. Though not a one-hit-kill game, the player character can take damage merely by touching enemies. The protagonist can also jump and crouch. His jump is a fair mix between tight and floaty, allowing for lenient mid-air control resembling that of a Mega Man game. He can also punch while crouching and in the air, but can only punch left or right--he cannot throw uppercuts to take down enemies above his head.While the primary means of self-defense is this simple punch, the player character can punch crates to collect power-ups in order to summon a floating drone which attacks with a different set of projectiles every time he punches. Drones are summoned once the player collects three drone power-ups, which are denoted as either Alpha or Beta. With the three slots and the two power-ups, there are six different possible combinations. Furthermore, punching a power-up changes it to its counterpart (punch an Alpha power-up and it will change into a Beta), so the player hascontrol over which drone they want to summon. If they happen to collect three alpha/beta power-ups while they already have a drone summoned, they will then don a metallic suit that increases strength and gives the player character a special attack corresponding to the combination of power-ups they've obtained.The player can also collect currency from crates, which can be used on power-up platforms that increase the strength of their punches; give an extra life; or replenish their health. Some crates will yield a moneybag which can be collected, but it's more beneficial to actually punch the bag repeatedly to generate extra money--similar to how one might collect multiple coins repeatedly from the same block in Super Mario Bros. games. Some creates yield grenades which will detonate after a short period of time. These cannot be picked up and must be avoided.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>tDetm8Etozk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22619</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587608-shatterhand</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/shatterhand</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shatterhand/3030-18628/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AuJT1p5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ZWi46M5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/VTyQxik.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/F7e0Xyv.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cOlgwrf.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/91wZQ15.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6QgKZ0M.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7fFHCB5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7KIiMNF.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7naJwPl.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vp9InpG.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IVOlw0t.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VHjq6qD.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OcCXHKU.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/TOkz2Ke.png</banner1>
</game>