<Game>
	<Name>Sherlock Holmes - Hakushaku Reijou Yuukai Jiken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sherlock Holmes: Hakushaku Reijou Yuukai Jiken ("Sherlock Holmes: The Kidnapping of the Count's Daughter") is an adventure game with action elements starring Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's famous detective Sherlock Holmes. It is the first of three such Famicom games from obscure Japanese publisher Towa Chiki, the next two being Meitantei Holmes: Kiri no London Satsujin Jiken and Meitantei Holmes: M-Kara no Chousenjou.Unlike its sequels, which are more traditional Famicom text adventures, Hakushaku Reijou Yuukai Jiken is primarily an action game: Sherlock travels to various cities across the United Kingdom searching for clues behind the kidnapping of the eponymous Count's daughter. In each location, Sherlock can walk around the city and investigate suspicious locations, such as sewers and buildings. Defeating the various henchmen (or regular citizenry) roaming around the cities and sub-locations will provide Sherlock with the funds necessary to move onto the next city via the railway stations. The ultimate goal is to pinpoint where the culprit is hiding with enough clues and confront them.Cheat: Continue - Maximum HealthAt the Game Over screen, press Right + A + B on Controller 2. You'll be returned to the game with full HP and half of your money. Additionally if you hold Left + A + B on Controller 1 before press the buttons on the Controller 2, your money won't be decreased.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/11/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Towachiki</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27271</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578342-sherlock-holmes-hakushaku-reijou-yuukai-jiken</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sherlock-holmes-hakushaku-reij-ykai-jiken-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sherlock-holmes-hakushaku-reijou-yuukai-jiken/3030-42175/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/etzQQ4t.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/etzQQ4t.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/7tDnvn1.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/IXgMvQi.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zg6dhRN.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/64H6gJk.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/erqGzGT.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7FJZgFW.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oLLoblH.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qtbJ2Kq.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nHJbSiG.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3LCu65Q.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4CEhHql.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Sherlock Holmes: Hakushaku Reijou Yuukai Jiken (loosely translated as Sherlock Homes: Kidnapping of the Young Countess) is an adventure game developed for the Famicom by Towachiki, and released in 1986. The game puts the player in the role of Sherlock Holmes, who must travel throughout England (by train) while trying to solve the mystery of a kidnapping. In this unusual portrayal of Holmes, his only means of interrogating anyone to obtain information is by attacking them with jump kicks until they run out of stamina and reveal clues. The game alternates between a zoomed out view of England streets, where every bystander can damage Holmes simply by running in to him, to a zoomed in side scrolling view of buildings or sewers or parks. Besides interrogating people for information, or simply beating them up for train fare, Holmes must search seemingly random cracks or trees in order to find important clues, or inventory items.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/59bc47bb-b2bc-4b7b-938b-d78519f35480.jpg</boxart4>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Towa Chiki</Publisher>
</game>