<Game>
	<Name>Silent Service (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Silent Service is an NES game in which the player controls a submarine and patrols and engages in skirmishes with other submarines. Its is more like a submarine sim then a traditional arcade game.Plot:Silent Service is set in the Pacific Ocean during World War Two. The player assumes control of a U.S. Submarine, the U.S.S. Raven, which is assigned missions to carry out. This side of the war is rarely told in games. There are two types of game modes to play; Convoy Actions and War Patrol. Convoy Actions are specific scenarios in which the player is given a specific objective to complete. In War Patrol mode players are given the ability to roam anywhere in the Pacific  for 30 days looking for Japanese ships to attack. Gameplay:This game is basically a submarine simulation game. It uses realistic tactics such as the End Around, as well as having the ability to adjust visibility and dud torpedoes. The game also gives you control of the rudders, periscope, and ballast, as well as displaying the speed, depth, and heading of your sub. You are placed in the waters of Japan and you are required to ping ships with your sonar in order to detect enemies. This game has a relatively steep learning curve to it.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Ultra Software Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2075</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587616-silent-service</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/silent-service</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/silent-service/3030-7565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xd8t6Dd.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xd8t6Dd.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/m7xwCzP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/p3bP18V.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/RbL1XTz.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZIzyXUx.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KHzbpvX.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/CwAAiG1.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/6TrltNe.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vsIx44g.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MksTLiw.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DVeWvyg.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NkBq0id.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yoTbvwv.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ZOAtWPp.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>You are now a member of the Silent Service, the US Navy Submarine command. For a long while after Pearl Harbor, you are the only forces capable of striking back at the Japanese in the Pacific. Take one of the "fleet boats" and go on extended patrols of up to 2 months from Hawaii, Australia, or New Zealand. Set your difficulty/realism level and time period (early means less tech for juicier targets, later means tougher escorts, more tech, lousier targets). Contend with factors like dud torpedoes, maximum depth, and more.</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b47a8a6-ccd6-4a3f-90dc-8797fe974da2.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3458eacc-2b0c-408f-aadf-2e713f354631.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ultra Software</Publisher>
</game>