<Game>
	<Name>Simpsons, The - Bart vs. the World (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The story takes place after Bart wins a trip around the world on the show of Krusty the Clown. Mr. Smithers rigged the contest for Mr. Burns to get rid of his "worst enemies" the Simpsons. Burns hopes to do this by sending many agents to the different places where Bart will go (4 places in all: China, Egypt, the North Pole and Hollywood) where Bart has to survive the different attacks from the evil duo's agents.Critical ReceptionWhen the Game Gear version was released in 1993 Electronic Gaming Monthly gave the review scores of 7,6,7 and 7 out of ten. Sushi-X, who gave a 7 wrote, "This cart is a big improvement over previous Simpsons' titles for the Game Gear. The graphics are excellent and are very bright and colorful. The sounds are really good too. There is a lot more variety to the game play and the control is very responsive. Of course the humor of Bart and his wacky friends is rampant throughout the game. Overall this is another quality Game Gear cart and Simpsons' fans should take note".Cheat: View CreditsPress and hold Select, then press Reset. While holding Select, immediately after the copyright screen appears, quickly press A, B, Up, Down, Left, Right, A, B. The secret credits message will appear over the top of the copyright screen. Press A + B to return back to the normal copyright screen and back to the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation, Sports, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1401</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563456-the-simpsons-bart-vs-the-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/simpsons-bart-vs-the-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-simpsons-bart-vs-the-world/3030-11108/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Olyo81s.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/4fWPabK.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/CAuHpEB.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/opkLMh9.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/TaNWEQ3.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QNEeNG5.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/WVa868P.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/i6GsimS.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/24h5XDR.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mhnqymh.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hAK8ClN.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ED6ftmT.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/XRfO3OD.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qr7Jceq.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Buzavi5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/xiyXvtL.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/lZqYv83.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/3MtNYfl.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/uSzCGMX.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/ugIE6SC.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/oHD0RZF.jpg</banner1>
</game>