<Game>
	<Name>Skate or Die (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Opening ScreenPlayers could compete in five different skate boarding events, either individually or sequentially. Up to eight players could compete, not at the same time, it was more pass the controller. The game was non-violent. It featured two ramp events, a freestyle ramp and a high jump, two downhill events, a race, and a jam where you did tricks, and a pool joust. The two downhill events and the pool joust could be played in two player mode. While the ramp events where single player.The NPC CharactersRodney Recloose; Wild punk rocker with a purple mohawk. He ran a skate shop in the game.Bionic Lester; Rodney's son. Had a green flat top. Was the Hard AI opponent on the down hill events.Poseur Pete; Was the easy AI opponent on the down hill events.Aggro Eddie; Was the medium AI opponent on the down hill events.Appearances in Other MediaThe game would later be referenced in future EA skateboarding game Skate 2. Players may download a Throwback Pack, which contains t-shirts branding the Skate or Die logo which can be worn by the player's created skater.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<Developer>Ultra Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>xBsLV6R8mkc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1418</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587621-skate-or-die</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/skate-or-die</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/skate-or-die/3030-8819/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/30mGCdm.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/CBTLw46.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/LOe98rX.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/t4AGq1V.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/h9wy9bc.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/WGb1kSP.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eziSmxs.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Dn5hAPR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SwhUGuK.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/a5rsY8W.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Hp5EA4e.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VqFAKwU.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/eaaA1sa.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/DnwEAoa.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/WX7T46L.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/N5SdRo3.png</banner1>
</game>