<Game>
	<Name>Skull & Crossbones (USA) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>So you've always wanted to be a swashbuckling pirate, sailing the high seas, journeying to the ends of the earth, exploring ancient castles and caves for precious booty. And if there's a beautiful Princess in distress to rescue, so much the better, eh matey? All this - and more - is yours to enjoy when you play Skull &amp; Crossbones - the great arcade hit now for play on your NES! Play alone or team up with a friend to become the pirates One Eye or Red Dog. Travel far and wide, battling zombies, skeletons, rats, bats - even ninja pirates (talk about East meeting West!) - all to rescue the kidnapped Princess from the evil Wizard! Skull &amp; Crossbones. It's the swashbuckling adventure of a lifetime!</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Domark Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>hU2kz_bitpc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2079</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587624-skull-and-crossbones</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/skull-crossbones</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/skull-crossbones/3030-4801/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/E5WGFn9.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Q9E3rjE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/taShvBh.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/OFtlAyN.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7vd12TU.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/dMMHD3z.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/isZVjFk.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZPbuGSN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1OZelTN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RZAa9pw.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/87UrcoF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/emJ8AlR.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9aFCDeO.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/keO1p6q.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ySiuwzW.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The player will fight as either Red Beard or One Eye through various pirate themed levels, like ships and forts, and even some non-pirate themed levels, battling ninjas, skeletons, and others in a quest to save a princess from an evil wizard. There's also a split screen mode for two players. The pirates will use several weapons to fight, such as pistols, swords, knifes and their bare fists. At each level, players will have to kill at least 15 enemies to move on and fight the level's boss. Each one of the six levels can be selected freely right from the start, differing only in difficulty (time limit to beat).</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/496b0935-b108-42e9-a57b-e730a1a57447.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d8f7209-8c04-4b82-a0ae-8de5e7427931.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tengen</Publisher>
</game>