<Game>
	<Name>Sky Shark (USA) (Rev 0A)</Name>
	<plot>History:Sky Shark is a vertical-scrolling shooting game in which you take command of a biplane and shoot enemies all around you. It was developed by the company Toaplan and published by Taito in 1987. It was previously called Flying Shark, but was released under the name Sky Shark in the US and was licensed to Romstar for distribution. It was also converted to  the amiga, Commodore 64, DOS, ZX spectrum, Amstrad CPC, Atari ST, FM Towns, and Nintendo Entertainment System.There was a sequel, Fire Shark. It was released for the Sega Megadrive and Arcade in 1990 and is called Same! Same! Same! in Japan.Gameplay:Sky Shark puts you in control of a biplane and makes you take out enemy planes, turrets, tanks and other land bases. The game starts you off with three lives and three bombs. For every one thousand points you get it rewards you with a life. If you make it to the base where you land your plane, the base racks up your points and if you haven't used any bombs it rewards you with an extra one. The game also consists of special power pick ups. You can get these pick ups by destroying a formation of enemy planes which come at you in V shape formations or criss cross style. If you manage to destroy the entire formation they release an S power up that makes you fire extra bullets. If you manage to destroy a formation of yellow enemy planes, you are given an extra 1000 points. ControlsThe controls are really simple. The D pad maneuvers the plane, while the B button makes you drop bombs on enemies. But the bombs have a limit, so you have to use them wisely. Mainly on big ships or swarms of enemy planes. While the A button makes  you shoot bullets out of your plane and are unlimited which you can pretty much mash mindlessly.Cheat: Extra 8 Lives and BombsDuring gameplay, press Start, A, B, A, A, A, B, B, A, A, B, A, B, A, A, B, B. This cheat can be used repeatedly.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>KCH44NdMOp8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2080</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587626-sky-shark</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sky-shark</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sky-shark/3030-6813/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/k9N7kdQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/4aaDY1d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/TGmVXuF.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/G3lJC94.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DMStwP0.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/BdoWneR.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZSCOJM8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5fpAcY3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2QJmXvN.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DSymgZk.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/158gHNz.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fFv00KA.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3D6s3AG.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sky Shark is a top-down shooter similar to Raiden. You start off with four lives and three bombs. With that (you can get more lives at certain point intervals, and more bombs can be found), you, the "Sky Shark" of your squadron, blast through five levels of enemy-infested battlefields with as many as six gun upgrades. (Aside from the bombs and the gun upgrade, there are no other weapons to be found at all.) Includes three difficulty levels and two-player support.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d94fc5ad-fbe4-4823-9b79-d3b2fa88ae59.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66513040-b741-4e6a-ba31-cc7fa6bd9bcb.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>