<Game>
	<Name>Soccer League - Winner's Cup (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Soccer League - Winner's Cup is a side-scrolling soccer game where the goal is to take an international side to the final and win the World Cup. The player can select from one of eight nations, in the order they appear on the select screen:JapanGermanyBrazilFranceSouth KoreaThe United KingdomArgentinaThe United States of AmericaThe game has the option for two-player, as well as a regular single-player competition against the CPU.Cheat: Last GameLast game passwords for each team:</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Data East</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>OECoW2ebdts</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>27278</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578626-soccer-league-winners-cup</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/soccer-league-winners-cup/3030-40171/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/fib1ZMz.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WMUOXX1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GRy9W6f.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1wdbTU4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SnmzH7S.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8HdGkjT.png</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Soccer League - Winner's Cup (サッカーリーグ ウィナーズカップ?) is a soccer game developed by SAS Sakata for the Famicom, and published by Data East in 1988. During game play, field scrolls horizontally across the screen. Players select one of eight international teams and attempt to win the World Cup. The teams that the player can select include: Japan, Germany, Brazil, France, South Korea, England, Argentina, and the USA. Players may choose to play solo against the computer, or compete head to head with another player. Although the game was never released outside of Japan, most of the options are written in English.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/599fd398-df49-4e5e-9dda-7100b9d88d8d.jpg</boxart2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>