<Game>
	<Name>Solar Jetman - Hunt for the Golden Warpship (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Background:Solar Jetman: Hunt for the Golden Warpship is the third  game in the Jetman series. It was designed and developed for the NES by Zippo Games for Rare and released in the US by the now defunct  Tradewest in 1990 (and in Europe by Nintendo).Gameplay:In Solar Jetman, the player takes controll of a jet pod launched to pick up various pieces of a warship.  The pod is able to rotate, thrust and fire a weapon.  As the gravity features the effects of gravity and inertia, steering of the craft was quite difficult for some players.  For example, in order to stop motion in one direction, the player is required to fire their thrusters in the opposite direction, creating a sensation of sliding while trying to move the craft.  The object of the game was for the player to travel into one of the 12 planets of the game (and one bonus level) and collect pieces of a warship with a tractor beam all while fending off enemy craft and watching fuel usage.Cheat: Maxed PasswordsThese passwords are so named because they will start you with 15 lives and 99,999 points on the designated level. You will be on a "Normal"-type map with the Nippon Sports Jetpod, which has the shield and thruster.Cheat: Glitch LevelOn the password screen, type in MMMMMMMMMMMM. It will take you to a shop where there are glitched items, then an oddly colored version of Planet 5 titled U, a glitched bonus stage, and finally Planet 12. You will have 666666 points, 6 lives and 6 jetpods. All items in the shop will be available, and you will start with the Italian racing pod.Cheat: 15 lives at any timeIn order to get 15 lives anywhere in the game, take the password you're given as you play through the game, and replace the first and fourth characters with 'Z'.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tradewest, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>mmI8pOMdwzA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2099</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587633-solar-jetman-hunt-for-the-golden-warpship</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/solar-jetman-hunt-for-the-golden-warpship</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/solar-jetman-hunt-for-the-golden-warpship/3030-20269/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TwcIRVG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/j2AS8Qc.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/4gJIh7R.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/wbMIdqo.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/Lzy146d.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/zmN2Lwq.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/6d9s8vp.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/P3xItpV.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Ahbx8qH.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/IHXKQ3P.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/syyH70b.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Jq793MR.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DUyGoFp.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ST5eKce.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LG8XYmB.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NxvPBje.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hdoSAHg.jpg</banner1>
</game>