<Game>
	<Name>Solomon's Key (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:In Solomon's Key, the wizard Dana adventures through 48 action-puzzle levels (and 15 "secret" levels), searching for items and avoiding danger. Dana uses his magic wand to strategically create or destroy stone blocks, in search of each level's key and exit door. Various monsters block Dana's progress, which he can avoid, trap with blocks, or fight with fire spells.Gameplay:The level design becomes increasingly devious as it progresses and often makes it possible for the player to trap themselves, making it impossible to finish the level. Other levels require precise timing to reach the key and the level's door, while enemies become more frequent and aggressive. Players start with three lives, but can continue by holding UP and pressing A + B from the "Game Deviation Value" screen. Once players move beyond level 40, continues return them there. Finishing the game means completing levels 40 through 50 with only 3 lives, a very challenging feat.Abilities:A typical Solomon's Key level.Players can do three things to help Dana move through each level, search for the key, and avoid danger.Create and destroy orange blocks in adjacent spaces, including blocks diagonally above or below.Break overhead blocks by jumping into them twice with his head.Shoot fireballs at enemies after retrieving red potions that are scattered throughout the levels.While movement seems simple at first, the game makes use of its limited mechanics to create ever more difficult puzzles that call for precise jumping and block creation. Players who can place blocks in mid-jump (creating a block below Dana while in mid-air) will find the game's hardest puzzles more navigable.Hidden Items and Game EndingsGame levels organize around the Zodiac's 12 houses, with 4 rooms per sign. Level 1 to 4 is Aries, 5 to 8 is Taurus, and so on, through Pisces at 45-48. When players pick up the constellation tile in the last room of each group (level 4, 8, 12, etc.), they enter hidden levels that contain spells and special items. While Solomon's Key ends after level 48 (or the Fairy room, details below), players can earn better endings by collecting Seals of Solomon and these special items.Worst ending: failed to collect Seals of Solomon.Better ending: collect five Seals (rooms 9, 13, 17, 21, 29), Page of Time (hidden room after 20), and Page of Space (hidden room after 44)Best ending: collect seven Seals (rooms 9, 13, 17, 21, 29, 46, 47), Page of Time, Page of Space, and save Fairy Princess (hidden room after 48)</plot>
	<releasedate>7/5/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>v13qRCxEcsM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2101</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/570522-solomons-key</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/solomons-key</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/solomons-key/3030-928/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/YlEQhoh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/swi2POo.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/TH9raF4.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/EVKt4nf.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jPQbmC7.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/omszT9e.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/cixDNNM.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/b5gzLj6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/44g4rlw.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bapoDr9.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Rj0smEX.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/CYbeaSn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/t65v3cq.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kNjfhE1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/SyB1Bvp.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eP1yM4o.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Solomon's Key is a platform game with both action and strategy elements. On each level your goal is to retrieve a key which can then be used to unlock the exit. To help out, you have a magic wand which can be used to create and destroy blocks (though some blocks can't be destroyed). In order to reach the key you will need carefully to arrange the blocks on the screen so you can jump your way around safely. Wandering around each level are a variety of enemies which will cause you to lose a life if you're caught. Some creatures can be killed by destroying the block they are standing on, others must be dodged. Hidden bonuses and magic can be found on many of the levels, sometimes even hidden in blocks. Some treasures give you bonus points, others can form magic spells to help deal with the enemies. To make the game more difficult, each level has a time limit in which it must be completed.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>r9JVHVr4hZU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/226ac196-f675-4468-9b45-836597feaf49.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eaa82817-06fe-4dbc-b569-22180d3e3abf.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5b40baa2-2e54-4053-9ea4-7a31ae39b32e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e70a0401-8b97-446b-9eff-31d242806c91.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e76db3f4-3232-4fd4-9761-75acba2616b1.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99fba05b-7f5b-4885-b8ab-4c1ba2fec56f.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e275342f-44a0-4ce9-8c62-7c3e2823209a.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d4e1d0d-ae03-49ed-ad67-0eb536c6f92d.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92a88cc6-4c92-46ef-8afc-f0ddd09faa8a.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a15c8df-3ba7-4c39-aadc-95d5fadb5e68.jpg</snapshot18>
	<snapshot19>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0de4067-a8e1-4bbe-9966-e5250e86525c.jpg</snapshot19>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>