<Game>
	<Name>Solomon's Key 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This is a pretty cool little puzzle game. You are Dana, a wizard, of Coolmint Island. Coolmint has become plagued with flames and will melt if you don't get rid of them. It's a bright and colorful little game that is simple and straightforward to play. The music is simple and unobtrusive, which is the way I feel a puzzler's music should be.Directions:Work your way through each temple, defeating all enemies within. Create blocks of ice next to walls to secure them in space and create stairs or bridges. Drop blocks of ice down onto enemies or push loose blocks of ice into them. When you create ice with your wand, you create it at an angle in front of and below you, so you must be standing on a surface that is higher and behind where you want to create ice.The time at the bottom of the screen is only for personal scoring and does not affect the game play. The only place where you have to worry about time is in the labyrinths. There you must destroy all enemies before the rising lava level reaches you. You cannot stop the lava with ice.If you have made a mistake that doesn't allow you to progress any further in a level, don't panic. You aren't trapped there and you don't have to reset the game. Just press start and choose "TRY AGAIN". No worries.Eventually you will get to tunnels that you can move through. You can move up through these. The levels get more and more difficult, sometimes requiring you to drop the enemies down by destroying the ice under them before you can destroy them. Keep trying and you will succeed! Controls:A Button: Create/Destroy IceB Button: Create/Destroy IceStart Button: Start GameHints:Create It Before You Break ItMake sure you really don't need a piece of ice before you destroy it. You can't get it back sometimes without restarting. Stand on top of loose pieces of ice and create a spare if you're not sure. Just make two more blocks, now there should be three, and destroy the middle one. Now you have an extra, just in case. http://consoleclassix.com/nes/fire_n_ice.htmlCheat: Bonus Levels &amp; Sound TestAt the title screen when the words "PUSH START BUTTON" begin flashing, input the codeCheat: Consecutive Progress PasswordsNote that these passwords assume that you're going in order and want to start at the named level. For example, the 1-8 password assumes you've beaten 1-1, 1-2, 1-3, 1-4, 1-5, 1-6, and 1-7, and no more.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>bdcHD1DzZBQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1449</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587277-fire-n-ice</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/solomons-key</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/solomons-key/3030-928/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/gCmYgwU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/3KjTVTX.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/TH9raF4.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/EVKt4nf.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/CYbeaSn.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/t65v3cq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/kNjfhE1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/bKl3xsD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BPqkqLi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/qjgPzWP.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kWVZuHD.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/KHX3jkQ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2tkdCCY.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JV8mICz.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BubJh7v.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Some levels contain pipes through which Dana can go, burning jars that melt ice or moving monsters instead of flames. There are ten worlds plus five secret worlds that contain ten levels. The first nine worlds can be played in any order. The tenth level of a world usually features a special challenge like moving flames or monsters and lava that is slowly rising from the bottom.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a7d3e6a8-1312-47c2-9bbf-d8c1fc25ddd4.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c00d703c-358c-40e1-9fdd-5f06a4717990.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>