<Game>
	<Name>Son Son (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In this game, you play the role of either Son Son or Ton Ton as you try to rescue your three friends from the clutches of a random bad guy who kidnapped them right in front of you. This game is a side scrolling adventure, where the game field advances automatically, and the screen is divided in six different floors, all of which are populated by enemies or obstacles that will kill you if you touch them; but both Son Son and Ton Ton attack their enemies by shooting small bullets at them out of their weapons (a magic cane and a pitchfork, respectively). Their attack can also stop many enemy projectiles! Your chosen character must jump from floor to floor, evading hunters, bats, fish, statues, insects, skull coins, and mad bombers! As you advance, you can pick up several food items to increase your score. Clearing the screen of enemies will also net you several hefty bonuses.The story is heavily based upon "Journey To The West"; the player characters as well as the kidnapped ones are based upon the main characters in the story. This game is also a port of Capcom's original arcade game.Cheat: InvincibilityAt the title screen, quickly enter:Cheat: Harder GameplayClear the game once, and the next playthrough will have more enemies to fight, thus making it harder.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>UCtm21B-OI4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>27279</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578273-sonson</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/son-son</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/son-son/3030-5046/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/B8rnesr.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7yhyauq.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZdQhRWd.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/RwoyV9e.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Ksy8H1x.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LChcH1K.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wBYNSJv.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/WcflT1k.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/1JoqSaY.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/7i2i7t6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/O5TXEEK.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UBuBC6K.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>SonSon (Japanese: ソンソン?) is an arcade video game by Capcom released in July 1984. It is loosely based on the novel Journey to the West. The player assumes the role of a monkey boy (who is patterned after Sun Wukong from the story) and fights their way from one side to another, eventually reaching the statue of Buddha. One battles bats, rats, and mad bombers along the way with his stout fighting rod that shoots balls of fire. The game was ported from the arcade to the Nintendo Famicom in Japan. A sequel, entitled SonSon II, was released for the PC Engine. The game is a 2-D sidescrolling platformer. The screen scrolls automatically, only stopping to fight major enemies. The screen features six continuous platforms that occasionally feature small gaps. Sonson and Tonton walk automatically across these platforms. Pressing up or down will cause them to jump up or down to the next platform. Pressing left causes them to move more slowly than the screen scrolls, essentially continuing to move forward but at a reduced pace. Pressing right does the opposite - SonSon and TonTon will move across the platforms faster than the screen scrolls. The duo have only one attack - the ability to fire energy blasts from their stalves. Touching an enemy or an unfriendly projectile causes the player to lose a life. If a player has any additional lives, they will return to the screen riding on a cloud that will give them temporary invincibility. If the player presses the control stick in any direction, the cloud will disappear and the character will resume its usual walking mode. The cloud will eventually disappear on its own if the control stick is not used. Power-ups come in the form of various fruits which produce points (with enough points giving the player an extra life). Gathering certain fruit will cause all enemies currently on a screen to turn into point-bearing fruits. Walking across certain platforms will randomly cause a bamboo shoot to sprout, yielding many extra points. It is possible to play the game co-operatively with partner who plays as TonTon (who is Zhu Wuneng in the original story).</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82e3e615-2275-449d-8107-184a3e6d1ee1.png</boxart2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>