<Game>
	<Name>Space Hunter (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Space Hunter is a sci-fi game from Kemco in which the player controls a female space hunter searching for a way to stop an alien missile bombardment of Earth. To do this, she travels to various planets in any order the player chooses, defeating the alien life that has inhabited each world and delving below each planet's surface to find the necessary items to stop the attack.The game is unashamedly based on the Nintendo game Metroid, which referred to its heroine as a "Space Hunter" in the manual. Though the games play differently, the success of Metroid clearly inspired more than a few elements of Space Hunter.Cheat: Max PowerStart the game and before entering any planet, press and hold on Right, A &amp; B on the 2nd controller. While still holding the buttons, enter a planet. If done right, you will have 255 Power.Cheat: Last Level PasswordEnter in "Password" in the main menu the following password:</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kemco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>27280</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578314-space-hunter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/space-hunter_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/space-hunter/3030-41748/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Q4nexsi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Q4nexsi.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eYfpPeY.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dl9q1Hn.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/M7SiHFf.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nLRGRVB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yD4FlCs.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/aGDA1LR.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PPj45J4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZfLyC5u.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/tOA8LOG.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KA34sD0.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LOuLzcN.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Space Hunter (スペースハンター?)[2] is a Japan-exclusive video game that was released in 1986 for the Family Computer. The game was published by Kemco; which was then known as Kotobuki System. The plot apparently revolves around a robotic revolt led by a robot named De Gaulle. It is the year 2199 AD. By the explosions of global nuclear war, society has broken up into nine small expulsions, one of them disappeared and Venus collided with another celestial object. Humanity only slightly survived. Its thread of life barely connected to a body; which was rebuilt into a cyborg. The heroine is named Al Tiana and is also apparently a robot who does not support the rebellion. She is out to prove her loyalty to the humans.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/07ae863e-1d0b-440d-843d-b256247d4d17.jpg</boxart4>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>