<Game>
	<Name>Spartan X 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Somewhat more faithful to the plot of the movie than the first Spartan X game, it attempts to tell the same story: In Barcelona, Mr. X has captured the pickpocket Silvia. In order to get her back, Thomas, a Kung-Fu master who runs a restaurant must travel the city, eventually reaching Mr. X's castle and attempt to rescue her.Spartan X 2 is an expanded version of the original Spartan X game (aka Kung-Fu). Similar to that game, Spartan X 2 is a side-scrolling fighting game. Controlling Thomas, the player is able to move left and right, jump, kick and punch. Thomas has an energy bar and is defeated if he loses all of the energy. Some enemies drop items such as potions which will help replenish this bar. At the end of each level, Thomas encounters a boss.Story cutscenes are displayed between each level, where Thomas contacts other characters through use of a computer.Cheat: Full HealthWhile gameplay, press UP+START to replenish your health. After the health meter becomes full, unpause the game. This can be done as many times as you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/9/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Irem Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>22517</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587397-spartan-x-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/spartan-x-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spartan-x-2/3030-13529/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/bhgTJjr.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/E0RKIN7.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6L7ozat.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/L8Dlwgp.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iBeh1C0.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/YrFfAwI.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/AMD5JRW.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/SZ61mjw.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/84KelFs.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/apYSVt9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/uQSdS0E.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Spartan X 2 (スパルタンＸ２ Suparutan Ekusu Tsū?) is a 1991 beat 'em up video game developed by Tamtex and published by Irem exclusively in Japan for the Family Computer. It is a sequel to Irem's 1984 coin-operated video game Spartan X (released internationally by Data East under the title of Kung-Fu Master), which was later ported to the Family Computer by Nintendo in 1985. The city has been corrupted by drugs for some time. Johnny Thomas, a man who lost his mother and sister as a result of his father being used as an experiment for a new kind of drug, is the only man who opposes the drug syndicates. After the incident, Thomas left the corrupted police department he was working for and became a private secret agent in order to investigate the illegal trafficking routes in his city. During his investigation, he learns that an international criminal organization known as "Hawk" is responsible for the majority of the drugs that has sneaked into the country.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40d92276-2592-40ab-a184-d425cf56e569.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95ec20c3-178a-43d5-9018-aa4a9119b9f5.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Irem</Publisher>
</game>