<Game>
	<Name>Splatter House - Wanpaku Graffiti (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Splatterhouse: Wanpaku Graffiti is the second game in the Splatterhouse franchise. It was only released in Japan on July 31, 1989 for the Famicom. The game was developed and published by Namco. Unlike the first Splatterhouse, Wanpaku Graffiti had "super-deformed" characters, probably due to the hardware of the Famicom. The game is a prequel to Splatterhouse. In Wanpaku Graffiti, the player takes on the role of Rick as he hunts the evil Pumpkin King though seven levels of gameplay.Gameplay:Despite the game's cuter style, there is a lot of gore.Wanpaku Graffiti is a beat-'em-up, just like the other games in the Splatterhouse franchise. Despite the game's "cuter" tone, there is still gore (as with other games in the franchise). Rick fights his way through seven levels, filled with a variety of enemies. Wanpaku Graffiti also has a level system. The higher the level, the larger the life bar is. Wanpaku Graffiti also contains numerous references to horror movies such as Alien, The Exorcist, Jaws, and Friday the 13th.Cheat: CreditsPress and hold Up, A &amp; Select on the 1st controller, then press Reset. If done right, the credits will be shown.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/7/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>SMhBvbX-YOg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22442</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/577840-splatterhouse-wanpaku-graffiti</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/splatterhouse-wanpaku-graffiti</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/splatterhouse-wanpaku-graffiti/3030-4912/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WHkEXVj.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ldRuQcv.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/3QNxcbs.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bb0ZGYL.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/q2E79s0.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ejBt8EN.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zmwecKM.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QxAKekI.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/svlCUz6.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Re5rCHg.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Y9HBL7b.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/boHoB2o.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TarOLZz.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yJoNWve.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Revived by his girlfriend's grief and a flash of lightning, Rick must chase down the Pumpkin king and save his beloved Jennifer once and for all!  A parody of the bloody horror beat-'em-up Splatterhouse, Wanpaku Graffiti assumes a much cuter appearance but retains the same fast-paced action of the original.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be230ff0-85f1-457e-bf64-e2b2ac8100c7.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1afbeb2d-7e82-46dd-8c6a-07dd1644e12f.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>