<Game>
	<Name>Spy vs Spy (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>M.A.D. magazines comic strip of the same name comes to life in this game which was designed for one or two players. The innovative split-screen shows both spies at the same time. Play with a friend or against the machine.The black crow and the white crow are out to beat each other before the time bell rings. Find the needed objects by digging through drawers, closets and furniture in the house. Foil your opponent by setting creative booby traps in the various rooms (a bomb in a dresser drawer, for instance).Fights ensue when both spies enter the same room.  Find hidden weapons in the rooms to help with those fights, since one of you will die if you run into each other.Cheat: Replenish your energy completelyIf you have the suitcase, and your energy is low, walk up to a piece of furniture. Press A so the Spy will hide the suitcase in the furniture. Press A to retrieve the suitcase. When the spy gets the suitcase back, your energy will replenish.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Kemco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>p8_ubn5H2wg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1451</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587639-spy-vs-spy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/spy-vs-spy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spy-vs-spy/3030-15637/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7JQN7NB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/o4ZOWSO.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/bpKVERR.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/63e55ca.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/vlRGBKo.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7imTTcA.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/dvDCZBb.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tcsVxfU.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9CZll80.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/thxV65o.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vKkQoBv.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/GvseRZM.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Ez9s264.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/wZOpaCQ.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8AooCbQ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JaLzQH3.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yalzlZ4.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The black Spy and the white Spy are out to beat each other before the time bell rings. Find the needed objects by digging through drawers, closets and furniture in the house. Foil your opponent by setting creative booby traps in the various rooms (a bomb in a dresser drawer, for instance). Fights ensue when both spies enter the same room. Find hidden weapons in the rooms to help with those fights, since one of you will die if you run into each other.</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72d10356-9416-45ea-871c-b9a10ca8408a.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a88a6ff4-7829-41f2-a5fe-2d56765b8d43.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>