<Game>
	<Name>Stadium Events (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Running Stadium was developed and published by Bandai and was released in Japan in 1986 and in North America in 1987 under the title Stadium Events. However, shortly after release, Nintendo purchased the North American rights to the Family Fun Fitness series and decided to market the series themselves. As a result, Stadium Events was renamed and repackaged under the title World Class Track Meet, and all Family Fun Fitness mats and copies of Stadium Events were pulled from store shelves. Stadium Events has become the hardest to find licensed game available on the Nintendo Entertainment System; there exist less than 10 known complete (cartridge, manual, and box) copies of Stadium Events.Despite the changes, the three games remain identical to one another, aside from the name change on the title screen. The game featured an Olympics-style competition, with events such as the 100m dash, 110m hurdles, long jump, and triple jump. Race opponents were named after animals, the slowest being Turtle and the fastest being Cheetah.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Athletic_World</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1452</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587781-stadium-events</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/stadium-events</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/stadium-events/3030-7309/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/KsPqeQW.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GMSXdV5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/5wCm9Dr.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/zNhTuTE.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/lfO3429.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/onmMJiE.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qPgsQug.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PdGKnjf.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/W25mPoO.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZUruLrS.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kNjqdu5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/n1LeOZ9.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5meR3p6.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/84m1L65.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QhKbUGd.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/luYCdxK.png</banner1>
</game>