<Game>
	<Name>Stanley - The Search for Dr. Livingston (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The game is set in Congo, Africa, in 1870, and its main character is a historical figure. You play as Henry M. Stanley (1841-1904), a reporter for the New York City Newspaper, who was sent by his employers to chronicle the work of the famous Africa-explorer, Dr. Livingston. Unfortunately, the Doctor left without you, hating press and everything connected to it. Recently he disappeared somewhere in the jungle of Congo, leaving only a few notes. Apparently, he was on the trail ofre-discovering the legendary lost temple of the Amut people, Am-Zutuk. You decide to follow his steps, to find the lost Dr. Livingston, and maybe to learn more about the mysterious people of Amut and the temple.The game takes you to Congo, where you can move from location to location on a "world map" with about a hundred accessible areas. You should make your way through platform levels populated with wild animals and other foes. Some of the levels are impassable or serve no purpose, others contain valuable clues and useful items. You can also visit town areas and talk to people. There is a variety of weapons to be found during your quest, including "native" ones such as blowpipe and spear.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsEnter the following at the password screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Electro Brain Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2109</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587645-stanley-the-search-for-dr-livingston</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/stanley-the-search-for-dr-livingston</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/stanley-the-search-for-dr-livingston/3030-9593/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/j12Pc2R.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HCWnuFJ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9PtV9sQ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/d2lfidC.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xzZOjdx.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7DGrU87.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OsmWG2V.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rmZa4Gw.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Tb65fkn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jbh4oJV.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/W5QF0WJ.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The video game takes place in the "deepest and darkest" part of Africa during the year 1871. Nations were sending their explorers to uncover the last remaining continent that was not fully mapped by the European superpowers. Dr. Livingston abandoned his original quest to uncover the temple of Am-Zutuk; who was worshipped as a god amongst the indigenous African people. The player, as reporter Henry Morton Stanley (after Sir Stanley, 1841-1904), is exploring the last of the mysterious jungle regions for European colonization when his professor, Dr. Livingston (patterned after Dr. David Livingstone, with an ending "e"), gets kidnapped by some African tribesmen. Now, the player must explore one of the last uncharted parts of Africa to save his mentor and end an era of exploring Africa. The player is automatically equipped with an gyrocopter to make those tricky landings much smoother.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f95034b1-eb9e-4e4f-a03c-8de5861088a5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d87ea090-874e-430e-a2e7-43e41724c908.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electro-Brain</Publisher>
</game>