<Game>
	<Name>Starship Hector (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Starship Hector is a deliberately old-fashioned shooter (even for its time) designed for core shooter fans and geared towards gathering high scores. To this end, it has a couple of alternate timed challenges to the main campaign mode with which players can practice getting as high a score as possible.Gameplay:The vertically-scrolling stages are very familiar to Xevious fans, as the ship is able to shoot airborne targets with their guns and ground-based targets with their bombs, and never vice versa. Unlike Xevious, bombs continue flying vertically upwards like gun bullets, instead of stopping short at a pre-defined point (i.e. when they hit the ground). Like Xevious, there are also special hidden areas the bombs might hit which create a smart bomb like effect, removing all other ground-based targets in the vicinity. Chances there that there's one nearby if there's a particularly heavy presence of ground-based enemies. Additionally, the player can constantly bomb the odd rock devil heads on the ground for small health boosts, as the player's ship has a health bar rather than the customary single hit point.The horizontally-scrolling stages are far more like Gradius or R-Type. Players can still bomb targets on the ground, but must be aware of the arc that bombs take to fall downwards. Once the bombs touch down, they continue rolling across the ground until they hit something much as they do in the vertically-scrolling stages.In both modes, there are no power-ups for either of the player's ship's weapons. Occasionally, this will mean that avoiding enemies is safer than trying to destroy them, as many require multiple shots. At the end of each stage is a boss, which usually can only be destroyed by systematically blowing up each gun turret and segment that comprises it.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>2114</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587652-starship-hector</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/starship-hector</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/starship-hector/3030-8092/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/czMNk48.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/czMNk48.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/99qP0s0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/bxgH3EO.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/OEHPyow.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2hMKaGj.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0l0Bejw.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AWosnt6.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BRunL5R.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5x3Lf4j.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nW8oLIT.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rhtCip1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0pq9VuI.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/48RV38w.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Your ship is equipped with both a standard laser and an independently fired ground weapon, which you must coordinate to defeat ground and aerial enemies. A shield bar keeps track of your damage and you can replenish it by defeating certain enemies, but otherwise its just you, your ship and several stages of alien enemies that alternate between top-down and side-scrolling perspectives.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be7faa77-487e-4a24-be39-b038a549e995.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5d0b4b6-346a-4b51-8c75-64e2a194d16d.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>