<Game>
	<Name>Star Trek - 25th Anniversary (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The U.S.S. Enterprise is in a Red Alert. A tremendous blunder in a warp experiment has created a rip in the fabric of space, catapulting the ship and crew across the galaxy beyond the Neutral Zone. The crippled ship must now boldly go back and repair the damage. Four spellbinding stages will take you on an energized adventure that transforms the look, the mood, the dialogue and the attitude of the original classic series from television to the NES! You become Captain Kirk and take command of your stellar crew, Mr. Spock, Scotty, Chekov, Uhura and Sulu. Operate the photon torpedoes, hand phasers, tricorders, transporters, and whatever it takes to see that your Star Fleet arrives safely in the Final Frontier. You'll see familiar phrases and recognize scenes from your favorite Star Trek episodes when you beam down to vast unexplored planets, collect dilithium crystals, encounter nightmarish aliens and use the reasoning skills of a Vulcan to solve perplexing problems. Not any old terrestrial tourist can wear the Star Trek insignia on his shirt, so you must live up to the mighty tradition and make the Federation proud! Setting things right in the universe won't be easy.Cheat: Level PasswordsThese passwords may be entered on the main menu after selecting the ''Continue'' option.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Ultra Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1453</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563461-star-trek-25th-anniversary</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/star-trek-25th-anniversary-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-trek-25th-anniversary/3030-9737/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/qVWZGCC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/lY9Jr3d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/RKWDJGG.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9dqs9MS.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/QNpHyLF.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FXMjTWu.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NkMx37E.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vNtQgkS.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jGQ5WOs.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7PnVLUU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8kbQET0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gLqD0o5.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/korqpBK.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lt4DdsD.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/gqJVwBS.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/HpgoG84.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6nu0JUR.jpg</banner1>
</game>