<Game>
	<Name>Star Luster (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Star Luster is a space sim/shoot-em-up for the Arcade and Nintendo Famicom (and much later, the Sharp X68000) that uses the Star Raiders model of having everything viewed first-person from the cockpit, and having to manually select which region of space to visit next and travel there by hyperspace. The goal is to intercept the "E"s on the starmap, which stands for "Enemies". The player can also visit friendly space stations (represented as "B"s, for "Base") to refuel and repair damage. The player can also opt to use one of their limited torpedoes to target an enemy region remotely, though this tactic must be used sparingly.In combat, the player must roll, pitch and yaw their craft to center the enemies on their screen before shooting them down. The player's map changes to a radar in order to help them search for enemies easier. Enemy attacks can also damage the player's ship, but they have to break through a regenerating shield before any permanent damage can be done. It is possible for the player to lose access to their radar and other computer systems after receiving heavy damage, in which case they must return to a base for repairs before they can be used again.Unlike Namco's previous games for the system, which were ports of their Arcade hits, Star Luster was the first to be created specifically for the Famicom. The Arcade version was released slightly later the same year (1985) with a graphically-enhanced Sharp X68000 version released almost a decade later in 1994.Cheat: Color SelectionAfter the title screen stops scrolling and the name starts flashing, quickly press Select, B, A, Right, Left, Up, Select, B, Down &amp; Right before it stops flashing. If done right, you'll go to a Color selection screen for your ship and text.Cheat: Hidden Ship RepairThere is a way to repair your ship without docking at a base. If you are very low on energy, and any of your systems are on "NG" status, hold A + B on the second player's controller, and use the microphone. If done correctly, a shuttle will appear and repair your ship as usual. This only works once per game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1985</releasedate>
	<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27285</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578261-star-luster</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/star-luster</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-luster/3030-41204/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/hqc2gHl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hqc2gHl.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/UaHyjzC.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TeYS69C.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/e8rg4Gc.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/E5UtPb4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/IkGRpTD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Uei2Seb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/taAepeN.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MyHGxwV.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5BDTCxM.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/reawY45.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/xg9QaK0.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Star Luster (スターラスター Sutā Rasutā?) is a first-person shooter and space combat simulator video game developed and published by Namco in 1985 only in Japan. It is an arcade-style, combat-dedicated, sci-fi flight simulator that was first released for the Family Computer. That same year, Nintendo adapted the title for play in the arcade as part of their Nintendo VS. System. The game's setting takes place in the UGSF universe, shared by other Namco games like Galaxian, StarBlade, Ace Combat 3, Bounty Hounds, and New Space Order. The game features free-roaming open space exploration, a cockpit view where the cockpit controls could be seen (and where the cockpit bobs up and down), bases where the player can be refueled, a map and radar displaying the locations of enemies and bases, a warp ability that allows the player to be warped to anywhere on the map, and a date system keeping track of the current date which can change when warping long distances. The game also introduced the concept of a regenerating shield mechanic.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d6ba9d8-b91d-4510-86b7-ae6481f4ad6d.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a7f99293-d2ba-41b9-8b84-a0aa9687476f.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>