<Game>
	<Name>Star Voyager (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Summary:Star Voyager is a space combat game viewed in the first person perspective. It was developed by ASCII Entertainment and published by Acclaim. The game was first released in Japan on December 23rd 1986 under the name Cosmo Genesis. It was then released in North America in September 1987 as Star Voyager.Gameplay:The goal of Star Voyager is to navigate the player's ship through space to intercept and destroy groups of enemy space ships before they reach the home star-base and destroy it.The player uses a sub-space warp system to travel between space-stations, planets and enemy units on the map. Using this warp system drains the ship fuel level therefore it is necessary for the player to dock at various space stations to refuel before the level reaches zero. If the fuel level reaches zero, the ship will explode thereby ending the game.Various upgrades for the ship can be obtained by travelling to planets and landing on them. Upgrades are distributed randomly across the planets so it is not guaranteed that an upgrade will be found when landing on a planet.The game is over when the player's ship energy level reaches zero or if the ship is destroyed by an enemy. The player wins the game by destroying all enemy groups shown on the star map and returning to base.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2113</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587650-star-voyager</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/star-voyager_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-voyager/3030-867/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/6Ioz76Q.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/oo9hqPL.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ZZOHFsM.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Wam0Frj.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/SCno3TH.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fwxEqvk.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/2hg8RWH.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/QbGM4vB.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NYoUAiD.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CloU5nt.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bxOiKrS.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/La1JCdb.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JNCi67X.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/aqkQT36.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/B4A3o0m.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Star Voyager's gameplay requires the player to venture through various sectors of the galaxy in search of different alien fleets so they can be defeated. Fuel stations are placed around sporadically and help if fuel is running low. There are several different planets that are either empty or have people that can upgrade the player's equipment to fight off the enemy fleets. These upgrades include the super laser, improved shields, and engines that enhance the ship's warping ability. Warping is a vital part of the gameplay. If players do not warp to different sectors wisely, they might end up lost, run into dangerous sectors such as the black hole or the asteroid field, or run out of fuel. The game ends if enemy ships destroy the CosmoStation Noah. Released in Japan as 'Cosmo Genesis'.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a898296-bd9d-47ea-9b7f-008407e247c4.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/573e19c3-c593-4b13-b00f-f11cff9c9a0a.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82f6fcb9-a377-43cf-86cc-1d8068bad478.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>