<Game>
	<Name>Stick Hunter - Exciting Ice Hockey (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Stick Hunter is an Ice Hockey Sim game, developed and published by K Amusement Leasing, which was released in Japan in 1987.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/nes/home/578528.html</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>K Amusement Leasing</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27283</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578528-stick-hunter-exciting-ice-hockey</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/stick-hunter-exciting-ice-hockey</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZuvZziy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ZuvZziy.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/pcMSSDX.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JSAXvAG.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qFJr4uR.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/rSk03ac.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/P1ZLVVi.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Ue7turk.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/nYL4lsB.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BkWmOoc.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6g6nLjk.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Stick Hunter: Exciting Ice Hockey is a game for the Famicom released only in Japan in 1987. It was never released in North America. Stick Hunter was the first actual ice hockey game created for a Nintendo gaming system. The game was designed so that 1 player could play against the computer, or 2 players could play simultaneously against each other. The length of the periods and difficulty level could both be adjusted. Playing as a character who has possession of the puck, the character could not only skate faster, but could only shoot the puck forward. So if the player wanted to pass to a teammate, the character on screen would have to be facing the person to which he's passing. The same applied to shooting at the net and attempting to score a goal. The character would have to be facing the opposing net. A player without the puck could only skate faster. If the goalie had control of the puck, he could only pass to a teammate. As in the real-world sport of hockey, the object is to score more goals than the opposing team.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b14b84d3-b4a5-4153-af87-9bbf14e67bb7.png</boxart4>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>K Amusement Leasing</Publisher>
</game>