<Game>
	<Name>Summer Carnival '92 - Recca (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Recca 92 is a classic scrolling shooter set in space played from the overhead perspective. The player's ship, Recca, must navigate numerous enemy waves per stage culminating in a large boss encounter. To aid the player Recca may collect power-ups and option units that appear after defeating on screen enemies. Finally, Recca can store plasma energy by not firing its weapons. Plasma energy will build up over time indicated by a meter on the bottom of the screen. This forms a barrier in front of Recca which can absorb enemy bullets, however enemies can still collide with the player and destroy them. This energy can be launched creating a large explosion that can destroy enemy units and projectiles.Power-upsThere are five power-ups that can be equipped by Recca altering the mechanics of its shot. By picking up multiple of the same power-up in a row their power and effects will increase.Balkan - A spread shot upgrade that makes bullets fire in a wider arc.Laser - A penetrative shot upgrade that allows bullets to continue through enemies.Beam - An almost straight power upgrade to Recca's shots. Bullets travel straight forward, similar to default shots, but do more damage.5-Way - Lowers firepower but shoots bullets in five directions around Recca.Homing - Bullets will now track enemies upon being shot.Option UnitsThere are five option unites that can be equipped by Recca giving the player various types of shields that will absorb enemy bullets and provide additional firepower. By picking up multiple of the same options in a row their number will increase.Option B - Flies behind Recca and will fire backwards.Option C - Moves and faces in the opposite direction Recca is traveling.Option R - Rotates around Recca automatically.Option S - Moves and faces in the same direction Recca is traveling.Option F - Stays beside Recca's side and fires forwards.Cheat: Change Limit and Infinite LivesChange Limit: After a reset, before the title screen, some swirling text appears. Hold Select while this text fades, and a dialog saying "CHANGE LIMIT" will appear. Press Start to exit.Cheat: Sound Test + Odd ImageTo access the Sound Test menu in Recca, hold Select and press a confiramtion button at the title screen (after the Naxatsoft logo). If you get to a small menu that says ''Change Limit'', just press B and you'll go to the title screen where you'll be able to use the code.Cheat: Second part of the game.When you cleared the game, and are confronted with the "to be continued" message, don't shutdown your console! Reset it, and you'll start the amazing second part of the game, featuring new levels even harder than the first ones.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/7/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Naxat Soft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.9</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>23762</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578141-summer-carnival-92-recca</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/summer-carnival-92-recca</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/summer-carnival-92-recca/3030-735/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uHVZDXf.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WOOEKGs.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xM0nj9B.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xapLW35.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OVzcYvz.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9CAM86L.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/82Bv7zf.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1yxUCnD.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/TaCrSXg.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ywkBWig.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ceVBLqh.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/oFUstHK.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Conceived as an entry for a game development competition, this game would later be published by Naxat Soft in 1992.  This frenetic shoot-'em-up taxes the Famicom system and the player's reflexes with huge quantities of enemies while maintaining smooth, fast gameplay!  In addition to a single player campaign, there are also score attack and time attack modes available.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>nfY79-3AdGY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76b610bf-7d51-4fc0-b63c-8ddd38eb9749.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/940d34f6-2128-4850-b95e-f6b67738e592.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f57c7062-b566-4454-ab33-a987552e77a5.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Gameloft</Publisher>
</game>