<Game>
	<Name>Sunday Funday - The Ride (USA) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sunday Funday is a Christian based video game by  Wisdom Tree released for the Nintendo Entertainment System. It was the last video game to be released for the US NES by any company. Sunday Funday was not officially licensed by Nintendo due to the religious overtones.The player controls a skateboarder who is late for Sunday School. He must defeat the obstacles that lie in his path to make his way to Sunday School.Sunday Funday comes with two other games: an arcade style game called Fish Fall, and a NES karaoke version of the song "The Ride" by a Christian pop band  4Him.Comparison To Menace BeachSunday Funday is nearly identical to game called Menace Beach.  Menace Beach was also released by Color Dreams, but when Color Dreams decided to make Christian games instead of action games, they began releasing their older games with a few graphically changes. In the case of Sunday Funday they also made changes to the story.ChangesObjectMenace BeachSunday FundayProtagonistBoy riding a skateboard Boy riding a skateboard while carrying a Bible Overworld Enemy 1Ninja Person in a white shirt Overworld Enemy 2 Sumo wrestler Overweight woman Overworld Enemy 3 Clown on a balloon throwing water balloons Clown on a balloon throwing water balloons Overworld Enemy 4 Mole in a manhole throwing bananas Mole in a manhole throwing bananas Overworld Weapon Bottle Newspaper Underworld Enemy 1 Elvis impersonator Plumber Underworld Enemy 2 Sumo wrestler Overweight man in a suit and bright green pants Underworld Enemy 3 Bat Butterfly Bay Enemy 1 Surfer man Surfer man Bay Enemy 2 Sumo wrestler Overweight man with a moustache wearing a tank top Bay Enemy 3 Person in a manhole throwing kisses Elder woman in a manhole throwing kisses Bay Enemy 4 Seagull Seagull Bay Weapon Bottle Newspaper Cave Enemy 1  Bear Enemy Killed The number "100" Dove In between levels Bunny, the protagonist's girlfriend, with her clothes gradually rotting away. The protagonist imagines what his Sunday school teacher would say. Cheat: Level SkipBegin a new game, then press Up on Controller 2 and Up+A+B on Controller 1 simultaneously. During gameplay, you can then press B+Select on Controller 1 to skip levels.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Wisdom Tree, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>0.6</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2119</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587660-sunday-funday-the-ride</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/sunday-funday-the-ride</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sunday-funday-the-ride/3030-22828/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/NxOWWbT.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9DTvvFU.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/3bh0PDn.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uU8TfJ7.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/eS98Jnp.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/GY0wLIh.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/aHK4Z0h.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/XuREKFW.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/V3VIi39.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/n2SZ1hx.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PJj5dbX.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/g6qzdKd.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sunday Funday is an adaptation of the game Menace Beach, and contains a changed storyline and some graphical changes. The storyline now deals with a boy trying to make his way to Sunday school. Gameplay consists of riding a skateboard through various obstacles and defeating enemies who try to hinder the player's progress.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f2bd2faf-e76b-4b6c-8aab-ba97a8ead931.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f479ce1-314a-458d-8444-648f2fc964d1.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Wisdom Tree</Publisher>
</game>