<Game>
	<Name>Super Dodge Ball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Dodge Ball was released for the arcade and later ported to the NES. It was originally released in Japan as Nekketsu K&#333;k&#333; Dodgeball Bu, part of the Kunio-Kun series.NES PortThe NES port of Super Dodge Ball consisted of 3 modes; Super Dodge Ball mode, Vs. Mode, and Bean Ball Mode. In Super Dodge Ball Mode, One player takes on 7 countries and their respective Dodge Ball teams on their way to Dodge Ball supremacy. Each team has their own strengths and weaknesses, as well as their own home court. The countries included in the single player, and vs. mode, are: England, Iceland, Africa, Japan, China, India, Russia, and the USA.Additionally, if the player can make it through all of the teams, they will play "Team Shadow." Team Shadow was an evil version of team USA with similar teammates, power throws, and home court advantage.Vs. Mode was simple 2 player Super Dodge Ball Mode.In Bean Ball mode, players were taken back to their days on the playground. This was less structured, and allowed players to run around all over the place. Play continued until there was only one player left standing.Currently, the only sequels that exist have yet to be released outside of Japan.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>CSG Imagesoft Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>nXp92WEPzas</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1457</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587662-super-dodge-ball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-dodge-ball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-dodge-ball/3030-3552/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Um6XtNC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iLnfe7R.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Bt7Pucw.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Lk1hFgr.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Exzq74Y.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/U1EQ9Oi.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/b4fTb5y.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hAkp1Ik.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zifwRZO.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zWlicOr.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Xg7Wb6d.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3qyZoZo.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/73KdZrX.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HQ15vLj.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UmqDrUx.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ez74caa.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This ain't elementary school and it sure as heck ain't gym class.  This is Super Dodge Ball.  Control your team of six players to pummel the opposing team into submission using only the ball and your team's unique skills.  Each player has his own special attacks and each team has their own unique attributes.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33aaa5f8-d8bb-4cf8-b7fd-b39a5759b53f.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/376bb145-f049-40b8-acf7-d10039e1c583.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aeed04e1-4c7d-406e-9462-0d8790b3ae92.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>CSG Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>