<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Bros. + Tetris + Nintendo World Cup (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Combo cart containing three Nintendo classics on one single cartridge. Super Mario Bros. stars "Jump Man" himself, Mario, along with his brother Luigi, and takes players through more than 30 colorful levels of varied theme and design, all of them packed with cute, stylized enemies like the goombas and a wide array of platforms and obstacles. Tetris is a faithful console adaptation of Pajitnov's insanely addictive puzzle game, and World Cup is a Technos developed soccer game.Cheat: Codes (Tetris)Hold A and press Start at the Gameover screen to continue from the first level of that world. Cheat: Passwords for all teams (Nintendo World Cup)These passwords work for all teams, the only difference is the last two letters. So, use the letter combination from the key below, and insert it into the last two places of the password you want to use.Cheat: More Choice Pieces (Tetris)Every time you move a piece over, the game counts it. The more you move it, the game thinks you have more trouble with that certain piece, and will dish out more of them. You can exploit this every time you get a Tetris (Long "I" shape) piece, just move it from side to side as it falls. You will get it more often every time that you do so.Cheat: When turning on the console, keep pressing Select. This resets an invisible time counter  to 0. Each time you press the A button, that counter goes up by 1, adding one minute of time for each half of the match (for example, press the A button 2 times to make each half of the match last 2 minutes instead of the usual 4).Cheat: The following passwords get you to a desired team in World Cup mode.Cheat: Play a "VS Match" and select the field you want to play the tournament on (Bumpy, Soil, Concrete, Sand, or Ice). At the end of the match, simply start playing "Tournament Mode", and the game will be set on the field you selected in "VS Mode".If you don't want to play the "VS Match" against someone, it's recommended to set the the timer to 1:00 minute (in codes section) and let the game play itself.Cheat: To access this warp, you must be Super or Fiery Mario. Go to the pipe at the end of the level and jump on top of it. Jump up and break the block over top of the part of the pipe farthest left. Then, position Mario on the edge of the pipe, with one foot hanging off the edge. Duck, then jump backwards as far right as possible.  If done just right, Mario will slide through the pipe and the bricks. Walk over to the warp zone area and enter the middle pipe. This pipe will take you to world 5, level 1. The same area can be acessed from a pipe in the same place in 4-2. However, this is meant to be a warp zone to 5-1, whereas the 1-2 warp to 5-1 is a glitch. After completing the jump trick in level 1-2, you can also go down either of the other two pipes, both of which will take you to Minus World -1. Cheat: After beating the game, if you do not turn off the console, you will return to the title screen. There, you can press the B Button to start as desired in World 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, or 8.Cheat: If you just walk along the sea floor, Bloopers will never be able to kill you because they are forced back up just before they hit the floor(or you).Cheat: Every time you move a piece over, the game counts it. The more you move it, the game thinks you have more trouble with that certain piece, and will dish out more of them. You can exploit this every time you get a Tetris (Long "I" shape) piece, just move it from side to side as it falls. You will get it more often every time that you do so.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>10.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>SL6tLpMFi7U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19890</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/930338-super-mario-bros-tetris-nintendo-world-cup</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-mario-bros-tetris-nintendo-world-cup</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-bros-tetris-nintendo-world-cup/3030-32012/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/t2CICpe.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TO9bhoA.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fL1wKRb.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5nFhzI8.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/dnuxgkk.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DzqtV2N.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xDj3Wzo.jpg</snapshot4>
</game>