<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Bros. + Duck Hunt (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Super Mario Bros. / Duck Hunt is the game cartridge that came with the Nintendo Entertainment System consumer package that included a control deck, 2 controllers, and a light zapper. The included games were:- Super Mario Bros.: The classic tale of an Italian plumber smashing bricks and stepping on mushrooms and turtles in order to rescue the princess.- Duck Hunt: The basic light zapper game for the NES. Two game modes allowed the player to either shoot ducks with the help of the trusty hound or to fire at clay pigeons.http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-mario-bros-duck-huntCheat: Continue from last world entered.When you get Game Over, wait until the 1/2 player screen comes up, Hold A then press start. You will begin the first level of the world that you died in. For example if you got game over in 6-3 you will restart in 6-1.Cheat: Have Second Player Control TargetsBy simply plugging an extra controller into slot two on the NES, player two can control the ducks and player one can try and shoot them with the blaster light gun. This works on one duck and two ducks but not on the discuss mode.Cheat: Start a target shooting game and have an extra controller plugged in to port 1 and the light gun in port 2. Press start on the controller in port 1 to pause the game when you unpause the game the targets will remain frozen for a few seconds giving you a clean shot.Cheat: When playing on Mode A (the one with only one duck), controller one can control the ducks to make a sort of multiplayer game.Cheat: To access this warp, you must be Super or Fiery Mario. Go to the pipe at the end of the level and jump on top of it. Jump up and break the block over top of the part of the pipe farthest left. Then, position Mario on the edge of the pipe, with one foot hanging off the edge. Duck, then jump backwards as far right as possible.  If done just right, Mario will slide through the pipe and the bricks. Walk over to the warp zone area and enter the middle pipe. This pipe will take you to world 5, level 1. The same area can be acessed from a pipe in the same place in 4-2. However, this is meant to be a warp zone to 5-1, whereas the 1-2 warp to 5-1 is a glitch. After completing the jump trick in level 1-2, you can also go down either of the other two pipes, both of which will take you to Minus World -1. Cheat: After beating the game, if you do not turn off the console, you will return to the title screen. There, you can press the B Button to start as desired in World 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, or 8.Cheat: If you just walk along the sea floor, Bloopers will never be able to kill you because they are forced back up just before they hit the floor(or you).</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-IhqCLL4xIo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6410</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563465-super-mario-bros-duck-hunt</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-mario-bros-duck-hunt</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-bros-duck-hunt/3030-12460/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vhFyS70.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/sML0qac.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/yVRjfBZ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/gDEa35A.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/wuK89Ly.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/pWqNOQL.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/VcoXKYX.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/fBVQRtZ.jpg</boxart8>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/mSLcQbU.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6ekOlky.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4U80b3o.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BtmXHuS.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lgE8d34.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/oxxqQDs.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/E8B4L3P.png</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/6rftt1h.jpg</banner2>
	<banner3>http://i.imgur.com/tJPVAfy.jpg</banner3>
</game>