<Game>
	<Name>Super Spy Hunter (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Spy Hunter, or Battle Formula, is a vertical-scrolling vehicular combat game that plays similarly to Spy Hunter. The player is driving a morphing combat vehicle capable of numerous weapon loadouts, acquired by destroying trucks carrying power-ups. These power-ups increase the firepower of the player's car, as well as extending their life bar and other bonuses.The game has an unusual cheat built in: If the player configures the cursor on the continue menu (found after losing all their lives), they can play a fast-paced game of Pong against a CPU opponent. If they win, they resume the game with 20 lives instead of the usual five. If they lose, they resume with zero extra lives.For its US release, SunSoft acquired the Spy Hunter license and promoted the game as a Spy Hunter sequel, but the game wasn't initially affiliated with Spy Hunter in any way. The game is a collector's item in Japan, fetching high prices.Cheat: CodesNormally, you have infinite continues in this game. If - for whatever reason - you wish to limit them, first start up the game. Before reaching the title screen, hold Start, then start a new game - you will be limited to 80 continues.Cheat: 20 LivesBeat the hidden Pong Mini Game and you'll start the game with 20 lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sun Corporation of America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>qqZKLNaYIiw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>382</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563466-super-spy-hunter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-spy-hunter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-spy-hunter/3030-8/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dmG5u66.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GQqjDjx.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Vh28aI6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Fy9XcVP.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/F99AsYc.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hkTlVIi.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gK7xnix.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/uPPPXj3.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nzcOVYo.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8nWAWQZ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JVeuAv9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/61ZQc0r.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wqb9iay.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The Super Spy Hunter has a super spy car. It's actually a well-armed car that can turn into a boat or a plane at opportune times. The action is fast vertical scrolling as the vehicle faces all manner of powerful vehicle threats from a well-funded terrorist enemy -- cars, trucks, helicopters, etc. Luckily, there are many powerups to collect along the way, both defensive and offensive.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11966e60-d132-4d2b-b514-dffa35c258bf.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2fcc719-1ac0-4aca-9189-e059b5c6cbd8.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a3197676-ee6a-4162-b778-a553bd3faa88.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c67df5d-495f-4e9f-ab6c-3d2f6edcc526.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/099e1e6b-dc57-46b8-9c6c-d6b807bf17d9.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e6c3d6c-f66d-45e1-b13a-451730c8d5b8.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66cb6843-07e9-4140-bfba-bf00d22ed0ce.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99caed7c-d43b-4d3c-b594-01c8c6605b10.jpg</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>