<Game>
	<Name>Super Team Games (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Family Trainer: Daiundoukai (lit: "Great Sports Meet"), known in the US as Super Team Games, is the seventh entry in Bandai's ten-game series that require the use of the Family Trainer/Power Pad accessory to play.The sports that the game emulate resemble those played at a Summer camp or school's sports day, with less serious types of events like a three-legged race and obstacle courses. The game can be played with either one or two players, who compete with either the CPU or each other, and a six-player mode in which two teams of three compete by sharing the Power Pad.Gameplay:The game is split into several different courses, with the idea being that the player who scores the most points overall across each event wins the game.CoursesObstacle Course A includes Log Hop, Water Cross and Wall Jump, as well as a straightforward sprint race.Obstacle Course B includes Belly Bump Ball, Crab Walk, Bubble Run, and also the sprint race.Super Obstacle Course is a combination of Obstacle Course A and B.Skateboard Race is a single event where the player must avoid obstacles on a skateboard.The six-player mode has three unique events of its own: A tug of war, a six-legged race and a relay race that uses the events of the single/two player mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2124</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587672-super-team-games</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-team-games</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-team-games/3030-10067/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MPrE0pB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MPrE0pB.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/hPysVq0.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/y9HXxt3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0b5cN4P.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uOBdYRf.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZcN3JQC.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DaCEXlW.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/DyRzdYS.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ve3Q1sY.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/0kDD3Rx.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HULvj6K.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PwZJdgv.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Super Team Games is a side scrolling game where two players compete in races on an obstacle course. The game utilizes the Nintendo Power Pad; to control your on screen character you will need to run in place on the Power Pad to make your character run, and actually jump to make him jump. In the basic game you need to run and jump your way to the finish line as fast as possible. Some additional game variations are available, such as the belly bump ball (you need to roll a giant ball through the obstacle course by running into it), the crab walk (make it to the finish line walking like a crab!), the water cross (water is found on the track; if you mistime your jump and land in the water you need to swim to get out costing you valuable time), the bubble run (racing through the course inside a giant bubble), or the skateboard race. Several cooperative games are included as well, including a tug of war, relay race, and six legged race.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>6xZIZ8wHr4k</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d2b44f01-d08b-4d8c-ad88-f9637202787d.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c798bbee-095d-49d3-ba89-1bc6da177f32.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>