<Game>
	<Name>Super Pitfall (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Join Pitfall Harry as he searches a vast subterranean cave dwelling high in the Andes. Harry's mission is simple - recover the Raj diamond. Interested in helping out? Perhaps a few details, before you volunteer. You'll have to be in great shape. The full extent of these caves is unknown, and you must be prepared to explore every square foot to succeed. So, a little dirt, a few cuts and bruises and total physical exhaustion doesn't scare you? OK, how about poisonous frogs, bats, snakes, scorpions, tarantulas, cavemen, lavapits and deadly condors? Oh, did we forget to mention Harry's niece, Rhonda, and his faithful companion, Quickclaw the Lion? They're both trapped below and must be saved before you leave the caves. Just a minor complication. Still with us? Good. Because it gets better and better - over 270 screens loaded with danger and adventure. New enemies and challenges at every turn. Sound like your cup of tea? Then step forward and join Pitfall Harry in the greatest adventure of his career!Cheat: Perfect EndingTo get the perfect ending,Cheat: Extra BulletsStart the game as usual and go forward to the first ladder. If you jump near it, a gun will appear that will give you 20 extra bullets.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>cFPwX_gFhy0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2122</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587667-super-pitfall</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-pitfall</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-pitfall/3030-13716/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TYgCPe3.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/urJNTR1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/x77ojZK.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/0E03joM.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Hng0NE9.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7Q7THki.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KAEGOgZ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Ebg16oy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/w1vrUsT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3MIeWBt.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kalYwyJ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/i1glUfO.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/zRcIH6y.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ik8Abqj.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1LbwudD.png</banner1>
</game>