<Game>
	<Name>Super Turrican (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Like other entries in the series, Super Turrican for the NES is a side-scrolling platformer in which players explore large levels filled with enemies items and secret areas. Three different, upgradable weapons are available: multiple (spreadshot), laser and rebound. Holding down the fire button activates a rotatable laser that is useful for discovering hidden power-up capsules.Despite carrying the same name as one of its big brothers, Super Turrican for the NES is based on Turrican and Turrican II. While some levels are very similar to those found in Turrican I and II (with only slight changes of layout and enemy types), others are entirely new. Apart from different/new level design, there are other notable changes: Holding down the fire button let's Turrican run, there is no time limit to levels anymore, energy wheel usage is limitless and the shield isn't time based anymore, but can sustain a certain number of hits.Cheat: InvincibilityAt the title screen enter the "Highscore" menu, once the scores show up, press Select, Left, Up, Right, Down, Left, Up, Right, Down &amp; Select. If done right, a sound will be heard.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Imagineer Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>etLUjXpgJp0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2125</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/567304-super-turrican</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-turrican_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-turrican/3030-44802/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/UjHGLUx.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/YGH0Nu0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/HEjaM7j.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zyIg2b5.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/peGJf88.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/u8NTkdu.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CujaY8j.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FWHQmrb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/chXJWMJ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/YAF5HBu.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dyNSFdE.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The lost colony of Alterra is a completely man-made lifeworld abandoned long ago in a nearby galaxy. Alterra is actually five colonies in one. Each self-contained habitat has been separately bio-engineered by a powerful ecosystem generation network known as a Multiple Organism Unit Link. MORGUL, for short. Early colonists used MORGUL to render Alterra inhabitable. But a cataclysmic quake severed all system interface functions, and MORGUL murderously rebelled. The few colonists lucky enough to escape told a grim tale of a higher intelligence gone berserk. For generations, mankind sought a return to Alterra. Finally, genetic science created a saviour: Turrican, a mutant warrior, bio-engineered for the task of planetary reclamation. In the meantime, MORGUL has diligently twisted Alterran life forms to his brutal, destructive purposes. Thus, Turrican's challenges consist in eliminating hostile organisms from Alterra's five multi-level worlds and, finally, destroying the three faces of MORGUL.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d29afe21-7913-4337-9d85-c5e17e331b13.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/264678f6-9fb8-4bd0-b563-1122e70b0600.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>