<Game>
	<Name>Super Spike V'Ball + Nintendo World Cup (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Super Spike V'Ball / Nintendo World Cup was a pack-in game included with the Nintendo Entertainment System Sports Set. The package included a standard NES console, four game controllers, and the Four Score Multiplayer Adapter. The cart included two games developed by Technos:- Super Spike V'Ball, a two-on-two beach volleyball game where you played on a tournament, ending with the world championship. The game supported up to four players on one match at a time;- Nintendo World Cup, a soccer game where you (and a friend) chose to represent a team and played several matches until you won the World Cup. The game featured little to no rules, which means that you could hit your opponents as much as you want, without fear of the Ref getting in the way.Both games were compatible with the included Four Score NES multiplayer adapter.http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-spike-vball-nintendo-world-cupCheat: When turning on the console, keep pressing Select. This resets an invisible time counter  to 0. Each time you press the A button, that counter goes up by 1, adding one minute of time for each half of the match (for example, press the A button 2 times to make each half of the match last 2 minutes instead of the usual 4).Cheat: The following passwords get you to a desired team in World Cup mode.Cheat: Play a "VS Match" and select the field you want to play the tournament on (Bumpy, Soil, Concrete, Sand, or Ice). At the end of the match, simply start playing "Tournament Mode", and the game will be set on the field you selected in "VS Mode".If you don't want to play the "VS Match" against someone, it's recommended to set the the timer to 1:00 minute (in codes section) and let the game play itself.Cheat: At the "CONFIGURATION" menu, point the menu cursor to the "MUSIC" option, then hold A + B on controller 2 and press Select or Down on controller 1. Using a four-score that lets you use four controllers, you will be able to control the ball.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 VS</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>314</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587669-super-spike-vball-nintendo-world-cup</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-spike-vball-nintendo-world-cup</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-spike-vballnintendo-world-cup/3030-35864/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uoQd58E.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0C0Rc8G.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/iNwW1qd.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JeSVX42.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/q7cXnH3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Orwz8pD.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2fZ3IZp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IAVz0fe.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mVR5g3V.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/WmDUlXi.png</snapshot7>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/UTtN4tN.jpg</fanart1>
</game>