<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Bros. + Duck Hunt + World Class Track Meet (USA) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>If you bought a Nintendo Entertainment System Power Set, which came with two controllers, a Zapper light gun and a Power Pad, then you got this three-games-in-one cartridge, including:- Super Mario Bros.: the Princess has been kidnapped by the evil Bowser, and it is up to Mario and brother Luigi to save the day.- Duck Hunt: in Duck Hunt you need to use the Nintendo's light zapper to shoot ducks which your trusty dog scares out of the swamp.- World Class Track Meet: this is a track and field game for up to six players requiring the Power Pad.http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-mario-bros-duck-hunt-world-class-track-meetCheat: Continue from start of current world.Hold A and press Start at the Gameover screen to continue from the first level of that world. Cheat: Start a target shooting game and have an extra controller plugged in to port 1 and the light gun in port 2. Press start on the controller in port 1 to pause the game when you unpause the game the targets will remain frozen for a few seconds giving you a clean shot.Cheat: When playing on Mode A (the one with only one duck), controller one can control the ducks to make a sort of multiplayer game.Cheat: To access this warp, you must be Super or Fiery Mario. Go to the pipe at the end of the level and jump on top of it. Jump up and break the block over top of the part of the pipe farthest left. Then, position Mario on the edge of the pipe, with one foot hanging off the edge. Duck, then jump backwards as far right as possible.  If done just right, Mario will slide through the pipe and the bricks. Walk over to the warp zone area and enter the middle pipe. This pipe will take you to world 5, level 1. The same area can be acessed from a pipe in the same place in 4-2. However, this is meant to be a warp zone to 5-1, whereas the 1-2 warp to 5-1 is a glitch. After completing the jump trick in level 1-2, you can also go down either of the other two pipes, both of which will take you to Minus World -1. Cheat: After beating the game, if you do not turn off the console, you will return to the title screen. There, you can press the B Button to start as desired in World 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, or 8.Cheat: If you just walk along the sea floor, Bloopers will never be able to kill you because they are forced back up just before they hit the floor(or you).</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>sFMjC7zP5MM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>17616</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587665-super-mario-bros-duck-hunt-world-class-track-meet</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-mario-bros-duck-hunt-world-class-track-meet</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-bros-duck-hunt-world-class-track-meet/3030-19967/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kLB8vp9.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mCA5ljI.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/dbL3So9.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/FlKmlKd.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ifoFOLB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/M0G0LkC.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4GwsC4i.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/x6dcSOr.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ow2CO7Q.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/u0MUANc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/lgE8d34.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VDxcRan.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wtthLjK.jpg</banner1>
</game>