<Game>
	<Name>Super Xevious - Gump no Nazo (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Super Xevious is a 2D shoot 'm up by Namco and is part of the Xevious series. Xevious is known as one of the hardest and fastest shooters around and Super Xevious is even harder and faster!The enemies of the first Xevious game are back! But this time they are not alone. No, the brought some nasty friends with them! It is your job, as a fighter pilot, to blast them away! Destroy everything in sight!Some ground structures that must be destroyed are hidden and are called Sol Citadels. To locate these hidden structures you must keep an eye on the target-sight that will flash when it goes over the structures.Super Xevious takes all the great elements of the original Xevious and has also some improvements. Some examples of improvements are, for instance, the shield option and the upgrade option. The shield protects you from immediately death if you got hit during an attack. The upgrade option gives you the possibility to upgrade your bombs, lasers and shields.http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-xeviousCheat: Secret Password MenuStart the game and before hitting any enemies, press Start to pause the game. While paused, press Up, Down, Left, Right, A and B. If done right, a password screen should appear.Cheat: 2nd LoopAfter the ending, when "Written and produced by" start to flash and before it disappears, press Start and you'll be taken to the 2nd loop of the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27305</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578313-super-xevious-gamp-no-nazo</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-xevious</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PhyCO3w.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/PhyCO3w.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/NO3sGpP.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/l6cqN2O.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KWusHPl.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Y9X1HVn.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/X43GDaW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/b59wkJS.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VpdutNx.jpg</snapshot6>
	<Notes>Super Xevious: GUMP no Nazo (スーパーゼビウス ガンプの謎?) is a video game released for the Family Computer and the Nintendo VS. System. The only way to progress through the game is to solve challenging riddles in each stage, each one more difficult than the last. Unless the player solves the riddle completely and meets certain criteria, the stage repeats over and over, thus making it harder to complete the game.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aca4980d-a17d-40c4-bdb7-20d4a120aa13.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/516e1aee-6f82-462b-8d46-35baa5142a16.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>