<Game>
	<Name>Super Sprint (USA) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Racing ActionSuper Sprint is a racing game with a top down perspective. The game has only 8 circuits, but cycles through them repeatedly, for a total of 85 races. Each cycle gets progressively more difficult by the addition of new obstacles, such as oil slicks and tornadoes. Wrenches could be obtained during races, which could then be used to upgrade the player's car in-between races. Upgrading the car allowed a certain degree of customization, since the car's traction, speed, and acceleration were upgrading independently.In arcades, the game could be played by up to three human players. The arcade version was controlled with a steering wheel and foot pedal.Cheat: Infinite ContinuesPower the console off, press and hold A + B on controller 1, then power it on again to have unlimited continues.Cheat: Add Extra LapsWhen your car is about to cross the line after completing a lap, repeatedly pause and unpause your game (if you have a controller with a Slow-Mo function, enable it here) as it goes over the line.  If your timing is right, your lap counter will increase every time you unpause your game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Tengen Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2123</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587670-super-sprint</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-sprint</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-sprint/3030-2776/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PB0Jwoh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/auGgD5n.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/TstqZtj.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/JxiY0lV.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/rvX0nud.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/yjHTLcU.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/t227J2h.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/s6WYE4s.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MpEeSjt.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7W2WahP.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bGVNH5F.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IjGGdnI.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/uzmGEFg.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WKIOeWa.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/coeTtZ9.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/aRVsJ9a.png</clearlogo1>
</game>