<Game>
	<Name>Super Arabian (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The player controls the Arabian who must jump his way through a variety of environments in order to save the princess that has been captured by a band of crows. The only way he can safely make it though each level is to collect the letters hidden in different vases. Once he does that he may proceed to the next level.Gameplay:This is pretty much a exact copy of the game Donkey Kong with a different theme. This means the Arabian can only jump over enemies rather than attack them directly and has to evade a lot in order to collect the vases scattered around each level. Each environment has a different type of object that he can climb: For instance, in the first level he has to scale the poles of the ship in order to collect everything. On level 3 he will also have to deal with flying carpets that he must scale to reach all of the letters. Once he gets past the 4 levels they will start to repeat until the player has run out of lives.EnemiesSmall Crows: They walk around the level going up and down to stop the Arabian's progress. They will periodically fly directly at him from wherever they are in the level.Pink Monsters: Most of the time they just go back and forth. But sometimes they will jump at the Arabian instead of letting him jump over them.Giant Crow: He stays the the top of the screen. Going back and forth. For whatever reason he doesn't attack the Arabian unless he runs into him.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/7/1985</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>27288</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578241-super-arabian</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/super-arabian</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-arabian/3030-7028/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AVqSS2Z.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/PI170St.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1xWG1YJ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zFaqONg.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AAWkzlK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FgsjxmI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/9ksR0Og.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jsZDfFd.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5JRrTUk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/fZP3mm7.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/keS3m01.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>An action platformer styled as an Arabian Nights-flavored "storybook", which follows the trials of a brave Arabian prince as he attempts to infiltrate the palace and save a princess locked in the tower. To reach said damsel in distress, the prince must complete four "pages" (or levels) of the book: an ocean-bound ship, a maze of caves, the castle walls, and the tower, each infested with an assortment of mythical enemies, like flying Rocs and evil Genies. Besides walking, jumping and climbing, the prince can cling onto vines, duck and crawl through tight passages, and glide along on flying carpets. Last but not least is the mighty kick, which sends the baddies sprawling. To complete a level, all the lettered jugs must be collected. A bonus is awarded if they're picked up in the right order to spell out the indicated word (different word in each level). Once a princess is rescued, the next section begins, more difficult than the last.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>-TA-RmIooOI</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/beab310d-425b-45ff-9bb5-8d48391912dd.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7500200a-b2eb-4cd5-bd27-dead8eb9bf11.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0627b532-459d-4710-be9b-1805599578ba.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eded6350-bed6-4862-842d-08b1d2a6a50c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3c5cbc50-5cf5-4755-bee3-0e6308773585.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb85d9f7-54f5-453f-8ecb-5db30d189692.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>