<Game>
	<Name>Swamp Thing (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Swamp Thing is an NES and Game Boy game released in late 1992 in Europe and the US, based on the ecological DC character created by Len Wein and Berni Wrightson. Specifically, it is based on the short-lived animated TV show that was airing during this period. Villain Dr. Arcane successfully detonates a bomb in the lab of young scientist Alec Holland. Rather than destroying his body the explosion, combined with the bio-restorative formula he was working on, mingled with the properties of the swamp waters transform Holland into the Swamp Thing.In this 2D side scrolling action-platformer Swamp Thing confronts Arkane and his henchmen toward the goal of saving the planet.There was a separate Genesis version planned, with a different developer, but this was cancelled.Critical ReceptionWhen the NES version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly issued the following scores, 3,4,3,3 stating, "...This game doesn't belong on a Game Boy let alone the NES! The graphics are mediocre and the control is substandard...This game doesn't do the Swamp Thing justice".Cheat: Extra LivesDuring gameplay, you can enter codes to earn one of two extra lives. These codes can only be activated in certain levels under certain circumstances, and only once per playthrough.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1459</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587674-swamp-thing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/swamp-thing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/swamp-thing/3030-2823/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wUvbobg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iDLVrBE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HRXSUei.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vANduD6.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/kL67vrM.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Kd7gnGW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zpJGE9W.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/riFY8qC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZXJUy8M.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7reTIZj.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LmjAEG9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/d3h22r7.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/qWJN74v.jpg</banner1>
</game>