<Game>
	<Name>SWAT - Special Weapons and Tactics (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:SWAT: Special Weapons and Tactics is based on an obscure manga by cartoonist Oki Hajime that focuses on five police officers working in a SWAT team and plays like a tactical turn-based RPG such as Dragon Quest, though far more involved and slower paced. In combat each member of the four person team chooses a target and one of their weapons to attack them with and the game plays out the battle turn by turn. The terrorists the player encounters in the otherwise nondescript office building the game takes place in can be wounded and interrogated for more information, or simply killed.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/11/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, First-Person, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Shouei</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27307</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578474-swat-special-weapons-and-tactics</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/swat-special-weapons-and-tactics/3030-22838/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XpdGncc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ue64sMT.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4pp47pv.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qG4pu8S.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/x1J6l75.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zdSbtlL.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jhjh7bC.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/fcdyDdi.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7PIjNI0.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BQ9nqzS.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/G99pLjy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZCAJi7V.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>SWAT: Special Weapons and Tactics is a role-playing game developed by Shouei and published by Toei Animation. This game was only ever released in Japan for the Famicom and was never translated from the original Japanese language. The player takes control of a five member team of special anti-terrorist agents as they break into a building where a hostage situation is taking place. Their goal is to take out the villains and free the hostages. Battles with gunmen take place in a traditional RPG style turn-based battle. Players enter the commands for each surviving member of the team, including what weapon to attack with, and which target to attack. When not in battle, the player views the building in a traditional 3D dungeon perspective, moving through the hallways, choosing which rooms to investigate, which traps to disarm, and how to proceed to the end of the game within a given time limit.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4875ecb-55e9-4ccb-9cef-2bcc4bf1b080.jpg</boxart3>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Toei Animation</Publisher>
</game>