<Game>
	<Name>Taboo - The Sixth Sense (USA) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Taboo: The Sixth Sense is the first NES fortune-telling game to be created entirely for a US audience. Though the format was not new to Nintendo's platform, this would be the first chance for players outside of Japan to divine their future with 8-bit software.As with Tarot, much of the game's clairvoyancy is derived from tarot cards. The standard astrological horoscope also factors into the game's divination process to some extent.Notably, the game was one of the first (official) video games to be promoted specifically as an "adults-only" product intended for players aged 14 and up. It also carried the warning that it was meant for entertainment purposes only and none of its predictions are meant to be taken seriously.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1989</releasedate>
	<Developer>Tradewest, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>vOiaYTA82us</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1420</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563468-taboo-the-sixth-sense</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/taboo-the-sixth-sense</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/taboo-the-sixth-sense/3030-4271/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JxaHanz.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9XGLWCA.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/OJ9jH41.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nqnpLbp.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vikgq1M.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gtsfKrf.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/3nNyPFQ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fBNc34j.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2WT8sgt.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/tWUzdqL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Mz2Ia16.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8dIxLXQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/9Lq9q3h.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QGSWJgP.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Turn the Nintendo Entertainment System into a tarot card deck with Taboo: The Sixth Sense. Write down a questions via the controller, and after a shuffling of cards, the game will attempt to predict your future. Some fortunes may be positive, offering wealth, fame and power. Other fortunes may warn the player to take care and use caution in future events. After the final card is revealed, the player has an option to choose their lucky numbers. Obviously, Taboo: The Sixth Sense is meant for entertainment purposes only, and should be taken as such.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb1253ab-9142-42f9-8d58-5c04110aa4de.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5df268d3-646e-4de0-a072-59c3d11d3eab.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Tradewest</Publisher>
</game>