<Game>
	<Name>Tag Team Wrestling (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Tag Team Wrestling was originally developed by Technos and released to arcades in late 1983. It was followed by home versions for the PC in 1985 and a C64/Apple II version in 1987. The NES version maintains the same gameplay as the arcade original, but expands to fill a full TV screen, as opposed to the vertically oriented monitor used in arcades, though with downgraded graphics compared to the arcade original.The opposing tag team was referred to as either Strong &amp; Bad or Strong Bads, depending on the version. This name would later find a resurrection with the Chapman Brothers, creators of the web comedy series Homestar Runner and, more specifically, the character known as Strong Bad. In a twisted turn of freakish events, Strong Bad and the cast of Homestar Runner began appearing in video games in August of 2008 in an episodic adventure series from Telltale Games known as Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People.Cheat: Continue:Normally, there are two people per side in the game, one in and out of the ring. Whenever the one in the ring is being hugged or otherwise kept in the air, the trapped fighter's partner can come in and rescue them. However, the traditional techniques do not work if this is happening while the fighter is also pinned to the floor.Cheat: InvincibilityBecome the champion and it goes to ERP4. When the tournament starts, touch your ally and you'll become invincible.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/5/1986</releasedate>
	<Developer>Data East USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1421</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587677-tag-team-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tag-team-wrestling</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tag-team-wrestling/3030-6068/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QYhHy5w.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mreZEpg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/kw2JegO.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/s68u2yK.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/6S5FDNH.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LIVloVy.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eJ1Hh4s.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/76sDoup.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kl68SPV.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/aJeu4Nt.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Htx7VJz.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/H2CGLDt.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9qQKez8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZCAJi7V.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>You are challenged to match the awesome skill of your opponents...to gain the Title in World Super Championship of Tag Team Wrestling. Teamwork and stamina are the keys, as you and your partner battle your way through the Title Matches on your quest for the Belt. Attack your opponents with Body Slams, Drop Kicks, Backbreakers, Flying Head Butts, or even throwing them out of the ring! To win, it's a pin for a count of three. Nothing can match the super excitement as the crowd cheers over this mania on the mat. Prepare yourself for Tag Team Wrestling! Data East brings you arcade realism at home!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e8d421cd-908a-4929-be50-6432a375ee6f.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75e290a9-09cb-4a25-967b-31439f8c3b4e.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>