<Game>
	<Name>Takahashi Meijin no Bouken-jima IV (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Takahashi Meijin no Bouken Jima IV is an Action game, developed by Hudson Soft and published by Hudson,which was released in Japan in 1994.Cheat: PasswordsChoose the password option in the main menu and enter these codes. Higgins will start at his house with certain conditions. These conditions are: the number of hearts, which powers have been obtained, which dinosaurs have been freed, the current warp egg location, as well as which items he has in his inventory. For easier referencing, use the following list: (ex. Tools=3 means you have the first three tools on the list, Dino=0 means no dinosaurs have been saved, etc.)</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>22191</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/580603-takahashi-meijin-no-bouken-jima-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/takahashi-meijin-no-bkenjima-iv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/takahashi-meijin-no-bouken-jima-iv/3030-22925/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Ej8GHGd.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2TXbRBI.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6VqMEGj.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7YH1o3D.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4nrRIkr.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/a4r7JHr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VOvAiqR.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/oliHHWV.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WCeX3xC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/IBbytx6.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/gbCGtBx.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/y7FWPUI.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/XbgEtXB.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The evil Eggplant Wizard kidnaps Master Higgins helpful creatures and later his girlfriend Tina, Master Higgins starts an adventure to save them and stop the evil eggplant once and for all. Master Takahashi's Adventure Island IV is the fourth and final Adventure Island game released for the Famicom. It bears the distinction of being the final official Family Computer game in Japan and was never officially released for the international market. Unlike previous entries in the Adventure Island series, Boken Jima IV plays less like a linear platformer and more of an action/adventure platformer, similar to the later Wonder Boy games. Adventure Island IV also has a unique password system that the earlier games in the series didn't have. It also features an egg item that allows the player character to teleport to the special spot where the player puts it. There is a large variety of weapons to choose from which are unlocked by the player throughout the game. Many special items can be won in races and challenges, such as an angel/fairy item that allows the player character to re-spawn once, at the spot where they lost all hearts and even an compass that acts like a map showing the player with an arrow where to go. Whereas in the earlier Adventure Island games the player character had a food meter and when it runs out, the player lost a life, in Adventure Island IV, the player simply collects 8 food items to regain 1 heart as health.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a410b6cc-6344-4270-819d-f5a18bf5921d.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8af91dfc-a335-487f-8223-8980f26986f2.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/572b6510-855c-49c2-89ec-719127482f9b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3371d696-4e6e-46c7-91b0-3c03c59e1e5c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9bdfea9-ff7e-44e1-8f77-e12d6a93c02a.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2561f9c-c667-49dc-96cd-ff494befda43.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0794770-db0e-45d2-a7df-780b1b484d52.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e2b3a02-a8d4-482b-8f1e-cf0b67decf13.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8771ec5a-2552-45e9-85f1-a974f1706c53.png</snapshot16>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>