<Game>
	<Name>Takahashi Meijin no Bouken-jima (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>You just found out that Princess Leilani was kidnapped by the Evil Witch Doctor and taken to Adventure Island in the South Pacific.You land on Adventure Island without weapons or food. The island is thick with tropical forest, mountains and caves. Hidden on the island are your skateboard, axe, food and other helpful tools you must find by exploring the island.Better find the weapons and food quickly because you will need them to fight the Witch Doctor's spiders, snakes, bats and demons. The Evil Witch Doctor has set lots of traps for you before you can face him one on one. Are you up for the challenge?! Can you live through Adventure Island to save Princess Leilani?!Cheat: Infinite LivesNear the end of the first level, before a sign that says ''G'' on it, jump up at the edge of the cliff that's after the platforms.  If you find an egg (that contains a bee), you know you've done it.  At any Game Over screen from now on, hold UP, A, and SELECT.  Then press START.  You should repappear in the start of the level you died at with some extra lives.  This game has a few versions and the code only works for some versions, oddly enough.Cheat: See the next boss ahead of timeWhen you defeat the first boss, pause the game as the first boss leaves the screen. You'll be able to see the next boss.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>K70mt9UCam0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1022</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587067-adventure-island</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/takahashi-meijin-no-bkenjima-iv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/takahashi-meijin-no-bouken-jima-iv/3030-22925/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/HXomfBR.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2TXbRBI.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6VqMEGj.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7YH1o3D.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4nrRIkr.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/a4r7JHr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VOvAiqR.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/oliHHWV.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WCeX3xC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/IBbytx6.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/gbCGtBx.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/y7FWPUI.jpg</banner1>
</game>