<Game>
	<Name>Takeda Shingen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:In this war strategy sim, the player takes control of legendary daimyo and military genius Shingen Takeda during the Sengoku period of Japan in the 16th century. The goal is to unify the nation of Japan under Shingen's rule. It was developed by Another and published by Hot-B and would eventually be followed with a sequel, Takeda Shingen 2, in 1989. Though the sequel received a US version (renamed Shingen the Ruler), the original remained a Japan-only release.Cheat: Menu CheatsStart a game and enter the main menu. There will be 12 items here, internally numbered 0 through 11 in consecutive order. Whenever you press A to enter a menu and then B to exit the same, it can contribute to entering one of the below cheats. Enter and exit the menus numbered below - which use the game's 0-11 numbering system (0 at the top, 11 at the bottom) - to denote which menus to enter, and then immediately exit. After entering/exiting all the named menus, press Start to apply the code: there should be a sound and message that will also occur. Note that you may advance the game one day by the use of these cheats.Cheat: Play As Other CountriesUse these passwords to start the game using other countries. Enter the Japanese characters noted in the Row X, Column X.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/3/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Another</Developer>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578569-takeda-shingen</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/takeda-shingen/3030-39959/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/n6skMvL.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/if9h0tl.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IzR6BRq.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/42uehZ4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/TopxTwI.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/beMLMvs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PSRcpda.png</snapshot6>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e38bf9c-395b-4320-a01a-f58dee7aad7d.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9b4cf43-e79f-4517-a8de-7b131eefb804.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2b37d8b-8e33-4606-9bfd-a011e3728b73.png</snapshot8>
</game>