<Game>
	<Name>Takeshi no Sengoku Fuuunji (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Takeshi no Sengoku Fuuunko is a board game simulation starring Japanese comedian-turned-actor "Beat" Takeshi Kitano. Similar to the Game of Life, players move around a board earning money and occasionally encountering events such as a minigame - in which the player can increase their wealth should they succeed - or a penalty. The game has a Sengoku era theme running throughout, from its samurai characters to the tattooed gambler that rolls a dice for determining how many places a player can move around the board that turn. Beat Takeshi appears frequently while the game is being played dressed in traditional Sengoku era clothing. The game is presumably in reference to the TV show Takeshi's Castle, which also starred Beat Takeshi and had a Sengoku era theme.Cheat: CPU GameplayStart a new "SENGOKU GAME", and when asked "How many players would you like?", choose the number of players,. Before pressing the A button on Controller 1, press and hold Up + Left + B on Controller 2. You'll be asked for another question: "How many human players would you like?", so you can select from one to four human controlled players; the rest of the players will be CPU controlled.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579349-takeshi-no-sengoku-fuuunko</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/takeshi-no-sengoku-fuuunko/3030-40008/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wXrdS4G.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zXgr62O.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/M2dpoAf.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pMKKf4R.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5N56YOX.jpg</snapshot4>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ffe38a02-0043-4242-bf42-2269ccfae772.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b05d8b8d-9bb1-47c8-8e20-6bf66d48d398.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0faef1ce-1a64-4112-89dd-8ad4a06f6482.png</snapshot6>
</game>