<Game>
	<Name>Takeshi no Chousenjou (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Takeshi's Challenge (Takeshi no Ch&#333;senj&#333;) is a game for the Nintendo Famicom designed by Japanese comedian Takeshi Kitano, who is better known under his alias Beat Takeshi. Unlike conventional games from that era, however, Takeshi's Challenge is infamous for its masochistic design philosophies. Indeed, the creator himself took this to heart by mentioning on the very title screen that "This game is made by a man who hates video games." As such, the game's notoriety is derived from the absurd challenges it poses to players in order to progress to the next sequence, some of which require unique uses of the Famicom hardware itself. Despite its high difficulty level and perceived mediocrity, Takeshi's Challenge sold approximately 80,000 copies in Japan and can also be bought on the Japanese Wii Virtual Console.Originally released in 1986, the game appears to have anticipated the open world, sandbox gameplay of the Grand Theft Auto series. Not only could the player roam freely across the city, but could also randomly attack pedestrians (and, much like GTA, the police chase the player character if he murders a non-player character) or punch random objects (and that includes even punching a menu). The game was considered unusual for its time, not to mention controversial because of its violent content (which may have been a reason why it was never released in the Western world at the time).The game features ridiculous challenges, including a karaoke sequence that made use of the Famicom's built-in microphone (though a button-pressing minigame was also available as an alternative) and the option to let a treasure map sit out in the sunlight, a task that requires players to set the controller down and touch nothing for a full hour. Upon finishing the game and letting it sit at its lackluster ending screen for five minutes, Beat Takeshi appears to chide players for taking his deliberately bad game so seriously.Cheat: Revive yourselfIf your energy gets drained, press the A and B buttons at the same time 3 times in a row. If done right, your character should get back up with full energy.Cheat: Pacific Island PasswordAt the password screen, press Left 2 times, Down 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Then Up 1 time, Right 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Now repeat that same pair of Japanese characters 8 more times. Then for the final two characters, press Up 1 time, Left 6 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 6 times, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Hit "End" to start on the Pacific Island.Cheat: Clear the screen of enemiesWhile playing the game, you can clear the screen of enemies by just pressing Select to go to the menu screen and then exiting it. If done right, all the enemies will be gone. You can do this as many times as you wish.Cheat: Microphone substituteThere are three parts in the game where you must use the Famicom's 2nd controller built-in microphone, the Pachinko Parlor, the Karaoke Bar and to reveal the map. If you don't have the microphone available, you can alternatively press Down + A at the same time on the second controller to manually switch from microphone input to controller input. That way when you are required to use the microphone, just press the A button on the second controller and that will qualify as using the microphone.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/10/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>iBbvYDOIvbY</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578340-takeshi-no-chousenjou</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/takeshi-no-chsenj</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/takeshi-no-chousenjou/3030-25669/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jHMD73M.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jHMD73M.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/PTv6sOX.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/GbyqsL0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bbfc6F9.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KA1lMD2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/qJ0mKjx.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vGMN5ck.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bL3OK3M.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sBFTjMw.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qEfagS0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/h0hKwau.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/xzi9d0B.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Takeshi no Chosenjo (たけしの挑戦状, lit. Takeshi's Letter of Challenge) is a Japanese action-adventure video game for the Family Computer (known internationally as the Nintendo Entertainment System) developed by the Taito Corporation. Though other video games bearing the names of Japanese celebrities had been developed prior to Takeshi no Chosenjo, comedian-turned actor and film director Takeshi Kitano (Beat Takeshi) was the first celebrity to actively contribute to the video game's development. The packaging contains several warnings that the game should not be attempted with conventional gaming skills, and the player must complete numerous near-impossible tasks in order to finish the game.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c85c1324-4eff-48ea-907c-e55c12fc5681.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5155cb65-2e52-4e16-a8db-f96a18269727.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e74847d6-6550-4469-9dd6-0e3cf29c8e50.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ebe4ab6-2aeb-4150-bcc3-0041274dc175.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b496d333-9505-4139-b917-eac327e04715.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ccabf08-38a9-440a-bb6b-ad4ba84cf5d4.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20e90962-f7f7-4dea-a504-d1e6f8ba0b62.jpg</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Taito Corporation</Publisher>
</game>