<Game>
	<Name>TaleSpin (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In case you've never seen the show before, this game involves the adventures of Baloo and Kit, two bears delivering cargo for Rebecca, another bear. However, Shere Khan, the evil tiger tycoon, wants to put Rebecca out of business, so he hires pirates, led by Don Karnage, to do his dirty work. Baloo has to deliver his cargo across the world while fighting the pirates who are trying to stop him. Anyways, the game usually has you control Baloo in the Seaduck, his plane, except for when you enter a bonus level, where you then control Kit on his airfoil.Controls:Seaduck:D-Pad: Controls the SeaduckB Button: Fires weaponA Button: Turns plane aroundStart Button: Brings up status screenSelect Button: Pauses gameAirfoil:D-Pad: Controls the AirfoilStart Button: Brings up status screenSelect Button: Pauses gameItem Values:Unlike most other games, collecting some items to get points doesn't just serve as points. When you collect certain items, such as moneybags or loads, you gain money to spend on upgrades for the Seaduck. These upgrades are essential for completing the game, as it is next to impossible to do without them. Below is a list compiling how much each item is worth, in points or money.Cherry: 100 pointsGrapes: 200 pointsBananas: 500 pointsStrawberry: 1000 pointsLoad: $1000 per loadMoneybag: $3000 per bagHints:Achieving A Perfect Score:To receive the perfect score bonus of 100000 dollars, you must do the following:1.) Get all loads and all moneybags located in the level.2.) Enter the bonus level. You do not have to collect every balloon.Reviewer: Raging_DemonTENhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/nes/file/587679/20972</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter, Action, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd., Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>MknJKlwVV-M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2789</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587679-disneys-talespin</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/disneys-talespin_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/disneys-talespin/3030-1777/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/yAa0wep.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GDy2Wo1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/0Bblv6X.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/tuqEb2L.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/k80EH0W.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lgEC9nt.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5VauUMY.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/TzYuI5a.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8oiffq3.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jBQzU6f.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/hEmsDi7.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/jM7u7uK.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/7byCXhu.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3myioOv.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/MFmVR8b.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Strap on your seat belt! Here's rollicking fun with Baloo Bear and his cargo plane, the Mini-Sea Duck. He's out delivering goods to all the people in the cape. But Don Karnage and his goofy band of pirates are hot on Baloo's tail wind, trying to swipe the cargo! It's high-flying adventure as Baloo dodges and shoots through the clouds and over skyscrapers. It's low-flying fun as he zips through a haunted house where hats and gloves join the chase. Alligators and natives rumble in the jungle. Cave dogs bash Baloo with bones. Submarines transform into helicopters. Baseballs as big as boulders give Baloo a rocky ride! Baloo's got 8 trips to make so he's got to be a frisky flyer. Grab your goggles, and don't smack into a bubble. It could mean trouble!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/402f88c3-d0bd-4f3a-b4aa-28b74143d742.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cfd9ca6a-e20a-4652-a391-107df82e6835.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43dfc148-12a3-4a25-9d9b-40f72c3f2ab6.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>