<Game>
	<Name>Taro's Quest (USA) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Taro's Quest is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Jaleco Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 1989.This is the US translated prototype version of the Japanese game.  It's not clear exactly how far the translation went.  It is a Dragon Warrior type RPG.  ~Rxhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/nes/home/587682.htmlCheat: Have Princess Hanna in Your Party (Second Scenario; US Version)When playing the U.S. version of this game and starting the second scenario, unlike the Japanese version, you'll find that you do not have Princess Hanna in your party. You can remedy this fact and greatly bolster your party's power by holding B on Controller 2 during the briefing for the second scenario. You'll now have Princess Hanna in your party.Cheat: Unlock harder difficulties and weapons.After beating the game with certain criteria, new modes and weapons shall be unlocked.Cheat: Sound Test (US Version)This can be done during the second quest of the game, the first one in which you can have the Princess Sakura as an ally. In the overworld, to the east of the Town of Inns (the first town), and south near the shoreline, there is a shop selling Eggplants for $50. Normally, you are supposed to go back to the Town of Inns and speak with the monster in the center of the town to turn it back into a human. However, if you buy an Eggplant, then use it through the item menu, you will access a sound test mode. Use the D-Pad to shift through the music, the A Button to play the music, and the B Button to exit the mode.Cheat: Extra ChapterIf you clear the chapters in order (Chapter 1 --&amp;gt; 2 --&amp;gt; 3), you'll unlock a hidden final chapter.Cheat: Easily Defeat Magic-Blocking BossesMany of the bosses in this game have a tendency to block any attacks you use through spells. This makes battles much more difficult because magic does fixed damage and can make quick work of even the most difficult of bosses. However, there is a way to circumvent this due to a programming oversight regarding the "Living SWD" item. Living SWD's are random item drops from Dragonflies in the final dungeon of the second quest; they deal a fixed 60 damage to the target. This even affects bosses, meaning that - if you have at least six Living SWD's - you can kill a boss in three turns or less!Cheat: Have Princess Sakura in Later QuestsAt the beginning of the game, you are given the choice of three quests in which to participate. Under normal circumstances, you are intended to proceed from the first, to the second, to the third, then onto the hidden fourth quest on Zakuro Island -- even so, it is possible to do them out of order if you wish. However, if you don't them in order, you will not have the aid of your second ally, Princess Sakura: she only becomes part of your party as a result of completing the first quest, thusly making it much to your benefit to do the quests in the order the game intends.</plot>
	<releasedate>unreleased</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587682-jajamaru-ninpou-chou</gamefaqs_url>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TMkAdj8.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Z92hZsz.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/mmydNAq.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/f4QvFsF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>This is an RPG much like Dragon quest. Very well received in Japan, they wanted to bring it to the America's. Unfortunately the game never made it overseas, However the game is still very much playable, although it is about 98% finished. Meaning in order to beat the game, you must get a Talisman... Which hasn't been implemented yet. However there are codes to give you that talisman by cheating.</Notes>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cee9bd4c-0676-421a-bd5d-545cd5ac4e8a.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1522447-7776-481c-beba-fd1b01b4d06f.png</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>