<Game>
	<Name>Tashiro Masashi no Princess ga Ippai (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Tashiro Masashi no Princess ga Ippai is an Action game, developed by TOSE and published by Epic Sony Record,which was released in Japan in 1989.Cheat: Extra 1,800 HealthDuring game, press and hold A + B on Controller 2 and shout to the microphone on the Controller 2. The message box with a boy shouting "Papa, go!" will appear. This trick works only once per level.Cheat: Last Stage PasswordAt the password screen, press Right 2 times and enter the Japanese character 9 times. Select "End" to start on the last stage with max energy.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/10/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>TOSE</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27313</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579489-tashiro-masashi-no-princess-ga-ippai</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VpxGsoo.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/VvtcMeZ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/AfhhP8U.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uT03E4U.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/L84qHcx.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Tashiro Masashi no Princess ga Ippai (田代まさしのプリンセスがいっぱい?, Masashi Tashiro Has So Many Princesses) is a Japanese video game for the Nintendo Famicom (NES) by former comedian Masashi Tashiro released in time for October, 1989. The story is about the hero Masashi Tashiro who has to rescue the four princesses in distress. One happy ending and four unhappy endings were used in the game; becoming one of the first video games to have multiple endings. The game was not very successful, but it started appearing frequently and getting high prices on online auction sites like Yahoo! after 2000, when Masashi Tashiro was arrested and convicted several times in connection with voyeurism and drug abuse.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c3b525a-a898-43c0-b32a-9ff6bea38e14.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd54c765-f90b-447c-9fb8-6265074066e8.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Epic Sony Record</Publisher>
</game>