<Game>
	<Name>Tatakae!! Rahmen Man - Sakuretsu Choujin 102 Gei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:One of the many Bandai anime license games for the NES, Tatakae!! Ramenman: Sakuretsu Choujin 102 Gei follows the eponymous warrior Ramenman as he attempts to track down his father's killers and bring them to justice with his many years of martial arts training.Tatakae!! Ramenman is a spin-off of the Kinnukiman franchise, known in the US as M.U.S.C.L.E.. Ramenman was among the many characters of that franchise. Though the game's title screen credits a company called Shinsei as the publisher, it was a toy company with no prior game publishing that would soon be merged with Bandai, suggesting it was used in a subsidiary role by the toy-producing giant.Notably, this game is the first true point-and-click adventure game for the system. While there had been many adventure games made for the NES, such as Portopia or Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom, they had been largely driven by menus. Ramenman is directed by using the cursor to select an area to walk to or interact with instead much like classic Sierra adventure games such as King's Quest.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/10/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27314</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578624-tatakae-ramen-man-sakuretsu-choujin-102-gei</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tatakae-ramenman-sakuretsu-choujin-102-gei/3030-40167/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wPtgGVG.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2C308Ga.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qWFSuiG.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FhKBJLk.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/p0weTS9.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9X1OD9U.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZdRIIYp.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nDifkPV.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/aD02leU.png</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Tatakae!! Ramen-Man: Sakuretsu Choujin 102 Gei (闘将！！拉麺男 炸裂超人一〇二芸? lit. Fight!! Ramen-Man: Explosion Superhero 102 Technique) is an adventure game developed by Human Entertainment for the Famicom and published by Bandai in 1988. It is based off the Tatakae!! Ramenman series, which itself is a spin-off of the Kinnikuman series, known in the US as M.U.S.C.L.E.. Ramenman is a popular character in the Kinnikuman universe. The game follows the eponymous warrior Ramenman as he attempts to track down his father's killers and bring them to justice with his many years of martial arts training. Notably, this game is the first true point-and-click adventure game for the system. While there had been many adventure games made for the NES, such as Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken or Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom, they are largely driven by menus. Ramenman is directed by using the cursor to select an area to walk to or interact with instead much like classic Sierra adventure games such as King's Quest.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ad393a8-8ce0-4e17-8344-088b81c80558.jpg</boxart2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>