<Game>
	<Name>Tecmo Cup - Football Game (Spain)</Name>
	<plot>Tecmo Cup Soccer Game (known as Captain Tsubasa in Japan) is a video game for the Nintendo Entertainment System. Released in 1992 by Tecmo, it is a football (soccer) game. In the game you must fight your way from junior league all the way to the finals of World Cup.Tecmo Cup Soccer Game is a heavily Americanized version of Japanese Captain Tsubasa football (soccer) game released for the Famicom system, featuring a different main character, a different introduction and more western-looking players. The game contains elements from role-playing games as the players have skill levels and are mostly controlled by different kinds of text commands. Because of the unusual interface and presentation, Tecmo Cup Soccer Game did not attract casual gamers in its time and therefore had a relatively small fanbase.Controls:Control Pad: move selected playerA button: confirm selectionB button: bring up menu while in possession/cancel selectionStart: pause gamehttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tecmo_Cup_Soccer_GameCheat: Begin the game with a level 20 teamThis password will enable you to play at the very beginning of the game with all of your players at level 20.Cheat: Hyugas NeoTiger ShootIn order to get this amazing and powerful shoot just loose the second match of your group, when playing in France.Cheat: Tecmo Cup final passwordThis password will start you in the very last game, the Tecmo Cup final versus Brazil Jr.  Please note that there are upper and lower case letters as well as symbols used.  Any symbol that needs to be explained will be put with a * between parentheses and explained below the password.  The password contains six sets of 5 letters/symbols: J(*1)G7q [space] 94mJ(*2) [space] XD!R+w (*3)V-x(*4) [space] (*2)wR0T [space] K4Z40Z *1 is a Heart symbol *2 is a Down Arrow symbol *3 is a Left Arrow symbol *4 is a Club symbol 0  is the number zero</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>7.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2131</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/562938-tecmo-cup-soccer-game</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AXVuzTD.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pr1Diqn.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DdGNwGS.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GtNv6Ac.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YJMJdsw.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1CkwXEx.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HBcbtn5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/85OuNe2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5yy45Gm.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/mKpdYk2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/AfrAzIL.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>