<Game>
	<Name>Tecmo Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Tecmo Baseball is one of the many baseball games released for the Nintendo Entertainment Systems. There are five modes in Tecmo Baseball: One Player, Two Player, One Player Allstar, Two Player Allstar, and a watch mode. In One Player mode you pick from one of the fourteen teams and challenge each of the other teams. A password feature allows you to continue from where you left off. You also have the option of using the DH rule.Gameplay: is similar to the many other baseball released for the NES. The camera angle when batting or pitching is from behind the pitcher. The pitcher can pitch the ball high and low, as well as curve it. Tecmo Baseball includes digitized voices for the umpire.Cheat: Chicago NM (NL) CodesEnter the code after selecting Chicago NM as your team.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2130</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587683-tecmo-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tecmo-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tecmo-baseball/3030-16272/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/51sCZlg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/51sCZlg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HsTmyWY.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JDpsGN9.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/QVYycPa.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eK7HLL7.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/E08pg9t.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6beI2lS.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/c9pRH8q.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bw4SLw2.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/l8FmJy4.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1To5Vhr.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vmenGIT.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Vsbeo49.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Gameplay is similar to the many other baseball released for the NES. The camera angle when batting or pitching is from behind the pitcher. The pitcher can pitch the ball high and low, as well as curve it. Tecmo Baseball includes digitized voices for the umpire.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6efd2894-0ee5-4840-a174-d1c02fe2a6bc.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33c5320a-f58f-47d2-bbb0-e8cee9a45175.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>