<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles - Tournament Fighters (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Trash the surf board and heave the 'za. It's a whole new breed of Turtles and they're fixated on fighting. We're dead serious, Tournament Fighters takes dude-on-dude demolition to new heights of intensity with 4 modes of pain-producing battles, deadly warriors, secret arenas, astounding graphics and sound effects that'll make you cringe! Clash with Krang-created clones of the Turtles, Casey Jones, April O'Neil, Ray Filet and Sisyphus, plus bosses Triceraton, Krang's Android and Karai. There's flying body presses, knee drops, head butts, rocket punches, elbow smashes, somersault throws, you'll feel and inflict them all. And the settings include Magma Ocean Planet, Jungle Planet, and every other bizarre corner of Dimension X!Cheat: Player 2 Match SkipDuring Story or Vs. CPU modes, the second player can skip to to the Vs. Player mode's player selection screen by pressing Start on their controller. This will not work during Story Mode's Bonus Game, however; to make it work during this section, you must press Up, A, and B together on Controller 2.Cheat: Play as Hothead agaisnt HotheadNormally, the game doesn't allow more than one player (most likely due to a glitch in the programming), but there's actually a way to bypass this in 1P vs. CPU mode. In the Player Select screen, choose to play as any character (1P) EXCEPT Hothead. Next, the game will ask you to select your opponent (CPU) and here is where you choose Hothead. Now play the game normally, it doesn't matter whether you win or lose.  When the match is over, go for a rematch. This time, choose Hothead to be your character. The game will once again ask you for your opponent, but look and behold! The CPU cursor is already on Hothead. Choose him and enjoy the forbidden battle (unfortunately there doesn't seem to be a way to do this with a 2nd player).</plot>
	<releasedate>2/5/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>cxlzZrNjrCg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2134</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587691-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters/3030-4896/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wJYToq2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/azuZ207.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/omEZsDu.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/NejtSh0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vyUVPH7.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IHe26NU.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/04Gh3rf.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wRnNpnY.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/11YaAjt.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FzPy2CE.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/49R2hB5.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9GokCyx.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/KDXe5vC.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/u5kjvES.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/8LAD81u.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BhogW7m.jpg</banner1>
</game>