<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:/GameplayThe Manhattan project is the third installment of the TMNT games for the NES. As usual you can pick from all four turtles. There are a few interesting moves here that have been added since the 2nd game TMNT 2 Arcade. In this title you are not only able to jump attack, and regular attack, but also by holding down and the attack button your able to spear/pick someone up and throw them behind you. There is also a special attack for each character that can be used by hitting both the attack and jump buttons at the same time. This however costs one point of health every time it is performed and so makes the game a bit more interesting and difficult with the limited amount of pizzas/health available. It really makes you decide when to use your special to clear some guys out but you have to keep in mind you'll be losing health to do it anyway and a boss could appear anytime. The levels range from a beach, to a floating section of the city in the sky, and even a submarine. Another interesting note about this game is it was the first (yes before turtles of time) to involve riding on things, such as a hover board across the sea to reach the submarine. These new portions of the game alongside the new abilities make it a fun and memorable TMNT experience.Bosses:Level 1 - Rocksteady (Rhino)Level 2 - Groundchuck (Calf)Level 3 - Mini Boss - Slash (Turtle)Boss-Bebop (Pig)Level 4 - Dirtbag (Rat)Level 5 - Mini Boss - Mother Mouser (Robot)Boss - Leatherhead (Crocodile)Level 6 - Mini Boss - Rahzar (Wolf)Boss - Shredder (Man)Level 7 - Tokka (Snapping Turtle)Level 8 - Mini Boss - Krang (Brain and Robot)Boss - Super Shredder (Man)Playable CharactersLeonardo (Leo)Considered by many (except maybe Raph) to be the leader of the Turtles and the most strong-willed Turtle, Leonardo wears the blue bandanna and has a long reach but a somewhat limited special with his Cyclone Sword Swing. The Cyclone Sword Swing is a move where Leonardo stands still and swings his two swords around his body, which will hit anyone around him. The problem with this move is that it has a limited range and you mostly want to use it if you are surrounded. It doesn't help you much if you need to attack enemies who are a few steps away from you which is usually the case. As such, Leonardo's Cyclone Sword Swing is the arguably the worst special in the game.Michaelangelo (Mike)The goofball and joker of the group, Mike (or sometimes called "Mikey") wears the orange bandanna. Like Raphael he is a short-range striker with his nunchuck weapons. His special ability is the Kangaroo Kick which is kind of like a front-hand spring where Mike jumps backwards on his hands and then pushes his body upward in an arc with his feet kicking forward. This move is arguably the third worse special as most enemies that you want to attack are on the ground and rarely in the air.Raphael (Raph)Raphael is the independant and rebellious Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle of the group and where's a hot rodding red-colored Bandana and wields the three-pronged "Sai" (pronounced "sigh") short-ranged weapon. Raphael's reach is even shorter than that of Michaelangelo which can make him a hard character to play as just like Mike. However he has arguably the second best special attack in his Power Drill Attack which is a spinning headbutt attack that launches Raph forward and damages any enemy in his way. Raph's attack is arguably the best special in the game although it is similar to Don's special attack.Donatello (Don)Donatello where's the purple bandanna and wields a wooden bo staff. Donatello is the smartest and most knowledgeable (and arguably intelligent) Teenate Mutant Ninja Turtle of the group and is not only level-headed but is always the Turtle that uses or builds devices and knows how to operate machinery and computers. Donatello is arguably the best character and the easiest to use because of the long reach of his bo, he has the longest reach of all the characters. Additionally, Donatello has arguably the best special in his Knockout Roll. This move is similar to Raphael's Power Drill Attack" that launches Donatello forward. In the move Donatello holds his staff out as he tucks in and spins forward vertically as he hits all the enemies in his path.Cheat: Cheat CodesAt the title screen, press A, B, Right, Left, Right, Left, Down, Down, Up, Up &amp; Start. If done right, you'll be able to increase your continues after picking your turtle.Cheat: Random SelectAt the player select screen, press Down five times for a one-player game, or press Down ten times for a two-player game. After you use this code, your next player will be randomly selected when you lose a turtle.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>nunSavTP-4E</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1428</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563469-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-iii-the-manhattan</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-iii-the-manhattan-project</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-iii-the-manhattan-pro/3030-1831/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lCr673C.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pPDExhO.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/T7KHcHf.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/vkXfU9u.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/3R8XFDx.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/qP8FAEs.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/26HQ5d2.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zwQwAtA.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/784LX1t.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/irSx0Aw.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MDvmfJv.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jO8mk5L.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/v3sNXGy.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/axcKQZw.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/nC7ALTb.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/mFQ3zfN.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/3y8IKfY.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/8D6E7ST.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/LdmYvBW.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/Ro52CLS.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/U86IyTC.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/AsAm3Sj.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>http://i.imgur.com/AhGbhtH.jpg</fanart8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mv1RsAO.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Surf's up, dude! The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles make a little getaway to the Sunshine State. Until Shredder makes a major getaway with the entire island of Manhattan! His power hungry plot gets even more bogus when April O'Neil becomes part of the heist. What a relaxing vacation. Not! Those mondo mutants must make waves to get back home to save April and Manhattan, and send Shredder on a one way trip to geeksville! So unless you want Shredder to ninja-kick sand in your face and make off with your best girl and your hometown, you better get busy. Squashing him once and for all will be no holiday.</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3edb7753-3255-431d-a311-b252ea6e0c7d.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75b300d1-65db-440f-8e47-6310bec2b771.jpg</boxart7>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/438e1562-ac03-44a6-999b-e3977334cde8.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a68fb52-c881-45bb-8f92-f1e51b641485.png</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>