<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game (Australia)</Name>
	<plot>April O'Neil, the reporter friend of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, is kidnapped by the villainous Shredder and his two goons, Bebop and Rocksteady. The four ninja turtles: Raphael, Michelangelo, Donatello and Leonardo fight their way through hordes of Foot Soldiers in order to rescue April. They battle familiar foes such as the mad scientist Baxter Stockman, General Traag from Dimension X and the evil alien brain Krang, up to the final showdown with Shredder himself.Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Arcade Game is a port of the popular arcade game made by Konami during the height of the cartoon series' popularity. Depending on the version of the game, up to two, three or four players can take part in the action. The game plays like a simplified Double Dragon. While most of the standard Foot Soldier enemies are easily dispatched, some attack with knives or ray guns and are thus more dangerous. At the end of each level, players encounter a boss (or in certain cases two bosses working in tandem, such as Bebop and Rocksteady).The NES version of the game features additional content not present in other versions of the game: two new levels (Snowy Central Park and The Dojo), new bosses (including Tora, Shogun and Baxter Stockman as a fly), additional music tracks as well as more variations of Foot Soldiers.Cheat: 10 Lives (Japanese version)At the title screen, press Right 3 times, B 3 times, A 3 times and Start. If done right, you'll have 10 livesCheat: Easier battle with ShredderDuring the final battle against Shredder, Shredder splits up into two forms. They're identical in appearance, but only one is real; the other is fake. However, both forms are able to use the lightning attack that instantly kills you by turning you into a normal turtle.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ultra Software Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>7Ve9_HvlqW8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1427</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587690-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-ii-the-arcade-game</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-ii-the-arcade-game</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/3030-23408/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ccj2p4m.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/AZIrYZy.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/D0Qv4Hu.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lVEMSnu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8wTkh4L.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6cST1mr.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OmO4Wju.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VL5RQH5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cSlyMyz.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VDKapWn.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NhgFr39.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5KT8mwM.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Jkl1rvO.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/A3K8qia.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/zDrt2oW.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/RyJGTeL.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/2qMiJji.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/cqBRxPW.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mutonuO.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Yo! After being treated like garbage by the Ninja Turtles, Shredder has trained a new, more merciless breed of Foot Soldiers to inflict his revenge: A clan of over 700 Taekwondo turtle terminators who have once again captured April O'Neil to use as turtle bait. Fortunately you don't have to face these freaks of torture alone. For the first time ever, two dudes or dudettes can join forces and double-team Shredder, kicking shell while covering each others tails. But to survive you've gotta fight through 8 action-packed arcade levels, including Vinnie's Valet "Stalking" Lot and the Soho Sewer System, plus two new never-before-seen shell-squashing stages! Each of these deathtraps is reinforced by lethal electro zappers, laser beams, freezer burners or enemies such as Scorpion Robots, Stone Warriors and Baxter Stockman. Shredder has also hired the all-powerful Tora and Shogun, two alien bounty hunters who have never known defeat. Even though Master Splinter has prepared the turtles well for battle, teaching them radical new attack moves, it doesn't mean this war to save April and turtlekind will be a piece of cake or even a slice of pizza. Because with the forces of revenge on his side and the bounty boys in town, it's payback time for Shredder!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a1189ff6-d947-45dd-9abe-6c5fab449f81.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/447cf811-6383-49af-9ffb-80ee11dac6f9.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ultra Games</Publisher>
</game>