<Game>
	<Name>Tenchi o Kurau (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In the era known as the Later Han, the people of China were plagued by a bandit horde called the Yellow Scarves. They searched for a hero that could amass a force strong enough to conquer these cutthroats and thieves. At that time, three men were separately gaining power by attaining the service of many Warlords. They each planned on ridding their country of the Yellow Scarves, but when that task is finished there will only be room for one Emperor. Return to a time of sword and honor, where an oath was signed in blood. Master the strategies in this role-playing game for the NES.Cheat: Fight Weaker Enemies In Caves!First, get into a fight somewhere around Xu Zhou castle where the enemies are very weak. After that battle, enter the cave you want to enter without getting into anymore fights. When you are on your way to the cave, it might help to get a gullwing and maybe some smokepots. Once you get into another fight on the overworld or into any boss fight, though, the enemies are back to normal.Cheat: Get Chi Tu MaYou can find Lu Bu's horse (aka Red hare) its just past the encampment to the south of The first castle. After beating Hua Xiong there, search around the encampment on the overworld slightly to the south west of the gate. You'll find it. Whatever general has it will automatically get the benefit of an agility up spell. </plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>HMEDr7Wo9vE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1267</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563402-destiny-of-an-emperor</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/destiny-of-an-emperor/3030-1624/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/582VY9G.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/z33Ib4A.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pCmTPKi.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IWL41Fe.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z36Yqi3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/HTRfkU6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cre71Eo.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2QVnJ03.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/CqpiEdm.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2pkAX2L.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/q7h320J.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/L9VTd7v.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/dxXqYj4.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/y551bOH.jpg</banner1>
</game>