<Game>
	<Name>Tenchi o Kurau II - Shokatsu Koumei Den (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tenchi o kurau II: Shokatsu Koumei-den ("The Devouring of Heaven and Earth II: The Story of King Ming") is a turn based roleplaying and strategy game developed and published for the Nintendo Entertainment System by Capcom on April 5th, 1991 in Japan. It is the second NES RPG produced by Capcom based upon the Tenchi wo Kurau manga series, the first being Destiny of an Emperor released in 1989.Gameplay:A traditional Japanese roleplaying game at its core, Tenchi o kurai II puts the player in control of a party of warriors and mages as they try to take down a great foe that threatens the peace of their land. Throughout there are random encounters, boss battles, an experience system and valuable and/or useful loot.The player's party can hold up to seven members at a time, with one members acting as a "tactician". The tactician determines the list of tactics available for use by the player during battle.Cheat: Chapter SelectStart a new game and at the name entry screen, press Up 4 times, Right 2 times, Down 8 times and Left 1 time. After pressing that button sequence, enter the following Japanese names below to start in the desired chapter. You'll start at Level 0 though. The format is Row #, Column #.Cheat: Item DuplicationBefore you try duplicating an item, you'll need to have a few things set up. First, you need the character at the front of your army to have his inventory full, with the desired item in it. Also, you'll need a weapon equipped. To start, simply drop the item you want to duplicate. Now, have that character unequip his weapon and then immediately equip it again. Then, use the Check option to check the spot where you dropped your item. You should pick it back up again.Cheat: Recover A Dropped ItemIf you discard an item, but you later want to pick it up again. Just step into the same spot where you dropped it and Search the floor to get it back.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>Hm8dwO2ygjY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>21136</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/577333-tenchi-o-kurau-ii-shokatsu-koumei-den</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tenchi-o-kurau-ii-shokatsu-koumei-den</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tenchi-o-kurau-ii-shokatsu-koumei-den/3030-15618/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QLX2txH.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AnXQmgu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9AnKrDx.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/hyQomIN.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hRIYUiG.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hKPfo5S.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oiuoOmJ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kMx8aL6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3vfsJhe.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/oDvUVPk.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ovaz51F.png</snapshot10>
</game>