<Game>
	<Name>Tenkaichi Bushi - Keru Naguuru (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Tenkaichi Bushi is a one-on-one martial arts fighting game set in ancient China.Using 2D side-scrolling graphics with a distinct cartoony design, the player takes control of a single fighter as he attempts to defeat his opponent in single-round fights. Combat is controlled with a single attack button which can unleash all sorts of moves when pressed in conjunction with the directional arrows. These moves vary among each fighter, as players can choose from 15 different fighters, each with their own stats and moves, and then compete against the others to see who gets the honor of becoming grandmaster.Additionally the game includes a story mode in which players can take control of a single martial artist and roam the countryside looking for challengers (the later done from a top-down map view). Starting abilities and health are minimal, but successfully defeating opponents will increase the player's health and allow the fighter to learn new moves and turn into the ultimate combatant.Cheat: See The CreditsAt the password screen, press Right 3 times, Down 4 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 3 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 6 times, Up 4 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 4 times, Down 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 2 times, Up 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 4 times, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Down 3 times, Right 3 times and enter the Japanese character. Now press Start.Cheat: Low HP For Enemies/2nd PlayerAt the game mode select screen, the first option is "Versus 2P", the other two are Versus the computer. Pick from any of the 3. On the next screen pick your character, then on the next screen you get to pick your opponent. Instead, select the bottom right option to input a password. Once inside the password screen, slowly press B, Left, Down and A. If done right, the game will start right away and your opponents will have super low HP.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/7/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27315</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579456-tenkaichi-bushi-keru-naguuru</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tenkaichi-bushi-keru-naguuru</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tenkaichi-bushi-keru-naguuru/3030-14368/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XtPq3GG.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dXePikB.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/FTCwGfH.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/n4aWEyQ.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ehBEeYW.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/QeuC8PB.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DaliNnQ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/gWeSsSe.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JJRPVj9.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cEn8lig.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iS0en7n.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZGkzpYG.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Tenkaichi Bushi Keru Nagūru (天下一武士 ケルナグール lit. The Greatest Warrior on Earth - Kick and Punch?) is a fighting video game developed by Game Studio and published by Namco. It was released for the Famicom on July 21, 1989 only in Japan. It is one of the earliest versus fighting games with role-playing video game elements.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62882b12-51da-4312-9751-b59b2817e4d1.png</boxart3>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>