<Game>
	<Name>Tetsuwan Atom (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tetsuwan Atom, also known as Astro Boy, is a famous robotic child created by famed manga writer and artist Osamu Tezuka. This NES title is the first of a series of games based on that manga and anime.The goal of the game is to locate the thieves that broke into the home of the kindly Professor Ochanomizu and stole a considerable sum of money and return said stolen funds to the professor. Astro Boy has a series of powers in his arsenal, but is powered by uranium which steadily depletes as the game progresses. He has a basic punch and is able to triple jump and even fly in brief spurts.The game is notably odd as there are several different actions that are required to recover all the money, some of which are ambiguous and poorly conveyed to the player.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27318</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578552-tetsuwan-atom</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tetsuwan-atom</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tetsuwan-atom/3030-23913/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zMfFSo8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zMfFSo8.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/jiWjPe6.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gO2QSMN.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y5BLtNL.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1Jwkfp1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nWdpw3w.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/e6vtDEN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1Cch0S9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ExfQaro.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NrBOqEg.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/WApwxhJ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/eN2eW3L.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Tetsuwan Atom (鉄腕アトム?) is an action game developed by Home Data and published by Konami for the Famicom in Japan early on in 1988. The game stars Tetsuwan Atom, a popular early anime character who is better known as Astro Boy outside of Japan. Tetsuwan Atom was originally created in 1951 by Osamu Tezuka. The successful series started as a comic strip and was turned into a black and white animated series in 1963. It was one of the first (if not the first) animated TV series produced in Japan, and has influenced countless Japanese animated series that followed. The little robot-boy is one of Japan's most recognizable character. The story takes place in the future, at a time where humans and robots live together in harmony. The powerful robot-boy Atom lives with Professor Ochanomizu, an old scientist who takes good care of the little robot, and helps him fight crime and injustice. One day, burglars break into Professor Ochanomizu's lab and steal all of his money. It is now Atom's duty to recover the stolen loot.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fd3050c5-888f-4ccf-b3b4-8ee14067de8f.jpg</boxart4>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>