<Game>
	<Name>Thomas the Tank Engine and Friends (USA) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>It's full steam ahead once again for Thomas, he's had a busy week at the Station and now it looks likely this week is going to be just as busy. The Fat Controller's head is spinning with all the special trips he has to organize. He's got to take the children to the seaside, medicine to the hospital, logs to the saw mill, coal to the power station, deliver the mail and take some oil to the oil refinery. It's a good thing that he has Thomas and his friends to rely upon. You control Thomas as he tries to complete all his tasks before the week is over. But be careful not to go too fast, you never know what's round the next corner!</plot>
	<releasedate>unreleased</releasedate>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587698-thomas-the-tank-engine-and-friends</gamefaqs_url>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DVCny3Q.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qeFG7IV.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pztYatm.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zRIFwuk.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/WZQPJDM.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Take a trip to the Island of Sodor with Thomas, Percy, Bertie, Sir Topham Hatt, and other friends from the PBS hit show, SHINING TIME STATION. Eight different adventures await you, as the game lets you explore the entire island on a network of various tracks. You can even design your own custom courses for Thomas and company to travel on! In Race mode, you play as Thomas against either Percy or Bertie in a test of your quickness. Younger players will find assistance in Special mode, and Sir Topham hat is along to pose some tricky trivia questions to everyone throughout the game. There are plenty of video puzzles to unscramble and lots of clues to uncover throughout this friendly collection of games for the younger set.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/00813fa1-2fd5-43e6-9ee3-5ad92a30f756.png</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5f1822d-7e14-4711-a428-606b7872621d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eafc288e-71c5-445f-8973-3a8428542696.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ec341764-e6fd-4a96-b31b-7e74d9b6f8d8.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/003436a7-335a-4c25-97dd-910e51f2ddfb.png</snapshot8>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
</game>