<Game>
	<Name>Thundercade (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Thundercade is a 1987 Arcade vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up originally developed by SETA Corp and published by Taito that was later ported to the NES in mid-1989 for the US market only. The NES version was developed by Micronics and published by American Sammy; this would be the publisher's first NES release, and certainly not the last.The goal of the game is to drive a high-tech motorcycle equipped with various weapons and the capacity for further upgrades into a terrorist base - belonging to AATOM, or Atomic Age Terrorist Organization of Miracali - and detonate a bomb within their atomic power plant's core to prevent them from using their nuclear power to threaten the world's safety. The player must make their way through difficult terrain and battle against numerous terrorists on foot, in cars, tanks, helicopters and submarines.Cheat: Debug MenuPower on the console and wait until the demo starts. Press A to skip it, then wait for it to play again. Skip the demo a total of four times. After the fourth time, wait until the title screen appears, and then wait until a blinking animation follows the titles name from left to right. Press the A Button exactly when the blinking begins, but before it passes the "T" letter in the name. If done properly, the debug menu appears.Cheat: Secret EndingIf you wait for an hour after beating the game, just sitting there at the ending animation screen, you'll find a new animation and a hidden message from the developers.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>American Sammy Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2139</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587702-thundercade</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/thundercade</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/thundercade/3030-21477/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TUuADYJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/QTu9rM3.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/M3PjHBm.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/V9vT2sg.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/CGWOBA1.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8dWtsFQ.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/U76RLDY.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hZI48nh.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ESGF8J3.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/k6qYfqp.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AoDPi8L.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iF1pn50.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/z06fuAR.gif</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Terrorism has reached new heights. AATOM (Atomic Age Terrorist Organization of Miracali) has constructed their own nuclear power plant, and threaten the world with atomic terror. The world powers have decided to initiate operation THUNDERCADE to stop AATOM. Equipped with a high-performance combat motorcycle, sidecar cannons, and backed by a precision B-7 bomber, you set out on the dangerous mission.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d636ef3-e299-452d-825d-6328ba347fa3.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/168d30e8-e6b2-4fe4-8a9f-28eaa7db4711.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>American Sammy</Publisher>
</game>