<Game>
	<Name>Tiles of Fate (USA) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>In 306 B.C. Lou Ban, the most acclaimed artist of the Chin clan, sculpted from the finest ivory, 7 sets of enchanted Tiles. Legends say the original set of Tiles was created by gods and played as a game. Wizards said when played by mortals, it was an art that could be used to predict the future. Priests said it was a dangerous gamble that actually altered the flow of fate. Soon the art of the Tiles had spread across the whole of China, but with it something strange was also spreading. Droughts and then flooding, terrible famines and then gigantic harvests. Everyday something more strange and unlikely would occur, the forces of fate had indeed been blown out of control. The influence of the Tiles on the land of China had to come to an end, but it would not be easy. Like the force of Yin &amp; Yang, each Tile has a match that when united, will allow both Tiles to achieve symmetry, and simply cease to exist. You must conquer 7 castles to defeat 7 sets of Tiles. It will take more than quick reflexes - you must use strategy, skill and luck to defeat the TILES OF FATE!Cheat: Level SelectNote that this is only available in Asian releases of this game, "Idol Shisen Mahjong", released by Hacker International. At the stage number screen, press Select, A, B. The music will start playing. Press A or B to select the stage number from 1 to 21, then press Start to view the stage's final image. Press Start to return back to the stage number screen, where you can now play selected level or enter the cheat one more time and select another stage.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<Developer>American Video Entertainment Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2140</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587704-tiles-of-fate</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tiles-of-fate</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiles-of-fate/3030-18313/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jgNR2TF.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jgNR2TF.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Otshf6T.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MMGElYu.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/L1ZCTQ0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/djPawMC.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kDuAvoU.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hUX0gmw.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rm1ZjeL.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kZOR1ZI.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zwAMcUm.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NPlxo8s.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ivs1qXb.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In Tiles Of Fate the object of the game is to clear the screen of all the tiles within the given time limit. This is done by selecting two tiles with matching symbols which will cause them to disappear due to the force of symmetry. However, the force of symmetry can only make two right angles at most, and can not pass through other tiles. To clear all the tiles, you will need to plan your moves carefully. To help out, you may discover one of three forces of fate under a tile which can be saved and used when you're stuck. The forces are The Flash of Chance (allows symmetry to affect any matching tiles on the board, even those surrounded by other tiles), The Force of Balance (will eliminate brick walls that block the path of symmetry) and The Flag of Knowledge (this will make your next move for you in case you can't spot what the best move is.) Also included is a level editor which lets you create your own tile challenges.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa9a7a63-f0dc-4141-8dea-2d061bda36a3.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bf03b38-881f-43a5-9520-b561b0a2e671.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Publisher>American Video Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>