<Game>
	<Name>Time Zone (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Oh, no! On the way to meet your girlfriend Haruka, our intrepid little hero has gotten ambushed by that nefarious, time-traveling villain, Professor Time. Now it's time to join him as he crosses time and space to save her from his evil clutches.In this run and jump action game, you'll find yourself flung anywhere from prehistoric times to the far future and back again, defeating anything from dinosaurs to samurai to aliens just to get her back.Your main weapon  your ever-sturdy baseball cap. Just toss it forward and let it simply boomerang back or jump as it boomerangs back to let it fly around you for a short amount of time. And if you're lucky enough to collect enough chimes, you'll get to witness the awesome destructive power and invincibility of the skateboard.Combined that with a host of hazardous obstacles so prevalent in platformers and you've got yourself into quite a pickle trying to tackle Professor Time. Pursue and flog him with your cap so that the hero and Haruka can live happily ever after.Cheat: Extra 30 LivesPress and hold A + B on Controller 2, then press Reset. Then start a new game.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/10/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sigma Enterprises, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>27319</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/570597-time-zone</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/time-zone_</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jVjEqkB.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Dmx7t4o.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FOpuSMm.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/vOAmzxm.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YWmmwRU.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IUZQz50.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MXdkSmq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/AnjOdMX.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/457mtja.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gMnaM83.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/H2Mv39S.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Oh, no! On the way to meet your girlfriend Haruka, our intrepid little hero has gotten ambushed by that nefarious, time-traveling villain, Professor Time. Now it's time to join him as he crosses time and space to save her from his evil clutches. In this run and jump action game, you'll find yourself flung anywhere from prehistoric times to the far future and back again, defeating anything from dinosaurs to samurai to aliens just to get her back. Your main weapon — your ever-sturdy baseball cap. Just toss it forward and let it simply boomerang back or jump as it boomerangs back to let it fly around you for a short amount of time. And if you're lucky enough to collect enough chimes, you'll get to witness the awesome destructive power and invincibility of the skateboard. Combined that with a host of hazardous obstacles so prevalent in platformers and you've got yourself into quite a pickle trying to tackle Professor Time. Pursue and flog him with your cap so that the hero and Haruka can live happily ever after.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/abea4de6-b72c-474c-9b7c-e8f834d5b518.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/689c8c3e-7113-42cc-b025-2368993c0e1a.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sigma Ent. Inc.</Publisher>
</game>