<Game>
	<Name>Tiny Toon Adventures Cartoon Workshop (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Tiny Toon Adventures: Cartoon Workshop was a game created by Novtrade and published by     Konami in December 1992.  This title gave you the ability to be in the director's chair and be able to make your own cartoons using Tiny Toons characters.  The player has the ability to pick the character, setting, sound effects, captions, and transitions.   You could only select up to two characters at a time and did not have  the whole roster of Tiny Toons characters.  Characters included:    Buster  Bunny,   Babs Bunny,  Plucky Duck, Little Beeper, Furball, and Calamity. Cartoons created could be up to five minutes long, and could be recorded to VCR to save them.  While similar to games like Videomotion or Color a Dinosaur, this game featured more customization and the ability to make cartoons. Cheat: View CreditsAt the title screen, simply press Up, Down, Left, and Right, in that order, to view the credits.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>2142</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587709-tiny-toon-adventures-cartoon-workshop</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tiny-toon-adventures-cartoon-workshop</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiny-toon-adventures-cartoon-workshop/3030-30983/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/U4ctyKz.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/U4ctyKz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eY5IhWu.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/3aKuz0n.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AHYILcO.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Y7pIzCM.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1HTxAPb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5UudZU8.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9WYUTaA.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gWeSsSe.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JJRPVj9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cEn8lig.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lgipFXK.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>Create a cartoon featuring Buster, Babs, Plucky, Furrball, Calamity, and Little Beeper! You pick the backgrounds, settings, and situations, then add in music, sound effects, and captions to tell the story!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46de47b6-6e30-4c49-8eef-eceef4b946c3.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6d4124b3-3c69-4da3-99d7-207676a806ac.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>