<Game>
	<Name>Tiny Toon Adventures (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:At the open of the game, Buster Bunny is watching TV in his rabbit hole when Montana Max appears with a kidnapped Babs Bunny. Babs is hanging over a pool of sharks at Max's Mansion and Buster must rescue her.Gameplay:The gameplay is similar to most action platformers of its time. You had to find your way to the exit before time runs out. If you take a hit, you lose a life, unless you have found a heart to give yourself a second hit.Stages:There are six worlds in the game, with three levels each with the exception of Wackyland which only has one:The HillsThe WetlandsThe TreesDowntownWackylandMontana Max's MansionSpecial StagesBuster battles Duck VaderIf a player's carrot count is a multiple of eleven at the end of a level, a battle with Duck Vader is triggered. If you can defeat Duck Vader and his two stormtwoopers you will get three extra lives. Duck Vader and the stormtwoopers are parodies of Darth Vader and the stormtroopers from Star WarsCheat: Stage SelectAt the title screen, press A, A, A, B, B, B, Select, Select, Select, A &amp; Start. If done right, the stage select menu will appear.Cheat: See Duck VaderFirst, collect a number of carrots equal to a multiple of 11. Then, grab a level ending key, and Duck Vader's ship will pick you up on the map screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>jqnjXaRIq9Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1384</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587707-tiny-toon-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tiny-toon-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiny-toon-adventures/3030-16460/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nwEGpqG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/gcvzDx4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/wXwxp1b.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/jR4oFuF.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iD0nGTz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/X9A328s.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SQgloGc.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/07K0lze.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jnX2FyM.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Ke5e6WM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jvgDnkx.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WAeHM7Y.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/slWUtSr.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bUM8NMm.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/vKeZ09l.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aKyJdqb.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>These Tiny Toons have big problems. That's right. The arch enemy of Acme Acres, Montana Max, has kidnapped the ever-so-popular Babs Bunny. Now the furry female's fate rests in the paws of Buster Bunny and his crime fighting pals - Dizzy Devil, Furrball and Plucky Duck. Four kooky buddies with their own special talent. Buster can bounce over bad guys with the best of them. Furrball uses his feline claws to climb walls. Dizzy Devil prefers to spin through them. And Plucky can glide through the air and swim like a fish. Choose which partner you want at the beginning of each level before you face-off against time and goofballs gone bad in 6 zany wonderlands. So you better get jumping or it will be curtains for our playful pals!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0cf75553-3bad-4785-a87f-c7f2c5f7b21a.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d88117b1-616b-4bc9-a0ef-d69b3248e232.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/51cdae69-4fbb-4fd9-bc05-443dafa93f6a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/24835eb2-3988-42ee-a75a-6d1aec2281f1.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e384bac2-b963-4584-8ee4-46bf3cda0039.jpg</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>