<Game>
	<Name>Tiny Toon Adventures (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:At the open of the game, Buster Bunny is watching TV in his rabbit hole when Montana Max appears with a kidnapped Babs Bunny. Babs is hanging over a pool of sharks at Max's Mansion and Buster must rescue her.Gameplay:The gameplay is similar to most action platformers of its time. You had to find your way to the exit before time runs out. If you take a hit, you lose a life, unless you have found a heart to give yourself a second hit.Stages:There are six worlds in the game, with three levels each with the exception of Wackyland which only has one:The HillsThe WetlandsThe TreesDowntownWackylandMontana Max's MansionSpecial StagesBuster battles Duck VaderIf a player's carrot count is a multiple of eleven at the end of a level, a battle with Duck Vader is triggered. If you can defeat Duck Vader and his two stormtwoopers you will get three extra lives. Duck Vader and the stormtwoopers are parodies of Darth Vader and the stormtroopers from Star WarsCheat: Stage SelectAt the title screen, press A, A, A, B, B, B, Select, Select, Select, A &amp; Start. If done right, the stage select menu will appear.Cheat: See Duck VaderFirst, collect a number of carrots equal to a multiple of 11. Then, grab a level ending key, and Duck Vader's ship will pick you up on the map screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>jqnjXaRIq9Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1384</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587707-tiny-toon-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tiny-toon-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiny-toon-adventures/3030-16460/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nwEGpqG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/gcvzDx4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/wXwxp1b.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/jR4oFuF.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iD0nGTz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/X9A328s.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SQgloGc.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/07K0lze.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jnX2FyM.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Ke5e6WM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jvgDnkx.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WAeHM7Y.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/slWUtSr.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bUM8NMm.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/vKeZ09l.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aKyJdqb.jpg</banner1>
</game>