<Game>
	<Name>Tom & Jerry - The Ultimate Game of Cat and Mouse! (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>EEEK! There's a mouse in the house! But that's no ordinary rodent. It's one half of Hollywood's most famous cat and mouse team - Tom &amp; Jerry! Can you help Jerry outwit Tom and rescue his nephew Tuffy from the trunk in the attic? It's a classic cartoon chase game filled with action, excitement and hilarious surprises! Start in the basement and race up into the kitchen. Then leap out into a tree, climb onto the roof, slide down the chimney, charge through the living room and dash up into the attic. It's enough to make a little mouse dizzy! Every floor is filled with hidden dangers. Bees and Squirrels, Bats and hot embers. And let's not forget Tom himself. So get a move on, Jerry! Tom's hot on your trail!Cheat: Shortcut through World 3-Stage 1This is very difficult to do, especially when you don't use an emulator so you don't have save states. Get to the first drop that you will have to fall into  the hole. If you have an emulator, use a save state. These leaves won't hurt  you when you touch them, but they will make you bounce off of them. If you time a jump right so you hit the leaf at the perfect angle, you could make this jump which you're not supposed to be able to make. Keep going to the right and do this over any big gaps and you will reach the end of this level in no time at all.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hi-Tech Expressions, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>TwsVhA-Uh_g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2144</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587712-tom-and-jerry-the-ultimate-game-of-cat-and-mouse</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/tom-jerry-the-ultimate-game-of-cat-and-mouse</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tom-jerry-the-ultimate-game-of-cat-and-mouse/3030-11563/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zfkI6zZ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0EEIBIw.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HHZEaYb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ICOzCXT.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5gkWjM4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YSlpmyz.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6Bd4jHd.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/aW346DF.png</snapshot6>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/kvUMfrq.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/zZ8EpFc.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/CukM6BG.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/ntx4VrK.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/AiOppA9.jpg</fanart5>
	<Notes>Tom has mouse-napped Jerry's nephew Tuffy and locked him in a trunk in the attic. You and your furry little buddy Jerry must dash, jump, and climb from the basement up through every level of the house to rescue him in time. Jerry's main defense is his unlimited supply of marbles. Pick up other items such as bubble gum, meat cleaver, cups of water, moth balls, hammer, invisible ink and drill to overcome the enemies and obstacles in your way. Make sure you outwit Tom whenever he appears.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49a35dc9-dbd1-4ae2-9ea4-45dc6d8c6b0f.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/86c53bcb-aa5a-42fb-9cd1-4acd918831e8.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hi-Tech Expressions</Publisher>
</game>