<Game>
	<Name>Top Gun - The Second Mission (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Just like in the first game, you fly an F-14 Tomcat in combat against the enemy equipped with Soviet equipment, although there is no direct reference to the Soviet Union anywhere. The only plot of this game is to destroy everything you see, excluding the aircraft carrier to which you must land at the end of each level.In addition to the basic game mode with anti-ship, ground attack and space battle levels, similar to the first game, the second mission adds two extra modes. In the first extra mode you can fight against top enemy aces flying a MiG-25 Foxbat, one at a time. The second extra mode is two-player game with split screen, in which you can fight against your friend, both flying Tomcats.You will have to fight against interesting level bosses such as a giant Tu-160 Blackjack bomber, a Mi-24 Hind attack chopper and an armed space shuttle.Another interesting detail about the game is that between fighting the aircraft and surface opponents you have to dodge between giant trees (yes, you read correctly!!), lightnings and laser attacks.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>EsPWzAbGn04</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1462</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587716-top-gun-the-second-mission</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/top-gun-the-second-mission</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-gun-the-second-mission/3030-6054/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/khlVXNV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nK6PQCA.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/F8Mh8xb.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/mlwIrIB.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/9m10nSr.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/81VkRCh.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zSbV68O.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DdlGUYH.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OVvzpON.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gDXpENB.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/QtHGNQZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/UpKQSG5.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8M5l0Zf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/YWGkF0J.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/iEfWLEu.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fVWLGAO.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>So you think you're a Top Gun hero, just because you splashed a few bogeys in the Persian Gulf. Well, before polishing your ego, you've gotta survive a second mission that's ten times more deadly than the first. Soaring against an Armageddon bound armada of planes, tanks, ships, and satellite laser beams, every ounce of your skill and courage will be drained as you fight fire with fire, while out-maneuvering anti-aircraft blasts, cannon bursts and heat seeking missiles that are looking to roast your tail.</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b5cff60-ad8a-4556-ac87-e0978d34eb6a.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9d9a49fc-37fe-42c8-b318-008e2d263160.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>