<Game>
	<Name>Top Rider (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Top Racer is a motorcycle racing game from a behind-the-bike perspective. In both these respects, it's a very similar game to Sega's Hang-On series of motorcycle racers. The player can choose from two modes: Grand Prix, in which the player partakes in several consecutive races and Touring, in which the player can choose one of four courses for a single race.The game is notable for its unusual peripheral: An inflatable motorcycle with a special handlebar controller built-in. The player can sit on the peripheral once fully inflated and use the handlebars to control the on-screen bike.Cheat: Play With Normal ControllerAt the title screen press A, B, Right, Down, Left, Up, Right, B, A on the second controller. See, Top Rider normally requires a special controller. However, using this code should let you use a standard NES/Famicom controller.Cheat: Special Name PasswordsEnter one of these as your name during the Grand Prix mode for the specified effects.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/12/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>bD3rbdMtdrY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>27322</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579371-top-rider</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/top-rider</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-rider/3030-40522/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/gqbN7WX.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/gqbN7WX.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/o8eOvxQ.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/PUkTlbJ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ouQ21pb.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/60RQtXg.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/PzQZ7su.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/YFGEUim.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/79vOCWv.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/XeWm7fF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/disTm7n.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VvaxUUY.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/tgm7ESN.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A motorcycle driving game developed by Human and published by Varie for the NES. It was released in Japan only at the end of 1988. Top Racer is a motorcycle racing game from a behind-the-bike perspective. In both these respects, it's a very similar game to Sega's Hang-On series of motorcycle racers. The player can choose from two modes: Grand Prix, in which the player partakes in several consecutive races and Touring, in which the player can choose one of four courses for a single race. The game is notable for its unusual peripheral: An inflatable motorcycle with a special handlebar controller built-in. The player can sit on the peripheral once fully inflated and use the handlebars to control the on-screen bike.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23b3701b-c2b9-47b0-9fbc-47b147d01f06.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50e410a2-0d80-4b12-a691-0b6837357205.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Varie</Publisher>
</game>