<Game>
	<Name>Total Recall (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the 1990 Schwarzenegger film of the same name, Total Recall for the NES generally adheres to the movie's plot across its nine levels. Unlike the various PC iterations, this title was created by Interplay and published by Acclaim.Players control Doug Quaid as he platform hops across Earth and Mars in search of his stolen memories and the responsible parties. A collection of police, soldiers, and creatures will try to stop him. Quaid's default attack is a strong punch, though guns can be knocked away from some guards and picked up for use. Cutscenes between certain levels tell the movie's plot, and feature likenesses of the actors from the film (including Arnold).Sequences in the film are also replicated more tightly than in the PC versions. Quaid will be chased by henchman Richter in the first level, and must battle his wife inside their apartment. The security x-ray scanner takes up a level, as does the subway battle after. The player will also commandeer a Martian taxi for a driving level inside the colony, and windows can be shot out on Mars, sucking out any unfortunate baddies nearby.Cheat: Continue from the Mars StageWhen finishing the cement factory stage, you may have noticed the message: ''To get to Mars fast, watch the movie and hold A and B.''  This ''movie'' isn't the animation in which Quaid is going to Mars, but the cinema at the beginning of the game, where you watch the credits. NOTE: This code will work only if you lost all of your lives AFTER having reached Mars. When beginning a new game after losing all your lives in the Mars stage, go into the cinema and simply hold the A and B buttons while watching the credits.  You will not only get an extra life, but you will warp ahead to Mars.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>bhf_kAL14l4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1464</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587718-total-recall</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/total-recall__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/total-recall/3030-19276/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4JCeWi2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/aeiLqGV.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/N26nVni.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/BUwb6Gv.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AnTFA2X.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/mlpGOrc.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VIiuqvg.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/imT7ftF.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hRMrUAV.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RPQdOnf.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/mibyjAI.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gUtPkRu.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Wmk0uNh.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1ofBYYr.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JTrmEpM.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7QAxgfo.jpg</banner1>
</game>