<Game>
	<Name>Ultima - Quest of the Avatar (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The ruthless Triad of Evil has been vanquished and peace now reigns in the land. But without the threat of danger the people have become corrupt. Darkness dwells in their hearts and minds. The countryside is plagued by dragons, trolls, and long-dead wizards. Only an Avatar, a shining example of heroism, can destroy the monsters and conquer the internal wickedness with his mastery of magic and weapons. Become the Avatar! Save Britannia! And master the challenges of the ultimate quest--the search for good within yourself.Cheat: Invisible Whirlpool to CoveNormally to reach the village of Cove, you need to either find the whirlpool or use the balloon.  There is an invisible whirlpool not shown on the map that never moves, allowing easy transport to Cove.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Infinity</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1388</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587741-ultima-quest-of-the-avatar</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/ultima-iv-quest-of-the-avatar</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultima-iv-quest-of-the-avatar/3030-14381/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/UhX6cpY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/eCVIZ3s.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/BNfbWPG.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/6E8sOJP.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1LOEOoU.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TjUbi9d.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mUSnzzY.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Sey2HfH.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3ZUKeAz.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YBJaXYo.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/viGlVi1.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HYlQLGE.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NwVWpmE.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yT6wRAS.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The fourth game in the Ultima series features an improved game engine, with color graphics and enhanced character interaction: the player can have conversations with non-playable characters by typing names of various topics. However, the main difference between Ultima IV and its predecessors in the series (as well as other role-playing games) lies in the game's objectives and the ways to fulfill them.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06f139c8-9920-4699-885e-1ca6c937814a.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5ff2164-1bae-4cec-993f-5ce5891d825a.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>FCI</Publisher>
</game>