<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Basketball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In Ultimate Basketball, the player can choose one of seven fictional teams that each have different skills such as having tight defense or a phenomenal passing game. Each team also has their own players who are given ratings on their quickness, shooting and defensive ability.The point of view is horizontal for the most part. Occasionally, a close-up action scene is shown on plays such as slam dunks and free throws. There are also two different play modes, "Tournament" and "One Game." Players can play alone, against a friend, or with a friend against the computer. Their is also a "Watch" mode where to spectate games fully being played by the computer.Cheat: Double Timer SpeedPress and hold Down + A on Controller 2, then press Reset. Now, the timer in the game will be two times faster.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>American Sammy Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>2158</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587743-ultimate-basketball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/ultimate-basketball-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-basketball/3030-23115/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/0Xqgvup.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/VI8AlyJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/8Zlbhii.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Gjt6DqX.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5m8jzxS.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z6MWiYv.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fbiZgY6.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gSUjl8g.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/aVZyOAO.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vl7IaS4.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Hwf5ywd.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/J88W5bX.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/mpTSdPx.gif</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Shoot some hoops with Ultimate Basketball. All of the traditional rules of basketball apply as you take control of a fictional team from one of seven American locales. Each team has its own full roster of players as well as unique strengths and weaknesses. For example, Houston has a tight defense and can shoot the three, while Dallas excels at the passing game. The point of view is horizontal for the most part. Occasionally, you will get a close-up action scene on plays such as slam dunks and free throws. There are also two different play modes, "Tournament" and "One Game." You can play by yourself, against a friend, or with a friend against the computer.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef13970c-0c21-431d-9fde-4d5776e7d4ce.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f210c63-edee-4ce3-97b7-06c0aeb66e13.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>American Sammy</Publisher>
</game>