<Game>
	<Name>Valkyrie no Bouken - Toki no Kagi Densetsu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Valkyrie no Bouken: Toki no Kagi Densetsu ("Valkyrie's Adventure: The Legend of the Key of Time") is a top-down action-adventure game with RPG elements. The player, as the warrior from heaven Valkyrie, must defeat the evil lord Zouna and restore peace and order to Marvel Land.The game plays similarly to that of The Legend of Zelda, which was released seven months prior, and could be considered one of the first games to follow in its incredibly popular footsteps. It also has a few elements from Japanese RPGs such as Dragon Quest. Players explore Marvel Land on a scrolling overworld, finding money and equipment to make Valkyrie more formidable. Valkyrie also earns experience from defeating monsters, which will eventually level her up and make her stronger, as well as give her access to powerful magic spells.Though it borrows a lot from its influences, it itself has also influenced other games: For instance, persistent negative status effects that continue to harm after a battle is over, tents that restore the party's HP/MP on the overworld and using a boat to explore more of the world are all common console RPG elements that were first seen in Valkyrie no Bouken.The game's Arcade and TurboGrafx-16 sequel, Valkyrie no Densetsu, would prove to be considerably more popular. The character of Valkyrie makes cameo appearances in many other Namco properties, most frequently in their Tales RPG series.Cheat: SuicideTo commit suicide, pause gameplay and then press A and B simultaneously on Controller 2.Cheat: Last PasswordWith this password, the last dungeon will be accessible.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>26411</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578306-valkyrie-no-bouken-toki-no-kagi-densetsu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/valkyrie-no-bken-toki-no-kagi-densetsu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/valkyrie-no-bouken-toki-no-kagi-densetsu/3030-20174/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/iFlxrKr.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iFlxrKr.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/UctMRyY.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WtxGNxg.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MwJgGSQ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qncAxjQ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dJAsSCS.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/rrm75OR.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3VTUc0T.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jSuB0fv.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rkV8RgH.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Oa41lyL.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/g27A6YU.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In the world of Marvel Land, people and nature lived together in a peaceful and harmonic coexistence. All the animals were docile. Humans, Sandras, Quarkmen, Taros, and other races mingled with one another and worked to make Marvel Land into an increasingly beautiful place to live. A large clock tower resembling a stone grandfather clock stood watch over the countryside of Marvel Land. Long ago, an ancient evil had been sealed within the clock tower. The people needn't fret, however. For those days had long since passed, or so they had thought. The Key of Time that rested in the center of the face of the clock tower had long since been used to seal away the ancient evil that lies within. Until one day, the clock tower mysteriously stopped working. In an effort to rewind the clock, a villager takes it upon himself to do just that. Fumbling with the key, the villager drops the Key of Time, foolishly. In a frantic manner, the villager picks up the key and tries to reset it back into place before a catastrophe befalls Marvel Land. But then, it was too late for the villager to accomplish the task. The ancient evil of legend, Zouna, the dark wizard who manipulates time itself was unleashed upon the world once more. And to prevent anyone else from sealing him away once again, Zouna takes the Key of Time for himself. Finally freed after many years, Zouna wastes no time in wreaking havoc and chaos over Marvel Land. Zouna unleashes his manifested darkness over the land, and lays waste to the countryside. Feeling confident in his reign, Zouna constructs his castle in which to preside over Marvel Land from. The peaceful inhabitants of Marvel Land cried out in terror as Zouna's manifested darkness came after them one by one. Zouna's darkness corrupted the hearts of anyone it came across, and possessed them against their wills. Once thriving towns and villages fell into ruination. Family members were parted from their loved ones. Only a few scattered towns remained standing; forming a last bastion in resistance to Zouna's dark invasion. A futile effort. Even Kurino Sandra would come to meet his heroic demise, subdued by Zouna's power. Marvel Land is in dire need of a savior. The desperate call has been answered by the heavens. The child of the gods, Valkyrie, a fledgling maiden descends to Marvel Land from heaven. Her first adventure, she wields a simple shield and a short sword (a mace of light in the remake), vowing to save Marvel Land from the darkness that has consumed it. Then her adventure to defeat the evil Zouna begins. The game has a scrolling overworld like Dragon Warrior/Quest, with a real-time combat system similar to The Legend of Zelda. The player controls Valkyrie in her quest to defeat Zouna and restore peace to Marvel Land. With brown hair and no helmet, she begins the game armed with only a short sword. The player helps Valkyrie fight monsters, collect gold and find stronger equipment which will increase her powers; eventually, she finds a helmet and cloak. With the people of Marvel Land terrorized or controlled by Zouna, she receives no hints or advice. The player must devise a plan to defeat Zouna, with many of Valkyrie's tasks not immediately apparent; some can only be guessed by exploration and experimentation. When Valkyrie defeats a monster, she earns experience points towards the next level and (usually) a small amount of money. Although money is scarce in Marvel Land, the player rarely needs it to buy equipment. All the game's items can be obtained for free if the player knows where to look. In addition to equipping weapons and armor, Valkyrie gains access to seven spells. When she learns each one depends on her intelligence, which increases with each level of experience. The first, and possibly the most valuable, of these is the healing spell.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>_eLuLJ5sFK8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1581d154-b483-4b56-8bdb-c277867129d6.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff767f91-d971-4f3b-a676-ed48d9079fe2.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e12d0ab4-839d-4bad-b8e3-b51503db8ffa.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b7bd28d-3338-43ad-928f-a6b426a78235.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8974fdb5-25d9-4989-bf9b-a8a8d0223450.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>