<Game>
	<Name>Vegas Dream (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Vegas Dream contains four gambling mini-games: Blackjack, Roulette, Slots and Keno. The goal is to raise as much money as possible at any one of these events; the player can create a persistent profile that carries over cash between each mini-game, so there's no penalty for switching.There are also certain events that occur while the player is gambling. These can include NPCs asking the player for money, or a particularly wealthy individual that challenges the player at a single game of the NPC's choosing. Usually, the results of these events have an equal chance to end in, or against, the player's favor, much like the gambling games themselves.Blackjack, roulette and slot machines are all commonly known venues for gambling. Keno is a bingo/lottery game where numbers are called out and payouts are based on how many of those numbers each punter correctly predicted would appear.Cheat: Cheat ModeStart the game and on the gambling game select screen, press Up, Down, Right, Left, Up, Down, Right, Left, A, B, A, B &amp; B. A sound will be heard if you did it right. Now, if you hold A &amp; B and press Start, you'll enter a "Message Test" mode. You can also hold A and press Start on Blackjack to see the game's ending, on Roulette to play a lucky slot machine, on Slot Machine to for a Face Test and on Keno for a soundtest.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsOn the password enter screen, enter the codes below:</plot>
	<releasedate>3/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>HAL America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2164</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587750-vegas-dream</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/vegas-dream</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/vegas-dream/3030-18035/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ncSZwmc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nI6voeV.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/oUZ6uxa.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/EesGztf.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EwEt9Jz.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Mq35vQz.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/pml3c38.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8lHuPLt.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/9Akewuf.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VP9WjBn.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Pbtvq95.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jvefHMz.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/2g6r3No.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/xhDPiSR.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4zxvjsB.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Bring a casino to your living room! Up to four high-rollers can play Blackjack, Roulette, Keno, or Slot Machines. Odds are you’re going to love VEGAS DREAM!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5ffc3505-0122-4b39-82d0-167cb586c774.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41600148-2a01-438c-bca3-cf043e7505c3.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>HAL America Inc.</Publisher>
</game>