<Game>
	<Name>Vice - Project Doom (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Quinn Hart and his partner, Detective Reese of the VICE squad both work to stop the trafficking of illegal substances. But something new has appeared on the scene, a neon gel with great addictive properties. During investigations as to the origin of the gel, Reese mysteriously disappears and leaves Hart without a lead. Time passes and Hart becomes romantically involved with his new partner, Christy, as he continues trying to track down the gel. But Hart is about to get a brand new lead...Vice: Project Doom is a game that features both overhead driving modes and side-scrolling platform adventure sequences. Hart's vehicle can accelerate or slow down and fire his weapon straight ahead. During side-scrolling sequences, Hart can jump, duck, climb or use his selected weapon. Weapons that can be selected include a Katana sword, a pistol and a grenade-type weapon. These weapons feature limited ammunition with the exception of the katana. Power-ups include ammunition, coins, and health.During both of these sequences, Hart must fight and maneuver his way past enemy foes to confront a boss. By destroying the boss and completing the level, Hart progresses and learns a bit more about the origins of the neon gel and what Project Doom is all about. Cinematics dialog between the levels tell the tale in a style similar to that of Ninja Gaiden.Cheat: Slow MotionAfter entering the stage select code and selecting a stage, during gameplay push Right on controller 2's D-pad to increase the slow motion effect, and Left to decrease it.Cheat: Stage Select/Sound TestTurn the game on, hold the A Button down and press the Reset Button. Press A or B on Controller 2 to bring up the Sound Test. Pressing Up or Down on Controller 1 will allow you to go through the Sound Test. Pressing B on Controller 2 will bring up the Stage Select Option.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>American Sammy Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>WpUkXBYIYBg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2166</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587752-vice-project-doom</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/vice-project-doom</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/vice-project-doom/3030-8193/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/z1KGzhY.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TaRSl6t.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aDMRp6F.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/aUry5AF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/49YdQ3v.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LlCGmSD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7lcdnkL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/uSox2I1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GPoraqm.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yblpGs3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hoJoprS.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/qECtgKe.png</banner1>
	<Notes>In the distant future, the B.E.D.A. Corporation, a company involved in the development of electronic equipment and military weapons, is actually a front operated by a race of alien beings who have been living on the Earth for centuries in secrecy. The aliens have developed a substance named "Gel", which was initially intended to be used as food for their species, but also functions as an addictive substance to humans that results in terrible side-effects and is now being sold as an illegal drug within the underworld. The player takes the role of Detective Hart, a member of the Vice unit who is assigned to investigate the B.E.D.A. Corporation following the disappearance of his partner Reese during a previous case. During his mission, Hart is assisted by his lover and fellow Vice agent Christy, and Sophia, an acquaintance of the two.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>o84PiCvcgdU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cdfeb9a0-e7b9-4851-8afc-972e31a6c58b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74cec258-8508-4763-8a85-cc6c55e604ae.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c80587f5-735b-4928-a3c5-628dc6bb9256.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b3e61c6a-daa8-410a-b01c-85c5ded4e6fb.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90b5d289-ac91-479c-8b21-b618792243eb.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0dec8917-00d4-43c2-b91f-b2a3f7373e2b.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6668b04d-f971-4485-ab08-e1f7c4df0a4e.jpg</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sammy</Publisher>
</game>