<Game>
	<Name>Volguard II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Volguard II is a Shoot-'Em-Up game, published by DB Soft, which was released in Japan in 1985.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/nes/home/578262.htmlCheat: InvincibilityOn the title screen, press Select to change the difficulty level to #2. Now play the game, beat the high score, get a game over and input your name as "NUKENIN?" on the high score table. Press Start and you'll be back on the title screen. For some reason, you must change difficulties or else the code won't work (if you want to keep the same difficulty, the press Select to scroll to it again). So now start a level and pause the game. Now enter at the same time Left, Up, Select &amp; B on the 2nd controller and Right, Down, Select &amp; B on the 1st controller. If done right, you'll be invincible.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1985</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>DB Soft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>26565</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578262-volguard-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/volguard-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/volguard-ii/3030-32737/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nsSCIdg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nsSCIdg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/SMgTxhv.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/G9OnIhM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/nhId13h.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zTxGk3F.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/w4ZFyMd.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MxPq7wZ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IVcZFgi.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/RIq2zfd.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mGoE4ov.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RQtyWQF.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/aBMrUKu.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The player controls a pilot who is trying to defend the Earth from an evil nation's global revolution sometime in the year 20XX. Given the assignment, the overall purpose of the game is to infiltrate their base and take out their defences and army, and then kill their leader. Enemies include a series of battle stations, various groups of aircraft, barriers, cargo planes, mechs, and other assorted enemies. Volguard II was a modified high-mobility combat mecha developed by the distant ancestors.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5c15e79-c85c-412e-a1ce-8f9667a25d45.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63ac7d2a-b2f4-45be-9587-1cfb7d9382cd.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>dB-Soft</Publisher>
</game>