<Game>
	<Name>Wagyan Land 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Wagyan Land 2 plays pretty much identically to the first Wagyan Land. You're a cute green lizard dinosaur thing, and you walk to the right and shoot various syllables out of your mouth, which don't actually hurt enemies. They just remain frozen for a certain period of time, depending on how powered-up your attack is. Once you get four power-ups you become invincible, and you can finally kill the damned things. Which doesn't happen often.So, how can you defeat the bosses with a crappy syllable that can't hurt anybody? Why you play minigames with them, of course! The whole game's pretty frustrating, with the whole "one-hit-and-you-start-the-entire-level-over" thing that's so popular in the world of videogaming. Honestly, it's fun and all, but I don't understand why the game needed to have two sequels.Translation Description:While this isn't iquite/i as polished as a href="http://www.spoony-bard.com/alanmidas/" target="_blank"Midas/a's translation of the first Wagyan Land game (the title screen, for instance, and the GYA syllables that he shoots out are left in Japanese), it's still all in English, and pretty fun to play. You can just pretend those projectiles are magical, uh, runes, or something.Reviewer: Spinner 8http://www.romhacking.net/trans/635/</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Now Production</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>26567</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/579878-wagyan-land-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wagyan-land-2/3030-37274/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7MYQIEO.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7u8OIIz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lJvpWWi.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MS3kCVO.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/olo1ZRb.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/cyFTOT5.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Wagyan Land 2 is an Action game, developed by Now Production and published by Namco, which was released in Japan in 1990.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/362b611b-fef5-4a96-9bf0-f954b6df81f3.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3165b61-5838-4bf6-a0f5-e652817e9c76.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>