<Game>
	<Name>Wall Street Kid (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Wall Street Kid is a simulation game developed and published by SOFEL for the NES platform.Wall Street Kid is loosely based on the Japanese video game series entitled Money Game (released on the Famicom) which include two entries: Money Game and The Money Game II: Kabutochou no Kiseki.Gameplay:At the beginning of the game, the player is told that they had a distant relative, a member of the Benedict family, who recently passed away and left them a massive $600 billion inheritance. In order to receive the entirety of this inheritance though, the player must prove himself a worthy member of the Benedict family. After being given $500,000 in seed money from the relative's lawyer, the player must trade stocks effectively enough in order to make certain large item purchases like a house or yacht, keep his girlfriend extremely well-pampered, and keep himself in peak physical condition as this is the Benedict way of life.If the player fails to complete any of the game's objectives, he loses all access to the inheritance, is effectively disowned from the Benedict family, and the game is over.ObjectivesPurchase a one million dollar mansionPurchase a yacht for your honeymoonGet marriedWin an auction for and purchase a European castle formally belonging to the Benedict familyCheat: View Final PasswordWhen you complete the game, after the ending credits, while the "SOFEL" logo is displayed, press Left + A on Controller 1. You'll get the final password to your ending.Cheat: First Week Password...Enter the following password at the SAVED GAME screen...(NOTE: The characters between the [ ] are the highlighted characters.)</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2170</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563475-wall-street-kid</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/wall-street-kid</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wall-street-kid/3030-13426/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/j4sgRbM.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/J0Buwka.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/PFeNW5U.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/z7S3Eay.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/N6cOxeA.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9ok0T3g.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BB0bMZ3.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VghBCwP.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MRX7i9S.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/UyHddMc.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/SiuVnT1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KPngTbZ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/IcM77Yr.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0qC17vx.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Where life, love and money all depend on how well you play the game. Make billions of dollars when you deal with the giants of Wall Street. Not only do you take risks by playing the stock market, but you must prove you can uphold a high standard of living. If you dream of fame and fortune, this Life Simulation game is your way to the top. You can taste the victory of success, but only if you're strong enough to face the challenge of life. Now, are you ready to deal?</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75caa8b0-e789-4811-9a06-4161ef4a1d39.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34e7db6b-08fc-4c0f-ae33-e9b5ac4ce940.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a41f81ef-0c02-48f8-bd75-33fe8bbea1fe.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/edd8d74e-9fa9-49bf-a997-5dc1fa3ded62.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71fea4d6-973d-47e1-a2be-488ebb701f64.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d5485aa-c493-4d0b-950d-1d40b851baf7.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dedfac66-83b0-4eb9-95fd-f76932d79de2.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sofel</Publisher>
</game>