<Game>
	<Name>Wanpaku Duck Yume Bouken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Bless me bagpipes! When will that thrillseeker, Scrooge McDuck, ever quit? Never one to turn away from adventure, Uncle Scrooge has taken on his greatest challenge - to discover the legendary Five Lost Treasures and become the 'Richest Duck in the World!' Join Scrooge and the DUCKTALES gang: gung-ho flying ace, Launchpad; the nephews, Huey, Dewey and Louie; and little Webby, on their search. Together they must trek through the treacherous Amazon Jungle, down into the diamond mines of Africa, and even to the moon! Are you 'Duck' enough to join them on their adventure? Come along to Duckburg Headquarters and see for yourself!Cheat: Huge time bonusBeat a boss and collect its treasure just as the timer runs out. When it comes time for the time bonus to be collected, the timer wraps around into letters, giving you a whopping $325,000.Cheat: Bad endingComplete the game with exactly zero dollars to unlock the bad ending.Cheat: Bonus StageWhen your score has a 7 as the 10-thousands digit(for example 170,000), call Launchpad to take you back home; he will drop you off at a secret bonus stage.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ToVcSY002Gg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1276</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587253-disneys-ducktales</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BdXeQ2j.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/VRR1kLp.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/J5aNEsW.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/TKSWli5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Tj7KYFw.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/X3473VS.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Ih9pdFJ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1rZiUlo.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Ty0DrdB.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QEDlhOG.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CIWb8W0.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vHVRC5s.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/OJiz4tH.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/Ona5rJ0.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/WEJ214P.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/7BlSog7.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/qLkpmbb.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/UpeE3ya.jpg</fanart6>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/G5azccN.jpg</banner1>
</game>