<Game>
	<Name>Wayne's World (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The purple blobWayne's World puts players into the role of Wayne, from the popular SNL skit about the fictional public access show Wayne's World, and the hit movie based on the skit. In the game, Wayne and his friend Garth are sucked into the Zoltar the Gelatinous Cube arcade machine mentioned in the movie. They must chase down a mysterious purple blob that captured Wayne's blond-haired friend. Released in 1993, this game came out on the  Super Nintendo Entertainment System, Sega Genesis and the Game Boy.Gameplay:Robo Elvis battleWayne's World is a combination of platforming and shooting. Wayne's main weapon is a guitar, which he can strum to attack with sound waves. These waves can be increased by finding amp upgrades in various levels. The player will face several wacky enemies based on the location, such as a man-eating donut in the donut shop or a person with a mohawk at a backstage level. There is a total of five stages with three levels each. Each level ends with Garth getting recaptured by the large purple blob.Cheat: Stage SkipWhen playing, pause and press A, B, A, and Select. You can use B to go to the next stage, or A to go to the normal game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>OkVb8HcWTGk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2771</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587760-waynes-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/waynes-world_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/waynes-world/3030-8565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/9B3xlwR.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eCmMo16.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Qv37a1E.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8w7oQIi.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/HiNgeGU.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gd6xMcq.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/651nIg5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Jc1FMRp.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fkOq0Cz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8OHeucm.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7QzMLis.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/WRI1oLX.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/z6Oyuhf.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>"Wayne's World, Wayne's World! Party time! Excellent! Woo, woo, woo!" It's Friday, it's 10:30 and like usual, Wayne and Garth are presenting their TV show. First they start off by reading a top-10 list of the worst games they recently played at the arcade. Then Wayne accounts on how he and Garth were suddenly sucked into a video game, and Garth was kidnapped by the mysterious Zantar. "Weeuuu, weeuuu, weeuuu!" FLASHBACK, and now you're suddenly in control of Wayne as he must embark upon a quest to save his good pal Garth.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94b13e6d-d7c9-4cc5-a570-f93a8d0ccc63.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43979ae9-e0fe-48ce-abcc-c76b16492b67.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>