<Game>
	<Name>WCW World Championship Wrestling (USA)</Name>
	<plot>WCW: World Championship Wrestling is an isometric  wrestling game of the National Wrestling Alliance. Players can choose to engage in one- or two-player matches as either 1vs1 solo bouts or 2vs2 tag-teams. Upon selecting a mode, players choose their characters from among twelve featured wrestlers from the NWA league. Licensed characters include: Rick Flair ("Nature Boy"), Sting, Lex Luger ("Total Package"), Mike Rotunda, Road Warrior Hawk, Road Warrior Animal, Steve Williams (""Dr. Death"), Kevin Sullivan ("Gamemaster"), Ricky Steamboat ("The Dragon"), Ric Steiner ("Dogface Gremlin"), Eddie Gilbert ("Hotstuff") and Michael P.S. Hayes. Each wrestler has unique abilities not shared by the other wrestlers, including finishing moves and rope toss.Prior to a match, the player is presented with a menu of eight "moves", of which the player chooses four to assign to the points of the directional pad. Once the match starts, the player is only able to use the four moves selected and the rope toss to attack the opponent. Each wrestler can move up, down, left and right inside the wrestling ring, climb the turnstiles at each corner and throw opponents out of the ring (where they will be disqualified if outside for 20 seconds). Each wrestler has a high damage "finisher move" which can only be performed when they are standing in the middle of the ring and the opponent's stamina bar is low.Cheat: Championship Bout as AnimalEnter the following at the password screen on Single 5 Minute Round...</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>FCI|Pony Canyon, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1391</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587761-wcw-world-championship-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/wcw-world-championship-wrestling</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wcw-world-championship-wrestling/3030-775/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/rYIBzX4.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/02fn8dd.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/vZnVn4Z.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LZdmoo3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iPFxgfV.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Dz2BwZp.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ViZBNWB.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8JziA5k.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HtW6uyI.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/IhBKSHw.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nyTAEpQ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aQPqaCO.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/iwm1Y4R.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BC9pAoP.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Challenge the world's greatest wrestlers in the grappling action game that puts you in the toughest competition of all!  Choose which wrestler you want to be or make up your own tag team from top NWA stars including:  "Nature Boy" Ric Flair, Sting, "Total Package" Lex Luger, Ricky "The Dragon" Steamboat, Road Warriors "Hawk" and "Animal," and "Dogface Gremlin" Rick Steiner.  Become your favorite wrestler as you battle it out in the ring! »  Twelve top stars of the NWA »  Pair up your own tag team with any two wrestlers »  1 or 2 player »  Wrestlers are thrown over the ropes and continue fighting out of the ring »  On-screen statistics of each wrestler »  Exciting animated graphics and realistic sound effects</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/27033bea-b9af-42ee-8682-526c41eaa7cc.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc18da24-175b-4f50-9578-0d2ad13d5d35.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f65bec1-be3b-4d03-9ccc-2db8f4894f5c.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26084ebc-92c8-4a4e-a0eb-a14cf670749f.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba71d7f0-9d57-456f-90bf-88ac21b5eec9.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>FCI</Publisher>
</game>