<Game>
	<Name>Wheel of Fortune - Junior Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Wheel of Fortune: Junior Edition is one of a series of NES games based on the famous TV game show. The goal is to solve a word puzzle by guessing letters. The players take turns spinning a wheel that has designated money amounts in most spaces, but can also bankrupt the player in the wheel lands on the wrong space. A player can guess a letter and if that letter is in the puzzle, those spaces are flipped to reveal the letter and the player earns the cash amount specified by the wheel spin, multiplied by the number of occurrences of the letter. Only English consonants can be guessed - the 5 English vowels can be purchased using a player's earnings.This NES edition of the game allows 1, 2, or 3 human players to play against each other. Human players can also elect to play against computer players and at 3 difficulty levels.Since this is the Junior Edition of the franchise, the puzzles are geared to be solvable for a younger audience.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/5/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-3 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1392</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587763-wheel-of-fortune-junior-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/wheel-of-fortune-junior-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wheel-of-fortune-junior-edition/3030-8864/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kKopYDU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/fOy8wa0.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/XmhCnjd.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/O6FOU1h.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/t0XWiAJ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/jgVA1Tj.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XcEo9l7.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vZX7YKc.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IV0JHs9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/yfkBRlX.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MyZiqSP.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/fdNFQEc.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/AHx526J.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/j50d9qT.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/5DiHoAa.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/uG6uD5F.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Now everyone’s favorite TV Game Show is just for kids! It’s got all the excitement of the adult version… everything you see on TV and more, But the puzzles have been created just for the younger player. It’s your turn to be the contestant. Compete against your friends or match wits with the computer. Press the button, hear the theme music, spin the wheel, solve the puzzle and win a fortune, or hit bankrupt and lose it all. There are over 1000 puzzles to keep you guessing, and if you’re stuck you can always buy a vowel. It’s time to play WHEEL OF FORTUNE!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/260435e2-7cc0-4523-a0b8-a57d7cd12454.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/644c3164-cd3b-41cc-ad8a-652b7fb37dcc.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc8d733d-b436-43f0-a845-944de4370eeb.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>