<Game>
	<Name>Where in Time Is Carmen Sandiego (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Where in Time is Carmen Sandiego is an educational adventure game from Broderbund Software and the sequel to their 1988 computer game Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego. In the game, the player uses a variety of clues linking a time and a place along with hints regarding the criminal's physical characteristics or preferences from people in each time period in order to narrow down on a single suspect and catch them before you run out of usable hours on a time machine called the Chronoskimmer.Konami ported a version of the game over to the Nintendo Entertainment System in 1991. A special copy of the New American Desk Encyclopedia including Konami game advertisements was included with the game to help players make sense of the various clues, time periods, and locations throughout the game.The game was later ported to the SNES and the Sega Genesis by Hi Tech Expressions and Electronic Arts respectively.A television game show loosely based on the game also titled Where in Time is Carmen Sandiego? aired from 1996 to 1998 on PBS.When released, the NES version was awarded the following scores from Electronic Gaming Monthly: 5,7,5,6 saying, "a very interesting and sometimes educational quest".Cheat: Alternate start pontGo to the Boiler Room and enter the door marked "CREDITS". Press and hold Right, then press A, A, A, B, A, Start, A, Select, A, Select, A, Start, A, B, A, A. "ERIK T. KISS" will appear on the screen to confirm correct code entry. Now go to the Personnel Apartment and your starting point will have changed from San Francisco to Vancouver.Cheat: PasswordsYou must enter your name as AdamL for these passwords to work:</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1991</releasedate>
	<Developer>Konami Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2178</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587766-where-in-time-is-carmen-sandiego</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/where-in-time-is-carmen-sandiego</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/where-in-time-is-carmen-sandiego/3030-13237/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/P7vzRUX.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/P7vzRUX.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9ccrke6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Hv7GFEg.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/EEqZ0Fy.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xhlg5Bi.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NABdJaD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/WLB7Ynb.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/16m6WfC.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9q6b6Bh.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JOiy0o5.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/wudVJNL.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VeFrODc.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Carmen Sandiego and her gang are loose once again, and it is the players job to capture her! This time round the player not only has to find where she is, but also when she is. Traveling to various locations, they need to assemble clues by questioning witnesses and searching locations to close in and capture Carmen Sandiego. Included with the game is The New America Desk Encyclopedia to help make clues more meaningful .</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb033e39-2da3-4cff-9d64-75819581f611.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/185c3c1b-effe-469a-8322-fef6be2249ac.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<genre>Adventure; Education</genre>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>