<Game>
	<Name>Widget (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Widget is a game about a perpetually smiling purple alien who must save earth from a gang of alien invaders. The action consists of side scrolling jumping and shooting. However, Widget has the capacity to transform into a variety of other creatures and objects ("widgets") which have application in different situations. These alternate widget forms include a cannon, a mouse, a rock-man, a bird-man, and a dolphin. Transforming uses up magic points which must be replenished. Widget also communicates with a helper named Mega Brain via a wristwatch device.Cheat: Level PasswordsSince you could select which level you want after the first excluding the final level, I will list these by what Transformation you will have because you can't beat the levels in order. Which ever password you use, it will also include all of the previous fomations. So for example, if you use the password for Rock-Man Widget, you will also have Bird-Man Widget and Mouse Widget. Same with the others. I also included the numbers before to keep them in order.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>-jJ7YwAP4ro</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2182</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587769-widget</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/widget</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/widget/3030-19468/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/X5RDDh7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/5yqIM8X.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Ki9JAxF.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/F0Eo4fr.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/95pojUG.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ijXwFnB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8y1ZZSP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VMUXSfQ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Kbko7KR.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/f9lyqhx.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FHb7UX3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Gjk64hv.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cAUWsDv.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A Widget for all troubles! When Widget accidentally sends himself to Earth, he finds a whole planet-full of problems. Luckily, he can transform into many different shapes and fight the criminals who are trying to destroy Earth. As a Cannon, a Bird, a Dolphin, and more, Widget can tackle these fiends and finally face his own corrupt twin. Now join in the most dangerous, action-packed adventure a young Widget has ever faced!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ddaab27e-2d05-4162-bc5c-3b2da6dae2b8.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/715e8e91-6a1a-4a07-be0a-f5034839b93f.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>