<Game>
	<Name>World Class Track Meet (USA) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>This is a track and field game for up to six players requiring the Power Pad. Only a maximum of  two players can play together on the pad at the same time. There are several events: 100m dash, long jump, 110m hurdles and the triple jump. When you beat the computer in the single player mode, you move on to a faster opponent. The AI opponents are (slowest to fastest): Turtle, Bear, Horse, Rabbit, Bobcat and Cheetah. With each defeated opponent, you earn a medal or a trophy. The harder the opponent, the better the award.Olympics is a 1-6 player event in which you will do all four events in a row. At the end, the computer will show you a total score. There is one player at a time in the jumping events and two at the same time (for two or more human players) in running events.This game was sold as a pack-in cart with the Power Pad accessory, and as a 3-in-1 cartridge with Duck Hunt and Super Mario Bros.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>21564</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587781-stadium-events</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/world-class-track-meet</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/stadium-events/3030-7309/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TaXfZI7.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9Y8aaL1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LAuMVq3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SruWjMQ.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MSedKmi.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/goLZJ2b.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0eDCjVg.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ykn2NwK.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/lVix47V.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/R6t25ca.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/jdmPtEb.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vS4P5eA.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Re-release of Stadium Events, which turns your home into an exciting stadium, dares you to increase your physical ability and better your athletic record. You'll compete against a runner in the Tournament Mode, and in 4 events for a total score in the Olympic Mode. The top 6 winners' names and their scores will appear on the electronic billboard. The top 3 winners will stand on the winners platform!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cb9f27c-cb7f-4ef3-9eaa-f82da840176a.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35b1352a-758e-4792-92df-90dc9dafb81f.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>