<Game>
	<Name>Yoshi's Cookie (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yoshi's Cookie was originally released in April 28, 1992 for the Nintendo Entertainment System. Initially developed by  Nintendo R&amp;D1 and published by  Nintendo, the game has been released in a variety of forms and versions since its original release. The ports of the game include the  Game Boy version (which changes little from the NES version), a  SNES version (which reskinned the game to reference  Super Mario World more frequently), and inclusion in a Japan-only compilation for the  GameCube titled Nintendo Puzzle Collection.The game included on Nintendo Puzzle Collection is technically an enhanced port of Yoshi's Cookie. There are added things, however, such as upgraded graphics and sound. Other than that, the game is completely identical to the  Super Nintendo Entertainment System version of the game).Gameplay:The game is made up of a square grid, broken up into 25 to 49 sections (5 x 5 or 7 x 7) depending on the version. Cookies of various decorations fill in the entire grid. The player manipulates entire rows either horizontally or vertically to try to match cookies that are alike. Once a row is filled with cookies of the same design, their point count increases by one and the row is wiped off of the screen.The multiplayer portion of this game has two of the cookie grids side by side, with a different player controlling each grid while different power-ups cycle on the screen. Once a player correctly aligns a row of cookies, the power up on the screen at that time is put upon the opposing player. This could range from losing five points to scrambling the cookies on their grid.Cheat: Higher Levels (Over 10)In the options, turn off the music, set the game to high speed and on Round 10. After that, hold Up on the D-Pad and press Select. The Round will then be at ''11.'' Keep pressing Select to make the round go higher.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/5/1993</releasedate>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>Jq30DedFRA0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1400</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587793-yoshis-cookie</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/yoshis-cookie</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yoshis-cookie/3030-16966/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xstnOxn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/eMBOLXE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/gguuv6m.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/e4oXVpJ.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bZgp1UF.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uCVVPP1.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XdYtvxF.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/aPTstd6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6ieErGJ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TABuDg7.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nu9gMF6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NkWDFFo.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sqsNt5g.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/GKCMSrU.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/39aYZGP.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Cookie chaos for Mario and Yoshi! Mario and Yoshi are filling in at the Cookie Factory and they need your help! Fresh baked cookies roll out of the ovens. It's up to Mario to sort and stack 'em before they pile too high! Line up a row of the same kind of cookies either vertically or horizontally, and they vanish! Clear the screens to move on to a new level of cookie chaos. Yoshi appears from time to time to stir things up. Play for a high score or head-to-head against a friend. The mouth-watering madness doesn't let up! And be sure to keep some cookies close by, 'cause you'll get the munchies during this lip-smacking good time!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/277dca53-7595-4623-b124-34b6883543d5.png</banner2>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b58509aa-f738-49e3-aff2-f18b8e8cbb4e.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/928dad49-3f6c-40ab-b842-c77a380b27cc.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<genre>Puzzle; Strategy</genre>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>