<Game>
	<Name>Youkai Douchuuki (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Youkai Douchuuki is an Action game, developed by Now Production and published by Namco,which was released in Japan in 1988.Cheat: Test ModePress and hold Up, A &amp; B on the 2nd controller and press Reset. If done right, the test mode should appear.Cheat: Unlock The EndingsThere are 6 possible endings in this game. Finish the last stage with the following Pious Points and you'll get one of six endings. In addition, press A during the credits to see the princess dancing again. Bear in mind that you can only increase your Piousness in temples before the last level and killing enemies or picking money in the last level reduces your Pious Score.Cheat: Change Title GraphicsHold Select and Reset the console. The game title will change from it's normal Japanese characters ("Youkai Douchuuki", which means "Demon Travel Journal") to some more ("Youen Douchuuki", which means "Erotic Travel Journal").</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Now Production</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>CMWEaSm-KvI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26403</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578594-youkai-douchuuki</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shadow-land/3030-39865/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/T65gHFt.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UWjeNXO.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iIslHC9.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7oqQ1mp.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/w9DhA8d.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/4f2rB6g.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/BC8ySQj.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DbLa2YU.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uLjv5iq.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/l7SdfPz.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LMDJclS.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The player controls a boy named Tarosuke, who travels through "Jigoku" (the Japanese concept of Hell) fighting off "yokai" (mythical Japanese monsters) on his way to his final fate, as determined by Buddha. He destroys his enemies by firing small Ki bullets, which can be charged to increase their power; however, if overcharged, he is left unable to move or fight for a few seconds. During boss battles, Tarosuke kneels at a shrine to Buddha and prays, summoning "Monmotaro" (not to be confused with "Momotarō"), a spirit which floats in the air and drops energy balls on the boss and any lackeys he has. Once the boss is defeated, Tarosuke goes to the next stage.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fe5bc82-5d60-4e95-bea9-4da4c8ed904c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab4a6e9c-445c-4ade-aaa5-6de24925f7d9.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>