<Game>
	<Name>Ys (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Woo-hoo! This is a most excellent translation of a most excellent game. If you haven't tried it yet, Ys play very much similar to Zelda, but is twice as fun and the dialogue is 10 times more engrossing. And it's pretty challenging, too! This is definitely the version of Ys to get, unless you happen to read Japanese or own a Turbo Duo. Heh.Translation Description:Makoknight and Co. did an excellent job with the translation; this is truly what I'd call a flawless script. It's much truer to the Ys saga than the Sega Translation was, and much more grammatically correct. So, what are you waiting for? Find the ROM, download the patch, and have a blast!Reviewer: wraithhttp://www.romhacking.net/trans/238/</plot>
	<releasedate>11/5/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Advance Communication Company</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>zyViKqIJLvw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23300</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/578632-ys</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Wdnsl6h.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lv1X22D.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5AtVyBJ.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1PeEni0.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nxOdSD8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1RPmeRU.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/M46nkWy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FHz70Bg.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fftZvR8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/YhTGOkm.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/5IiuKjk.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/OUoSSWj.gif</banner1>
	<Notes>In this game, the player takes the role of Adol Christin, a red-haired adventurer and expert swordsman. One day he encounter a fortune teller who sends him on a quest to find information about the six books of Ys. It appears that there was once an ancient land called Ys, whose secret was sealed in those six books. Before long Adol learns that the six books were all stolen by the evil wizard Dark Fact (Dulk Dekt in the Sega Master System version, Malificus in the English-language computer versions). It is Adol's task to defeat the villain and discover the secret of Ys! Ys is an action role-playing game with its own trademark combat system: instead of pressing the "attack" button, the protagonist simply runs into the enemies he encounters. More damage is inflicted upon the enemies if Adol charges at them from the back or from the sides - a head-to-head collision might result in the hero's death if the monster is stronger than him. The player gains gold and experience points for defeating foes; once enough experience has been accumulated, Adol levels up and becomes stronger. The hero can buy and equip swords, armor, shields, and other accessories.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>qx2hDGpVMco</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/989b8def-e25a-4b6c-8592-24cf42f21ab9.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8dac7e31-6d1a-4e43-b959-bedd776f47d5.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/526bf811-f191-432c-8250-249cd2564b4b.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Victor Musical Industries</Publisher>
</game>