<Game>
	<Name>Yume Penguin Monogatari (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Title Screen Yume Penguin Monogatari is a game developed by  Konami for the  Famicom and released in 1991. The story revolves around a penguin named  Penta who is dumped by his girlfriend Penko because he is too fat. She then gets a new boyfriend called Genji. The player must then play as Penta in a quest to loose weight to get back together with Penko. He does this by drinking diet soda and avoiding enemies which Genji has sent after Penta to force-feed him.It is believed that Penta is really  Pentarou, a character from other Konami games.Gameplay         The gameplay is a mix of platforming and shooting. Instead of a life-bar, you have a fitness-meter. This meter must be filled to a certain point marked by a broken heart, before each level is completed. Otherwise the level is restarted. To fill this meter, Penta has to collect diet soda. The meter goes down if Penta is hit by enemies or otherwise eats unhealthy food. There are six levels in the game. Three platforming levels, and three side-scrolling shooter stages. The goal is the same in all levels, to collect diet soda and fill the meter while avoiding enemies. The seventh level is the last boss, Genji, which is also a shooter level, but this time view from the rear.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>g9lfRs48lGE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26404</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/570532-yume-penguin-monogatari</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/yume-penguin-monogatari</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yume-penguin-monogatari/3030-9867/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/esmVNMB.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iI1EZmm.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SrC8cpB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pMOguUI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/bNgiH8H.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9jjfiof.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7gi7oVz.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EnCj7ss.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fMKDDgk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ATWeLMh.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/oixsT4B.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JeAiyrX.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Penta, a cute blue penguin, has a tragic flaw - he really enjoys eating. As a result, his girlfriend Penko left him for another fashionable penguin called Ginji because, she thinks, he has become too chubby for her liking. And yet, she decides to give him a second chance - if he manages to lose all this weight and keep it off, then she will give all her love and attention to him. But the covetous Ginji doesn't share the same sentiments and will do everything in his power to stop the poor flightless seabird before he slims down.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9d668f9b-30b5-4797-b84b-c860c22c9b48.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b583f40-0a04-4df9-a98f-63e8f9077d0d.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>4.75</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>