<Game>
	<Name>Zelda no Densetsu 1 - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to the Legend of Zelda. Where the only sound you'll hear is your own heart pounding as you race through forests, lakes, mountains and dungeonous mazes in an attempt to restore peace to the land of Hyrule. Along the way you'll be challenged by Tektites, Wizzrobes and an endless array of ruthless creatures who'll stop at nothing to prevent you from finding the lost fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom. But don't despair. With a little luck and a lot of courage, you'll conquer your adversaries, unite the Triforce fragments and unravel the mystery of the Legend of Zelda.Cheat: How to bring up The Secret Save ScreenFor this code you need Two Controllers. On controller 1 Press start. On controller 2 Press Up and A at the same time. This will bring up The Secret Save Menu. So now you don't have to die to save.Cheat: Entrance to the Second QuestAt the name entry screen enter Cheat: Automatic health restorationWhen your health gauge is low, visit a lake of a Great Fairy to restore your life. When you approach the lake, your health will slowly fill. While your health is being restored, press start to enter the item selection subscreen, and your health will continue to fill. Using a controller in port 2, press Up + A to return to the save menu. Select SAVE, and load your character's file. Once loaded, instead of remaining at the default of 3 filled heart containers, Link will have his health fully restored at the start.Cheat: Fewer enemiesKill all the enemies except for one in a particular screen, and next time you go through there will only be that one enemy there, instead of them all coming back.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/8/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>W0RmGNrNhHE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19053</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/563433-the-legend-of-zelda</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7pvYURZ.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/q5pzoS7.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zScDooY.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XBgC03f.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jyiB5p6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/aThJBKs.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mNtYmZ9.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7V7o3IF.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GykWLNt.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5gBFqM9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/V2oua6e.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>