<Game>
	<Name>Zoda's Revenge - StarTropics II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Zoda's Revenge: Star Tropics II is the 1994 sequel to the original StarTropics. Like the first game, it was developed for the NES. It was also one of the very last games released for the platform. The game has since seen rerelease via the Wii's Virtual Console service.Story: Mike Jones, hero of the original StarTropics, has returned home to Seattle along with his uncle. While his uncle is attempting to decipher the text in a mysterious book, Mica, princess of Argonia, contacts Mike telepathically with a message that helps Mike solve the puzzle.However, as soon as Mike figures out the answer and reads from the book, the text transports him through time and space to the prehistoric era. In order to return home, Mike must jump from one period of history to another to locate mysterious Tetrads. However, Zoda, the antagonist of Mike's previous adventure, is back and hunting for the Tetrads as well.Gameplay:As in the original StarTropics, gameplay in Zoda's Revenge is split between two primary modes. In the game's overworld sections, the player, as Mike, must talk to NPCs to gather clues and items to access the game's dungeons levels and other secrets. In the dungeons, the game takes on an overhead perspective, with Mike defeating enemies and hopping on tiles to trigger doors and find items and power-ups.Instead of a yo-yo, this time around, Mike earns a series of progressively powerful weapons as he travels through time, ranging from a stone axe to a dagger and swords. He also learns to use psychic attacks.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>37q0VybbpFA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1278</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/nes/587654-zodas-revenge-star-tropics-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/nes/zodas-revenge-star-tropics-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zodas-revenge-star-tropics-ii/3030-17335/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WPjzEMg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SDeKrIk.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/qKi3f6P.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Wsch3dV.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KGBdIot.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/rk0C1te.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gvVn3MW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DsspLXU.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kH3Ix1s.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lnC0WEW.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/M0yTljo.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HwB6oNf.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/qiazHV0.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/30rOe3h.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Stop Zoda's revenge and break the code! Intrepid adventurer Mike Jones, just back from the South Pacific, is off on a new journey through time and space. Mike's mission: to save seven mystic Tetrads while he faces the avengers of his foiled foe, the evil Zoda! Now three alien clones are hot on his trail through time! Unfold nine new chapters of adventures to decipher codes, solve mysteries and battle dragons with heroes of days gone by. Mike won't stop until the Tetrads are found and the Zodas are history!  - Wind your way through more than a dozen action-packed stages in eight settings! - Save your progress and continue your time travels with the battery-backed memory!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7cf5638-3e94-4a98-9109-139f47ece01d.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5e857a1-cc9a-490b-abc7-f28de6228aa4.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46b7d088-8e78-4dda-a7ca-8f92d9fc07aa.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2ac72a35-a69c-4d21-b00a-02522da049be.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/969d011e-5918-4912-9aa0-8db83932f746.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f8ecdb0-4f8a-4e35-98fd-f45af96c27d9.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>