<Game>
	<Name>After Burner (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:After Burner, is an arcade flight sim/shooter, developed by SEGA and first released in 1987 in Japanese Arcades. It was designed by legendary Sega game developer Yu Suzuki. It was ported onto many systems, including Sega's own Sega Master System just a few months after the Arcade launch, but most of them weren't able to match the original Arcade version's visceral speed and graphical/sound quality.It is the first game among a series of franchise sequels such as After Burner II, After Burner III and the 2006 release of After Burner Climax which ran on the then newly developed SEGA Lindbergh arcade hardware. After Burner II was re-released in 2004 for the Playstation 2, in the SEGA AGES 2500 series of budget anniversary re-releases.After Burner Arcade MachineIn After Burner the player controls a F-14 Tomcat, a type of jet, and the object of the game is simply to shoot down other enemy jets while evading their return fire with deft maneuvers. The player-controlled Tomcat is equipped with a machine gun and a small number of missiles as a secondary weapon which replenishes after each completed stage.The original After Burner machine is a rarity, exclusively available in the Japanese Arcades. It was controlled with a simulating flight stick, with buttons that controlled the cannon and missile weapons. Movement such as dropping/gaining altitude and barrelrolling was also perfomed by movements with the flight stick.The arcade version also featured a deluxe cabinet, which rotated according to the player's movements (much like Space Harrier and Galaxy Force). This was featured in the arcade scene of the 1991 hit movie Terminator 2: Judgement Day, where it was being played by a teenage John Connor.Cheat: Blind SpotsIn some levels of After Burner you can hold the upper-left portion of the control pad/joystick and enemy fighters will miss you even when they get the radar lock. This is very useful for avoidingbig dog fights.Cheat: Blind Spots*NOTE* This trick does not help on enemy fortresses.Cheat: ContinueWhen you lose all your lives, and the Game Over screen appears, press Button 1 and 2 at the same time, to continue where you left off.  This works only twice, and up to the 8th level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ExzchhbgqQE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1613</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588024-after-burner</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/after-burner</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/after-burner/3030-3629/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/1613-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/1613-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/19107-after-burner-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49344-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen-2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49345-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-shooting-down-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49346-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-zero-g.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49347-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49348-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-crash-and-burn.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49349-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen-3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49350-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-fire.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49351-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-taking-off.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128955-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-take-off-from-carrier.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128956-after-burner-sega-master-system-screenshot-enemy-fighter-shot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/1613-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/1613-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/1613-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BIemXhC.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/1613.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You're a Navy Air Captain. At your control is the most advanced fighter jet ever to set the sky on fire! You supply the skill, reflexes, and guts. Your F-14 Thunder Cat gives you Mach 2+ speeds, unlimited firepower and a state-of-the-art battle computer which targets your enemies for destruction. Fire guided missiles, then blast away with your Vulcan cannon. Roll your F-14 left and right! Enemy missiles slide under your wings. Your afterburners roar as you dive for the wave tops! In this sky battle you're outnumbered. But that's O.K. When it comes to flying the unfriendly skies, you're the one they call "The Ace."</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3457e709-0d90-4ad1-beec-329932ac8a83.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2063fb15-1d2a-4659-8852-41b2b8802584.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/17ba390b-8b6f-4d17-820a-6c00d57269ea.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57306912-d79c-486c-956a-fec38bc67272.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/372f9151-416c-4a3a-90d4-f9c6b5c1cf99.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/05eaf0cb-852c-4dbd-9213-94950ced1d6a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e212850-0f8b-4b4a-9669-5127596dda9e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4e4a456d-90f7-4e61-aff2-886ff4d1ea2f.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>