<Game>
	<Name>Alex Kidd - The Lost Stars (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Alex Kidd: The Lost Stars (&#12450;&#12524;&#12483;&#12463;&#12473;&#12461;&#12483;&#12489; &#12470;&#12539;&#12525;&#12473;&#12488;&#12473;&#12479;&#12540;&#12474;) is the second game in the Alex Kidd series. It is a platform game in which the characters are searching for the twelve zodiac signs. The game appeared on the Sega Master System and also in the arcades. The two versions are very similar, although the arcade version features superior graphics and a two-player co-operative mode. The arcade release came first, a mere month after the release of Alex Kidd in Miracle World. The Master System port came later, with the Wii Shop release coming in 2009.Gameplay:Alex Kidd: The Lost Stars features Alex Kidd (and Stella, if playing the Arcade version in multiplayer) searching for the twelve star signs of the Aries Constellation, which were stolen by Ziggurat. Ziggurat previously tried to capture them some 5,000 years ago but was stopped by Alex Kidd. Now, you have to go through twelve levels (and then go through them again...) to save Miracle World.There are seven levels in the game. At the end of the seventh level, you are teleported back to the first level and must redo the six levels again; this time facing different or a greater amount of enemies than before. Items around the levels include a 'J' block which allows Alex to jump higher, 'S' which replenishes arrows, and 'SP' which replenishes time. If time runs out, Alex loses a life and must start over from the nearest check point.Stages:The game features seven stages which Alex Kidd must complete before facing Ziggurat.Aries &amp; LibraThe first stage features a whimsical setting. Packs of cards and small dogs challenge Alex Kidd in this stage.Taurus &amp; ScorpioThe second stage of the game is set in a futuristic environment. Laser beams, hand rails and holes are just some of the obstacles facing the player.Gemini &amp; SagittariusA horror themed level. Alex Kidd must navigate past zombies, giant killer marrows and, strangely enough, naked boys with sunglasses, to reach the end.Cancer &amp; CapricornThe game's first and only underwater stage. Features dangerous jellyfish and squid.Leo &amp; AquariusA somewhat Jurassic-themed stage. A huge dinosaur head set piece features towards the end, as well as a short balloon ride obstacle.Virgo &amp; PiscesA lava level makes up the penultimate stage in the game. Various strange green enemies try to stop Alex Kidd.ZigguratThe final stage. Alex Kidd must navigate the platforms of this space-themed level before he reaches Ziggurat and finally saves Miracle World.Multiplayer:The Arcade version of Alex Kidd: The Lost Stars features a two-player co-operative multiplayer mode. The second player controls a female counterpart to Alex Kidd named Stella. The multiplayer mode did not make the transition to the Master System.Release datesAlex Kidd: The Lost Stars was originally released in the Arcade in 1986. The game was ported to the Sega Master System in 1988. The Master System version was later ported to the Wii Virtual Console on March 9, 2009 (in North America) and on April 17, 2009 (in PAL regions).</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>sU226PphCxk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5498</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588025-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/alex-kidd-the-lost-stars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alex-kidd-the-lost-stars/3030-16061/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5498-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5498-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89314-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37966-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37967-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-dog.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37968-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-killer.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37969-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-monorail.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37970-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-oh-you.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37971-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-alex.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37972-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-bluehead.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37973-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-look.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37974-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-alex.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37975-alex-kidd-the-lost-stars-sega-master-system-screenshot-look.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5498-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5498-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AMGUGrb.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The Kidd is back! It's Alex, the little Prince with big ears and unlimited courage. When danger threatens the Miracle World of Aries, Alex Kidd is there to meet any challenge. This time, the evil Jigaratt has stolen the stars from the Aries constellation. The skies above the city of Radactian are now cold and dark. Only someone of royal blood can get them back ... and that's the Kidd! Join Alex in fourteen rounds of adventure to worlds where anything is possible! You have legs that jump like steel springs and magical cloud shot to stop the enemy. But the key to getting the stars back is strategy. Are you good enough to beat Jigaratt?</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e064aa6-5f79-459c-a136-15c186af08ed.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/630bae7a-482d-43d9-81af-c144daa084ca.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4dc784ce-f0ef-4f64-ab57-e8adaea3c9c7.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f1f6e766-d912-49a7-981e-2e71bfe0f557.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f1e8670a-ffef-4e77-8d08-566886f9538d.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e5d694e-3a51-47e0-92bd-4a299e6d1c03.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bccaeef5-a556-4015-87d1-d6a89e4aa92c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7feb25fc-ffe0-4957-b58c-027d86c48aac.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>