<Game>
	<Name>Alex Kidd - High-Tech World (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Alex Kidd: High Tech World is a side-scrolling adventure/platformer for the Sega Master System. It is heavily based on Anmitsu Hime, a tie-in game for an unrelated Japanese manga and anime TV show. Alex Kidd: High Tech World is a modified version of Anmitsu Hime. The game's original female protagonist, the princess Anmitsu Hime, was replaced with Sega's male mascot Alex Kidd, as part of the Alex Kidd franchise.Plot:A new arcade - the titular High Tech World - has just opened near Alex Kidd's castle home. He wants to go play some Sega games, but the only map has been torn to pieces! He will need to hurry if he is to make it before closing time!Gameplay:The game's levels alternate between two distinct styles of play:AdventureThe castle and town (levels 1 and 3) are large, free-roaming areas with emphasis on exploration and puzzle solving. Some events occur according to the in-game clock which normally runs in real-time, but jumps ahead by 5 minutes every time Alex opens a door. If the clock reaches 5pm, the arcade closes and the game is over.PlatformingThe more civilized areas of the world are connected by dangerous backwoods paths (levels 2 and 4) which Alex must traverse while under constant attack by ninjas. These sections are more traditional and straightforward in design - Alex can jump and shoot projectiles, and the goal is simply to make it from one side of the screen to the other. Any money collected in level 2 can be spent on items in the following adventure area. The clock continues to run down in real-time.Cheat: Exit Castle at 11:55Enter this case-sensitive code, case sensitive to leave the castle at 11:55:Cheat: Exit Castle at 11:55To start the game with all the Map Pieces, enter this code (case-sensitive):Cheat: Get Extra GPShoot the yellow clouds on the Ninja sections five times to reveal boxes worth 200 GP</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>uSDaLK-su48</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5536</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588026-alex-kidd-high-tech-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/alex-kidd-high-tech-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alex-kidd-high-tech-world/3030-7108/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5536-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5536-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/153934-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37470-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37471-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37475-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37483-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-mama.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37484-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37485-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-alex.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37486-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-name.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37487-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-don.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37488-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-out.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37489-alex-kidd-high-tech-world-sega-master-system-screenshot-alex.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5536-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5536-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5ZBsJ6i.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Get ready to join the Kidd in his third great Sega adventure! Being the Crown Prince of Planet Aries is never easy. On top of being a galactic hero, you have to deal with parents, teachers and palace retainers! But you're a Kidd at heart, and you just have to go to the new High Tech World video arcade to play the newest Sega games! The problem is, the map to the arcade has been torn up into eight pieces and hidden in the castle. As you look for the pieces you'll discover just how weird life in a castle can be! If you find them, you'll have to fight your way through a forest filled with blue Ninjas. Survive this ordeal and you'll have to find a travel pass in the village to make it over the border! It's a game of wits, intrigue, action and excitement. There's even a PASSWORD so you can save games. Survive all the obstacles and you'll play in the hottest arcade in the land. But if you don't get there before the 5:00 closing time, you'll be left out in the cold! Better hurry!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5760b2f-11e0-4b74-8c85-4218ac907b82.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc9012bf-61c8-4e1f-b473-1fab2140032b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a34d51b-fcb7-4b92-81cc-70a1dc0b7a43.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/930467f6-5778-446e-9d3b-eaaff4700c1c.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f62054ee-8688-4d7a-965b-9914be66bce7.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b3d97bf6-37c7-4140-b334-4d47e40a32d0.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3778cdc5-8e5b-4d8a-b1d4-685b45f056ef.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>