<Game>
	<Name>American Baseball (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Ever wanted to play in the big leagues?Now is your chance.Step up to the plate with Sega's Reggie Jackson Baseball.It's so real you'll be grabbing for the hotdogs as you hammer 'em out of the ball park!Play against the computer or with a friend.Take your pick of twenty-six American or National City teams.You can choose a mini two-out-of-three tournament, go for the Series or test your batting skills in the Home Run contest.Reggie Jackson Baseball gives you the power to select your pitchers and pitches, to bat high and low, to lead off or try to steal your way around the bases.Is there a man leading off on second?fake a pitch and catch him off base.Move fast and snatch a ground ball from the infield for a double play!When the game is over, you'll get tips from Reggie himself.Go far enough and win the Series!It's baseball action like you've never seen before, only from Sega.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>gXxr6HQPfTU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2688</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588130-reggie-jackson-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2688-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2688-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/4/gfs_3853_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/4/gfs_3853_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/a/4/gfs_3853_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/b/4/gfs_3853_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/4/gfs_3853_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/5/9/gfs_3853_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/9/gfs_3853_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/9/gfs_3853_2_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/2/9/gfs_3853_2_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/9/9/gfs_3853_2_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Reggie Jackson Baseball (American Baseball in Japan and PAL countries) is, as the name implies, a simulation of USA's most beloved sports: baseball. There are four modes in the game: Exhibition, Tournament, Watch Mode, and finally a Home Run Contest. In the Watch Mode the computer just plays against itself, and in Tournament Mode you compete against the computer. The other two modes can be played against computer or a human opponent as well. You can choose Major League Baseball teams in all of those modes. During the game, the player controls the pitcher and the batter from a third-person view; the view changes to top-down after a strike by a batter, so that the player can view a large part of the field. Events such as injuries or cheerleader performances are graphically shown in the game.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5af0ce04-a7b0-45c1-bc73-a7f7d8502b40.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9c51082-1575-4c14-ad06-5891bd59b905.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ee8d922-35d3-4729-b44c-bcf0b4710938.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>