<Game>
	<Name>Asterix and the Secret Mission (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>The druid Getafix is out of magic potion, and Ast?rix and Obelix are set out on a secret mission: to find the necessary herbs, so he can brew the potion again.In this side-scrolling action game, the player can choose to play either Ast?rix or Obelix at the start of each one of the six levels. Although the main setting of each level is the same to both characters (forests, caves, deserts, underwater stages, waterfalls and such) the level design for each one may vary. In two player mode (Master System version), players will take turns playing as Ast?rix and Obelix. Both characters jump (by pressing button 2), punch enemies and break blocks (by pressing button 1). Ast?rix can run can run (by pressing and holding button 1 while moving) and double jump (by pressing 2 in the middle of a jump). Ob?lix is stronger and can break several bricks in a row when jumping over them (pressing 1 while jumping), and can also slide down hills (by pressing down at them).Ast?rix can get some potions (thrown by pressing up and 1), which can break rocks, kill or shrink enemies. Obelix can get miniature menhirs which can be thrown (by pressing up and 1) against enemies. Both characters can also get bones throughout the game, granting access to bonus stages where the player controls Dogmatix. Some levels also involve minor puzzle solving, like pushing switches or moving rock blocks.http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/astrix-and-the-secret-missionCheat: Infinite LivesOn the first level, break the rocks and use the water spout to reach the cloud platforms. Go across to find an extra life, go back so where the extra life was is off the screen. Return back to where the extra life was and it will re-appear. Do this until you have 9 lives (the maximum). You can also do it on other levels.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>uajZNDVUV0Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2694</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/581785-asterix-and-the-secret-mission</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/astrix-and-the-secret-mission</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/asterix-and-the-secret-mission/3030-16284/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2694-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2694-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/238529-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213503-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213504-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213505-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213506-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213507-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213508-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213509-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213510-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213511-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213512-asterix-and-the-secret-mission-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2694-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Xhl8Jut.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The druid Getafix is out of magic potion, and Astérix and Obelix are set out on a secret mission: to find the necessary herbs, so he can brew the potion again. In this side-scrolling action game, the player can choose to play either Astérix or Obelix at the start of each one of the six levels. Although the main setting of each level is the same to both characters (forests, caves, deserts, underwater stages, waterfalls and such) the level design for each one may vary. In two player mode (Master System version), players will take turns playing as Astérix and Obelix. Both characters jump (by pressing button 2), punch enemies and break blocks (by pressing button 1). Astérix can run can run (by pressing and holding button 1 while moving) and double jump (by pressing 2 in the middle of a jump). Obélix is stronger and can break several bricks in a row when jumping over them (pressing 1 while jumping), and can also slide down hills (by pressing down at them). Astérix can get some potions (thrown by pressing up and 1), which can break rocks, kill or shrink enemies. Obelix can get miniature menhirs which can be thrown (by pressing up and 1) against enemies. Both characters can also get bones throughout the game, granting access to bonus stages where the player controls Dogmatix. Some levels also involve minor puzzle solving, like pushing switches or moving rock blocks.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Ku8ux0DNKW8?list=SRasterix-and-the-secret-mission-game-gear</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ddbb0988-a68a-474a-80aa-a5a53cda0718.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41940ec4-1282-4ad8-b635-f1be40518dba.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5aa80f38-f260-4e47-8fc8-f8f9cec7b96b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/419c43f3-b54a-4c59-8c70-171e93f6d748.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c89fdb0-94d1-420e-ac52-66e59399cd15.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>