<Game>
	<Name>Aztec Adventure - The Golden Road to Paradise (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Nazca '88: The Golden Road to Paradise is an action game where the player assumes the role of an adventurer named Ni&#241;o as he attempts to find a lost paradise somewhere in Peru. Though Nazca features heavily in the game (especially the famous Nazca Lines) the Western releases place the game far further North in Central America, in the ancient territory of the Aztecs.The game plays as a top-down perspective, as Ni&#241;o races to beat three rival adventurers (which are controlled by the CPU) to the target. This involves crossing through deserts, jungles, marshes and ruins, destroying various enemies on the way with found weapons. The player can also hire computer-controlled helpers, by throwing money bags at certain enemies, who will assist them in their battles and increase the player character's projectile weapon strength.Cheat: Level SelectPress Up five times after the Aztec Adventure scroll closes on the title screen. Press Right three times after Nino tosses money at the other characters. Press Left, Down after all characters are walking toward the left side of the screen. Nino's face will appear next to the Aztec Adventure scroll to confirm correct code entry. Use the D-pad to change the level numbers appearing below the face. Cheat: Level SelectPress Start during game play. Press Left, then Right twenty times after the faces appear. Nino's face will appear to the right of the rainbow to confirm correct code entry. Use the D-pad to change the numbers appearing above the face to select a sound, then press 1. To resume game play, select sound 00 and press 2.  </plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>y8VKTBO2iGQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2698</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588036-aztec-adventure</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/aztec-adventure</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aztec-adventure-the-golden-road-to-paradise/3030-6159/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2698-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2698-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/134367-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97109-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97110-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-nino-and-his.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97111-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-screen-tells.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97112-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-forest.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97113-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-get-the-money.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97114-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-and-throw-them.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97115-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-two-of-the-enemies.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97116-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-cannot-continue.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97117-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-first-enemy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97118-aztec-adventure-sega-master-system-screenshot-there-is-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UWH9fS5.png</banner1>
</game>