<Game>
	<Name>Bank Panic (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bank Panic is a Sega published Arcade game originally developed by Sanritsu. The goal is to scan a dozen doors in a Wild West frontier town bank, allowing innocent citizens to make bank deposits while shooting any outlaws or bombs that appear.Sega would later port the game on their Sega Mark 1 and Sega Mark 3 consoles, the latter of which is better known to Western gamers as the Master System. The game would receive various other ports for home computers as well.The game later influenced an iOS game named Westbang.Gameplay:Each level contains 12 doors. From this doors can either enter customers with intention to deposit money or bandits that come to rob the bank. The player must allow the customer to make the deposit and shoot the outlaws before they shoot back.Each door has a counter attached to it. To pass the level every counter must be filled with at least one bag of money. There is a time limit to each level and if a counter has only one bag for too long it will disappear making the player to come back there again and wait for another deposit. From time to time, there will be time bombs placed in a door. In that case, another timer shows and the player must shoot the bomb before the timer runs out.The player loses a life if a bandit shoots them, if the bomb explodes, if the level timer reaches zero or if the player shoots an innocent customer. Sometimes bandits will hide behind customers. Some customers will be tied up and the player has to shoot the rope to free them. In this case, the customer gives 3 bags of money.Sometimes, especially at the beginning of each level, a small cowboy appears holding a gift that the player must shoot to get bonus points. The player gets point for receiving bags of money and shooting outlaws. If the player doesn&#8217;t shoot the bandit before he draws his gun (which the game considers an "unfair" kill and thus is worth less points), a very quick timer will appear and additional points will be granted to the player by shooting the bandit with as little time as possible left on the timer.Points scoringPoints by shooting an outlaw:Before he draws his gun: 100 or 200 pointsWith the timer on 0.26-0.33: 300 pointsWith the timer on 0.21-0.25: 600 pointsWith the timer on 0.16-0.20: 700 pointsWith the timer on 0.11-0.15: 800 pointsWith the timer on 0.01-0.10: 1,000 pointsWith the timer on 0.00: 2,000 points for brown shirt gunmanWith the timer on 0.00: 3,000 points for green shirt gunmanWith the timer on 0.00: 5,000 points for red shirt gunmanDeposits:First bag of money: 200 pointsSecond bag of money: 400 pointsThird bag of money: 600 pointsFourth or more bag of money: 1,000 pointsShooting the rope on a customer who is tied up: 3 bags of money worth 1,000 points eachEnd of level bonuses:Money bags 1-12: 50 points eachMoney bags 13-24: 100 points eachMoney bags 25-36: 150 points eachMoney bags 37-48: 200 points eachOthers:Shooting the bomb: 100 pointsIf a woman is held up and the gunman is shot: 500 pointsIf a man is held up and the gunman is shot: 200 pointsTrivia:In the last stages of the games, the boy who carries the hats is seen lifting up the woman client's skirts.Alessandro Giuriato and Gary A. Hatt share the official record for this game, with a maximum possible 9.999.999 points.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>Y1dOtpk5IWA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2702</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/569355-bank-panic</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/bank-panic</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bank-panic/3030-11214/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2702-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2702-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/77156-bank-panic-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38550-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38551-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-our-gunslinger-ready.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38552-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-bank-teller-stares.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38553-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-thanks-ma-am.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38554-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-destroy-the-dynamite.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38555-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-set-me-free-and-i.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38556-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-hey-pal-watch-where.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/38557-bank-panic-sega-master-system-screenshot-you-ve-saved-the-bank.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/7/e/gfs_88118_2_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/a/e/gfs_88118_2_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2702.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Bandits are holding up a bank and have taken people hostage, and as a gunslinger, it's your job to shoot them. The bank has 12 doors, and the bandits are behind each one of them. When they pull a gun out at you when you open a door, you have only a few seconds to shoot them before they shoot you. If you shoot them too early (ie: before he sticks his gun out at you), it is considered unfair, and you won't score any points, but if you're too late, he'll shoot you and you lose one of your three lives.If you waste too much time, a bandit will come out from one of the doors and stick dynamite on it. You must then shoot the dynamite to get rid of it.  If you're lucky, either a man or a woman will throw you a bag of gold coins. If you shoot any of these people by accident, you also lose a life. More often than not, the person will throw his/her hands up, saying "I haven't got anything". That's when they will be replaced by bandits.  Some men will carry three to five pieces of gold on top of their heads, and shooting at all of the gold will award you with a bag of gold coins. Others will be tied up with rope. If you shoot the rope, there's more money for you, because not only will you receive one bag of gold coins, but you'll get three bags of gold coins.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a0d145e-ec3f-4051-8c41-99aedacc632b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6606c648-27c9-46a8-bb7f-b506078c46c8.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45a1b649-dd79-4dd7-8365-c63c8c62d60e.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>