<Game>
	<Name>Batman Returns (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Batman Returns is an action game based on the 1992 film of the same name. Multiple unique versions of the game exist, developed sometime between 1992 and 1993:The Super Nintendo Entertainment System version, developed and published by Konami in April 1993 features a sidescrolling beat-em-up style in similar vein to the SNES version of Final Fight. It also features some 2D platformer levels and a Batmobile racing level using Mode 7 technology.The Genesis version, developed by Malibu and published by Sega in 1992, played like a traditional 2D action platformer. An enhanced version for the Sega CD, featuring enhanced music and added 3D Batmobile and Bat Skiboat levels, was released in 1993.The Nintendo Entertainment System version, also developed and published by Konami in January 1993, features a sidescrolling beat 'em up style similar to the NES version of Double Dragon and sidescrolling Batmobile and Bat Skiboat levels.The Game Gear and Sega Master System versions, developed by Aspect and published by Sega, is a traditional 2D action platformer.The Atari Lynx version, developed and published by Atari, is a traditional 2D action platformer.The Amiga version, developed by Denton Designs and published by Konami, is a traditional 2D action platformer.The PC version, developed by Spirit of Discovery and published by Konami, is a point-and-click adventure game.As the titular Batman (depicted in cutscenes by Michael Keaton), players fight a gang of circus performers (the Red Triangle Circus Gang) while foiling the plans of deformed The Penguin (depicted by Danny DeVito) and cat burglar Catwoman (depicted by Michelle Pfeiffer).Cheat: Infinite livesAt the title screen, press Up, Up, Up, Down, Down, Right, Left, 2. You should hear a sound if entered successfully. Your lives will now never decrease.Cheat: Infinite livesAt the title screen, press Up, Down, Down, Up, Left, Right, 1. You should hear a sound if entered successfully. You will now start with 50 lives instead of 3.Cheat: Level Select MenuOn the title screen, hold in the buttons Up, 1 and 2. You should then see a level select menu appear.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>-bjiENrHYxQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5245</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588037-batman-returns</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/batman-returns_______</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/batman-returns/3030-9710/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5245-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5245-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/254070-batman-returns-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139988-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139989-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-choose-a-route.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139991-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-bad-guy-is.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139992-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-straight-jab.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139994-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-this-man-is-so.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139997-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-watch-out-for.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139998-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-hang-gliding.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/139999-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-game-over.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189732-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-final-boss.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189733-batman-returns-sega-master-system-screenshot-select-a-route.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5245-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vwfrPUm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5245.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Frigid winter winds swept over an already chilled Gotham City. Random street crimes were running at an all-time high, despite the holidays. Down below, in the city's frozen sewers, Oswald Cobblepot, known as The Penguin, planned more mayhem and schemed the take over of the fightened metropolis. His loyal army of missle-packing Penguin Commandos and the bizarre Red Triangle Circus Gang are energized by the evil genius of the web-footed orphan. A desperate call to Batman goes up. Partner with Batman to salvage Gotham City from The Penguin's cold-hearted plot. Guide him in swift, life-like moves from dark alleys to rooftops in vivid scenes based on the hit movie, "Batman Returns." Control his combat style, and help conduct relentless interrogations of The Penguins many allies. Use the Batcave computer to input clues, analyze evidence, and review enemy bios. You're in charge of weapons, too. Stock Batman's Utility belt with enough heat to match the diverse fighting styles of The Penguin and cold-blooded, sewer-dwelling minions. Gotham City is in trouble.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c437bd82-65f1-4fac-bdc6-06fd20330ca2.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/adaa5c4c-579b-45ad-9a99-c68ba528a273.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44e35949-34a1-42f0-9011-16d45555e2ba.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c0ce06e3-6630-4fc6-b6e8-36d3015d063e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f3d21f73-db53-4132-9ff0-51a2d8e13a33.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>