<Game>
	<Name>Black Belt (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The cover of Hokuto no KenBlack Belt is a brawler developed and published by Sega for the Sega Master System platform.Black Belt is the localized name for Hokuto no Ken, an anime and manga better known as Fist of the North Star in the US. The characters, story and setting were all changed in the international versions because they lacked the license. Even though much was changed in this version, the gameplay stayed the same.Hokuto no Ken was the third game to be released in the cartridge format in Japan. The format had all but supplanted the earlier Sega Card format, which had less memory space than the new cartridges.Plot:One of the many boss encountersWang has kidnapped Kyoko who is the girlfriend of Riki. The kidnapper also happens to be Riki's rival, and he sets out to rescue Kyoko from Wang. Riki will fight his way through various cities and towns defeating enemies in order to fight against Wang. In the Japanese version, it plays the story of Hokuto No Ken facing familiar enemies up to the final boss, Raoh.Gameplay:Traverse Japan inspired locationsBlack Belt is a side scrolling brawler where the player controls Riki, a martial artist (or Kenshiro, in the Japanese version). Riki will travel through six stages, walking left to right, using his fighting skills to defeat Wang's henchman. Riki is able punch and kick enemies, and upon defeating them the enemies will explode. As he travels he will come across various enemies and mid-bosses, which will eventually lead Riki to confront Wang. In the boss battles the fighting mechanics do not change, and Riki simply uses punches and kicks to be victorious. The only difference is that the player is always facing the boss.Name changesBecause of the licencing issue, the names of the characters had to have been changed from the Hokuto No Ken characters to generic characters.Black Belt CharactersHokuto no Ken CharactersRikiKenshiroKyokoYuriaRyuShinHawkColonelGontaDevil RebirthOniTokiRitaSoutherWangRaohAppearances from other charactersThe Four Jacks (Club, Spade, Diamond and Mr Heart)Mad SargeFoxUighurCheat: Bosses LevelAfter you do the last hit (a punch) in Wang, imediately hold 1 and 2 buttons simultaneously and press Up and Down alternately until the final screen (a black one that contains a text) disappear. If you did it correctly you would play in a special chapter which you could fight against the 6 bosses, one by one, again.Cheat: Infinite LivesPush Button 1 at the title screen. Hold the Reset button at the black screen after the red screen, until Riki appears on the screen. Once this happens, release Reset and the game will start, giving you infinite lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>hIiMz_NUDEw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2706</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588039-black-belt</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/black-belt</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/black-belt/3030-16176/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2706-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2706-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/301051-black-belt-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81498-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81499-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-get-ready-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81500-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81501-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-riki-shattered-his.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81502-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1-boss-1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81503-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1-boss-2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81504-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-you-missed-hah.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81505-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1-boss-3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81506-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1-boss-4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81507-black-belt-sega-master-system-screenshot-chapter-1-boss-5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In this game, you play Riki. Kyoko, your beautiful Japanese girlfriend, has been kidnapped, and in order to rescue her, you must get through a tireless army of enemies. These enemies come equipped with weapons that include whips, knives, swords, and flamethrowers, but Riki has to make do with his well-trained martial arts body. Black Belt is a side-scrolling game that is split into seven chapters. During these chapters, you are fighting Chinese Kung Fu men, wrestlers, jujitsu men, eagles, ninjas, and black women. When you get halfway through the chapter, you will fight a different enemy than one that you encounter before. At the end of each chapter, you have to defeat several bosses before continuing on to the next round. Each type of these has their own personal strengths and weaknesses. Once you touch an enemy or boss, you will lose energy. once you lose all energy, you lose a life, but more life can be restored by getting the cake when it comes across the screen in mid-air, or by defeating an enemy that will come at you halfway and you receive a bonus for doing so. Black Belt is a modified version of the Japanese-exclusive Hokuto no Ken, with the licence removed and new level designs.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c637317-19c0-4391-8288-f8ff95e453be.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3b9dd67-670e-483d-9589-1b4bbb022c82.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bf1f261-ef71-4e28-9cea-0a00e195391f.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c212223-b192-4405-92dc-a39d022913a0.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0c389d2b-01af-4cc1-931c-a5542062a461.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06cce4a1-54c4-4e19-a16d-d1fd9eaba749.PNG</snapshot11>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>