<Game>
	<Name>Captain Silver (Japan, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Captain Silver puts the player in control of the dauntless adventurer Jim Aykroyd, as he attempts to fight his way across several stages to locate the lost treasure of the titular pirate. Each version of the game - the Arcade, the Sega Master System and the NES are all slightly different in their execution, but all play mostly the same.The Arcade version, released in 1987, has a total of three stages. After defeating the now undead Captain Silver at the end of Stage 3, the player restarts the game with slightly tougher enemies to defeat. The US Master System version was released on a 1mb Cart and has a total of four stages, with two pirate captains (including Captain Silver) as bosses. The Master System versions for Europe, Australia and Japan were all the same 2mb Cart version that instead had six stages, with six bosses instead of the US version's two. The Japan-only NES version is the most divergent from the original Arcade game, as it features more platforming and less swordfighting. There are different bosses and stage layouts, a health gauge instead of the one-hit kill rule found in other versions and NPCs that will either help or harm Jim if he talks to them.Gameplay:Jim fights using his trusty cutlass, which swings horizontally while walking or crouching and vertically when Jim is climbing a ladder. There are a few power-ups Jim can acquire also, those the effectiveness tends to vary per version:Fairies: These provide Jim with magical powers, allowing him to fire projectiles from his sword. They can be powered up a total of six times, increasing the power and size of each projectile.Longsword: A powerful sword that can take out enemy projectiles fired at Jim. It is only available in the Arcade version.Boots: These allow Jim to jump higher and walk faster. Like the Longsword, it is a temporary item. In the Arcade version, if a second pair of boots or a second longsword is found while Jim is still equipped with the previous, they become permanent (at least until Jim loses a life).Treasure: Simply adds to the player's score.Keys: Open treasure chests and item shops, where many of the above items can be bought. The player uses their own score for currency in the Arcade version.Potions: A potion will give Jim a second chance if he is hit, saving him from an untimely demise. In the Master System version this bonus remains with Jim until he needs it, though it's only temporary in the Arcade version.Letters: These symbols can be found after defeating enemies and will give the player an extra life if they find all of them, which spells out "Captain Silver".Weapon Upgrades: Unique to the NES version, these upgrades to Jim's attacking power can be bought in stores with money.Cheat: ContinueHold up and hit both buttons before the game resets.  If for some reason after 20 or so uses it doesn't seem to work, try circling clockwise while rapidly hitting both buttons.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>bhYgaD9Qrg4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2712</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588044-captain-silver</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/captain-silver</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/captain-silver/3030-19904/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2712-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/74399-captain-silver-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/74400-captain-silver-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76050-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76051-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-get-ready.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76052-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-scene-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76053-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-jim-slashes-something.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76054-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-exploring-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76055-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-jester-throws.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76056-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-village-fountain.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76057-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-shop.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76058-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-wicked-witch.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76059-captain-silver-sega-master-system-screenshot-dead.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>You're Jack Avery, a lad with a taste for treasure and high adventure! In this hot Sega adventure you are fast on the trail of the most feared sea pirate's treasure, Captain Silver. It doesn't matter that he's dead. His ghost goes on haunting the treasure...and all who try to find it...with a bloodthirsty vengeance that has chased strong men to their graves! But you have no fear..or do you? With a tattered old treasure map in hand, you must track down the sea dog's golden hoard, battling creatures both from this world from beyond the grave! You'll start the game with your trusty cutlass and your wits. Fight well and you'll be able to increase the power to slow down the hands of time and make your self temporarily invisible. Wield your cutlass well and you'll face the ghost of the Captain himself...with a chance to own all his buried treasure. But fail in your quest, and who knows what spirits will haunt you?</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fece7605-a490-4127-94b6-03506d2e45da.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/711c0b92-dc30-4edc-8b77-2a475e1792f0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b628733-d528-4299-ab7b-a373ddc3e21a.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/89adef4f-09f8-4471-b027-e0cb80d61c4b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49a71026-45ec-441c-85f5-cd3d900e0e2f.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>