<Game>
	<Name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Castle of Illusion starring Mickey Mouse (known in Japan as I Love Mickey Mouse: Great Mysterious Castle Adventure) is a 2D sidescrolling platformer developed and published by Sega for the Sega Genesis on November 20, 1990. It is the first in a series of Sega-produced games starring Disney mascot Mickey Mouse (known as the "Illusion" series).As Mickey, players must embark on an adventure through the evil and mysterious Castle of Illusion to rescue Minnie Mouse from the evil witch Mizrabel, who plans to steal Minnie's youth. To do so, he must find the seven Gems of the Rainbow (guarded by the Masters of Illusion) hidden within the magical worlds (including an enchanted forest and a toy-box) scattered throughout the castle. The game's Practice difficulty changes the goal, in which Mickey must find three gems (collected by completing a particular level from the game's first three worlds) that would make Mizrabel see beauty in herself.The game was later remade for the Sega Master System and Sega Game Gear in 1990-1991, featuring redesigned levels and simplified graphics (as well as different enemies, items, and bosses), as well as completely changing one of Mickey's attacking mechanics from flinging apples (and other items previously collected) to picking up and hurling larger solid objects found throughout each level (such as indestructible barrels, which double as a puzzle mechanic).The original game was bundled with QuackShot starring Donald Duck in Japan on October 15, 1998 as part of the Sega Ages series of game collections for the Sega Saturn. It also received a full remake on September 3, 2013 (almost 23 years after the original game's release) as a downloadable title for the Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC by Sega Studios Australia (under supervision of the original game's director, Emiko Yamamoto) featuring a variety of new gameplay mechanics (such as transitioning between 2D and 3D platforming) and a spoken narrator. The original game was released for the PlayStation 3 (for owners who pre-purchased the remake after August 20, 2013).Gameplay:As Mickey Mouse travels through these wacky and dangerous worlds, he will have to defeat a variety of enemies to advance. To attack enemies, Mickey can stomp on them, or fling apples and marbles at them, which can be collected throughout the game. Mickey Mouse can also collect icons that restore health, add extra lives, or boost your score.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>BE-rFtBnvjY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3084</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588046-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse/3030-9513/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2370009-genesis_castleofillusion.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SSkLmb9.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/137146-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3084-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3084-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3084-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3084-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3084-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/41231-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/41232-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/41233-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/41234-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/41235-castle-of-illusion-starring-mickey-mouse-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3084-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3RAV356.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3084.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game is a side-scrolling game putting the player in control of Mickey Mouse in a magical quest to save Minnie Mouse from the evil witch named Mizrabel, who kidnapped Minnie to steal her youth.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/086203e2-fe28-417d-97c7-58f33633f0b2.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aef3dd51-f1e6-4f26-8b95-6229b78572b1.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f298800-d597-4e52-9fc0-9a76b583282f.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6a72dd6-4e90-489a-9996-3e4fa2fc0623.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fb771775-69c3-4fef-bbac-26b3ac057cbc.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d039852-252c-433f-86f0-8b8a6426db76.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b816ddc7-3a96-497c-884e-060a4b717b60.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60363106-5d15-40f5-80ab-5ebe2d31ae99.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/25eb1903-de23-4ffd-a829-367c5b49c238.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c330d9e8-213b-4632-9e1b-dc5bb42424df.jpg</snapshot15>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>