<Game>
	<Name>Chapolim x Dracula - Um Duelo Assustador (Brazil)</Name>
	<plot>A spooky romp through Count Dracula's incredible haunted house.You're Mick.And the good news is that your grandfather just told you that you're to inherit the family jewels.A flashy collection of diamonds, rubies, sapphires, even opals.All yours.The bad news is that they're hidden inside Count Dracula's mansion.They have been for years.First, you have to wipe out the bats, Draculas, and eventually their annoying henchman.Then you have to find the hidden keys and passageways that should lead to your family's long lost treasure.Ghoul luck -- you'll need it.Cheat: Temporary Invinsibility.Find one of the altars that are scattered through each stage. When you walk past one of them, you should see something that looks like an arrow fly from the side of the screen straight towards you. Jump on it, and it should disappear. Now walk past the altar again and then jump on the arrow again. After repeating this a few times, you should become invinsible for a short time.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>xd1Ce7v9Uyk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2791</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588070-ghost-house</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/chapolim-x-drcula-um-duelo-assustador</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador/3030-5065/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2791-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2791-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182544-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182545-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182546-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182548-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182549-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182550-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182551-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182553-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182554-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/182556-chapolim-x-dracula-um-duelo-assustador-sega-master-system.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2791.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Chapolim X Drácula: Um Duelo Assustador (which translates Chapolim vs. Dracula: A Frightening Duel) is an authorized "hack" of Ghost House, with Ghost House's hero, Mick, replaced by Chapolim (or El Chapulín Colorado in original Spanish), a famous Mexican character from a TV series. Chapolim is a parody to superheroes in general. He dresses a red grasshopper costume with a yellow heart in the chest with the leters "CH". He also usually carries his Marreta Biônica (Chipote Chillón in the original, Squeaky Mallet in English) a red (toy) hammer. At each stage, Chapolim must defeat five vampires that are in torpor within their coffins. The coffins are locked, so he must first find the keys to unlock them. He'll find the keys killing the most diverse enemies that haunt the mansion he's in, such as ghosts, bats, fire blowers, mummies, etc. Once he's got a key, he must unlock a coffin and then defeat the vampire who sleeps there.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73a939f2-a5ff-4839-8633-393c3047d882.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/122becdf-0ab4-4a92-a3cb-657cc1bd9797.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4fa2d9c5-81b7-4314-8b1a-c21f226dd7f9.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bec4abae-06b2-4ee8-876b-1f73177867f5.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tec Toy</Publisher>
</game>