<Game>
	<Name>Comical Machine Gun Joe (Taiwan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Comical Machine Gun Joe is a third-person shooter in which the player only has the space along the bottom of the screen to shoot and evade incoming enemy fire, similar to Cabal (Comical Machine Gun Joe pre-dates Cabal by a few years, however). Enemies wander in off screen, occasionally on the same plane as the protagonist, and the player must quickly shoot them all before they are hit themselves. The player can shoot forwards and to either side, as well as at 45 degree angles diagonally up-left or up-right.Comical Machine Gun Joe was released exclusively in Japan for the Sega Master System, one of a handful of SMS games to never see release outside of the system's nation, and was only available in the short-lived card-based Sega Card format.Cheat: InvincibilityPause the game, press the A button 8 times and then unpause. This can only be done if you're alive.Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsIn the Graveyard stage, survive for 1 minute and 30 seconds without triggering the boss appearance (don't kill too many enemies). The stage will change to night-time and you'll get 100.000 points.Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsIn any stage, defeat El Doba (the boss) before he fires 10 shots. In the next stage, don't lose any lives. Instead of his normal form, El Doba will appear as a schoolgirl and will shoot faster.Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsYou can do it as many times as you wish, so El Doba appears on his true form on all subsequent stages.Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsOn the beginning of any stage, the number of hundred's value in the score has to be either 0,1,4 or 5. Then, the 1st shot you fire on the stage has to hit the 3rd enemy that appears (you can't miss). Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsIf done correctly, a character - that changes depending on stage - will appear at the upper part of the screen and net you 10.000 points.Cheat: 100.000 bonus pointsA easy way to test this is at the beginning of the first stage, since the score will always be 0.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>GURE5jWahDk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26439</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570181-comical-machinegun-joe</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/comical-machine-gun-joe</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/comical-machine-gun-joe/3030-48926/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728591-9407273053-30656.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/26439-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/301780-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578470-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578475-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-at-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578476-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-joe.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578477-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578478-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-defeated.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/578479-comical-machine-gun-joe-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-graveyard.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728595-6313601945-u0jkw.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728594-8526720634-mKlMXxyt.png+</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728593-9365662333-FAJZxSBH.png+</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/8/4/gfs_8607_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>