<Game>
	<Name>Daffy Duck in Hollywood (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Uh-oh! Mad Professor Duckbrain has stolen Yosemite Sam's previous golden movie awards, and he wants a million bucks for 'em! What to do? Well, call Daffy Duck of course! Daffy grabs his trusty bubble gun and explores different film sets to retrieve the awards. But watch out! The film sets are also rigged with dynamite that must be deactived, or else Hollywood is sure to blow up! All of the film sets are themed after various adventurous movie genres and locations, including horror, western, jungle and sci-fi! Daffy can power up his bubble gun to fire an array of different bubbles, and enemies are defeated by capturing them in bubbles and having them float away. As another trick up his  sleeve, Daffy can call for help from a fairy duck mother, who flies around with Daffy and protects him.Cheat: Invincibility and Stage SkipInput this code at the main menu to be invincible or skip stage.Cheat: Invincibility and Stage SkipPress the following commands at the main menu to view one of three endings.Cheat: Multiple Cheats and Fergus McGovern headTo enter multiple cheats, enter the code, but instead of starting the game, enter the Music/Sound test menu then exit it. Do this to activate both the level select and invincibility codes, then press Left, Right, Left, Left, Left. Now start a new game, and instead of playing as Daffy Duck, you will be playing as Fergus McGovern's (the founder of Probe) head.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>eJXeorvvxzw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2724</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570233-daffy-duck-in-hollywood</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/daffy-duck-in-hollywood_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/daffy-duck-in-hollywood/3030-7905/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2724-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/8/9/30889_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523671-1143377043_02.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523669-1156361592_07.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523668-1156361592_06.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523663-1156361592_02.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523662-1156361592_01.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523660-1156258374_06.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523658-1156258374_04.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523656-1156258374_02.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523655-1156258374_01.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1582/523654-1156258374_00.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2724-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2724.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Presenting the world famous Daffy Duck P.I. Armed with your lethal buble gun search the Hollywood film sets for Yosemite Sam's Golden Cartoon World Movie Awards and the despicable Mad Professor Duck Brain."</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4f3850e7-322b-4609-8f34-dbcda5a29538.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3a0c59b-a11e-4e5b-81c4-357aa34b447f.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/969efee1-acd2-45e5-accf-ee963c665802.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04e1c2a9-80e1-4ca4-9895-b99d19f176b8.PNG</snapshot11>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>