<Game>
	<Name>Dead Angle (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dead Angle is an on-rails shooter set in the 1930s that was released in 1988 in the Arcades and ported to the Sega Master System in 1989. Developed by Seibu Kaihatsu. It features the exploits of the private detective George Phoenix as he attempts to shut down a criminal empire and rescue his girlfriend.Gameplay:The game is essentially a rail shooter in which players control both the cross-hair to aim, and the detective simultaneously. Controlling the character, albeit without controlling the game's movement, makes this game straddle the line between a rail shooter and third-person shooter.The game progresses through several stages. Once a set quota of enemies have been killed a boss will appear before moving on to the next stage.The Master System port has fewer levels than the arcade version and also has fewer mechanics. In the arcade version the player could throw grenades at enemies, however this wasn't present in the Master System version.Despite being a rail shooter, the game doesn't support the light phaser.Cheat: Hard Difficulty SettingOn the Main Menu, use Controller 2 to change the difficulty.Cheat: Level SelectKeep pressing left, right on control pads 1 and 2 until a  sound plays. Then press a button on controller one to goto the next level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>bj4xtmkMW28</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2727</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588053-dead-angle</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/dead-angle</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dead-angle/3030-12758/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2727-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2727-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71485-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71487-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-level-1-napoli.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71486-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-when-in-front-of-an.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71488-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-you-can-move-up-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71489-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-enemies-appear-in.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71490-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71491-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-level-2-new-york.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71492-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-enemies-appear-in.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71493-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-goons-jumping-off.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71494-dead-angle-sega-master-system-screenshot-your-character-ducking.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>You're George Phenix, one very tough private eye. You're so tough that you were the one who was able to put mob kingpin Robert King behind bars. He vowed revenge, but at the time you laughed it off. However, while you were in Italy with your girlfriend, Jane, King got his revenge. His thugs got their hands on Jane and disappeared. Now you stalk the streets of the city of Napoli, your blood boiling, your gun drawn! "Dead Angle" takes you back to the 1930's, when the mob did almost anything they wanted to. Now they've crossed the line, and you can put an end to the reign of Robert King. Put your enemies away with your revolver, or if you're lucky, pick up a Tommy gun and let 'er rip! Save Jane from the Big Sleep!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d972aeb6-bf6b-48b4-8352-e38182bde054.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f9adeaf-3f6f-4c39-98f0-48132578f65a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb9ff2f1-53bd-4d54-aa65-2be2a9a9693e.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8be8d2d4-3e46-443d-81ea-d12896217892.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>