<Game>
	<Name>Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E. Coyote (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Released by Probe Entertainment in 1994 this Loony Toons licenced Platformer featured Road Runner and his nemesis Wile E Coyote. It was released on Sega Game Gear and Sega Master System.GameplayThe aim of the game is to collect stars littered throughout the level on path to the Exit sign. These stars add an extra second to the time remaining countdown. Each stage contains 250 stars. Stages are broken up into worlds. Collecting BirdSeed replenishes Road Runner's health which can be lost by running into enemies in the environment. Some Birdseed stations also act as checkpoints to respawn in case of death. Enemies are killed by jumping on them. The platforming is difficult to control but level layouts are similar in style to other Master System platformers of the time. Cheat: Cheat ModeTo access cheat mode, go to the options menu and set the Tune to 09, and the sound to 12. Then go up to the Game Mode and press left/right and select CHEAT. You will now be invincible in hard mode.Cheat: Cheat ModeTo access level select, go to the options menu and set the Tune to 10, and the sound to 07. Then go down to exit and press Left or Right to choose which level you start on. Easy - 10 Levels, Normal - 12 Levels, Hard - 14 Levels.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>PLh8c0BY0Cw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18804</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570219-desert-speedtrap</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-c/3030-9023/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18804-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/18804-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/142787-desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18804-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18804-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18804-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/100240-desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote-sega.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/100239-desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote-sega.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/100241-desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote-sega.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/100242-desert-speedtrap-starring-road-runner-and-wile-e-coyote-sega.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5768/660048-desert.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/b/b/gfs_88542_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/6/b/gfs_88542_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>This is a platform game starring Looney Tunes famous Road Runner(who you control) and nemesis Wile E. Coyote. Road Runner can jump, eat birdseed to replenish life and run, of course! Holding the D-pad down speeds him up. The clock is ticking and if you run out of time a try is lost, collecting stars adds time to the clock There are various items/powerups and bonus areas 3 difficulty settings, choice to play with or without music and/or sound effects and an option to play the game music while not in game</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>5ptjlmjD1bY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/17651bab-58f1-4ce5-b74b-e45f781ea6f1.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5914d12e-12f2-4c2c-adda-43be941d02d4.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d146263-da26-42f6-b60f-99e5e925e363.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8009b168-ba7d-4c09-a05e-21a533db4da2.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ca45ca0b-9c95-4a54-b99f-3e6f4b8989d7.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Sega Enterprises Ltd.</Publisher>
</game>