<Game>
	<Name>Dick Tracy (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dick Tracy is a side-scrolling shooter developed by Sega of America based on the Dick Tracy franchise. While released around the time of the 1990 Dick Tracy movie and heavily inspired by its look and setting, the game does not follow the movie's plot, instead telling an unrelated story about Tracy tracking down a suspicious nitroglycerin shipment.Story:Receiving word that Big Boy's gang is up to something at the train yard, Tracy arrives just in time to see them getting on a train carrying a shipment of nitroglycerin. Concerned, he tracks the shipment to a warehouse, only to see The Brow speed away with it. The Brow leads him to Lips Manlis, who reveals Big Boy has a secret explosives factory going, using the TNT produced to take out the competition.Hitting the streets for information on the factory, Tracy corners Shoulders who points him back to the warehouse. Tracy returns to investigate, however Big Boy's hitman Flattop awaits him there, to lure him into a trap. The trap fails, and Tracy manages to get the defeated henchman to give up his bosses' location. Now hot on Big Boy's trail, Tracy tracks him through the sewer, leading to the harbor, before a final confrontation in the nearby drawbridge gearhouse.Gameplay:The game is a side-scrolling shooter with occasional light platforming. To progress to the next scene, Tracy must get to the right end, avoiding or defeating the suit-clad mobsters who constantly pop out of doorways, behind objects, or the edge of the screen, going after Tracy with fists, knives, guns or explosives. Tracy himself is armed with a revolver and a tommy gun, the former for enemies at his front or back, while the latter fires stream of bullets used to take out enemies hiding in the background. His guns have unlimited ammunition, but Tracy will punch instead of shoot if enemies enter brawling range, gaining a "punch bonus" for each enemy defeated that way.Tracy has 4 to 8 health segments, depending on difficulty chosen, 2 lives, and 3 to 5 continue credits selectable from the options. As there are no items in the game, Tracy only regains health between scenes, but shooting gallery bonus levels between each stage allow Tracy to earn extra points and credits by hitting crooks while leaving cops and civilians unharmed. Most scenes have time limits between 3 and 4 minutes, and must be completed within that time or Tracy loses a life.Some scenes change the rules somewhat:Unarmed scenes strip Tracy of his guns, usually for flimsy story reasons. Because he does not have the tommy gun, they do not feature the enemy filled extended backgrounds, instead adding a bit of verticality with ladders and paths higher up on the screen.Vehicle scenes are fixed scrolling survival scenarios, where Tracy hangs on the outside of a police car, dodging incoming fire and shooting back at enemy cars, trying to stay alive for a set amount of time until he reaches the destination.Boss scenes play much like regular ones, except the stage boss is running around in the background, constantly attacking Tracy, and the scene doesn't end until the boss's health bar is depleted.Levels:The game consists of 6 stages, each divided into 3 scenes.StageSceneNameType1ATracy Gets a Leadregular1BSteve's Train Yardunarmed1CThe Wrong Side of the Tracksboss: Itchy2ADestination - 7th St. Warehouseregular2BThe Chase!vehicle2CA Browbeating Under the Elboss: The Brow3AHitting the Streetsregular3BRacing Down First Streetvehicle3CDrinks Are on the Houseboss: Lips Manlis4AA Hold Up in the Back Alley!unarmed4BBack to the Warehouse!regular4CAn Explosive Confrontation!boss: Pruneface5ASearching the Warehouseregular5BA New Lead?vehicle5CTracy Falls into a Trap!boss: Flattop6AAfter a Rat!unarmed6BHarboring a Fugitive!regular6CShowdown at the Gearhouse!boss: Big Boy</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>n2f0BXP5a2E</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3088</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588054-dick-tracy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/dick-tracy_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dick-tracy/3030-40441/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3088-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3088-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/73403-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134336-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134337-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-splash-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134338-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-options-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134339-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134340-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-level-1-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134341-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-level-1-on-the-road.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134343-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-dick-is-dead.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134344-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-dick-once-again-on.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134345-dick-tracy-sega-master-system-screenshot-game-over.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3909/362026-10.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3088-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3088-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3088.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Calling Dick Tracy! Calling Dick Tracy! The mob's got the city by the throat! The next move's yours. You've got to grapple with the meanest guys around and break this crime ring before it breaks you! You've got pistols, machine guns, dynamite fists, and the law. The mob's got Molotov cocktails, a trainload of nitro and bad intentions. Shoot it out with the likes of Lips Manlis, Flattop, The Brow, and Pruneface. Hang onto the side of a speeding car in frenzied street gunbattles. Blast'em in alleys, railyards, and warehouses. Hit the right targets on the gun range and get more time to fight. Clean up the town's seamy side. Then rip into the racketeers at the Ritz. Blast your way to the final showdown with Big Boy Caprice. Think you're tough? Here's your chance to prove it, Dick Tracy.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82130055-1c89-408a-8de2-972ee702648e.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/365fd322-f74e-494a-8573-c677c6556c11.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d1e6279-9a7f-43d9-9194-5f8fb3b3019b.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/00585733-ad99-468f-97b2-245b144d6e77.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbd143c2-6cc9-4099-af33-d79343233c63.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>