<Game>
	<Name>Double Target - Cynthia no Nemuri (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>If you hate aliens, you'll love Quartet! You see, space colony Number Nine is being threatened by an invasion of the most dangerous kind. Alien attack. And the place is crawling with them. These vicious, vile parasites have even managed to confiscate the casket of the late great Queen Cynthia. It's your job to exterminate these treacherous creatures. To return the casket to its hallowed tomb. And save the colony from certain collapse. You'll have special equipment to help you along the way. Like a supersonic jet engine, a special bomb, missiles and a magic key. But time is running out. So don't just stand there thinking about it. Get on it. And get rid of this gruesome group. For good!Cheat: Level SelectOk, for this nifty little trick to work, you'll need to be in a 2 player game. One the title screen, press ''Pause'' 12 times on the first controller. Then hold both buttons and upper left corner on the second controller. This will open a Level Select screen.Cheat: Level SelectEnter these at the Title Screen</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>OBPwfwMiP20</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2983</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588124-quartet</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2983-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/5/1/23251_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/7/a/gfs_88143_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/e/b/gfs_68197_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/3/b/gfs_68197_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/8/b/gfs_68197_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/9/b/gfs_68197_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/b/gfs_68197_2_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/b/gfs_68197_2_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/b/gfs_68197_2_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/9/a/gfs_68197_2_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/2/a/gfs_68197_2_9.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>