<Game>
	<Name>Enduro Racer (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:One of Sega's most highly regarded Arcade games, Enduro Racer is a follow-up to Hang-On and focuses more on the stunts and jumps unique to motocross among all other forms of motorbike racing. Players must reach the finish line within the time limit, avoiding other players and obstacles and carefully navigating over each jump.Most home ports attempted to emulate the Arcade's ever-shifting 3D perspective to varying degrees of success depending on each respective system's graphical power.For the Sega Master System port, Enduro Racer is depicted from an isometric perspective and plays very differently. It does allow players to customize their vehicle with upgrades between each race, using points earned for how many vehicles they overtook. This would be the version that would later see a rerelease for Nintendo's Wii Shop, specifically the Virtual Console. Unfortunately, a lot of the content was removed for the US and international versions, including several tracks.Ending CreditsThe game contains a message for players once completing all of the stages in record time:Congratulations!You successfully completed all of the stages!"Enduro" is a symbolic journey through life via the media of race.The results are insignificant and what really counts is competing.Of particular importance are the lessons to be learned concerning one's self from the various encounters you experience along the way.There is no victor or loser in this test of endurance.The only thing that really matters is that you make a commitment to begin the long and trying trek.This game is then dedicated to all of the "Life riders" who have started out on the solitary trip to find their own individual limits.Last but not least, may we sincerely congratulate you on a perfect run.Cheat: Super jumpTo do a super jump, you need to drive 200 kph and press Down, Up at the top of the jump. Then 1 while in the air and 2 before your bike lands on the ground.Cheat: Super jumpOn the title screen, enter the following code to choose the track you want to race on:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>OQN5E9OfHrM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2737</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588058-enduro-racer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/enduro-racer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/enduro-racer/3030-5699/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2737-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2737-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/119352-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68233-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68234-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-start-race-1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68235-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-track-forks.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68236-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-jump-over-ramps.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68237-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-finish-line.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68238-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-begin-race-2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68239-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-racing-another-bike.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68240-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-end-off-race.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68241-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-watch-out-for-rocks.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68245-enduro-racer-sega-master-system-screenshot-to-late.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iHVTWMe.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2737.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The player rides the dirt bike through five stages and must avoid other riders as well rocks and trees. They can also jump over them with assist from the logs. The game's most definitive feature was the 'Wheelie' feature that allowed players to pull up the handlebars on the cabinet to perform the wheelie.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8be0ebbb-681a-468e-98ca-eaac76a818f7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83701de5-2207-44d9-9cd5-76ad6aea3b5c.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/543522ed-174d-4b03-839e-3954de4c3a87.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/632b2f39-4b66-4391-90a7-a21789d6dd29.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/882f6665-8634-4a2f-a761-d88b747d4e67.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>