<Game>
	<Name>Gain Ground (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Gain Ground is a top down shooter that focuses on tactics. It was developed and published by Sega, and originally an arcade game before being ported to the Master System, Genesis, and Turbografx-16 CD.The Genesis version has since appeared on several compilations, and has been released on Wii Virtual Console.Gameplay:Players begin with three different characters to choose from, and can gain more by saving them and running to the exit. Each character has a normal shot and a special weapon. The special weapons vary; because of the altitude, range, pattern, and angles they shoot at. The characters also have different speeds they move at.There are a total of fifty levels, split into five rounds, each containing 10 stages; all have a boss at the end. There are two ways to complete a level; players can either kill all the enemies or run each characters to the exit zone, though not all stages have an exit. When a character is hit, they are captured and stay at the spot where it happened. That character can be rescued and taken to the exit, where they will be playable again.PC System RequirementsMinimumOS: Windows&#174; XP or higherGraphics: 32MB or greater graphics cardDirectX&#174;: DirectX&#174; 9.0 or greaterHard Drive: 50MB free disc spaceCheat: All characters and level select aka Special ModeWhen starting up your Master System hold down UP and both 1 and 2 on the controller(s) that will be used to play the game until a screen saying Special Mode appears on the screen (after the title screen dissappears). You will now have one of each character and be able to choose the round and the stage that you will play, even on stage 5. Your characters will be restored at the beginning of each stage NOTE: You will not be able to gain additional characters throughout the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>k8H2Y3JZJu8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2751</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588066-gain-ground</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/gain-ground</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gain-ground/3030-13666/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2362896-sms_gainground_au.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2751-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/340650-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen-and.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/340651-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-fighting-enemies.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/340652-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-fighting-in-another.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/340653-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-high-scores.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487685-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-thanks.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487686-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-thing-in-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487687-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-statistics-for-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487688-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-heavy-fire-from.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487689-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487690-gain-ground-sega-master-system-screenshot-round-2-takes-place.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2751.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Gain Ground became a sensation overnight as the newest human vs. Android competition. One day, though, the Mother Computer that controlled the androids went crazy and trapped spectators in the Coliseum. Join the group of skilled fighters who are trying to defeat the system, and save those innocent people from a fate worse than death!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/edb3f4c8-dd97-4fe7-b8bd-87bce88553e7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33cd528e-977c-4026-bcd2-264445809e54.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44cdaafb-7960-4ea7-a044-3764b0d8a65b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5605748-d749-433c-a7f9-9aaae82f9fe3.PNG</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>