<Game>
	<Name>Heroes of the Lance (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Heroes of the Lance is an action-adventure game developed for various home computers and consoles by U.S. Gold and published by Strategic Simulations in 1988. Telling the stories of eight heroes as they traverse across the ruined city of Xak Tsaroth, the game pits players against various enemies leading up to a confrontation with the ancient dragon Khisanth who holds the Disks of Mishakal, an ancient and powerful relic. It is the first in a series of three games developed by U.S. Gold under the Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons name.Gameplay:Differing drastically from Dungeons &amp; Dragons games from the past, Heroes of the Lance's central focus is on side-scrolling action as opposed to role-playing. Although the game would use relevant statistics, spells and rules from the official tabletop game, a difficult to use graphical interface and severe limitation on character use (forcing players to control one at a time, thus limiting creativity) meant that this arcade-like style of gameplay would be short lived for the series as fans rallied against the switch.Characters:NameDescriptionPortraitGoldmoonA human cleric betrothed to Riverwind. Uses a Blue Crystal Staff.Sturm BrightbladeA human fighter. Uses a two-handed sword.Caramon MajereA warrior. Uses a spear and longsword.Raistlin MajereCarmon's brother. A cunning but weak mage. Uses the Staff of Magius.Tanis Half-ElvenMaster swordsman and archer. Leader of the Companions.Tasslehoff BurrfootA pickpocket who uses a hoopak--a type of sling weaponRiverwindOutcast of the Que-Shu tribe and Goldmoon's betrothed. Uses a bow and longsword.Flint FireforgeA fearless dwarf strong at smithing. Uses a battleaxe and throwing axes. KhisanthAn ancient dragon. Holds the Disks of Mishakal. </plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Strategic Simulations, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>HqTC1nIImxs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2824</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/581298-heroes-of-the-lance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/heroes-of-the-lance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/heroes-of-the-lance/3030-14197/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2824-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2824-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/26062-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49582-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49583-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-credits.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49584-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-sturm.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49585-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-ad-d-credits.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49586-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-goldmoon.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49587-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-goldmoon.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49588-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-sturm.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49589-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-caramon.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49590-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-raistlin.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/49591-heroes-of-the-lance-sega-master-system-screenshot-tanis.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Based on the later parts of the Dragonlance book Dragons of Autumn Twilight, the heroes descend into a ruined city in search of the disks of Mishakal. The gameplay consists of horizontal fighting with a maze like map using doors to change the view. The party consists of the 8 Heroes of the Lance, using one at a time and the player can switch between them at any time. Each character has different types of attacks and spells making them more suited to fighting different enemies as well as acting as lives. One of the AD&amp;D games that takes a break from the usual RPG style.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a33bfe7b-88b5-413d-ba3b-894c3d02d2c8.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c629b069-6ea2-47f1-a061-22099a4d2fed.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4c5f9cf0-46a2-48da-aeef-cad9926bdf08.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90748d56-0ede-40da-b729-91f7930b992e.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Strategic Simulations, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>