<Game>
	<Name>James Pond 2 - Codename RoboCod (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:James Pond 2: Codename RoboCod is the second game in the James Pond series, which is also known as Super James Pond. It features the piscine special agent in a new mission at the North Pole. Unlike its free-form predecessor, James Pond 2 is a far more traditional side-scrolling platformer.The game was originally released on the Commodore Amiga, Atari ST and the Sega Genesis in 1991. They were followed with ports to the Amiga CD32, C64, Game Boy, Game Gear, Sega Master System and the Super Nintendo. It has recently received additional graphically enhanced ports for the Nintendo DS, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Network.There have been multiple publishers for the game. The SNES port alone has three: Victor Interactive Software published the game in Japan, American Softworks in the US and Ocean Software in Europe. EA, US Gold and others have published the game on other systems.Gameplay:James Pond 2: Codename Robocod is a side-scrolling platformer which is very similar in feel and gameplay to the early Super Mario Bros. games. The player takes on the role of James Pond; a walking fish with body armor who must free all of the Penguins and Toys that the evil Dr. Maybe has captured. In addition to the more traditional elements of platforming, the player has the ability to extend James' body vertically in order to reach platforms and items. He also has access to a number of vehicles throughout the game, such as cars, biplanes and a flying bath.Trivia:The UK version of the game contains one of the earliest known forms of in-game product placements with the Penguins in the game advertising the "Penguin" chocolate bar by McVities.The SNES version of the game was called Super James Pond in North America, whereas in other regions it was called Super James Pond 2.The Playstation, Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS versions of the game are re-makes rather than ports, with changes to music, level design and art, they are generally considered to be inferior games.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly's Mike Weigand revealed little in his short review of the SNES version of the game other than his review score of 5 out of ten. He wrote, "...James's ability to make himself tall is quite interesting, but that is really the only special thing about him". He suggested that fans of the franchise may prefer Aquatic Games.Cheat: Infinite LivesAt the start of the game go through the first door and head right and past 2 sets of spikes and you will see these items. lips, ice cream, violin, Earth, snowman collect them in that order to give you Infinite LivesCheat: Infinite LivesWhen you first start the game run right and stretch up onto a roof. There are five objects a hammer, an apple, earth, a cake and a tap. Collect them in the following order. Cake, Hammer, Earth, Apple, TapThis spells out the word cheat and makes you invincible for around 10 minutesCheat: Infinite LivesTo restore your health pick up items in this order. penguin, oil can, wine glass, Earth and racket. This Spells out Power</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>Dh97wdIDnok</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2861</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570268-james-pond-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/james-pond-2-codename-robocod</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/james-pond-2-codename-robocod/3030-397/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2861-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2861-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/164369-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2861-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152212-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152213-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152214-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152215-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152216-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152217-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152218-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152219-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/152220-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2861-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2861.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The gameplay takes place across worlds themed around particular types of toys, such as sporting goods, candy and aircraft. The levels scroll sideways, although a small amount of vertical movement is included. On each level Pond must collect 2 penguins and reach the exit, although there are usually multiple exits and lots of secret areas to explore. After completing each pair of two worlds (each of which has three sub levels), a boss must be faced.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f1025df-308d-4dc8-8ecb-2b100cf1aac5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1fb35588-3fc0-42c0-8e42-d3583710704a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fb59af26-9b2a-4d57-9e93-89684cb3bafe.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41465566-caf7-4c01-a790-29f85324d524.PNG</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7028294d-bf64-4ca3-bfaa-ab6f515fbd2c.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Publisher>
</game>