<Game>
	<Name>Kenseiden (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In Kenseiden, you play Hayato, a fearless samurai warrior. You must get back the stolen swords and scrolls, and defeat the evil waiting in the Black Castle!Kenseiden is a one-player game that comprises of sixteen levels. Each of the levels are side-scrolling, with bamboo houses or dank, haunted caves as their backdrop. These levels see Hayato beseigned by ghosts, skeletons, and other spirits of the supernatural. On his side is his curved sword, which he can swish at will against the monsters. If Hayato comes in contact with a monster, he will lose some life.At the end of each level, you will have to fight a warlock or one of their henchmen. More often than not, there is a hut with a sealed door, but the door is not unlocked unless a warlock or henceman is defeated. You gain a new special power whenever you recover a scroll from them. These special powers range from high jumping to the ability to whirl your sword around like a windmill.Cheat: Continue CodeWhen you see the Game Over screen, enter the following to continue at the last round you've played:Cheat: Level SelectBefore you turn on the console, press and hold buttons 1 and 2. Then turn on the Master System and keep hold the buttons until appears the title screen. Let go of all buttons. Now press: diagonal top-left + button 1.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>iEp-eODfYcA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2874</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588089-kenseiden</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/kenseiden</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kenseiden/3030-20283/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2362942-sms_kenseiden.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2874-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/121128-kenseiden-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76020-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76021-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-exploring-the-bamboo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76022-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-an-undead-skeleton.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76023-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-one-of-the-big-guards.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76025-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-map.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76026-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-flying-skulls.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76027-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-watch-out-for-the-spider.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76028-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-stop-you-must-speak.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76029-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-just-your-typical-japan.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76030-kenseiden-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kSHhR01.png</banner1>
	<Notes>It was a land of peace and plenty... until the evil Warlocks returned in a storm of ruin and destruction! Now, they have struck the final blow by stealing your heritage... the Sword of the Dragon King and the Five Secret Scrolls. You are Hayato. The blood of the Dragon King runs in your veins. Armed only with a samurai sword, you must travel through the 16 provinces of ancient Japan, battling the Warlocks and their monstrous armies in nightmare caves and castles! If you defeat the Warlocks, you will learn the sword magic of the scrolls and... maybe... regain the Sword of the Dragon King. Fail, and your country is doomed to a thousand centuries of terror! It is a battle only you can win!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0f048bd-415e-4031-879b-2fd3e1678615.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34fb6c12-c1df-4c5a-a0ed-1f53876dddb0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95dda2f1-e259-4f0d-8fa8-355647209bc4.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8fe15512-7312-4e2b-8c71-b0c06be4d69a.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/de74326c-166e-4a6a-87f2-9d97fcfc1246.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>