<Game>
	<Name>Kung Fu Kid (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kung Fu Kid is a side scrolling beat 'em up that was originally developed and published by Sega for the Sega Master System platform.Brazilian Release ChangesThe Sapo Xul&#233; Toy.In 1995 a version of Kung Fu Kid was released in Brazil with the main character changed to Sapo Xul&#233;. The title of this version is Sapo Xul&#233;: O Mestre do Kung Fu, which means Sapo Xul&#233;: the Master of Kung Fu. Sapo Xul&#233; was a popular toy line in Brazil in the 1980's. This release was developed by Tec Toy.The Sapo Xul&#233; toy that the character was based off of is a frog wearing tennis shoes. The toy came with a satchel of a smelly substance that was placed in the shoes. The reason for this was that when the shoes were removed the feet were supposed to smell bad.Gameplay:The player can jump, leap off of walls, kick, and throw explosive talismans that are collected and powered up. Thugs, animals, and supernatural beings that the evil Madanda has released upon waking from his slumber must be defeated. The game plays as a side-scrolling platformer/beat-em-up, with an agile character that controls very tightly but has a limited move set.There are seven colorful levels of various lengths and difficulty including one level where the player must fight a series of new bosses in rapid succession. Most bosses follow predictable patterns. Talismans, talisman power-ups, health power-ups, and jugs of water that provide protection against fire-breathing enemies can be found when enemies are defeated or when specific hidden areas are discovered. Like most games of the era, the player is sent back to the beginning of a level upon death.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>XO0CtSvcZA8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2439</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588092-kung-fu-kid</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/kung-fu-kid</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kung-fu-kid/3030-12779/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2439-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2439-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/130695-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71933-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/184801-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-japanese-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71934-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-get-ready.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71935-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-round-1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71936-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-jumping.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71937-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-dead.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71938-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-in-the-bamboo-forest.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71939-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71940-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss-hurt.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/71941-kung-fu-kid-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss-trying-to-give.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/fMkmLPZ.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Get ready to perform the martial arts with the precision of a master. Now is the time to accept your fate as the most courageous man alive. You're the invincible Wang. The most skilled Kung Fu artist in the history of ancient China. Armed with the mysterious and traditional Talisman, your talents are the only defense against the wicked Madanda, the most dreaded creature to ever live. He's just awakened from a sleep of several thousand years and his desire is to terrorize your village and devour its people. The battle will be furious. And nobody knows the outcome for sure. So fight with pride and power to send this unnatural force to a final resting place.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b806690b-7dab-4b4e-b5fe-d5a033816a6f.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a87a9ce-f062-4713-8cb3-69f28a588578.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aefab6ee-569e-434c-8b2a-b5c744df23d6.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56b421e8-63d2-4634-aea1-40a923df1bb8.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3443a802-d9ad-42aa-820d-c9bbfc5d3a3d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eeb9c40d-d15a-4c9c-996b-8d65ca236117.PNG</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>