<Game>
	<Name>Maou Golvellius (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Enter the world of Golvellius. Where demons rule the valley of water... and control the creatures of land, sea and air. Where almost everyone stands against you. There is only one way in... and no way out except victory or death! It's an adventure that will take you across deserts and mountains, oceans and forests... through eerie graveyards and caves filled with danger and surprise. Golvellius has a password save feature that lets you keep all your possessions. So you never have to start an adventure empty handed!Cheat: Sound TestYet another use of the up-left-1-2 button combo.  Hold those buttons down while watching the opening sequence.  When the old woman gives you the sword, she'll instead be a sound test.Cheat: Invincibility TrickIf you have all the hearts for your meter, and both the green and purple herbs, fill to full life, then get dropped to nothing.  Let all the herbs get used automaticcaly like normal, but when your last hit is taken off, you won't die.  You'll be invincible until you heal, so don't pick up any of those potions that enemies drop.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Compile</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>NOLWIrQshE8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2802</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588077-golvellius-valley-of-doom</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2802-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2802-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/b/gfs_87386_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/1/gfs_83181_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/1/gfs_83181_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/9/6/gfs_87386_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/4/6/gfs_87386_2_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/f/6/gfs_87386_2_3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/6/gfs_87386_2_4.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/5/6/gfs_87386_2_5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/6/gfs_87386_2_6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/6/gfs_87386_2_7.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2802-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>