<Game>
	<Name>Pit Fighter (Brazil)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pit-Fighter is a fighting game released by Atari Games in 1990. Though it was widely reviled by critics for its lackluster game play and fighting style, it is notable and revolutionary for being the first fighting game to utilize blue screen-captured digitized versions of real people for use as the games characters. This would later be used by the Mortal Kombat series, among others, to greater effect.Characters:Pit-Fighter was short on available fighters, and only three were available at the select screen: Buzz, Ty and Kato. These three fighters operated in a similar fashion gameplay-wise but had their own unique attacks and fighting styles to make up for this.CharacterDescriptionBuzzBuzz is an ex-pro wrestler, has a slow movement speed but makes up for this in his brutal available attacks which included a body slam, a headbutt, and a pile driver.TyTy is slightly faster than Buzz, though not to a great degree. He has great leg reach due to being a kick boxer, and could execute a roundhouse kick, a flying kick and a spin kick.KatoKato is the most agile of the fighters, is the easiest to KO, but uses very formidable Karate skills to make up for this, such as a powerful backhand, a flip kick and a combo punch.There were also eight unplayable characters who were, nonetheless, given a digitized sprite just like the main characters, and were available as opponents as the game progressed.These unplayable characters, in order of appearance, include:Executioner - Wears a hood and flexes his muscles. He is the first available boss.Southside Jim - A black, normal dressing street character, who is extremely fast.Angel - A femme fatale, who has fast combo kicks and incredible agility.C.C. Rider - A generic biker, who has extremely powerful punches but slow speed.Mad Miles - A dreadlocks sporting maniac, has some punishing combos.Heavy Metal - Has a very reminiscent 80's rocker look.Chainman Eddie - Has a chain mail chest and a look close to Bennett from the Arnold Schwarzengger film Commando.Masked Warrior - The final boss, has a terrifying mask and is extremely difficult to KO.PortsThough the arcade version of Pit-Fighter quickly became irrelevant due to the introduction of Mortal Kombat and other highly successful fighters, it was ported to many home consoles and portable devices, which included the Amiga, Atari ST, Commodore 64, Amistrad, SNES, Genesis, Atari Lynx, Sinclair Spectrum and Game Boy. These ports varied widely in quality, though all retained the basic characters and gameplay style that Pit-Fighter was known for.The arcade version of Pit-Fighter was also featured in a recent greatest hit compilation known as Midway Arcade Treasures 2, which was available on Playstation 2, Xbox and Gamecube, as well as a PC-only compilation named Midway Arcade Treasures Deluxe Edition.Cheat: Minigame and MessagesGet a high score and enter one of these as your name:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Domark Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>IwxtuLn2QpE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2966</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570265-pit-fighter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/pit-fighter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pit-fighter/3030-12530/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14206/1033815-pf2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/275739-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/275740-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72346-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72317-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72318-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-pick-your-character.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72319-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-get-psyched.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72322-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-they-change-colour.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72323-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-end-of-match.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72325-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-southside-jim.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72326-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-continue.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72330-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-executioner.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/72331-pit-fighter-sega-master-system-screenshot-hes-hopping-mad.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In the Pit, it's mean, it's tough and it's no place for the fainthearted. Take on all comers - the fighting's below the belt and rules don't exist. Survival and the prize are all that matter. Welcome to the world of the Pitfighter!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad57cc58-e6eb-41a8-a92d-4366d99d91ce.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa8fabce-29ac-4cc5-b373-b7fdd2be98e6.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Domark</Publisher>
</game>