<Game>
	<Name>Poseidon Wars 3-D (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In Poseidon Wars 3-D, you have just entered the navy as a cadet and you must make your way up to Admiral. To do this, you must go out at sea with a submarine and destroy several enemy targets. Once you have defeated each enemy target, the mission is completed, and, upon completing some of them, your rank increases. Before defeating each target, however, you also need to destroy enemy jets, choppers, and submarines who will launch missiles or rockets at you. If you are hit by any of these, damage is inflicted to the submarine, but you can shoot down any of the missiles or rockets. You will need to keep an eye on the built-in radar and sonar to find out where enemies will hit next. Your fuel is limited, and can be increased by destroying certain enemies. The game ends when your submarine is destroyed or you run out of fuel.Cheat: Infinite ContinuesIf you get a Game Over, and want to continue playing, wait until the Game Over screen shows up. Then, enter Down, Down, Down, Down, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Left. This will reward you with a continue.Cheat: Infinite ContinuesIn the beginning of the game, when the start option falls down on the screen, press Up, Left, Left, Down, Down, Down, Right, Right, Right, Right.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>XoiGKg2iBEI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2971</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588118-poseidon-wars-3-d</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/poseidon-wars-3-d</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/poseidon-wars-3-d/3030-20312/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2971-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/72462-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/72463-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93419-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93420-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-mission-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93421-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-battling-it.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93422-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-i-m-hit.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93423-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-land-ho-land.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93424-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-your-first.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93425-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-mission-completed.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93426-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-some-helicopters.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93427-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-another-enemy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93428-poseidon-wars-3-d-sega-master-system-screenshot-night-has-fallen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Battle Stations! Battle Stations! Your country is being attacked. You'll be fighting on the U.S.S. Poseidon; an armor-plated attack cruiser with radar, sonar, 76mm cannons and surface-to-surface missiles. First come the training rounds. They'll throw everything they have at you... jets, cruisers, torpedoes, cannons. And then the fun really starts! Combat missions! You're on the open seas. You have blips on the radar. Line up your gunsights and let 'em have it. You pick up an enemy cruiser on your sonar. Get ready with an armor piercing missile and send them to Davey Jones locker. If you complete your missions, you will be awarded with the Navy's highest honor... a promotion to Fleet Admiral.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e9e25b1-2289-4e63-922c-7b3643e59569.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e760fb9f-f905-4dc5-ad86-08cfe9b2dd21.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>