<Game>
	<Name>Pro Wrestling (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dump Matsumoto is a tag-team wrestling game developed and released by Sega, for the Sega System 16 Arcade system and the Sega Master System (SMS) console, both versions of which are known outside Japan as Body Slam and Pro Wrestling, respectively. While the latter shares a name with the Nintendo-developed release Pro Wrestling for the NES, the games are entirely unrelated.Players choose from one of four tag-teams and face the other three teams repeatedly, ten falls at a time. After winning ten matches against a team, the game advances to the next team. In the Japanese version the wrestlers were all women (the game's namesake, Dump Matsumoto, was one of these female wrestlers). In the US, they were all changed to male wrestlers that superficially resembled those working in the WWE (then WWF) circuit at the time.The original Arcade version allowed players to form custom duos composed of two members from each faction. Both the Arcade and SMS versions were originally released in Japan as a celebrity tie-in for the Japanese female wrestler Dump Matsumoto.Tag TeamsMad SoldiersOrient ExpressGreat MaskmenCrush Brothers Cheat: Challenge the alien championsTo challenge the alien champions, press any direction, 25 times at the game over screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>Pm3e51r1K1w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2978</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588122-pro-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/pro-wrestling_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pro-wrestling/3030-4962/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2978-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2978-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/134374-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412568-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-rage-fueled.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412569-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-team-select.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412570-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-10-falls.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412571-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-mad-soldiers-entrance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412572-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-orient-express.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412573-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-kick.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412574-pro-wrestling-sega-master-system-screenshot-down.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728611-7020032255-3WKYJ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728610-3089176978-utNqx.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2728609-6882669504-h1CVFJc2.png+</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The single player game has the player selecting one of four sets of tag teams: THE CRUSH BROTHERS - two European blonde men, one big and older and one younger and smaller THE ORIENT EXPRESS - two Asian men, one smaller (Dragonfly) and one bigger and bearded (Giant Bull) THE MAD SOLDIERS - stereotypical powerhouse team of Muscle and Iron in the vein of the Road Warriors THE GREAT MASKMEN - two mysterious masked wrestlers, one in green (Green Mask) and one in gray (Stone Head)</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63aa795c-a345-477d-bdc1-91a8eb6623ec.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/09386726-8a05-48b8-8937-f8c872df5f54.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>