<Game>
	<Name>R-Type (Unknown) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:R-Type is a classic side scrolling shoot-em up game produced by Irem Corp. The game was first released to Japanese arcades in July 1987. The player controls a spacecraft and is tasked with defending humanity against the alien life forms known as Bydo. R-Type is infamously known for its extreme difficulty.R-Type was originally released in the Arcades and became a major early hit for Irem. It was eventually ported to many home computers and consoles of the era, with the unusual exception of the NES (a bootleg Chinese cart exists, however). The PC Engine of R-Type was split across two releases, but the US TG-16 version manages to fit the whole game onto one HuCard. This TG16 version is also the one that was added to the Wii's Virtual Console in 2006.R-Type also saw multiple sequels and spin-offs, as well as inspiring many future horizontal-scrolling shoot 'em ups.Gameplay:Set in the 22nd century, the game takes place in the Bydo Empire. The player must make their way through the 8 merciless levels and defend mankind from the evil attackers. Bydo Dobkeratops - Boss of the first levelThe Bydo are biologically engineered weapons created by mankind to be used against their enemies in their quest for universal domination. This plan backfired however and the Bydo began to attack their creators.  The Ship The player pilots a ship called the R-9a "Arrowhead". The ship is named for its distinctive shape and is the 9th model of the R series of star fighter. The ForceThe R-9a "Arrowhead" can be equipped with an indestructible living weapon called "The Force". The force, a spherical pod that can be attached to the ship, is made of Bydo flesh and can absorb energy in order to increase in power. To obtain the force, the player must obtain a weapon power up. The force will appear behind the players ship and they can obtain the force by flying into it. The force acts as the ship's weapon system and will fire in the whatever direction it is facing. The force also acts as a shield and can be used to block incoming enemy attacks. The force has three levels of power. Collecting weapon power ups increases the power level of the force. The forces visual appearance changes as it increases in power.Red - A powerful counter-air laser beam that fires horizontally.Blue - Three thin laser beams. One forward firing and two that fire at a 45 degree angle from the front of the ship These beams rebound off walls.Yellow - Two flame beams that fire above and below the ship. These flames can travel along the ground or walls to destroy enemies.The force can be controlled by the user by using the force button. By pressing the force button, the user can attach the force to the front or the rear of the ship. They can also propel the force forward to execute an attack called the "force ram". Wave CannonThe R9-a is equipped with a beam weapon called the wave cannon. Holding the fire button will charge up the wave cannon and increase its power. Wave Cannon    Cheat: Extra ContinuesPush in a clockwise circle to get free continues.  Keep going in circles until time is about to expire, then hit button 1.  This can earn you up to 12 continues.  You don't have to get all 12 in one try. When those are expired, push the pad counter-clockwise to bring up the sound test.  Hold button 2 and go right to sound 62.  Play it 3 times then exit the test.  Then resume the clockwise circles to earn more continues.  After getting 30 more, you will need to replay sound 62 3 times again to get more.Cheat: Secret LevelIn the stage with all the green cells (either Level 4 or 5), look for a section about 45 seconds in where the top border suddenly has a gap about 3 ship lengths long.  Fly  into the gap and move backwards.  If you're quick and the back edge doesn't scroll off screen, you will teleport to a bonus stage.  As a note, the boss of the secret stage doesn't flash when he's hit, unlike all the others. Cheat: Access the Sound TestIn the continue screen, rotate the D-Pad in a counter clockwise direction until the sound test screen comes up. Inputing 00 will return you to the continue screen and if button 2 is held during choosing the various sounds, sounds 01 to 95 would be available.&amp;lt;p /&amp;gt; Cheat: Access the Sound TestYou need to have 2 controllers and plug them both in. With the system off, on controller 1, hold Down-Right, and on controller 2, hold Up-Left + Button 1. Turn on the system. After R-Type finishes flashing across the screen, you can let go. This usually takes a few tries to accomplish.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>Y7BgS78b4t0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2996</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/563497-r-type</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/r-type</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/r-type/3030-13745/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1253970-rtype_amiga_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2996-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/71839-r-type-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50285-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-wave-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50286-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50287-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-entering-base.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50288-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-destroyed.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50289-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50290-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-boss-2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50291-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-centipede.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50292-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-made-it-through.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50293-r-type-sega-master-system-screenshot-entering-another-base.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2712461-rtype003.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2996-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2996-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aryuSDJ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2996.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>R-Type is set in the 22nd century, and the player flies a futuristic fighter craft called the R-9a "Arrowhead", named for its shape, and because it is the ninth model in the 'R' series of fighter craft (but it is the first of the series to actually be used in combat; the previous models were all prototypes). The mission is to 'blast off and strike the evil Bydo Empire'. The significance of the R- in the series title refers to the production code as well as the term of endearment for the player fighter craft, the "Round Canopy".</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5a8bc26-97b4-40ad-aa5b-e7fc3811d012.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/55700331-01d7-45ee-99b5-702bed3a745d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>