<Game>
	<Name>Rainbow Islands - Story of the Bubble Bobble 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The story of Bubble Bobble continues! Bubby is on a magical, mysterious journey. The good people of the Rainbow Islands are being held prisoner, and only Bubby's rainbow power can save them!Cheat: World SelectAt the title screen, push the following in this order: Left, Button 2, Right, Up, Down, Left, Right and Button 2. The words ''PRESS START BUTTON'' will be replaced by ''WORLD 1'', press button 2 to change the world number and button 1 to select the world.Cheat: Unlock The Real Last LevelIn each island, collect 7 small Gems of each color and after beating the boss of the island, you'll get the big Gem. Do the same thing on each island to get the 7 big Gems. Once you beat the boss of the 7th island, instead of getting the bad ending, you'll proceed to a final 8th island.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>ITL</Developer>
	<VideoURL>WMTzBEjijHs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2986</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570216-rainbow-islands</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2986-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2986-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/d/gfs_88145_2_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/d/gfs_88145_2_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2986-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>The basic premise of the game is that each level is an island which is slowly sinking into the sea. The player must therefore get to the top of each level, by jumping on platforms and making use of the game's most distinctive feature: the ability to produce solid rainbows, which are used both as platforms to stand on, and as a weapon.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bdf86836-d548-46be-8892-43585b4ea211.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d8b26a2-f28a-413c-9679-e607c605173a.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>