<Game>
	<Name>Rampage (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:City being destroyed by a monster!Rampage was first released in arcades in 1986 by Bally Midway. Taking inspiration from giant-monster movies like Godzilla and King Kong, Rampage puts players in the role of one of three oversized monsters-- George the ape, Lizzie the lizard, and Ralph the wolf.The players start wreaking havoc in Peoria, Illinois, then cut a path of destruction through the United States. In the arcade version, the monsters' attacks take place over 128 days. After those days end, the cities start to repeat, and after five cycles you get to day 768 and the days reset to 1. The console iterations had an actual ending added. The goal in each stage is to knock down every building in the city. The monsters can climb up the sides of buildings and punch out sections of their walls, occasionally eating the hapless humans that they find inside. Take out enough pieces of a building and it will come crashing down. Watch out, though--the National Guard is out in force and will harass the monsters with tanks and jets. If enough damage is taken, the monster will revert to its original human form, sans clothes. In a multiplayer situation, any remaining monsters can grab and eat the ex-monster.Rampage has seen a number of remakes and sequels over the years with varying degrees of success. Follow-ups include Rampage World Tour, Rampage 2: Universal Tour, Rampage Through Time, and Rampage Puzzle Attack, though none of them have garnered the same positive response as the original.Cheat: Continue GameWhen you loose all health on your last life, keep pressing Button 2 until you leave the screen as a Human.  If successful, you should return to the game as the Monster you picked at the beginning of the game with a score reset back to 0.Cheat: Bonus livesIn each level, there is a woman in a yellow dress - find her and eat her for a bonus life in each level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1988</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>KDL9FSXlhIA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2988</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588128-rampage</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/rampage</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rampage/3030-4940/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2988-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2988-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/253264-rampage-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2988-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50295-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50299-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-copyright.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50300-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-select-character.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50294-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-get-that-car.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50296-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-smashing-the-building.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50297-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-rampage.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50298-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-eat-that-guy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50301-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-level-2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50302-rampage-sega-master-system-screenshot-building-goes-down.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AlSfxCN.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2988.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Rampage players take control of gigantic monsters trying to survive against onslaughts of military forces. Each round is completed when a particular city is completely reduced to rubble. Up to three simultaneous players control the monsters George (a King Kong-like gorilla), Lizzie (a Godzilla-like dinosaur/lizard), or Ralph (a giant werewolf), created from mutated humans.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d29d25d4-521a-4dc5-820f-4efe9248e0d0.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f59ed786-f4ec-4540-80cf-951b7310eebd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5615077c-aab7-4be5-b639-ae6345bc64b3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5ee68752-cd92-412e-8453-99ba0ff67b76.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>