<Game>
	<Name>Road Rash (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Road Rash is an aggressive motorcycle racing game where the player assumes the role of a biker who takes part in a series of illegal races across the U.S.A. Starting at the back of the pack the objective is always to finish first on a linear course, overtaking the other bikers. This is achieved by driving very well or by playing it dirty, knocking opponents of their bikes using clubs, crowbars or your bare hands. The other racers fight back in a similar fashion and there are also hazards. All the races take place on the regular road with normal traffic (in both directions) and the cops, as well as occasional oil slicks and stray cows.By winning races you can get promoted to a stronger division and earn cash with which you can buy a better bike. Whenever you're knocked off your bike or hit something you will have to run back to your bike and lose valuable time, plus your bike will suffer some damage. When the player crashes with cops nearby, it is possible to get busted and then you have to forfeit the race.Like the whole Road Rash lineage, the game has arcade-like gameplay with no intention to be a motorcycle simulation. While the game has a two-player mode, this is not simultaneous.Cheat: Start on Level 4 with 10,000 DollarsType As a Password 00001 01R60 10839 4Q2LNCheat: Start on Level 4 with 10,000 DollarsEnter the following at the password screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8QDVV-75C10</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2557</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570267-road-rash</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/road-rash</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/road-rash/3030-8251/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2557-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2557-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142273-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-u-s-gold-logo.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142274-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-probe-logo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142275-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142276-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-course-selection.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142277-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-biff-gives-advice.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142280-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-sierra-nevada.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142283-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-natasha-gives-advice.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142289-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-sledge-gives-advice.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142291-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-redwood-forest.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142290-road-rash-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-nice-little-jump.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/EaGzOPW.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2557.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Presented in a third-person view similar to Hang-On, the player competes in illegal road races and must finish in the top 3 places in every race in order to proceed to the next level. As levels progress, the opponents ride faster, fight harder and the tracks are longer and more dangerous. Placing in each race gives a certain amount of money which increases considerably as levels progress. This money allows the player to buy faster bikes which are needed to stay competitive. The game is over if the player can't pay for the repairs when their motorcycle is wrecked, or can't pay the fine for being arrested.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f83ce83d-ac8f-4c72-ad5d-73d6df5b7ed2.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/672a4266-4acb-4dcc-8ffe-d311c87deb73.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fdb8553-71dd-4a97-a882-b55781cb3b19.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold</Publisher>
</game>