<Game>
	<Name>RoboCop versus The Terminator (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:RoboCop Versus the Terminator is a licensed action game that hypothetically pits the two eponymous cyborg movie characters against each other, placing RoboCop in the role of the savior of humanity from Skynet and its legion of T-800s and other robots. It is based on a comic book series with the same premise.In the near future, the worlds of RoboCop and The Terminator merge into a single reality. RoboCop is placed in charge with saving mankind by destroying the Skynet super computer and preventing a possible future where machines reign supreme. The player, as RoboCop, must traverse 10 levels of action, fighting against thugs and machines alike, all while utilizing a combination of pistols, laser guns, bazookas and even the deadly ED-209 Gatling gun. The player can destroy Skynet and save the world. The game was released for Sega Genesis, Super Nintendo, Sega Master System, Game Boy, and Game Gear. An NES version was developed but never officially released.The SNES and Genesis versions have slightly different stages and stories, though are similar games in practice. The NES and Game Boy games are similar to the SNES game, while the Sega Master System and Game Gear versions are similar to the Genesis game.Levels (Sega Genesis version)Level 1 - Trainer LevelLevel 2 - Streets of DetroitLevel 3 - Delta City under ConstructionLevel 4 - The Toxic FarmLevel 5 - OCP office ComplexLevel 6 - Terminator OutpostLevel 7 - Underground ComplexLevel 8 - Underground BunkerLevel 9 - The wall to SkynetLevel 10 - SkynetCheat: Change WeaponsStart the game and press pause. Then, press Up+1, Down+1, Down+1, Up+2, Down+2, Up+2, Up+1, Up+1. This will earn you nine extra lives.Cheat: Change WeaponsStart the game and press pause. Then, press Down+2, Down+1, Up+2, Down+2, Down+2, Up+1, Down+2, Up+1. This will skip the current level.Cheat: Change WeaponsStart the game and press pause. Then, press Up+1, Down+1, Up+2, Down+1, Down+1, Down+2. You will now be able to select any weapon you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>B013h9S3Jxs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2994</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588132-robocop-versus-the-terminator</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/robocop-versus-the-terminator</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/robocop-versus-the-terminator/3030-12494/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2994-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2994-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/93199-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59202-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59204-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59205-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59206-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59207-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59208-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59209-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59210-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59211-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59212-robocop-versus-the-terminator-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2994-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2994-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<Notes>In the future, human soldiers of John Conner's resistance force against the machines are fighting a losing war against Skynet and it's robot forces. Discovering that one of the foundation technologies for Skynet is the cybernetics technology used in the creation of Robocop. One of the resistances' soldiers, Flo is sent back in time before the Rise of the Machines to destroy Robocop and stop Skynet from being built. However Skynet learns of the time travel attempt and sends Terminators to stop Flo. In the game you control Robocop who may move across the screen, jump, fire and exchange weapons. Robocop starts with the Auto-9 which has unlimited ammunition... other weapons may be more powerful but contain limited ammo.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe57df78-1597-47d4-80ff-ec3409a3c29f.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15c0b54a-7d7e-40d9-8ab2-606f08f30fef.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Virgin Games</Publisher>
</game>