<Game>
	<Name>Secret Command (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>You are Rambo, the super hero of the movies. And you come to life on your own screen. You must go deep into enemy territory to rescue your comrades from concentration camps. Blow those camps. And escape with your skin. It's no picnic. You're menaced by infantry. Artillery. Flame throwers and rocket launchers. Everything the enemy can throw at you. So you must use every tactic at your command. Your weapons? Your M-60. A supply of arrow-bombs. Your savage strength. And steel nerves. Play the game by yourself. Or with your partner. Alone or together, you'll find yourself in the middle of enough color and action for a battalion to take on. And remember. You take no prisoners.Cheat: ContinueTo continue, have both players must hold down 1 + 2 and rapidly press Left and Right. This only works after level 3.Cheat: ContinueIf you run out of lives on a stage, enter one of the following codes at the title screen depending on what level you died on. For example if you died on level 2, press down, up, left, right to continue from that level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>WITYnVFbroI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3002</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/925764-rambo-first-blood-part-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/secret-commando</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rambo-first-blood-part-ii/3030-7663/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3002-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/7/0/41970_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1186970-fusion_2009_11_07_09_59_37_53.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1186969-fusion_2009_11_07_09_59_16_35.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1186968-fusion_2009_11_07_09_59_03_07.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1186967-fusion_2009_11_07_09_57_30_08.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1186966-fusion_2009_11_07_09_57_16_61.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2238/382094-ramboii_spec_19.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2238/382093-ramboii_spec_18.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2238/382092-ramboii_spec_17.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2238/382091-ramboii_spec_16.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2238/382090-ramboii_spec_15.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Secret Command is a top-down action/shoot-'em-up developed and published by Sega for the Sega Master System. Secret Command was released several times under different names. In Japan, it is known as Ashura. In North America it was tied with the Rambo movie franchise and renamed Rambo: First Blood Part II (with only minor graphics and music changes occurring between releases). In Europe and in later re-releases of the game, it is labeled as Secret Command, however the title screen reads Secret Commando.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d94307ea-30e5-4a5f-be1c-57e70344e10e.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0646806b-f27e-49dc-ab65-3e991e04bfe2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>