<Game>
	<Name>Shadow of the Beast (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>While very young, Aarbron was kidnapped and enslaved by the Priests of the Beast Lord. He grew up on drugs made to destroy his own will and turn him into the Beast Messenger, a powerful creature serving Maletoth, The Beast Lord himself. He did his job, until one day he noticed a man about to be sacrificed in a ritual, his face triggering ancient memories... and as the sacrificial knife descended into the man's body, Aarbron recognizes the face. Of his father.As his father dies in the altar, memories of his childhood and tormented past at the hands of the Beast Lord emerged, and as feelings of hate over his captors took over him, he swore revenge and fled the temple, knowing the road to avenge his father and redemption would be hard.Shadow of the Beast, one of Psygnosis most popular titles during the 16-bit computer era is a side-scrolling platformer best known for the use of parallax scrolling along lush graphics, a musical score  by David Whittaker, a iconic cover by Roger Dean and what many consider to be unforgiving gameplay, balancing between the "very challenging" and the "impossible". The player has to navigate through several areas filled with enemies and traps, collecting keys and activating triggers than open new areas or give Aarbron the means to overcome a sub-boss. The number of moves the player has at disposal is limited: duck, jump and only two attacks: punch and a flying kick. While most enemies die with just one hit, the player must time each attack accurately. However, there are also traps of objects that cannot be destroyed, and these require the player to jump, duck or move according the sequence. The player has only one life with 12 hit points that can be replenished by collecting some objects hidden in the level (like an off-route location or a under a megalith), which also contributes to the difficulty level.Cheat: Extra LifeDrop a coin down the well at the start of Level 3 to get an extra life.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Psygnosis Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>2KmyfWn2SO8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3007</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588138-shadow-of-the-beast-1992</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/shadow-of-the-beast</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shadow-of-the-beast/3030-7681/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3007-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89348-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89349-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141632-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141640-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-thy-fate.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141635-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-beast.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141638-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-a-bleak.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141639-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-hitting.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141641-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-inventory.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141642-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-giant-claws.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141644-shadow-of-the-beast-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-nasty.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2729101-7256010456-YD6WR.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2729100-7338546149-ca7qZ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3007.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>From beyond the edge of darkness the warrior cries revenge. Shadow of the Beast is unleashed on the Master System in a superlative arcade adventure. Relentless combat as the Beast battles over 100 different alien forms in eight hostile regions of a supernatural world. It feels so real - you can almost taste knuckle!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>2KmyfWn2SO8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ac07a49-cc1e-4219-a1e3-080c051283a4.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71e9b9fb-eb2a-41f8-8ed7-cfc911556145.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>TecMagik</Publisher>
</game>