<Game>
	<Name>Star Wars (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:This game is based entirely on the first Star Wars movie, Episode IV: A New Hope. The opening of the game features an animated cinematic of the opening scene of the film. After that the player takes control of  Luke Skywalker, driving the  landspeeder across  Tatooine in search of  R2-D2.   Luke Skywalker explores various locations throughout Tatooine, fighting numerous enemies including Jawas and Stormtroopers. The game features many locations from the movie including the Chalmun's Cantina in Mos Eisley where Luke meets Han Solo for the first time. This section of the game features a classic 8-bit rendition of the "Cantina Band" theme as played by the fictitious band, Figrin D'an and the Modal Nodes, in the feature film. The game also contains many famous lines from the movie including Obi-Wan Kenobi's plea to Luke to join him in his trip to Alderann and Han Solo's description of the smell from the Death Star's trash compactor.   The player eventually lands on the  Death Star and has to destroy the tractor beam to escape. The game also features first person segments of piloting the  Millenium Falcon through that Asteroid field that was once  Alderaan, and shooting down  Tie Fighters in both the Millenium Falcon and an  X-Wing fighter. The finale of the game features a top down view of Luke Skywalker's X-Wing flying through the Death Star trenches. After the player successfully fires a torpedo into the Death Star's exposed exhaust port, a cinematic of the Death Star exploding and Luke Skywalker being awarded a medal on Yavin IV is shown. The game featured the characters Luke Skywalker,  Han Solo,  Obi-Wan Kenobi,  Princess Leia, R2-D2, and C-3PO. The game however does not feature  Darth Vader or  Chewbacca, both of whom are major characters in the film.Cheat: Stage SelectAt the Title Screen press Right, Up, Down, Right, Up, Down, Right, Up, Down, Right, Right, Right on the title screen. Lose a life and you will see a stage select at the continue screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>-UXWPA_5lc4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3030</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/575967-star-wars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/star-wars_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-wars/3030-54/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3030-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/164512-star-wars-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/164513-star-wars-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412616-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412617-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-opening-cinema.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412618-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-surface.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/412619-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-cave.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487400-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-was-it-so-hard-to.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487401-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487402-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-chase-between.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487403-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-meeting-c3po.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487404-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-inside-the-jawas-transporter.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/487405-star-wars-sega-master-system-screenshot-jawas-jump-very-high.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3030-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NuvpZMY.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3030.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Your mission: Rescue Princess Leia from Darth Vader's EVIL clutches! Seek help from Obi-Wan Kenobi and Han Solo, but first you must find them. Finally, blast your last, fatal missile and destroy the Dark Side's headquarters... and MAY THE FORCE BE WITH YOU!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>8UJMY2PZMmE</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/19847e59-8a45-4338-8833-01baf4b9e37a.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/110aed3c-5690-4820-ab52-42c0955a3ac7.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5629244f-37cc-4c48-9e5d-a91bb72d73d3.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Publisher>
</game>