<Game>
	<Name>Super Monaco GP (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The game was released in arcades in 1989 and for the Sega Mega Drive in 1990 and is an arcade racing game in the style of Formula One.Although the original arcade version of the game consisted of the one circuit, a re-imagination of the Circuit de Monaco, the Sega Mega Drive port has a world championship mode, which consists of 16 race weekends. The 1989 F1 season is used as a basis for circuits and drivers, although the drivers only loosely resemble the real world counterparts.Gameplay:The arcade version of the game was simpler in design than the Mega Drive counterpart, featuring only the one track. The player chooses between automatic or manual transmission and then begins qualifying. The player must qualify in under 45 seconds to progress to the race. In the race mode, the player must stay in front of a certain position in the field. This begins at 20th, but increases as the player reaches checkpoints, finally ending at 3rd place.In the Mega Drive version, The player can fail to qualify and begin the race from the back of the grid.The World championship mode, not featured in the arcade version, gave the goal of winning a season, with points being awarded similar to the real life sport. To add replay value, one the season is over the player goes on to defend the title. In the second season the player is given a seat at the games fictional super team, and is assigned a difficult rival.In this mode, the player drives for team Minarae, and is able to choose another driver as his rival. If the player beats the rival in 2 consecutive race weekends, the rivals team will offer a place to the player. This allows the player to drive for faster cars, and acts as a difficulty curve.If the player wins two championships, the game is considered over.DriversClass ADriver NameDriver TeamReal world DriverReal world Equivalent TeamA. AsselinMadonnaAlain ProstHonda Marlboro McLarenF. ElsserFirenzeGerhard BergerScuderia FerrariG.AlbertiMillionsRiccardo PatreseWilliams GP EngineeringA. PicosBestowalNelson PiquetBenetton Formula 1Class BDriver NameDriver TeamReal world DriverReal world Equivalent TeamJ. HerbinBlancheJean AlesiBrabham / Motor Racing DevelopmentsM. HamanoTyrantSatoru NakajimiTyrrell RacingE. PachecoLoselLuis P&#232;rez-SalaTeam LotusG. TurnerMayJohnny HerbertMarch EngineeringClass CDriver NameDriver TeamReal world DriverReal world Equivalent TeamB. MillerBulletsEddie CheeverFootwork ArrowsE. BelliniDardanAndrea De CesarisDallara AutomobiliM. MoreauLindenRen&#232; ArnouxLigier lotoPLAYERMinaraeN/AMinardi F1 TeamClass DDriver NameDriver TeamReal world DriverReal world Equivalent TeamR. CotmanRigelNigel MansellRial RacingE. TornioCometJJ LehtoScuderia ColoniC. TechnerOrchisStefan JohanssonOnyxP. KlingerZeroforceBernd SchneiderZakspeedAn additional Driver becomes the players main rival after winning the first championship:G. CearaBulletsAyrton SennaFootwork ArrowsCircuitsThe Mega Drive version features 16 race weekends:Autodromo Enzo e Dino Ferrari, San Marino. (Commonly called "Imola")Jacarepagua, Brazil. (Now named "Nelson Piquet International Autodrome".)Paul Ricard Circuit, France.Hungaroring, Hungary.Hockenheimring, Germany. (Full name "Hockenheinring Baden-W&#252;rttemberg" but usually just referred to as "Hockenheim".)Pheonix Street Circuit, USA.Circuit Cilles Villeneuve, Canada.Silverstone Circuit, United Kingdom.Autodromo Nazionale Monza, Italy. (Commonly called "Monza".)Autodromo do Estoril, Portugal. (Officially called "Autodromo Fernanda Pieres de Silva".)Circuito Permanente de Jerez, Spain.Autodromo Hermanos Rodriguez, Mexico. (Rodriguez Brothers Racetrack.)Suzuka Circuit, Japan.Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps, Belgium. (Commonly called "Spa".)Adelaide Street Circuit, Australia.Circuit De Monaco, Monaco. (Street Sircuit in Monte Carlo, in which the game takes it's name.)Trivia:Sega had law suit filed against them because the unlicenced use of the Marlboro trademark was seen to advertise to children.. However, all advertisements were misspelled and altered with the exception of an advert for another Sega Game.Pressing A, B, and C as you cross the finish line changes the trophy ceremony. The Driver will hold his head in his hands instead of lifting the trophy.The game was the first racing game to have a rear-view mirror.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>yv8dxIsUzNU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3040</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588153-super-monaco-gp</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/super-monaco-gp</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-monaco-gp/3030-532/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3040-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/42165-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/42166-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140169-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-intro-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140170-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140172-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-name-entry.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140173-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-vs-battle-setup.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140174-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-machine-settings.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140175-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-vs-battle-run.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140176-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-g-p-setup.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/140177-super-monaco-gp-sega-master-system-screenshot-grand-prix-on.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/702843-1118955280_04.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/702838-1118955280_03.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Fly up the track on long straightaways, or downshift into neck-wrenching hairpin curves. Super Monaco GP sends you screaming around the most demanding tracks on earth in the hottest racecar ever built - the Formula 1. Choose your car's transmission. Slide through a practice run with an automatic transmission or battle rival drivers grinding gears to victory piloting a 3, 5, or 7-speed machine. The on-screen track display gives you the lay of the road and position of the other drivers. Super Monaco GP's World Championship sends you and your pit crew on a 16-race international circuit. Burn rubber with the best drivers around in a piston-pounding test of speed, road savvy, and endurance.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fbccbcb-1ade-46aa-9c16-a92473161389.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd38db07-811a-418c-a6bd-44733fb00b32.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc6959d8-acaf-4aec-9083-72de5cedaa6e.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/683a0cd3-ee7d-40ee-991e-737ae6e582de.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c7690bc-8067-4552-8c9c-d9d3b025b6d6.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>