<Game>
	<Name>Teddy Boy (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Teddy Boy Blues was originally an 1985 Arcade platformer that was later ported to the Sega Master System (which was still then known as the Sega-1000 Mark III) and became one of its launch titles when the system was released in Japan in October the same year. A Sega Genesis version was released only in Japan on Sega MegaNet and in compilations. The title comes from a song released in 1985 entitled Teddy Boy Blues and was performed by Yohko Ishino.When the game was localized to the US and Europe, the title was changed to simply Teddy Boy.Connections to Alex KiddTeddy has a few strange connections with SEGA's original mascot Alex Kidd. First, an enemy that appeared originally in Teddy Boy later appeared in Alex Kidd in Miracle World. The left image is from Teddy Boy and on the right is from Alex Kidd in Miracle World. This enemy is a daruma which is a popular Japanese Buddhist symbol.A secret screen found in the game QuartetAnother connection occurred in the Sega Master System port of the 1986 arcade game Quartet (also known as Double Target). A hidden screen within the game contains Mary, one of the game's heroes, as well as Opa Opa from Fantasy Zone, the main character from Pit Pot, Alex Kidd and Teddy Boy.Cheat: Access Cheat MenuIn the title screen, press Up, Down, Left, Right on the control pad.Cheat: Access Cheat MenuIn the title screen, press Up, Down, Left, Right on the control pad to access a secret cheat menu.  In the menu, press Up, 8 x Down and Button I to be able to select a level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1986</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>blN_3elwK1I</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3052</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588157-teddy-boy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/teddy-boy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teddy-boy/3030-16551/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3052-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3052-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/301138-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92714-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92715-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-get-ready-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92716-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-round-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92717-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-get-the-balls-quickly.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92718-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-or-these-little-guys.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92719-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-round-2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92720-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-bonus-game.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92721-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-bonus-game-statistics.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92722-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-round-3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92723-teddy-boy-sega-master-system-screenshot-put-mustaches-on-balls.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QEtPXs1.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Teddy Boy stars a young boy who is armed with a gun. Each level is an infinitely repeating maze with several dice. Each die is filled with monsters which hatch out and the player must shoot to shrink, then collect them. If the player does not collect each shrunken monster quickly, it turns into a time-eating bug which flies to the time limit bar and consumes a chunk of it. If you touch one monster or run out of time then you lose a life. The game ends if all lives are lost.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36dc5684-8b60-4586-8870-3d9265dda930.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6216ddfc-553c-4b74-b3e2-7d57a559d891.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c9efd54d-a8b5-43f3-a75d-af44210c50ee.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/469b8b36-8ed0-4126-a516-2b6c9014252a.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c019fa8-b3d1-417e-a980-df8a1e6dd346.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c8da1f8-a1c9-4fa5-9926-141d5911aa37.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/066248c0-5347-472f-8601-1696e5408e90.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/963a0b2d-d55a-4cf8-82c9-81cf71ba78fa.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>