<Game>
	<Name>Tennis Ace (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:On your first serve, the ball explodes off your racquet like a fiery missile. Instinctively you move toward the net. your opponent returns your serve, but you're ready for him. with lightning speed you raise your racquet and smash the ball. He never had a chance. You're the Tennis Ace! ~ From the blurb on the back of the case.   Game Modes- Training Match- In the training match, you play to practice and improve your skill level. This mode can be selected only when one person is playing. The first to win three games wins the match. Exhibition Match- If one person is playing, select either single play (player 1 vs the computer) or doubles (player 1 vs computer, computer, computer) when two are playing, you can choose to play at the same time (against each other, or doubles against the computer, or doubles against each other), or take turns.Grand Slam Tournament- When you select this option, a map of the world will be displayed on the screen, showing the various countries in which you will compete, one at a time. The sequence includes: Japan, Australia, Italy, France, and the United States.    Singles play commences first. You will be displayed at the top of the roster. When singles play is over, doubles play will start.   If you win three consecutive matches in singles and doubles in a country, you become that winner in that country and move onto the next tournament. If you lose during a tournament, you can press CONTINUE and play the match again.     Open Tournament- To play in the open tournament, you need to install two control pads into the power base. To play, select one of the countries that hosts a Grand Slam Tournament. Play commences, but the action ends after the tournament is over; you cannot advance to other tournaments. Either one or two players can enter the tournament. The method of selection is the same as that in the Exhibition Match games.      In the Open Tournament, you can continue to play as long as you win. If you lose a match, the game ends.   Tennis Ace also has a password system.Cheat: Various PasswordsAt the title screen, enter the password menu and put in the following passwords.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>J5bj9etoAyA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3053</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588158-tennis-ace</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/tennis-ace</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tennis-ace/3030-19900/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3053-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3053-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/46458-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212691-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212690-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-cute-little-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212692-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212693-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-selecting-your-player.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212694-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-selecting-game-mode.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212695-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-okay-now-concentrate.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212696-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-game-begins.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212697-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-uh-oh-i-think-i-lost.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212698-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-ball-becomes.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/212699-tennis-ace-sega-master-system-screenshot-exhibition-mode-menu.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>On your first serve, the ball explodes off your racquet like a fiery missile. Instinctively you move toward the net. Your opponent returns your serve, but you're ready for him. With lightning speed you raise your racquet and smash the ball. He never had a chance. You're the Tennis Ace!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ee865738-1d29-403b-ab63-69e42e1d1f2b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/310d4c0e-bafa-4acb-9c2d-de9ef107ea46.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7abb214c-769b-4f60-8b88-a7e348692be9.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/974c9f0e-342b-4cec-9311-fa8e8121636d.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>