<Game>
	<Name>Turma da Monica em O Resgate (Brazil)</Name>
	<plot>To save Monster Land from the evil Meka Dragon, you've entered his castle and are about to go into battle. If you defeat the dragon, a terrible surprise awaits you... a curse! You'll turn into a lizard-man, and more. The only way you can return to human form is to find the Salamander Cross, a magical item with the power to remove curses. But where is it hidden? Finding it is an adventure that will take you across strange lands, against strange creatures, into battles where you never know what strange shape you'll turn into! Hawk-man, Lion-man, and more! You'll be able to buy armor, weapons and use magic items! Hidden rooms hold even greater surprises! Can you beat the dragon's bosses and recover the Salamander Cross? When you look at the shape you're in, it's your only hope!Cheat: All armour/equipment &amp; formsEntering the following will allow you to begin the game with all swords/equipment and all forms unlocked. You will also begin as Hu-Man, this form will be lost if you transform. On the continue screen, input: WE5T ONE for the first 7 characters, the rest of the characters remain as O. Make sure it's a ''5'' not an ''S''Cheat: All armour/equipment &amp; formsEquip the Tasmanian sword, and jump into the air. While in the air, hold and let go of 1 on controller 2 and 2 on controller 1 at the same time. You'll transform when you land!Cheat: Beginning Passwords...Enter the following passwords at the Continue screen...Cheat: Beginning Passwords...Enter MJWH WC5TY3B XJR to go directly to the end of the game. Cheat: Beginning Passwords...In the manual for the game there is a picture of the password screen in which the password is fully visible.  Entering that code will allow you to play through the game with all the weapons/armor/shields and as the Hu-Man than you start the game as.  If you enter any transform booth you will become Lizard-Man, and you can't change back to Hu-Man without reentering the code.Cheat: Beginning Passwords...This is an update to the other Human code I posted.On page 5 of the manual, there's a screen shot of the password screen.  If you squint real hard you can make it out as:3YGU PYZ ZY7K NRRThis will put you at the beginning of the game with every puece of armor, shield, and weapon.  You will also be the Hu-Man-which is normally not availible after the opening sequence.  If you use the change room in the town to change to the Lizard-Man form, you will be unable to switch back to the Hu-Man form.Cheat: Beginning Passwords...At the password screen,  found in the main menu when the game is turned on, the following passwords have various effects. Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomAs Hawk-Man return to the Mummys Tomb and travel all the way to the end where you would fall through the floor to fight the dragon. Don't fall through the floor, instead fly directly upwards and you will find a treasure room containing money and health.Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomSick of having to sit too close to your Sega Master system just so you can pause it, and sometimes accidentally causing problems by hitting the system too hard?Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomSimply plug in a second controller and sit it right next to you. When you need to pause, press up, down, left or right on the second controller and voila! Your pause menu, without having to touch the sometimes sensitive system!Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomThere are two secret treasure rooms you can access in Lizardman's and Mouseman's quests: As Lizardman - when you enter the locked tomb, travel all the way to the end. Normally you would fall through the invisible gap in the floor next to the fire-breathing stone head, but there is a ledge underneath the head which seems to lead to a dead end. Jump over the gap and land on that ledge. You will find that you can pass through the wall in front of you and you will enter a room with a chest! The chest contains 5 coins, 1 money bag, 1 large heart and 1 medicine. This is useful for preparing you before you fight the Mummy Dragon. You will automatically be dropped through the invisible floor gap upon exiting the room. As Mouseman - once you have travelled through the open forests where the fire dropping smogs chased you, you will enter a screen containing a mouse-block maze. If you look carefully, there are three paths leading through the maze and opening up to the next screen. Taking the middle path will continue your journey, but before you do, travel to the very top-left corner of the screen via the highest path. If you attempt to jump forward into that corner of the screen, you will jump into a secret treasure room! The chest contains 1 coin, seven money bags and 3 little hearts. The money will be useful if you haven't enough to purchase the Shogun items in the next shop. When you exit the room, you will be automatically be dropped outside the mouseblock maze.  </plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>West One</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>OBdu19yBNkQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3108</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588172-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragons-trap</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/turma-da-mnica-em-o-resgate</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate/3030-10947/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3108-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3108-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181986-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181987-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181988-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181991-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181992-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181993-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181994-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181995-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181996-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181997-turma-da-monica-em-o-resgate-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Brazilian port of Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap, with characters and story based on the popular Monica's Gang comic books.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>9N7xuPqjG5Y</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d8d4e25-a3e8-483d-be55-4f091e279c2e.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5871bba-10f9-4ed4-8f97-79118eee0879.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eeeafd93-0249-460d-9f31-2b2066168b7d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5a658c3-ad3f-4620-8a04-0484d7736bf7.jpg</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tec Toy</Publisher>
</game>