<Game>
	<Name>Walter Payton Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Walter Payton Football, or American Pro Football, as it is called in Japan and Europe, is a simulation of American football. There are two modes in the game. One is called "Monday Night Game" and is the same as a friendly game or exhibition mode; the other is "Road to Superbowl", and is basically a play-off tournament in the NFL.The player can choose his favorite NFL team to compete against the computer or another player. The game allows you to assign basic strategies to the teams, both in defensive and offensive plays. The game is viewed from a top-down perspective, with the exception of kick offs and field goals, which are viewed up close from a third person perspective, and allow the player to regulate the strength of the kick.Cheat: Score a touchdown every timeChoose a Bomb Pass play, but instead of passing it, run with it. The CPU opponent cannot stop this for some reason.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>bicsppbKJxA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20619</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588033-walter-payton-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/walter-payton-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/walter-payton-football/3030-14074/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20619-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/277966-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/277968-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276927-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-nice.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276929-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276930-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276928-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-road.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276931-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276932-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-heads.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276933-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-kick.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276934-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-ball.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276935-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-your.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276936-walter-payton-football-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-quarterback.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>It's the snap! You sweep to the right. the quarterback hands you the ball. You head for daylight as the linemen open a hole. Suddenly, 250 lbs. of screaming tackle is heading your way. He wants to make you splat city. What will you do? This game gives you the chance to find out. With Walter Payton Football you can play against the computer, or against a friend, in a Monday Night Game or in a series on the Road to the Superbowl. Choose from 28 west, central and eastern teams. Offense and defense. Should you run or pass? Will a reverse throw 'em off guard? In the middle of a hot series, you can save your standings with a Password save. The Superbowl ring has never been this close. If you like football, then Sega's Walter Payton Football is the game for you!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c85d5a1-6f82-43ad-99c2-f650061f719e.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>