<Game>
	<Name>Wimbledon (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The oldest of the four Grand Slam tournaments, held in London on grass every July, is the basis for this tennis game. The ball comes off the grass surface fast and low, reflecting the surface's reputation for providing the most exciting tennis. It's viewed in the typical third person perspective, although with quite a distinct 3D effect and with shadows. You can play standard 1 or 2 player matches, or play the full tournament from the quarter-final stages onwards. You can play standard shots as well as lobs and drop shots, and full service rules are featured. You can select your character and build up their skills as the game progresses.http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/wimbledon-championship-tennisCheat: Full Creation PointsTo get more than enough points to create a player with full attributes, enter the following code at the password screen: IKM JKI POCCheat: Full Creation PointsEnter SOU NDT EST as your password to access the sound test.Cheat: Full Creation PointsEnter the following passwords to see the desired ending:</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<VideoURL>rdNg8tD8ax8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3101</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588169-wimbledon</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3101-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/5/9/48659_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/c/8/gfs_87410_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/5/5/gfs_87410_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/8/5/gfs_87410_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/3/5/gfs_87410_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/2/5/gfs_87410_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Control one of the world's top players, or enter yourself in the Tour and test your skill. Singles, Doubles, practice, four exciting tournaments - fast, heart-stopping action from beginning to end!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7262c43-a205-444c-bcab-9ac9b40ae687.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>