<Game>
	<Name>Wimbledon II (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The oldest of the four Grand Slam tournaments, held in London on grass every July, is the basis for this tennis game. The ball comes off the grass surface fast and low, reflecting the surface's reputation for providing the most exciting tennis. It's viewed in the typical third person perspective, although with quite a distinct 3D effect and with shadows. You can play standard 1 or 2 player matches, or play the full tournament from the quarter-final stages onwards. You can play standard shots as well as lobs and drop shots, and full service rules are featured. You can select your character and build up their skills as the game progresses.http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/wimbledon-championship-tennisCheat: Normal Difficulty PasswordsEnter the following passwords for the desired effect. Apart from the qualifying tournament passwords, this player has all stats maxed out, making it very easy to beat the computer!</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>w34Mf1xQMAk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3103</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/570215-wimbledon-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/wimbledon-ii</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3103-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/293468-wimbledon-ii-sega-master-system-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/8/b/gfs_87411_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/1/6/gfs_87411_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/c/6/gfs_87411_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/7/6/gfs_87411_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/6/6/gfs_87411_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/d/6/gfs_87411_2_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/0/6/gfs_87411_2_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/b/6/gfs_87411_2_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/7/gfs_87411_2_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/7/gfs_87411_2_9.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>You started out at the bottom, an unknown name in a field of highly talented players. You worked your way up the ranks, playing in America, Australia and France. And now, the big day... the day you take on the best tennis players in the world for the Wimbledon Open Cup!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57aab548-5b56-4a05-8790-b8cffd14399f.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>