<Game>
	<Name>Wolfchild (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Wolfchild is a 2D shooter/platformer from British developers Core Design, which would later go on to create the Tomb Raider franchise. It features Saul Morrow, a man who is able to transform into a powerful werewolf form in order to fight the evil Chimera organization who kidnapped his scientist father Kal, from whom he received his powers. The game is a standard 2D platformer with shooting elements, and the player must collect energy before they can transform similar to Altered Beast.Wolfchild was originally released on the home computers Amiga and Atari ST, before being ported to various consoles like the Genesis, Master System, Mega-CD, SNES and Game Gear.Critical ReceptionWhen the SNES version was released Mike Weigand of Electronic Gaming Monthly awarded the score of 5 out of 10. He wrote, "...It's got great graphics, and some of the sound effects are dynamite, but Wolfchild loses big in the gameplay department. The punching and other attacks are awkward. This was a new idea, and the levels are huge, but the overall game is dull and rather unappealing".Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter the password MARIO for a secret message as well as the ability to select your starting level.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>mqFPj1lvBdI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3105</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588170-wolfchild</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/wolfchild</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wolfchild/3030-8653/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3105-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3105-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/164755-wolfchild-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128990-wolfchild-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128991-wolfchild-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-game-begins-level.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128992-wolfchild-sega-master-system-screenshot-very-easy-opponents.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128993-wolfchild-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-levelboss-of-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128994-wolfchild-sega-master-system-screenshot-the-forest-level-2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2640007-wolfchild001.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/806491-1212759146_01.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/806490-1212759146_00.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/806489-1212759145_02.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/806488-1212759145_01.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Using his father's scientific knowledge, Saul Morrow transforms himself into the powerful WOLFCHILD and seeks revenge on the evil Chimera organization who have murdered his family and kidnapped his father. Guide Saul in his quest to rescue his father from the clutches of the corrupt Chimera corporation. Change his form to that of a powerful psychic werewolf as you fight your way through 5 levels of action-packed adventure, featuring over 400 screens of exciting and addictive gameplay!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b91cf8a-96f0-4b8d-adf2-0d95419db3a1.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eea98554-5f22-4176-b372-277839f3879b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Virgin Games</Publisher>
</game>