<Game>
	<Name>Wonder Boy III - The Dragon's Trap (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap is a platformer for the Sega Master System, Game Gear and TurboGrafx-16 and part of Westone's Wonder Boy series. It is the first Wonder Boy game not to be developed originally for the Arcades, as it was specially made for Sega's Master System console. Like many Wonder Boy games, however, it was eventually ported by Hudson to the TurboGrafx-16 with a different name to avoid copyright violations.The game begins with the player infiltrating a castle and defeating its boss, a menacing dragon. Upon killing the dragon it unleashes a curse, transforming the player into a green lizard. After this short introduction, the game opens up into a vast, explorable world. To regain Wonder Boy's human form, the player must explore this open world, and kill all of the dragon bosses protecting each dungeon. Killing a boss rids Wonder Boy of his current animal form, while transforming him into another. The gameplay is reminiscent of Metroid, and could be considered an early Metroidvania.Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap was originally released in Europe and the US on the Master System in 1989. Japan never received this version, as Master System development had already ceased in light of the Sega Mega Drive (Genesis). They, as well as the US and Europe, did eventually receive the Game Gear port in 1992. The TurboGrafx-16/PC Engine version was released in 1991.Gameplay:The game's hub world, a small village complete with shops and a save point, gives the player access to all the world's main areas. At first, most of the world's pathways are blocked off but they become open to once the various animal forms and their associated abilities have been gained. The player is not allowed to change forms at will, meaning that the while the game's world is in the Metroid vein, progress largely becomes a linear task due to the limits of each animal form. However, later in the game special transformation rooms become available which allow the player to shift between all previously-earned forms.The various forms (and their inherent abilities) Wonder Boy goes through during the game are:Lizard-Man (fire breath, cannot wield weapons)Mouse-Man (small size, wall walk)Piranha-Man (swimming)Lion-Man (tall sword arc)Hawk-Man (flight)Hu-Man (no special abilities)Each new area of the world follows the same basic pattern: Wonder Boy begins by making his way to the dragon's lair, fighting enemies and using his newly acquired abilities to progress. Eventually the player reaches the dragon's dungeon. Once the player makes his/her way through that, they are met with a boss encounter in an enclosed space. Typically the key to defeating each boss is timed jumps and sword attacks. Dragon bosses include;Meka-Dragon (robot, final boss of Wonder Boy in Monster Land)Mummy DragonDragon ZombieCaptain DragonDaimyo DragonVampire DragonThe game features an inventory system and an equipment upgrade system, as well as loot drops in the form of money or luck gems.Additional NotesWonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap shares its Roman numerical title with Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair, an arcade game with a Mega Drive port, adding to the confusing Wonder Boy series timeline.The TurboGrafx-16 version is named Dragon's Curse and drops the Wonder Boy name. This has been standard practice for Hudson's previous ports of the Wonder Boy series: the first (Wonder Boy) was transformed into Adventure Island, and the second (Wonder Boy in Monster Land) was transformed into Bikkuriman World.Dragon's Trap is also considered to be the second game in the Monster World sub-franchise. The Japanese name for the Game Gear version is called Monster World II: Dragon's Trap.The cheat code WE5T 0NE (after the game's developer) allows the player to play in human form outside of the intro.Cheat: All armour/equipment &amp; formsEntering the following will allow you to begin the game with all swords/equipment and all forms unlocked. You will also begin as Hu-Man, this form will be lost if you transform. On the continue screen, input: WE5T ONE for the first 7 characters, the rest of the characters remain as O. Make sure it's a ''5'' not an ''S''Cheat: All armour/equipment &amp; formsEquip the Tasmanian sword, and jump into the air. While in the air, hold and let go of 1 on controller 2 and 2 on controller 1 at the same time. You'll transform when you land!Cheat: Beginning Passwords...Enter the following passwords at the Continue screen...Cheat: Beginning Passwords...Enter MJWH WC5TY3B XJR to go directly to the end of the game. Cheat: Beginning Passwords...In the manual for the game there is a picture of the password screen in which the password is fully visible.  Entering that code will allow you to play through the game with all the weapons/armor/shields and as the Hu-Man than you start the game as.  If you enter any transform booth you will become Lizard-Man, and you can't change back to Hu-Man without reentering the code.Cheat: Beginning Passwords...This is an update to the other Human code I posted.On page 5 of the manual, there's a screen shot of the password screen.  If you squint real hard you can make it out as:3YGU PYZ ZY7K NRRThis will put you at the beginning of the game with every puece of armor, shield, and weapon.  You will also be the Hu-Man-which is normally not availible after the opening sequence.  If you use the change room in the town to change to the Lizard-Man form, you will be unable to switch back to the Hu-Man form.Cheat: Beginning Passwords...At the password screen,  found in the main menu when the game is turned on, the following passwords have various effects. Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomAs Hawk-Man return to the Mummys Tomb and travel all the way to the end where you would fall through the floor to fight the dragon. Don't fall through the floor, instead fly directly upwards and you will find a treasure room containing money and health.Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomSick of having to sit too close to your Sega Master system just so you can pause it, and sometimes accidentally causing problems by hitting the system too hard?Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomSimply plug in a second controller and sit it right next to you. When you need to pause, press up, down, left or right on the second controller and voila! Your pause menu, without having to touch the sometimes sensitive system!Cheat: Another Secret treasure roomThere are two secret treasure rooms you can access in Lizardman's and Mouseman's quests: As Lizardman - when you enter the locked tomb, travel all the way to the end. Normally you would fall through the invisible gap in the floor next to the fire-breathing stone head, but there is a ledge underneath the head which seems to lead to a dead end. Jump over the gap and land on that ledge. You will find that you can pass through the wall in front of you and you will enter a room with a chest! The chest contains 5 coins, 1 money bag, 1 large heart and 1 medicine. This is useful for preparing you before you fight the Mummy Dragon. You will automatically be dropped through the invisible floor gap upon exiting the room. As Mouseman - once you have travelled through the open forests where the fire dropping smogs chased you, you will enter a screen containing a mouse-block maze. If you look carefully, there are three paths leading through the maze and opening up to the next screen. Taking the middle path will continue your journey, but before you do, travel to the very top-left corner of the screen via the highest path. If you attempt to jump forward into that corner of the screen, you will jump into a secret treasure room! The chest contains 1 coin, seven money bags and 3 little hearts. The money will be useful if you haven't enough to purchase the Shogun items in the next shop. When you exit the room, you will be automatically be dropped outside the mouseblock maze.  </plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>OBdu19yBNkQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3108</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588172-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragons-trap</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/wonder-boy-iii-the-dragons-trap</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wonder-boy-iii-the-dragons-trap/3030-2192/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3108-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3108-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/92916-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36770-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36771-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36772-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213211-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213212-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213213-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213214-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213215-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213216-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/213217-wonder-boy-iii-the-dragon-s-trap-sega-master-system-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gxxE3T4.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap takes place immediately after the events of Wonder Boy in Monster Land, Wonder Boy travels into the Mecha Dragon's lair in order to slay him. However, upon doing so, he is inflicted by a curse that transforms him into "Lizard-Man". In the game, the player controls Wonder Boy as he tries to undo this curse by journeying across the land, defeating other dragons, and defeating finally the Vampire Dragon to obtain the Salamander Cross – the only object that can remove his curse.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b93cab4f-9cb9-418a-aeaa-746819be3463.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f51e5315-646e-4b14-aa0c-f88b8b771acf.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60eb849a-b294-4f74-9acd-8076cb536843.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>