<Game>
	<Name>World Soccer (World)</Name>
	<plot>This version of Great Soccer is on the Sega cartridge. The other version of Great Soccer is on the Sega card and an entirely different game.Dribble, pass, shoot and score! Two game selections are available to play. The first is a top-down perspective soccer game. The second is a 3rd-person perspective penalty kick contest. The team that scores the most goals in either game selection wins. However, if regulation time runs out in the regular soccer game mode, there will be a penalty kick shoot-off to determine the winner.All the same rules apply to this soccer game as in a real life match. There are kickoffs, offside violations, slide tackles, corner kicks, out of bound throw-ins and goalie saves all during gameplay.Choose from one of eight nations to compete in a match of professional soccer. The nations available are Argentina, West Germany, France, Brazil, Great Britain, Italy, USA and Japaneach with their own strengths and expertise.http://www.mobygames.com/game/sega-master-system/great-soccerCheat: Stop every Penalty KickIt's very easy to stop any penalty kick when you are the goalkeeper. Simply PAUSE the Master System when the player shoots and you see where the ball will go. Then, prepare the D-pad, unpause the game and stop it.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/1/1987</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA
</Developer>
	<VideoURL>KiVsMAff24c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3119</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/sms/588082-great-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/great-soccer/3030-40645/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3119-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3119-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/e/8/gfs_3831_2_4.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/8/gfs_3831_2_5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/8/gfs_3831_2_6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/8/gfs_3831_2_7.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/e/9/gfs_3831_2_8.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/5/9/gfs_3831_2_9.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/a/4/gfs_3831_2_10.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/1/4/gfs_3831_2_11.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/c/4/gfs_3831_2_12.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/9/3/gfs_8601_2_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>World Soccer, known as Great Soccer in the US (though not the same as Great Soccer released in Europe and Japan), and Super Futebol in Brazil, is a sports game developed and published by Sega for the Sega Master System. The game was rereleased in Japan a year later under the name Sports Pad Soccer, which was bundled with the Sega Sports Pad.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd7dc9e5-b350-4a3f-b0e9-bf088dfbbf11.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4cab8b65-063d-4e27-b844-5df63a2fa0ce.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>