<Game>
	<Name>Double Dragon (1989)(Activision)(NTSC)</Name>
	<snapshot1>https://archive.org/serve/Double_Dragon_1989_Activision_NTSC/Double_Dragon_1989_Activision_NTSC_screenshot.png</snapshot1>
	<plot>Twin brothers Billy and Jimmy Lee learned to fight the hard way -- for survival in the unforgiving city streets. Their brand of combat -- classic martial arts maneuvers mixed with anything-goes street brawling -- has turned them into walking lethal weapons.
Now, the Lees must summon all their fighting abilities and cunning into meeting the greatest challenge of their lives -- rescuing Billy's girlfriend, Marion.  She's been kidnapped by the Black Warriors, the savage street gang led by the mysterious Shadow Boss.
The twins pursue the Black Warriors through the city streets and its outskirts.  Finally they fight their way into the Secret Enemy Base.  There, Billy and Jimmy meet the Shadow Boss.  It's a battle to the finish, with Marion as the prize!</plot>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<releasedate>01/01/1989</releasedate>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/21041-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27307-double-dragon-atari-7800-front-cover.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/21041-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxback2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27308-double-dragon-atari-7800-back-cover.jpg</boxback2>
	<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27309-double-dragon-atari-7800-media.jpg</media1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55260-double-dragon-atari-7800-screenshot-atari-logo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55261-double-dragon-atari-7800-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55262-double-dragon-atari-7800-screenshot-beginning-the-game.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55263-double-dragon-atari-7800-screenshot-outnumbered-as-usual.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55264-double-dragon-atari-7800-screenshot-watch-out-for-that-whip.jpg</snapshot6>
	<Notes>Twin brothers Billy and Jimmy Lee learned to fight the hard way -- for survival in the unforgiving city streets. Their brand of combat -- classic martial arts maneuvers mixed with anything-goes street brawling -- has turned them into walking lethal weapons. Now, the Lees must summon all their fighting abilities and cunning into meeting the greatest challenge of their lives -- rescuing Billy's girlfriend, Marion.  She's been kidnapped by the Black Warriors, the savage street gang led by the mysterious Shadow Boss. The twins pursue the Black Warriors through the city streets and its outskirts.  Finally they fight their way into the Secret Enemy Base.  There, Billy and Jimmy meet the Shadow Boss.  It's a battle to the finish, with Marion as the prize!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ffa58778-32ba-4d6c-b93c-feae004f0126.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b0eb46b-4bd7-4b02-b087-737bac314813.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fdfb5d3f-f754-449e-ad14-cfdc92352f22.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/151c6d3d-4f90-4bee-8bbb-00ccc6515063.png</snapshot8>
	<rating>1.6666666666666667</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Developer>Technōs Japan</Developer>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>