<Game>
	<Name>GATO (1987)(Atari)(NTSC)(proto)</Name>
	<snapshot1>https://archive.org/serve/GATO_1987_Atari_NTSC_proto/GATO_1987_Atari_NTSC_proto_screenshot.png</snapshot1>
	<plot>Title Match is a wrestling game which can be played by one or two players. There are four different wrestlers you can choose from, and two modes of gameplay (one on one, or tag team). Each wrestler can kick, punch, and perform several moves such as the airplane spin, body slam, power lift, and more. Using the available moves you need to deplete your opponents energy  and pin him for three counts (though be careful, as some of the more powerful moves also use up a bit of your own energy). If your opponents energy is low enough and you successfully pin him that will count as a fall, and the best out of three falls will win the match! </plot>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<releasedate>1989</releasedate>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/21101-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82997-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-atari-logo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82998-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82999-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-select-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83000-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-beginning-a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83001-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-oof-that-s.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83002-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-my-player-is.jpg</snapshot7>
	<Notes>In Gato, you play the commander of a United States submarine in the Pacific Ocean during World War II against Japanese warships. Gato is a 3D real-time submarine simulation game. Gameplay consists of missions where the primary directive is to navigate your submarine to track and intercept (multiple) enemy warships (patrol boats, destroyers, etc.) on the randomly created map and close in for the kill with torpedoes. Combat itself consists of a direct visual of enemy ships (via periscope) and firing torpedoes at the correct angle to ultimately sink the ship. Be warned that although you have the element of surprise, enemy ships can fire back! When all hell breaks loose, an identified submarine is a sitting duck to those Japanese guns. Be prepared to direct your damage control team to fix up your damaged submarine ASAP! The mission ends when you have successfully eliminated all targets in the map.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>YMA3eJ9n90Q</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95c3ec1a-f081-4129-a471-247935e555aa.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/467a3b39-17a8-499e-8801-20a73fac5fa2.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Developer>Atari</Developer>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>