<Game>
	<Name>Super Pac-Man</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>2008</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>t's a Bird...It's a Plane...No, it's Super Pac-Man!!! The Monster Gang from Pac-Man is at it again! Who will stop their dastardly deeds? Never Fear! Super Pac-Man is here to save the maze! Super Pac-Man is a port to the 7800 of the arcade game of the same name. Pac-Man and the monsters from the original Pac-Man return, but this is no ordinary Pac-Man game! In Super Pac-Man you must eat the keys to open doors blocking tasty goodies that you need to snap up to clear the maze. Chomp a Power Pellet to gobble up the Monsters like in classic Pac-Man or forego the mild-mannered munching with a Super Pellet and become the super-sized, super-fast, super-invulnerable Super Pac-Man, capable of smashing down the doors that block your passage! All we have to say is that if Bob DeCrescenzo was writing games for the Atari 7800 "back in the day", the system surely would have been a stellar hit! Super Pac-Man is one of Bob's latest Atari 7800 creations, and another great arcade classic he's brought to the 7800. Super Pac-Man has a unique style compared to most Pac-Man games--your goal in this game is to gobble up keys that open doors giving Pac-Man access to fruits and prizes he must devour, as opposed to dots. Pac-Man can eat Super Power Energizers which turn him into Super Pac-Man. Super Pac-Man is considerably larger in size, can zoom much faster, and can crash through any locked doors. Super Pac-Man can also pass through (over?) ghosts without dying. Pac-Man fans will not want to miss Super Pac-Man on the 7800. Even the intermissions from the original arcade game are included!</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4d431cb-80a9-4d74-bdbc-a3cf1f396ef5.jpg</boxart1>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/460863fe-e2e4-4dae-8097-b47cd92e33c0.jpg</media1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e09d3457-31b9-4028-ba51-fa621e07e792.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3dfa32e4-f815-49c1-b99a-50d19a4ffd96.jpg</snapshot2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action</Genre>
	<Developer>Bob DeCrescenzo</Developer>
	<Publisher>AtariAge</Publisher>
</game>