<Game>
	<Name>Title Match Pro Wrestling (1989)(Absolute Entertainment)(NTSC)</Name>
	<snapshot1>https://archive.org/serve/Title_Match_Pro_Wrestling_1989_Absolute_Entertainment_NTSC/Title_Match_Pro_Wrestling_1989_Absolute_Entertainment_NTSC_screenshot.png</snapshot1>
	<plot>The screams of the crowd shake the arena as the Title Belt contenders circle one another.  Mad Dog makes the first move smashing his fists into Skin Head's chest who gasps for air, then retaliates with a shin cracking kick.  
Mad Dog growls and grabbing from behind drags Skin Head across the ring whipping him around in an airplane spin;  letting go so he flies into the ropes and bounces back to meet Mad Dog's concrete forearm across his neck...a perfectly executed clothesline.  
Wasting no time Mad Dog elbow drops him. Skin Head's face winces in pain as he fights his way up and staggers to his corner to tag his partner in.  
Big Chief takes the tag, grabs Mad Dog lifting him over his head and body slams him into the mat.  Mad Dog's stunned, he's not getting up.  Big Chief, looking for the pin, climbs the ropes for a dive.  
As he lunges into the air, Mad Dog scrambles to his feet and Big Chief's 
sweaty red skinned body splatters on the empty mat.</plot>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<releasedate>01/01/1989</releasedate>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20613-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20613-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82997-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-atari-logo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82998-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82999-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-select-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83000-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-beginning-a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83001-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-oof-that-s.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83002-title-match-pro-wrestling-atari-7800-screenshot-my-player-is.jpg</snapshot7>
	<Notes>The screams of the crowd shake the arena as the Title Belt contenders circle one another.  Mad Dog makes the first move smashing his fists into Skin Head's chest who gasps for air, then retaliates with a shin cracking kick.   Mad Dog growls and grabbing from behind drags Skin Head across the ring whipping him around in an airplane spin;  letting go so he flies into the ropes and bounces back to meet Mad Dog's concrete forearm across his neck...a perfectly executed clothesline.   Wasting no time Mad Dog elbow drops him. Skin Head's face winces in pain as he fights his way up and staggers to his corner to tag his partner in.   Big Chief takes the tag, grabs Mad Dog lifting him over his head and body slams him into the mat.  Mad Dog's stunned, he's not getting up.  Big Chief, looking for the pin, climbs the ropes for a dive.   As he lunges into the air, Mad Dog scrambles to his feet and Big Chief's  sweaty red skinned body splatters on the empty mat.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>AzSkQ9oXAMo</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab788ac2-3041-4882-9358-831f021cb9b7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95153cb8-a25a-4b35-a6fe-17d3acaf337b.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Developer>Alec DeMeo</Developer>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>