<Game>
	<Name>Xenophobe</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1989</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Hostile aliens - Xenophobes - are infesting space stations vital to your planet's security.  These aliens threaten to overrun the stations, rendering the space stations useless. You are part of an elite team who is ready to speed to these endangered space stations.  Your mission is clear: destroy the aliens, regain control of the space stations, and pick up any valuable hardware you might discover as you sweep the stations for aliens. The aliens are a swarming band of uglies, straight out of your worst nightmare. You'll need to use your talent just to stay alive as you rid each space station of these pests.  You don't want to let them catch you.  It's them or you. The message has come.  It's up to you and your teammates to cleanse each space station of aliens.  Your Mother Ship brings you to the vicinity of each overrun space station.  You then enter the space station via a transfer disk. Team up with another member of your elite squad, or work on your own to clear the aliens from an infested space station.  Just be careful as you enter a space station.  The aliens are everywhere!</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL>rW6arASzdSE</VideoURL>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/382ff9ef-cbf2-46cc-a36b-f7e70120a3cc.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fcf54bbb-74c0-4860-96e4-9109383a7b48.jpg</boxart1>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba0aa9a4-a6c8-4d4c-a06e-0fb400aefbcf.png</media1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a172cafd-1633-4e25-8849-5cf1764629e2.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52ed82d8-b861-4037-85ca-b99c13fc6a42.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f19f01a-bdd4-457f-9fff-2f2eca5c6762.png</snapshot2>
	<Rating>0.5</Rating>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Xenophobe_(video_game)</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Genre>Platform</Genre>
	<Developer>Bally Midway</Developer>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>