<Game>
	<Name>6-Pak (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Grab the 6-pack that'll quench your thirst for gaming! SONIC THE HEDGEHOG: This is it! The original that started it all! GOLDEN AXE: Ride a flame-spitting monster to victory! Three characters, each with special magic and weapons, battle to save the kingdom! COLUMNS: The brilliant puzzle game that will challenge your mind, not just your trigger finger! SUPER HANG-ON: Red-line your bike and blow away the competition! There's no better thrill than the roar of your pipes as you leave another rider behind, except maybe customizing your bike into an unbeatable racing machine! REVENGE OF SHINOBI: Use deadly ninja attacks to defeat the evil Neo Zeed army! If you fail, their beautiful prisoner dies! STREETS OF RAGE: The ultimate in street combat! Three characters, 40 moves, and a relentless onslaught of weapon-wielding thugs!Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameHold Down Left + A + C. Release and press startCheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameNote: This code is for the golden axe game in the 6-pak catridge.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameAt the "New game/Password" screen, hold A and Start to go into a cheat menu where you can adjust the game difficulty, adjust the timer, change the language and listen to game music.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gamePress left,left,B,B,B,C,C,C and start at the title screen.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameNote: This code is for the streets of rage game in the 6-pak catridge.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe game Hold Down/Left + B and press Start at the character selection screen.Use the directional buttons to change it to the level you desire.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameNote: This code is for the golden axe game in the 6-pak catridge.Cheat: 9 continues for the golden axe gameWhen Sonic is wagging his finger at the title screen, press Up, C, down, C, left, C, right, C then press and hold A and C and press start. You will know if this code has worked or not because all the score and time area will have lots of numbers and letters when the level starts. B changes Sonic into a different sprite, A switches through the sprites and C will place a sprite into a level.  Cheat: Infinite shuriken in The Revenge of ShinobiGo into the options menu and change the ammount of shuriken to 00. Wait for around 20 seconds and the 00 will change into a infinite symbol. You will now have a unlimited supply of shurikens to use in the game.Cheat: Columns Extra Magic JewelsThere is a way to trick the game into giving you a second magic jewel. To do this you must set up the screen in a certain way. Have one row of the normal jewels stacked up almost to the top of the playfield. There must be vertical space for only two of the three jewels in the next block to come on the screen. Watch the "Next Block" preview box. When you see that the magic jewel block is next, get ready to quickly move it on top of your prepared stack. After the magic jewel eliminates the 'touching' color jewels, all of the remaining jewels will drop down as will the one magic jewel that was off the screen. This magic jewel will drop down and eliminate another group of colored jewels.Cheat: Start arcade mode. When you get to the character select screen, hold down+left and hit A+C+Start. Nothing really confirms the code except until you get game over. If you input it correctly, the next time you get Game Over, it should say you have 9 credits instead of 3.Cheat: Use this code provided, then go to sound select, and select sounds 9F for the ending or 9E for the creditsCheat: When you ride the green block accross a sea of lave, there are a couple of big blocks in front of you with rings on. If you hold the D-PAD DOWN button, Sonic will crouch. The green block will go underneath the blocks, but sonic will remain on it, and pass through the walls. Note that this ONLY WORKS WHILE CROUCHINGCheat: Using the level select cheat, scroll down and select "Special Stage".  Upon completion on the stage, you will receive a chaos emerald, and begin playing your game on the first stage.  At this point, RESET the game via the RESET button on your Genesis, re-enter the level select code, and repeat the process.  You will enter the next Special Stage level, and have a chance to earn the 2nd Emerald.  You can repeat this process over and over until you have all 6 Chaos Emeralds.  However, once you have all six, do NOT reset the system and select a level, or else you will lose them all.Cheat: Press Left,Left,B,B,B,C,C,C, Start at the title screen.Cheat: Go to the main menu. Hold down (A) + (B) + (C) + RIGHT on controller 2 while selecting Options on controller 1 (best if done with two people). You can now select how many lives you start with and which stage to start on.Cheat: When you get to the final boss playing 2-player mode, have one player choose ''yes'' and the other choose ''no''. You will be forced to duel against each other.Cheat: To get the Bad Ending, you must be playing as 2 players. You must also be in 2 player mode before Level 8 or else player 2 can't come into the game on Level 8. When both players reach Mr. X in the final room and he asks his question, make sure one player answers yes and the second answers no. Mr. X will have both players fight each other to the death. Have one player lose and choose game over. Afterwards, Mr. X will ask a second question. Be sure to answer NO to that question as well to trigger the final boss battle. When you beat him, you will become the Boss. NOTE: If you answer yes, you will again be shut back 2 levels and still not be ale to get the bad ending.Cheat: Enter the following code at the Title screen....  A + Start  Then a new menu should appear with many new optionsCheat: At the main menu, highlight Arcade Mode and enter the code.Cheat: These are passwords for SHO's career mode. You also start out with lots of money.Cheat: 5FZ09000300000 3FJJDO9D6FGDRLCheat: You can use this password in arcade mode to play with the best bike available.Cheat: If you want to earn 30,000 bonus points, make sure you end a level with eleven times more shurikens than the number of lives you have left.Cheat: One the second stage of level four,fire at the base of the first conveyer belt.A special Musashi symbol will appear.Hop onto the conveyor belt and let it carry you to the end.You lose a life but you gain 2.Keep doing this until you have as many lives as you want/need.Cheat: Go to the Options Screen, move the pointer up to Shurikins and set them to 00, wait about 30 seconds (without moving the pointer). You will here a sound and the ''00'' should change to an infinite symbol. Start the game and you will have unlimited Shurikins.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4392</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/579589-6-pak</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/6-pak</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/6-pak/3030-37005/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4392-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4392-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/31758-6-pak-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/105333-6-pak-genesis-screenshot-title-select-interface.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/462824-6-pak-genesis-screenshot-title-select-interface-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1992/2076785-gen_genesis_6_pak_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1992/2076784-gen_genesis_6_pak_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/b/gfs_49736_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/b/gfs_49736_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/f/b/gfs_49736_1_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/b/gfs_49736_1_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/5/b/gfs_49736_1_5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/8/b/gfs_49736_1_6.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KsCcNL4.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>6-PAK is a compilation of six of SEGA's most popular "franchise" games released in the early days of the Genesis. Included are the following:  •Columns  •Golden Axe  •Revenge of Shinobi  •Sonic the Hedgehog  •Streets of Rage  •Super Hang-On</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>MwJpFVGYxms</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea05a400-d39d-4383-b34b-bd6a15997c96.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/517c1a8f-a4b4-4d7f-98e7-53266764993d.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2075af26-fc2e-4d04-b63d-19904d0ccdd3.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab2b27e0-cd22-489b-83d4-d0f441a50466.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93238af9-06df-4a8e-b73f-3802008c1b9f.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>