<Game>
	<Name>After Burner II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Arcade VersionThe arcade version of Afterburner II was available in a stand-up model as well as a deluxe sit down cabinet modeled like a fighter jet cockpit. The cockpit was built on hydraulics, which simulated flight by moving the player roughly 25 degrees in both a horizontal and vertical axis, in a rough representation of the fighter's in-game movement. As the cockpit was enclosed on almost all sides, spectators who stood too close to the moving cockpit could be injured, so large screens (simulcasting the gameplay) were frequently mounted above the cabinet. This deluxe version often cost upward of $1.00USD for a single credit.Stereo speakers were placed at the ear level for the deluxe cabinet version, creating a very immersive (and sometimes deafening) play experience. The arcade controls consisted of a flight stick with multiple buttons and a throttle stick which could be used to slow down the aircraft or activate it's afterburners. The addition of the throttle was the most notable change from the original After Burner.There 23 stages in the game: Stages 5, 13 and 23 are non-playable landing cutscenes and levels 8 and 17 are canyon bombing runs. The remaining stages involve air to air combat using an unlimited cannon, and a limited supply of missiles. The missile supply is restored approximately every 2-3 levels in a non-playable air-air refuelling sequence, as well as in the first two landing cutscenes. Cameo's from the vehicles in Hang-On, and Out Run, make appearances during the first two landing cutscenes, driving down the runway in front of the F-14 as it is taking off.Points were rewarded for both distance traveled and enemies destroyed. For unknown reasons, the designers decided to reward players with literally millions of points for performing any sort of action in the game, making the high score table sometimes showing players with scores in the billions.Cheat: Cheat CodesTo get extra missiles, press the following while refueling:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>AcaXbr6l-54</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>446</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563310-after-burner-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/after-burner-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/after-burner-ii/3030-2139/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/446-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/446-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/17682-after-burner-ii-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37556-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37557-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-part-of-the-game-s-demo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37558-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-press-start-play-me.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37559-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-loop-de-loop.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37560-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-launching-from-the-carrier.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37561-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-cannon-fodder.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37562-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-missile-locked-on-target.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37563-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-skidding-across-the-water.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37564-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-and-blowing-up-in-the-air.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/646821-after-burner-ii-genesis-screenshot-refuelling.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/446-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Kef17Vk.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/446.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Similar to its predecessor, the premise of After Burner II is to get on the F-14 Tomcat and fly mission after mission of shooting planes out of the sky. At your disposal is a vulcan cannon (basically a machine gun) and a limited number of missiles. In some versions of the game the guns fire automatically all the time. Sometimes you come across a friendly supply plane and if you dock with it you can replenish your missiles. The game is viewed from behind the plane with you fighting wave after wave of enemy fighters. But at heart it offers the usual shooter mechanics, meaning you spend most of your time dodging and shooting. You also can speed up and slow down to deal with enemies which appear behind you.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>BBR2cD5Frh0</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/168e4a05-0f01-4015-aedd-5a7ab01095d4.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d593067f-1132-4306-aed7-578672a350d7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b79a1b07-8ec2-4ae0-a3fa-8113b9b95d60.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/29325156-3eb0-4ad4-8d97-8b74b857070d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cf90884-3f8e-446e-ba48-b5f5034fa1f5.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e157415-fb74-4066-85b7-63ba8a2de16f.png</clearlogo2>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>