<Game>
	<Name>Aq Renkan Awa (China) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>Aq Renkan Awa (&#38463;Q&#36899;&#29872;&#28846;) is an unlicensed educational game for the Sega Mega Drive by C&amp;E Inc. released in 1995.There are five game modes. The first three are some variants of the normal gameplay: you are a student on a game board-like path. You roll a die to see how many spaces you move. At most spaces there is a building where you are asked five questions. If you get a certain number correct, you can stay at the spot you were in; otherwise you go back to the previous position. Play continues with the next player.The fourth game mode has various minigames (TODO describe).The fifth game mode is a basic quiz game show.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/1/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>13676</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/13676-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/13676-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<Notes>Aq Renkan Awa (阿Q連環炮) is an unlicensed educational game for the Sega Mega Drive by C&amp;E Inc. released in 1995. There are five game modes. The first three are some variants of the normal gameplay: you are a student on a game board-like path. You roll a die to see how many spaces you move. At most spaces there is a building where you are asked five questions. If you get a certain number correct, you can stay at the spot you were in; otherwise you go back to the previous position. Play continues with the next player. The fourth game mode has various minigames (TODO describe). The fifth game mode is a basic quiz game show.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>mUpDmvjZB9s</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3687975a-e36c-453f-9350-bb7817e0d987.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aad2343c-19b4-4882-896b-9bf48ea985be.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<Developer>C&amp;E Inc.</Developer>
	<Publisher>C&amp;E Inc.</Publisher>
</game>