<Game>
	<Name>Arrow Flash (Japan, Europe) (En,Ja)</Name>
	<plot>In the 30th century, Viking terrorists, led by the vicious Great Hilagi, are plundering and destroying planets throughout the Galaxy. They move in warships capable of travelling in Nether Space... and Earth is their next target. Now, there has been an assault on the laboratory of the renowned scientist Dr. Zerrek Keene, who, in a state near death, has summoned his granddaughter, Zana Keene. 'Zana,' he said, 'while experimenting with Nether Space transmission, I caused a huge magnetic field to be formed around our planet, and it has attracted the attention of the barbaric Viking Terrorists.' Dr. Keene pressed a keycard into her palm, and with his last breath, whispered, 'Zana, use this... save Earth.' Zana Keene, trained as a test pilot at the United Government Military Academy, knew what he had given her... access to the 'Chameleon' ERX-75 space fighter - capable of combat in Nether Space, and of transforming itself into a robot - the strongest weapon ever developed by the United Earth Army. Zana Keene knew what she must do. 'Use this... save Earth.'Cheat: InvincibilityAt the options menu, switch the setting, ''Arrow Flash'', from ''Stock'', to ''Charge''. When the story demo is over, wait for the demo of the gameplay to begin. Then press Start to start the game. Now, when you hold C for five seconds, you'll be invincible for about 10 minutes.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Renovation Products, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>Ex3ZOIvj4Qo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3865</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586032-arrow-flash</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/arrow-flash</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/arrow-flash/3030-12266/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3865-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3865-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/72159-arrow-flash-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102429-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102424-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-in-a-galaxy-far-far-away.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102425-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-the-heroine.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102432-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-in-a-flashy-shield-robot-form.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102427-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-the-heroine-and-her-spaceship.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102428-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-let-s-start-with-some-destruction.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102423-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-beginning-a-stage.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102430-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-hey-i-m-too-small.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102431-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-uh-oh-that-doesn-t-look-good.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102426-arrow-flash-genesis-screenshot-come-on-you-big-bully.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/bMS1Vi4.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3865.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Arrow Flash is a side-scrolling space shooter. The player controls a female spaceship pilot who is sent on a mission into deep space to save the Earth from an assault by an evil dragon from another galaxy. Moving vertically or horizontally, players must avoid or kill the enemies and make it to the end of the level alive where a boss battle awaits. During gameplay, the player can switch at any time between two modes: normal spaceship and flying robot. The two forms use different weapons and also have different special abilities, called Arrow Flash. While the spaceship can fire destructive lasers for major damage, the robot can raise a shield that will protect from enemy attacks for some time and instantly kill anything that touches it. The Arrow Flash attacks can be charged by holding a button for several seconds, or collect icons during your flight to release it quickly afterwards.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1aa46977-039e-40b3-86cf-59df5433960d.png</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f161ec44-a876-4f9d-90e2-6001f755948c.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5130609-408b-4f3e-a64c-462684dc4739.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e969c4ad-4922-4914-a003-6f44e9901210.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ba3df71-9551-4aa6-9648-184172e6a7b3.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc062c54-d500-4128-ba05-2d1b9831fd66.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/408b9bff-b2e6-487d-9cba-b68d6d966983.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Renovation Products, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>