<Game>
	<Name>Art Alive (World)</Name>
	<plot>Surprise yourself and impress your friends with astonishing graphics you can make in minutes. Animate them and your TV screen becomes a lively work of art. All with just your television and the 16-bit Genesis system. It's simply the easiest way to be an artist. Create masterpieces that run, jump, and dance! You can even record them on your VCR. It's better than a game... it's ART ALIVE!Turn your imagination loose with the gallery of tools: A rainbow of colors to paint with; 3 different pencil tips for freehand drawing; Circles, rectangles and squares in 3 different outline widths; Spray cans for shading patterns; An eraser and clear feature to make mistakes vanish; Over 50 supplied graphics and animations, including Sonic the Hedgehog and ToeJam &amp; Earl, or create your own; Predrawn backdrops you can color with the fill bucket.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/home/586033.htmlCheat: View CreditsAt the SEGA logo, hold down Left + A + C.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>BZtlNTYUgMA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>450</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586033-art-alive</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/art-alive</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/art-alive/3030-782/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/450-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/450-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/280052-art-alive-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/c/1/gfs_56949_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/5/c/gfs_56949_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/450-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/450.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Surprise yourself and impress your friends with astonishing graphics you can make in minutes. Animate them and your TV screen becomes a lively work of art. All with just your television and the 16-bit Genesis system. It's simply the easiest way to be an artist. Create masterpieces that run, jump, and dance! You can even record them on your VCR. It's better than a game... it's ART ALIVE! Turn your imagination loose with the gallery of tools: A rainbow of colors to paint with; 3 different pencil tips for freehand drawing; Circles, rectangles and squares in 3 different outline widths; Spray cans for shading patterns; An eraser and clear feature to make mistakes vanish; Over 50 supplied graphics and animations, including Sonic the Hedgehog and ToeJam &amp; Earl, or create your own; Predrawn backdrops you can color with the fill bucket.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e93a1ac9-b652-4683-a238-387a93634066.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cbaf6dbc-aac0-4099-8652-eb9ae92416ae.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9cd9e1cc-dfc3-4a15-a629-febe12294f8b.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76ac213e-a8d1-4a08-af2d-b5b17d218ce0.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2399c78b-5c82-4826-af83-9ddb567215f2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63c30ab6-9153-4341-ad0d-911ce109ff86.jpg</snapshot3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>