<Game>
	<Name>Bare Knuckle - Ikari no Tetsuken ~ Streets of Rage (World) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>"What was once a happy, peaceful, productive city, full of life and activity, has fallen into the hands of a secret criminal syndicate. The leader of the syndicate has somehow managed to keep his identity a secret. The organization soon absorbed the city government (anyone can be had if the price is right). They even had the metropolitan police force in their back pocket. Looting, random violence and destruction are rampant. No one is safe walking the streets, day or night..."As the chaos continued at full strength, three young police officers tried to establish a special attack unit. They were repeatedly turned down by their superiors, most of whom had been bought by the organization or were too afraid to make a stand. One day, when they could no longer stand by and watch their city being demolished, they quit the force!'"Adam Hunter, Axel Stone and Blaze Fielding decided to forgo their careers in legal law enforcement and put their lives on the line. They are without weapons, but each possesses great hand-to-hand combat abilities. Take them into the heart of the city and battle the most dangerous wave of bad dudes and chicks ever assembled. Make the city a place where people no longer have to walk the Streets of Rage!"</plot>
	<releasedate>2/8/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting</genre>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>7.6667</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>971</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/971-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/971-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/971-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/971-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/971-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/971-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/971-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/971.png</clearlogo1>
</game>