<Game>
	<Name>Bare Knuckle III (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Translation Description:All the text in the game has been translated. This includes both dialogue in the story mode and the win/lose quotes in the Battle mode, and the Engrish in the battle mode has been fixed. The patch has been thoroughly tested and works on the hardware. If you find a platform it doesn't work on, contact the author.There are currently no known bugs. Please note, however, that the patch has only been tested on an American Sega Genesis Model 2. The code has been written in such a way that it should work on all models, though.http://www.romhacking.net/trans/1375/Cheat: Extra Lives SelectGo to the options screen and select the ''Lives'' option. Press and hold UP + (A) + (B) + (C) on Controller 2, and press LEFT or RIGHT on Controller 1 to select the number of lives you can start the game with. You will now be able to select 9 lives, past the default max of 5.Cheat: Extra Lives SelectAt the title screen, hold Up and B, then press Start.  A kangaroo named Roo will now be available at the character select screen.Cheat: Extra Lives SelectAfter beating Shiva in the first stage when you get the last hit, press B+Start and hold it.  When the continue screen comes up you'll be able to play as Shiva.  WARNING: He is weaker than his Streets of Rage 2 character.Cheat: Extra Lives SelectTo select Ash, defeat him, then hold A on Controller 1. After losing all of your lives, you select to continue and you can choose Ash as your character.Cheat: Extra Lives SelectPress C to select a player, then quickly hold A and sweep the D-pad in a clockwise circle until Axel appears. Then press A.  Note: This cheat is very hard to get working. Cheat: Extra Lives SelectOn the Character Select screen, hold C button on both gamepads when selecting Zan and keep holding them until the game start. You will have Super Zan afterward.Cheat: Extra Lives SelectHold Down+C on controller 2 as you enter 2 PLAYER mode with controller 1.Cheat: Shivas infinite comboWhen playing as Shiva, you can hit the opponent over and over again until they die without them being able to escape you by pressing Z on a 6 button pad or B and C together on a 3 button one over and over again. This will work on any opponent apart from the ones that can block and the bosses (excluding Jet)Cheat: Another way to get RooWhen you fight the clown and Roo, defeat the clown first and Roo should hop away off the screen.  When you lose all your lives and continue, cycle through the characters and Roo will now be available.Cheat: Another way to get RooTo get Ending 1, successfully rescue the Chief in Stage 6 before his health runs out. Then, at the end of Stage 7, defeat Robot Y before the time limit runs out. You will see the true ending. Cheat: Another way to get RooTo see Ending 2, manage to rescue the Chief before his health runs out in Stage 6. Then, in Stage 7, defeat Robot Y but let the time limit run out. You will see Ending 2. Cheat: Another way to get RooTo see Ending 3, let the Chief's health run out in Stage 6. When you go to Stage 7, you will see that it is changed. Make it to the last boss and defeat him. You will see Ending 3. Cheat: Another way to get RooTo see Ending 4 , simply set the difficulty on Easy Level and beat Robot X in Stage 5. Cheat: Another way to get RooPick Skate. As the first level starts, lose a your first life having 0 points. You will now be Super Skate, with a much more powerful combo.Cheat: Another way to get RooIn Stage 1, at the Warehouse Area, go to the bottom-left most region blocked by the crates in the background and press B in the area. You'll get 5000 PTS. and a 1-UP.  Also in Stage 7, (City Hall) there are lots of hidden items as well. Search in areas blocked off by the background such as lampposts, flower pots, etc.Cheat: Another way to get RooOn Stage 5, in the first room with all the ninjas, there are three secret routes you can take other than the normal route. You can access them by killing all enemies here. These rooms have more items than the normal rooms. The way to get to the rooms are as follows: 1.) Above the door where you follow your normal route, there is a white wall in front of you with cracks near the top. Punch it to access Secret Route 1. 2.) At the bottom of the screen is a very unlikely secret that most of you won't suspect until reading this. Go to the bottom center part of this room and punch a few times. You'll eventually bust a hole in the floor leading you to the basement of Stage 5 and also Secret Route 2. 3.) Go to the top of the screen and go up to the red walls. There is a certain red wall with a few cracks in it. Punch it to access Secret Route 3. Beware. There are a lot of enemies here, so be careful.Cheat: Another way to get RooHold B and Up, then press Start.  The Stage Select will appear on the options screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/2009</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0c1VnSyaLcI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2653</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586496-streets-of-rage-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/streets-of-rage-2/3030-18122/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2653-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2653-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/uvwqdJt.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/168784-streets-of-rage-2-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/694-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/53346-streets-of-rage-2-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/53357-streets-of-rage-2-genesis-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DvnsX3i.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2653.png</clearlogo1>
</game>