<Game>
	<Name>Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi (China) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>This world was once a civilization brought together by magic and technology. As civilization advanced, those who possessed the power of technology and magic segregated due to their differences in ideas, and formed two separate societies of humans and demons.The human race continued to develop their civilization with technology, while the demons started to construct their own society with magic. This balance did not hold for very long, however, and technology was gradually replacing magic.Soon afterwards, an ultimate weapon from technological civilization appeared, and in an ironic twist of fate, lost control and destroyed the whole world, along with all civilization therein.Nearly a thousand years have gone by without incident, until one day the ancient technology lying deep within the earth was excavated. Mankind was once again on its way to committing the same mistakes of the past...The world now is divided into four kingdoms, each representing one of the four natural forces and with four temples: - The Cruz Kingdom governs the water with the Moon Temple. - The bold Galien Kingdom emerges as a tropical desert climate near the Sun Temple. - In the polar regions is the Zak Empire that expert in technical research, with the power of the Star Temple. - The Lear Kingdom lies among a picturesque scenery protected by the Wind Temple. The world was at peace, when suddenly demons from legend appeared throughout the land. Humanity panicked and was at a loss. What have the demons come for? What secret do the temples hold? Just who is behind all of this? Who will see through this shrouded mystery?Cheat: Additional logosAt the title screen, press A + B + C + Start to see additional company logos.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Chuanpu Technologies</Developer>
	<VideoURL>i5-Ni69opFc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20298</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/718794-barver-battle-saga-tai-kong-zhan-shi</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20298-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/8/9/gfs_323236_2_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/5/9/gfs_323236_2_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/9/gfs_323236_2_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/f/9/gfs_323236_2_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/9/gfs_323236_2_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/9/gfs_323236_2_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/2/9/gfs_323236_2_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/f/8/gfs_323236_2_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/4/8/gfs_323236_2_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Barver Battle Saga: Tai Kong Zhan Shi – Mo Fa Zhan Shi (BARVER BATTLE SAGA 太空戰士 魔法戰士) is a 1996 RPG by Chuanpu for the Sega Mega Drive. The game was released in Taiwan and Russia with titles that make it seem connected to Square Enix's franchise Final Fantasy, which has never been released on a Sega system.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e5db179-aadf-4fe8-91a4-52d0cea775a5.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/489eacdb-17be-470e-a12d-451cbd6e7105.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff6ce05f-5b9b-490d-855b-dcaedfa777c3.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2becddcd-60e0-4d45-a2fe-124ec0576f5f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7fa8a03-e290-4fdd-b6fe-fac33cc37e8d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd17bc9f-3b1e-4e0e-a210-54f25da00c13.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a848d5fd-c849-4725-8652-2ed4b59113cf.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eca699c4-0c30-4271-89be-cd54f31250ec.jpg</snapshot15>
</game>