<Game>
	<Name>Batman - Revenge of the Joker (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The Bat is back in blue and grey, so it's Caped-Crusader to you then, not Dark-Knight. Previous Batman games have more in common with the movies, and Dark Horse comic sty-lings which there based, and the Batman franchise in general.This time it's a platform-er, again, what else would it be? You have to take on thirteen platform-er levels with the usual assortment of pit-falls and hazards, and four non-DC comic related bosses and two encounters with the Joker. Some of the bosses in this game are so hard it's completely ludicrous, especially the final confrontation with the Joker.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/review/R105069.htmlCheat: Cheat Mode PasswordFirst enter in the password 1408, this will enable Cheat Mode which is accessed by controller 2. After turning on the cheat, you can use on of the following passwords to start on the level of choice. During gameplay, the Start button on controller 2 will pause without bring up the pause menu. The C button on controller 2 will restore Batman's health, the A button on controller 2 will skip to the next stage. And finally, the B button on controller 2 will show the end game credits.Cheat: Cheat Mode PasswordFirst, use password 5257 as a password and on the bottom of the screen objects will appear confirming correct password entry. Then, Type in the password for what level you want to go to:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>_-ykPd5EgO0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4280</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586048-batman-revenge-of-the-joker</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4280-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4280-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/1/8/gfs_38813_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/8/5/gfs_38813_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/5/5/gfs_38813_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4280-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jqYPcUY.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4280.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Joker has somehow managed to escape from Arkham Asylum once again, and Batman must fight him across seven stages to restore peace to Gotham City. Batman carries a gauntlet shooting basic bullets by default. This can be upgraded with weapon powerups located in boxes throughout the level, giving access to homing and energy weapons. Every upgrade weapon can be charged up for a secondary attack, different for each weapon. Batman also has a slide useful against most enemies and some bosses. Boss fights introduce a system where life is measured by points instead of tick marks or bars. In these sections, Batman has significantly more health, and can take many more hits when rumbling with these stronger foes.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d06555c-92ae-4021-a05e-2e6c0438b184.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/91163a30-86fd-423f-a162-7c99ffdb4469.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sun Corporation</Publisher>
</game>