<Game>
	<Name>Battle Mania Daiginjou (Japan, Korea)</Name>
	<plot>Battle Mania Daiginjou is the sequel to the game we got stateside known as Trouble Shooter, and, like all good things in the video game world, it was left in Japan. Looks fun though.Overview::Two mercenary ladies with a need for destruction. The premise is not of the usual kind of shooter. But the rest is fairly common to all of us: containers with power-ups, flashing shots and a gigantic enemy army.Typical and reasonably challenging shooter action with some quick puzzles around on certain stages to break the ice. The gamer (playing the role of the mercenary Mania Ohtori, also known as ''Madison'') has the partnership of Maria ''Crystal'' Waneda (whom is equipped with a heavy bazooka) and a weapon pod (which the gamer selects amongst four different types and each one is capable of a devastating attack when activated at a full charge weapon bar). The funny and strange elements of the game, such as the little lab hamster - and others that the gamer will find while delving further into the game, frenetic action and ausence of slomo are its gameplay's greatest assets.Translation Description:From MIJET's site:"In what has become a MIJET trademark, this is a "dual-language" patch, meaning that it supports both Japanese and English. However, it goes far beyond simply supporting both English and the original Japanese; it contains two different English translations and a selection of three English fonts.This patch is contained within two different IPS files, but the only differences between the two are the default script and font to use if none are selected by the user. That's correct; it is possible to select the desired script and font by holding down certain combinations of buttons prior to the Sega logo appearing. See the included documentation for more details."They even fixed some bugs that were in the original. How 'bout those guys, huh? PLAY THE GAME. :DReviewer: RedComethttp://www.romhacking.net/trans/1075/Reviewer: Light Showerhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/review/R52322.htmlCheat: Stage SelectIn Options, move the cursor to BGM, change the entry to SILENCE, and press the A button 4 times.  Then change the entry to NOTHING 13, and press the A button 3 times.  Now, start a new game and the Stage Select menu appears.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Vic Tokai</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>vEF6oyZI-bA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20713</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570424-battle-mania-daiginjou</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/battle-mania-daiginj</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battlemania-daiginjou/3030-33255/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20713-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20713-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413195-battle-mania-daiginjo-genesis-screenshot-a-clock-in-the-opening.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413196-battle-mania-daiginjo-genesis-screenshot-demonstration.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413197-battle-mania-daiginjo-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413198-battle-mania-daiginjo-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413199-battle-mania-daiginjo-genesis-screenshot-first-level.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1646481-101_26.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1646480-20080930003206.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1646459-finalbattle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1646458-stage8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/44493/1646403-101_32.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/20713.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A group calling itself the Kikokukyou have resurrected the leader of Blackball, the antagonist group of the original game, and the Trouble Shooters are called to stop Blackball and destroy Kikokukyou.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/254876af-7dc5-4556-b54e-e43d6635876c.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5538560-eb26-4359-85d8-44a903d99f78.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8fb626b9-f5a0-4e40-ae2b-161e6bbf8218.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57f8034f-ad69-4d04-8e42-8ec3e3dc3909.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93c4a1a9-1374-4968-8f96-8e8d539f23ee.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Vic Tokai</Publisher>
</game>