<Game>
	<Name>Beyond Oasis (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Beyond Oasis is an action adventure similar to the Legend of Zelda series, whilst taking a more action/combat heavy approach. The game has a series of elemental dungeons, where the player can acquire one of four elemental spirits needed to progress through the game. These can be upgraded through finding hidden "spirit gems" in the world, often using the corresponding spirit to find it.The Return of the PrinceIn Beyond Oasis, you play as the ever resourceful, Prince Ali. On one of his treasure hunts, Ali comes across an unchartedAli, escaping the island.island, and decides to explore the island's cave. There he discovers the Golden Armlet. Curious, Ali decides to put on the Armlet. As he does, a strange glow fills the cave. A face appears and begins to tell Ali that "[m]any ages ago, a devastating battle was waged in the shadowlands of the Kingdom of Oasis...", expounding that Ali must find the four spirits that the Golden Armlet governs, to stop the the evil of the one who wears the Silver Armlet. As the face disappears, the cave begins to shake and crumble. Ali swiftly makes his way back to the boat and escapes, and the island sinks below the ocean. Ali arrives at the shores of Oasis.Ali is in pretty good physical condition, and is able to preform various combat techniques, most of which involve flips and spins. He can also sprint for an unlimited amount of time.The MapOasisThe Map is used throughout the player's adventures to check the current location and itinerary. While the world is open, the player may only go to certain places through certain quests, revolving around one of the four spirits and beyond. While it may look small, Oasis is quite a big place, full of secret areas and challenges.The Four Spirits"Dytto" The Water SpiritThe ever helpful Dytto can be a lifesaver in tough situations. She can be summoned from any source of water, including spouts of water and water droplets. She is key to surviving the hidden underground gauntlet.Abilities:Pressing the A button once will summon a "Magic Bubble" to stun enemies.Pressing the A button twice restores a significant portion of health.Holding the A button and releasing will summon a "Magic Storm", which will damage anything in its path."Efreet" The Fire SpiritThe mighty powerhouse Efreet can smash through enemies, and destroy certain structures with powerful fire attacks. He can be summoned from any fire, and, if fast enough, though explosions. Efreet punches enemies automatically, protecting you from most threats. Efreet is used to win the special race, using his fireball dash ability.Abilities:Pressing the A button once will cause Efreet to breathe fire, which can beset enemies and unlit torchesPressing the A button twice will cause Efreet to transform into a fireball, dashing at quick speed in the direction the player is facing.Holding the A button and releasing will summon a "Melt Bomber" firestorm, which can decimate multiple enemies, and also set unlit torches on fire."Shade" The Shadow SpiritWhile not as attack focused, Shade offers a special passive effect, protecting you from attacks and saving you from falls unscathed. This, of course, comes at the price of the SP bar being reduced per hit and fall. Shade can be summoned from reflective surfaces, including Knight's armor.Abilites:Pressing the A button once will summon Shade's "Dark Claw", which can be used to grab hooks and hard-to-reach objects, as well as damage enemies.Holding the A button and releasing will cause Shade to become your "doppelganger", which can be used to solve certain "puzzles"."Bow" The Plant SpiritThe hungry plant Bow is required often, to eat through certain green "caged" doors; however, he can also be used to attack. Bow can be summoned from tiny plant saplings.Abilities:Pressing the A button once will cause Bow to bite.Pressing the A button twice will summon Bow to where the player is standing.Holding the A button and releasing will cause Bow to pop, releasing "Poison Pollen", which slows and stuns enemies in the area.Food and ItemsThroughout the game a variety of foods can be used to restore health. These can be found in numerous areas and are often awards for defeating a room of enemies. Not all types of food will heal, however, as fruit will restore spirit. Some items will effect both statuses. Here is a comprehensive list of foods and their effects:(H.P = Hit pointsS.P = Spirit Points)Cheese H.P 1/4Fish H.P 1/2Steak H.P 3/4Roast Beast H.P To FullOrange S.P 1/4Apple S.P 1/2Pomegranate S.P 3/4Grapes S.P To FullMushroom H.P/S.P 1/4Lettuce H.P/S.P 1/2Garlic H.P/S.P 3/4Toadstool H.P/S.P To FullThere are also summon items, which can be used to summon a specific spirit, without having to use their traditional method of summoning. A pitcher of water will summon Dytto, a lantern will summon Efreet, a mirror will summon Shade, and a plant pot will summon Bow.Genesis CollectionBeyond Oasis recently appeared in Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection for the Xbox 360 and PS3. Even though Beyond Oasis was called The Story of Thor in other parts of the world (including Europe), the European "Mega Drive Ultimate Collection" version still contains an emulated version of "Beyond Oasis", even when the menu still says "The Story of Thor". This is easily understandable, as there is no reason to emulate a separate version of a game that is identical. The same applies to all of the box art for the games, which are all North American.Freeing Dytto earns a 20G AchievementSoundtrack &amp; TriviaThe game's soundtrack is provided by Yuzo Koshiro and his studio Ancient, and an early demo of the game's song 'Concentration' can be found on the Streets of Rage 3 soundtrack, which he also contributed to. Strangely, Ancient ported over most of the sound library from Streets of Rage 3 and while they can be found in the cartridge data, hardly any of them are used besides the item pickup/eat food sound.System RequirementsOS: Windows&#174; XP or higherProcessor: Intel Pentium 2.0 GHzMemory: 2GBGraphics: 32MB or greater graphics cardDirectX&#174;: DirectX&#174; 9.0 or greaterHard Drive: 50MB free disc spaceCheat: Best Players ScreenTo view the best players screen (which is firstly seen on completion of the game), press B + Start at the title screen.Cheat: Best Players ScreenAt the title screen, press and hold Down + Right + Start to view the demonstration.Cheat: Best Players ScreenTo instantly switch from your Alt. Knife to the weapon currently selected in the weapons menu and vice versa without needing to open the weapons menu up, hold Mode and press B. Please note that this command requires a 6-button controller.Cheat: Best Players ScreenThese codes require a six button controller.  Before proceeding, make sure that on the Diary screen with the 4 save slots it highlights an empty save slot by default.  On the title screen, hold the buttons listed in the cheat and keep them held as you press Start twice (once to open the Diary screen, the second to begin a new game)  A sound effect will confirm success.  For the area select and dialog viewer code, hold the MODE button as you open the save screen during gameplay to access the area list.  To access the dialog viewer, hold X and Z, and then press A or C to close the menu you just opened.  With X and Z still held, walk up to a NPC and press B to talk.  The game will now cycle through the story text.Cheat: Best Players ScreenAt the Diary (save select) screen, press B + Start to access the game's sound test screen.Cheat: Secret IslandNOTE: This will only work after you have the Warp Device. Go to the seashore on the lower west side of the map. Use Shade's Doppelganger to locate the invisible silver crack (the warp), then use your Warp Device to open up the warp. You'll then be transported to a secret island located on upper west side of the map. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>H40274WHGhI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20573</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586061-beyond-oasis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/beyond-oasis</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/beyond-oasis/3030-211/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20573-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YL4q4Zf.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/IU6sGAg.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/5cTCRbV.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/vR5ecGV.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/qT16OfX.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/uYnEbwE.png</boxart7>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/159270-beyond-oasis-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39483-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-us.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/257501-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-european.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39481-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-ali-hits-the-jackpot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39480-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-intro-close-up-of-ali.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39482-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-he-finds-the-legendary-gold.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39484-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-save-game-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39485-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-the-ruins-collapse.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39486-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-ali-gets-back-to-his-land.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39487-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-he-is-met-with-some-unexpected.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39489-beyond-oasis-genesis-screenshot-entrance-to-the-castle.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kmrlhW3.png</banner1>
	<Notes>On the mystical island of Oasis, Prince Ali embarks on a crusade against evil. The warrior prince must unleash the powers of the four Wild Spirits to stop the resurrection of a ruthless sorcerer and save the empire! As Ali, you can call on the powers of the four wild spirits to battle the evil minions of Agito. Fight off enemies with Ali's weapons, punches and kicks... or dig deeper to discover the Hidden Super Moves...a Sega first! Flip switches, trigger plates, and use what's left of your brain to solve mind-boggling puzzles that lead to Huge Bosses... like the Fire-breathing Red Dragon!</Notes>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78872d24-9d86-452e-a805-0f66e0c7ff55.png</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82b6c5a9-27f9-4d3c-8346-e9c75b17489e.jpg</boxart9>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5bf37cf-1af0-4527-ac3a-236755e14520.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f680906-4862-4bbc-93fa-29804d8bbf94.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18f3c909-6e88-41f3-a14e-d56119627d45.jpg</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>