<Game>
	<Name>Blades of Vengeance (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Gameplay:The game features three playable characters that they player can choose from. There is the huntress(fast character), the warrior(powerful character), and the sorcerer(ranged character). Each has their own strengths and weaknesses and are somewhat balanced.The game features simplistic, 2-D environments and fantasy combat. Enemies are typical representations of fantasy lore and each level ends with a boss to conquer. Many secret areas can be found in each level, along with many items to help ease the character through the tougher boss battles.Each level has a few power-ups that will evolve the player character a bit, changing their appearance as well as the strength of their attack. There's a bit more customizability via an item shop which can be accessed between levels.The game is somewhat of a challenge, even though extra lives can be bought throughout the game with collected coins. Once a player has run out of lives and continues the game was over and would have to be started over. Lives were easy to lose as well since there were many chances for the character to fall to their death.Cheat: Secret Level SelectIn the first level, play through the first part of the level all the way until you get to the door that takes you to a new part of the level.  This is the door near the button on the ground that pops out a treasure chest behind you.  Use your jump attack to jump onto an invisible platform just over the left part of the top of the door.  It's fairly difficult to reach, unless you are the girl, but you can reach it with any character.  Once you're up there, jump up and to the far right, there's another invisible platform against the wall.  Once you're against the wall, just keep jumping up until you get to the secret door!  Cheat: Secret Level SelectInside the door there are several chests with gold and silver and all kinds of potions, several power stars, and 7 more doors.  The doors will take you to the different levels of the game.  The first door takes you to level 2, the second to level 3, etc...</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Gh1lIwhholM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3875</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586066-blades-of-vengeance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/blades-of-vengeance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/blades-of-vengeance/3030-16733/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3875-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3875-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/97030-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46097-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46098-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-come-just-a-little-closer.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46099-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-what-s-going-on-ere.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46100-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-character-select-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46101-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-bit-depressing-isn-t.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82816-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-a-secret-passage.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82815-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-hot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82817-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82818-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-scores.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/82819-blades-of-vengeance-genesis-screenshot-after-every-level-you.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gR4mtMN.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3875.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The evil Dark Lady has unleashed an onslaught of barbarians and beasts upon the land, and it's your duty to come face-to-face with all that she can throw at you in an attempt to protect your homeland. In BLADES OF VENGEANCE, you can choose your gladiator from three different classes: Huntress, Warrior, or Sorcerer. Each character has its own special powers and abilities, so you'll have to decide which one best fits your fighting style and then get ready for the fight of your life! Along with your standard weapons battle-axe, rapier, mace, crossbow, and fireball you can also make yourself invincible with special armor and weapons that are strewn about each of the eight levels. If you've got the strength and courage to defeat all eight of the bosses, then you'll have a shot at the Dark Lady are you ready?</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a95a9ccc-7545-4654-bd9f-3b5d2ddbaf65.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/093f3f03-8096-4951-add1-448de1163f69.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38dc2444-17b3-477b-8339-f2ea83808bfb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1a1b19b-998f-48fc-8269-36fa9901e1df.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>