<Game>
	<Name>Bloodshot (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:A futuristic FPS modeled after Return to Castle Wolfenstein, The player is required to fight their way through twelve levels of intense action. In each level the player must find the power node at the center of a maze of corridors and destroy it. This triggers a self destruct sequence in the level giving the player limited time to retrace their steps back to the entrance before the node explodes.Plot:On the 29 of December 2049, an Earth Moon base known as Yaz 67 is destroyed by an unidentified Alien battle cruiser. Earth Federation Starfleet Command (EFDC) responds by sending two ofThe Alien Battle Cruisertheir own battle cruisers in an attempt to disable it. The boarding party finds upon entering the ship that instead of an organic crew it is manned by robots, some of which are pre programmedkilling machines. Eventually the boarding party is completely destroyed by these machines. Earth Federation defense force (EFDF) decides that boarding the ship is not an option and so instead tows the Alien cruiser back to Earth until it&#8217;s robot protectors can be disabled by electromagnetic fields. Upon completion of this it is found that the Aliens plan to send a fleet of these carriers each containing thousands of robots. The troop&#8217;s transporters cannot be destroyed via conventional weapons and instead must be boarded and destroyed from within. The player is drafted as an Elite Trooper, after weeks of training within environments that will simulate the challenge ahead you are deemed worthy. On the 7 of February 2050 EFDS detects that the troop transporters have entered the Solar System and are heading for Earth. On the 8 of February 2050 your brain is implanted with a Battle Frenzy Chip (BFC) that will give you lightning reflexes, superhuman strength and the desire to kill. On the 12 of February 2050 you and 11 other Elite Troopers board the largest Alien transporter and the battle begins.Weapons:RB101 Ricochet Bullet DeflectorFires high energy bolts that while slow moving are capable of bouncing off walls and inflicting very heavy damage.Lock-on Zero OneFires moderately fast bolts in rapid succession that will lock on to any enemies standing within direct line of sight of the player; however it drains ammunition very quickly.MTX225 Plasma Mortar Assault CannonFires very slow but very powerful rockets that can eliminate any medium sized enemy in only two hits. Also inflicts splash damage on nearby targets.40-40 Semi-Automatic Rapid Pulse RifleThe fastest firing weapon in the game. The bolts inflict little damage but are so high in number that it can make quick work of any enemies.TRIBOLTFires three bolts, a central bolt with 2 slower bolts either side of it. The spray effect allows for poorer accuracy and can hit three enemies simultaneously. While it has relatively small power the ammo drain is very low despite its spray effect.WEPONEX Hi-Charge Matter Independent Combat LauncherAlso known as &#8220;The Piercer&#8221;, it fires a single slow moving but extremely powerful bolt that can pierce through walls and shields. The games maze like design makes this very handy for eliminating enemies taking cover around corners.GRENNA-KIL Pump Action Grenade Propulsion UnitFires high explosive grenades in a parabolic arc in front of the player. Direct hits will instantly eliminate all but the toughest enemies and high levels of splash damage can critically injure enemies close by.MTX 9X1: User Controlled Shrapnel GrenadeAlso known as &#8220;The Breaker&#8221;, this weapon fires a disk directly in front of the player which can be remote detonated releasing seven powerful shells in an arc. Tricky to use but when mastered can destroy multiple high level targets in a single shot.&#8220;King Hell&#8221; MegaFluxll Local Fusion ReactorExtremely rare and powerful weapon. Will only be found once per level and fires a single but massively powerful shot that can destroy any target on a single hit.60-60 Wide Area Cover Plasma RifleSimilar to the 40-40, this fires in an arc but displays the same ammo drain. As such it can eliminate medium range enemies very quickly.Enemies:SentryBasic foot droid. Comes in four varieties, these are found in high numbers in each level and will attack en masse to compensate for their little power and durability.StrollerSimilar to the sentry but more powerful and highly durable. It requires a great deal of damage to be destroyed and present a much greater threat to the player throughout the majority of the game.BeastEight foot tall mutant electro beast. It carries an indestructible shield that can only be defeated by grenades or piercer bolts. Careful timing required with other weapons to only fire when he lowers his shield to attack.Plasma ManA very rare, fire-based creature that has the ability to transcend matter. Presents a high challenge to destroy.TatbotVery large and slow robot that requires enormous amounts of damage to destroy. Some carry grenades and all posses a high degree of accuracy with their weapons. Players are recommended to use grenades when fighting these behemoths.BborgFloating head creature from another dimension. Very fast moving and is formed via a mixture of biological and mechanical technologies. Bears close resemblance to cacodemons from the Doom series of games.WireheadSimilar to the Bborg but possesses a fully formed body. Each of its limbs in turn must be destroyed before it will fall. Very rare enemy.Cheat: Battle Frenzy CheatsPause the game, and press one of the following button sequences. A sound effect will confirm correct entry.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, First-Person, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>Domark</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>6YuzKZ9sh6g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20300</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/576362-bloodshot</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/battle-frenzy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bloodshot/3030-21718/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20300-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89808-battle-frenzy-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89809-battle-frenzy-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103363-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103361-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103360-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103362-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-two-players-mode.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103359-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-found-an-item.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103364-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-locking-on.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103365-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-found-some-big-thing.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103366-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-in-front-of-a-door.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103367-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-exploring-exploring.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103368-battle-frenzy-genesis-screenshot-this-level-is-green.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/20300.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Bloodshot, known as Battle Frenzy in Germany, is a Sega Mega Drive and Sega Mega-CD game developed by Domark. It is notable for being a 3D first person shooter - one of the few available for the Sega Mega Drive and the only game of this genre for the Sega Mega-CD. Bloodshot was only released in Mega Drive cartridge form throughout Europe and Australia. It was exclusive to the Sega Channel in North America where it was called by its German name, Battle Frenzy. It is assumed the game was retitled to make the game sound less violent, though the game does not contain any blood ("Bloodshot" is a code name for the fictional "Battle Frenzy" chip implanted in the player"). The Sega Mega-CD version was also exclusive to Europe until 2003, when a North American version under the Battle Frenzy name was released. This version was developed and published by Good Deal Games without the consent of Domark or Acclaim.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8deb973b-c759-43de-96e8-bb2646bee85f.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2500940-3a45-47f2-8549-fc9d6e393682.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4cb30a84-1b35-4c0a-b1f8-629e588bf002.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>