<Game>
	<Name>Bonkers (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The game is based on the Disney TV series of the same name. Bonkers is a bob-cat police officer. One day, he reads in a newspaper that a contest for the best policeman is announced. Since his partner is away, Bonkers decides that would be the best opportunity to grab the first prize. In order to win the contest, Bonkers has to catch four famous criminals.Catching each one of the criminals is a separate mini-game. The first one involves you running horizontally in a museum room and throwing doughnuts at thieves who are trying to steal valuable things. In the second one, you try to lock a criminal in a yard by quickly building a brick wall around him. In the third one, you must find clothes hidden in crates before a bomb explodes. Finally, the fourth and last game involves you driving a car from top-down view, chasing a criminal. Each mini-game also features a unique bonus game, which you get when you successfully complete three games with gradually advancing difficulty in a row.Cheat: Level select and sound testEnter the code at the Sega logo.  A sound effect will confirm success.Cheat: All Easy Mode PasswordsThese Passwords are for Easy Mode.  The Passwords are in order of Stage completion.  To clarify, "TNT" is the TNT with the open parachute, while "Unopened TNT" is the TNT that's vertical with the unopened Parachute.Alos keep in mind, Passwords will keep track of how many lives you have and which stages have been completed in what order so these Passwords may change depending on Gameplay performance.Cheat: All Easy Mode PasswordsThese Passwords are for Hard Mode. The Passwords are in order of Stage completion. To clarify, "TNT" is the TNT with the open parachute, while "Unopened TNT" is the TNT that's vertical with the unopened Parachute. Also keep in mind, Passwords will keep track of how many lives you have and which stages have been completed in what order so these Passwords may change depending on Gameplay performance. In Hard Mode, Passwords also keep track of how many items you've lost in the Harry The Handbag Rounds.Cheat: All Easy Mode PasswordsThese Passwords are for Normal Mode.  The Passwords are in order of Stage completion.  To clarify, "TNT" is the TNT with the open parachute, while "Unopened TNT" is the TNT that's vertical with the unopened Parachute.Alos keep in mind, Passwords will keep track of how many lives you have and which stages have been completed in what order so these</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4291</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586070-disneys-bonkers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/bonkers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bonkers/3030-575/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4291-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4291-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1539/515365-pausescreen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1539/515350-inexplicablepassword.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1539/515341-hpim1188.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/1/7/gfs_38827_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/8/a/gfs_38827_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wOGhcpn.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4291.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game is based on the Disney TV show of the same name. Bonkers is a bob-cat police officer who lives in "toondom", a cartoony land where people co-exist with various creatures from cartoon movies.  One day, Bonkers and his partner Lucky hear about a shocking robbery: Hollywood's most valuable treasures - Sorcerer's Hat, Mermaid's Voice, and Magic Lamp - were stolen! Now it is up to Bonkers to capture the thieves and to take back the stolen treasures. This is an action platform game. Bonkers can jump and dash, throwing enemies aside and even destroying some obstacles. Enemies can be killed by jumping on their heads. You can also collect various items such as bombs to throw at the enemies, cakes to refill your health, or hyper juice to make you dash continuously. Besides the common license, this game is totally different from the Genesis game Bonkers.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bfa1c704-67fc-43e3-a955-adfe5b0cfe3b.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e13484db-3b86-4f85-90da-e7e48a257d34.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f8a2ba2-1db2-4c06-8ed8-4ed27ae8ec9b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>