<Game>
	<Name>Boogerman - A Pick and Flick Adventure (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Boogerman: A Pick and Flick Adventure is an action platformer that was initially released for Sega Genesis and SNES. Players control Snotty Ragsdale, an eccentric millionaire with a curious mind. Players burp, flick, fart, and spit their way through the dimension of X Crement. The game takes place in 5 different worlds of unique and disgusting themes; each world ends with a boss fight.Story:On a dark and stormy night Professor Stinkbaum has built a device to rid the world of pollution. This device gets rid of pollution by transexisting it to another dimension that goes by the name of X Crement. Snotty Ragsdale (Boogerman) is an eccentric millionaire who takes a job at Stinkbaum's lab in order to see what is really happening to all the pollution. On this particular night Ragsdale disrupts the machine by sneezing on the crystal that makes the whole thing work. A large hand comes out of the machine and takes the crystal back to dimension X Crement. Ragsdale is left with only one option - He heads into the men's room and comes back out as Boogerman. Following the hand, he finds himself on a quest to save the world.Worlds/BossesWorld 1: Flatulent Swamps -- Boss: HickmanWorld 2: The Pits -- Boss: RevoltaWorld 3: Boogerville -- Boss: Fly BoyWorld 4: Mucous Mountains and Nasal Caverns -- Boss: Deodor AntWorld 5: Pus Palace -- Boss: BoogermeisterCheat: Fly on screen.Anytime during the game, press: A + B + C and Start on controller 2. Use controller one and the D=pad to make Boogerman fly around the screen to collect icons and otherwise. Just do the same input to make Boogerman move again.Cheat: Fly on screen.To get a free carrot, when in-game press Up, Down, Left, Right, B, Up, Down.Cheat: Fly on screen.When on the title screen, press: Up, down, left, right, C, B, A. Then, press up and down to select any level. Cheat: Fly on screen.As the title screen loads, press Up, Down, Left, Right, Down, Down, B. You will now go to the sound test menu.Cheat: Level and boss passwordsLevel 1: Scab Creature, Abdominal Sewer Man, Pus Creature, Miner Goblin Boss 1: Ghost, Nose Goblin, Ghost, Pus Creature Level 2: Pus Creature, Scab Creature, Ghost, Boogerman Boss 2: Troll, Miner Goblin, Nose Goblin, Ghost Level 3: Scab Creature, Ghost, Abdominal Sewer Man, Boogerman Boss 3: Boogerman, Pus Creature, Miner Goblin, Scab Creature Level 4A: Nose Goblin, Scab Creature, Ghost, Troll Level 4B: Nose Goblin, Pus Creature, Ogre, Scab Creature Boss 4: Ghost, Scab Creature, Troll, Miner Goblin Level 5: Pus Creature, Boogerman, Ghost, Pus Creature Final Boss: Pus Creature, Abdominal Sewer Man, Boogerman, Miner GoblinCheat: Level and boss passwordsEnter the following password go to the level shown. Key:0 - Boogerman1 - Green Spearman2 - Fat Yellow Monster3 - Orange Monster4 - Sad Green Horned Monster5 - Yellow Spotted Pink Monster6 - Miner7 - White Ghost8 - Red Monster9 - White Bigfoot MonsterCheat: Credits scrolling, lets have fun.After you beat the game, while the credits start to scroll, you can walk into the bathroom and change into civilian clothing. You can use the duster and everything too. Anytime you want you can walk back in and change back into BoogerMan. You can even fly around. Just remember that the door on the right is the bathroom. The one on the left just makes you exit.Cheat: Free Spit mucasTo get free Mucas when in-game press Up, Down, Left, Right, A, Up, Down</plot>
	<releasedate>18/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>iRJPDuzSnXA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4292</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586071-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure/3030-16717/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4292-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/16515-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/189936-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4292-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46037-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46030-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46031-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-boogerman.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46032-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46034-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46035-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-and.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46036-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-apart.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46026-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-and.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46027-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure-genesis-screenshot-if.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4292-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PVCI7B0.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4292.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You will have an adventure in an unknown world as a caped hero who slings his own boogers to vanquish his foes. The hero of the game is a booger-tossing, noisily burping, fart-spewing man named Snotty Ragsdale. While he lives his normal life as an eccentric millionaire, his natural "in-stinks" come in handy when he dons the mask of the smelly hero Boogerman.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3c05d8b-fa05-49e2-af00-0d46a7108568.png</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a473a3b2-f1b2-440e-9564-1aeb53fe8a2f.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35b4c747-387c-41ae-ae5a-1208dd709f10.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d5d14ef-7b14-40c6-8282-6eeea2cbb773.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14d9edec-919f-4c51-badf-c4f0049684e5.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>