<Game>
	<Name>Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bram Stoker's Dracula is a 1993 video game released as a tie-in based on the Francis Ford Coppola movie of the same name. In the game, the player takes on the role of Jonathan Harker, who must stop the vampire Dracula. Versions of the game were released for a multitude of platforms ranging from the Amiga and NES to the Sega CD and PC.There were numerous variations between each version, though they all played similarly and shared the protagonist Jonathan Harker.NES, Game Boy, Game Gear and Sega Master SystemThe 8-bit and portable versions of the game skewed closer to standard platformers than the other console versions, with floating platforms and other standard platformer obstacles.SNES and GenesisThe 16-bit versions were action games that focused more on combat and adventure game elements than platforming. The sprite used for Harker was larger, and the games had more enemies to face down.Sega CD and AmigaSimilar to the SNES and Genesis, these versions were more action-oriented. They included FMV cutscenes from the movie and digitized backgrounds.DOSThe Bram Stoker's Dracula for PC MS-DOS systems was a first-person shooter, taking after games like Doom and Wolfenstein 3D (or Blood and Heretic, which share similar gothic horror settings).Cheat: Gain Health and 99 LivesAt the ''Beware'' screen, press A, Left, U, C, A, Right, Down.  The screen border turns white if entered correctly.  While playing the game hold down A and press Start, Start to fill your health and get 99 lives. Cheat: Gain Health and 99 LivesAt the ''Beware'' screen, press A, Left, U, C, A, Right, Down.  The screen border turns white if entered correctly.  Then enter one of the following button combinations to begin on the chosen level: Level 1 = Hold C and press Start Level 2 = Hold B and press Start Level 3 = Hold C + B and press Start Level 4 = Hold A and press Start Level 5 = Hold A + C and press Start Level 6 = Hold A + B and press Start Level 7 = Hold A + B + C and press StartCheat: Gain Health and 99 LivesDuring the intro sequence, where it shows the battlefield and flags, press Down, Right, A, C, Up, Left, A (DRACULA). You should hear a laughing sound to confirm correct entry. When in-game, press pause and press Up / Down to choose the level.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>9OxknDofGY8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3073</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586073-bram-stokers-dracula</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/bram-stokers-dracula</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bram-stokers-dracula/3030-1792/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3073-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3073-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/47678-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39994-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39995-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-options-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39996-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-each-level-appears.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39997-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-inside-dracula-s-castle.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39998-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-outside-the-castle.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/39999-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-boss-battle.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40000-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-stepping-out-of-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40001-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-fighting-some-animal.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40002-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-shooting-wolves.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40003-bram-stoker-s-dracula-genesis-screenshot-boss-battle-against.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3073-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/e7pfpDn.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3073.png</clearlogo1>
</game>