<Game>
	<Name>Bubsy in - Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bubsy in: Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind (known in Japan as Yamaneko Bubsy no Daibouken, translated to The Adventures of Bubsy Wildcat) is a 2D platformer developed and published by Accolade for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and Sega Genesis in 1993. This pun-filled game stars an anthropomorphic wise-cracking bobcat named Bubsy, as he tries to stop enemy aliens (called Woolies) from stealing Earth's supply of yarn balls.The game later spawned a series of platformers (ending with Bubsy 3D). An enhanced version for the PC, titled Super Bubsy, was released in 1995. Super Bubsy contained upscaled graphics, new sound effects, and the unsuccessful pilot episode for the Bubsy animated series.Gameplay:The game plays like a traditional 2D sidescrolling platformer similar to Sonic the Hedgehog. Players run through levels, attempting to reach the end of the level (before the time runs out) while eliminating enemies, gaining score, collecting powerups, and avoiding deadly obstacles. The game includes fifteen main levels (called "chapters") split up into six main areas (ranging from forests to the Wild West) and one final level (set in space).Bubsy has two abilities at his disposal: jumping (by pressing the Jump button) and gliding (by pressing the Glide button). Gliding reduces his downward falling speed, and activating it at the right time before bouncing up allows Bubsy to be propelled much higher than usual.Running into enemies, touching deadly obstacles (such as water, spiked pits), and fall damage can kill Bubsy in one hit (as he has no health system whatsoever). However, jumping or gliding onto enemies can eliminate them (getting them out of Bubsy's way while giving the player score). Due to the difficulty, there are plenty of checkpoints (for Bubsy to respawn at) and extra lives (as if starting with nine lives, like the cat mythology, is easy enough) scattered around levels.Cheat: Level SelectEnter the following at the title screen on Control Pad 2, A, Left, A, Up, Down, Down, Down, Left, A, Right, Right, B, Up, B. No audio or visual confirmation is given. When you have done this enter one of the following on Control Pad 2 to go to the level shown.Cheat: Level PasswordsAt the title screen, press A to bring up the options menu. Move to the password option and press Right and enter the following codes:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ZcsBhSg6IJk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>459</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586079-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind/3030-20205/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/459-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/459-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/31558-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83877-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83878-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83879-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83880-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83881-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7395/1190734-sonic_rip_off.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4187/265132-bubsy05.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4187/265129-bubsy04.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4187/265128-bubsy03.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4187/265126-bubsy02.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iFvgcf2.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/459.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The plot focuses on a race of fabric-stealing aliens called "Woolies", who have stolen the world's yarn ball supply (especially Bubsy's, who owns the world's largest collection). Naturally, Bubsy does not take too kindly to the theft and sets out to "humble" the Woolies.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbfd12d7-b3f6-48fe-b13a-7db7fa59f500.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45ac2966-8245-44b0-b1ae-20aab2699e2a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/101b2f7a-14b6-4d59-b04d-41f4f46ad209.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>