<Game>
	<Name>Bulls vs Lakers and the NBA Playoffs (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The sequel to EA Sports' classic basketball title Lakers vs. Celtics.  The core gameplay of the original is supplemented with a variety of new features, including:1. All 16 1991 NBA Playoff teams (up from 8 in Lakers vs. Celtics) plus the East and West All-Star Teams, plus courts with official team logos/colors. Player game stats updated while the game is in progress.An Instant Replay mode.New "signature moves" for star players.Improved defense and passing controls and a foul shooting meter.Multiplayer options include cooperative and head-to-head modes.Cheat: 76ers Championship Matchup Codes76ers vs. Warriors: 28OBFBBB 76ers vs. Blazers: 78OBFBBB 76ers vs. Suns: 68OBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesBlazers vs. Bulls: KBOBFBBB Blazers vs. Celtics: 7BOBFBBC Blazers vs. 76ers: MBOBFBBC Cheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesBucks vs. Suns: HDOBFBBB Bucks vs. Blazers: CDOBFBBB Bucks vs. Spurs: FDOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesBulls vs. Jazz: NXOBBBBL Bulls vs. Lakers: OXOBFBBC Bulls vs. Supersonics: MXOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this code to be in the first round, game seven, against the Celtics: WXVBQCVLCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this code to be in the second round, game four, against the cavaliers, Bulls 3-0: WXZBQJBDCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this code to be in the third round, game four, against the Knicks, Bulls 3-0: WXXBQ2BKCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this code to be in the finals, game four, against the Warriors, Bulls 3-0: WXOBTBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesCeltics vs. Blazers: HNOBFBBB Celtics vs. Warriors: BNOBFBBC Celtics vs. Rockets: MNOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this password to see the ending: NXWBBBBDCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesHawks vs. Spurs: 24OBFBBC Hawks vs. Rockets: 64OBFBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesJazz vs. Pistons: LVOBFBBF Jazz vs. Hawks: MVOBFBBC Jazz vs. Bucks: WVOBFBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesKnicks vs. Lakers: HJOBFBBB Knicks vs. Suns: KJOBFBBB Knicks vs. Warriors: BJOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesLakers vs. Bucks: BLOBFBBF Lakers vs. Bulls: CLOBFBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesPacers vs. Supersonics: NOOBFBBB Pacers vs. Lakers: COOBFBBB Pacers vs. Rockets: GOOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesEnter this password: NXOBBBBLCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesPistons vs. Supersonics: NSOBFBBB Pistons vs. Jazz: 1SOBFBBB Pistons vs. Blazers: 7SOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesRockets vs. Hawks: M2OBFBBC Rockets vs. Pacers: T2OBFBBB Rockets vs. Pistons: Q2OBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesSpurs vs. Bucks: BGOBFBBD Spurs vs. Bulls: FGOBFBBB Spurs vs. Hawks: HGOBFBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesSuns vs. 76ers: PZOBFBBB Suns vs. Celtics: LZOBFBBD Suns vs. Bulls: FZOBFBBBCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesSupersonics vs. Bucks: BQOBFBBD Supersonics vs. 76ers: MQOBFBBCCheat: 76ers Championship Matchup CodesWarriors vs. Bucks: P6WBBBBC Warriors vs. 76ers: 560BFBBB Warriors vs. Hawks: M60BFBBC </plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4300</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586085-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs/3030-2778/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4300-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/85923-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/88382-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29496-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29497-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-gameplay.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29498-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-team.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29499-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-tv.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29500-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-player.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29501-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-sixers.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29502-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29503-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29504-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-vlade.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/29505-bulls-vs-lakers-and-the-nba-playoffs-genesis-screenshot-make.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4300.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The sequel to EA Sports' basketball title Lakers versus Celtics and the NBA Playoffs. The core gameplay of the original is supplemented with a variety of new features, including:•All 16 1992 NBA Playoff teams (up from 8 in Lakers vs. Celtics) plus the East and West All-Star Teams, plus courts with official team logos/colors. The rosters are based on the 1990/1991 season. • Player game stats updated while the game is in progress. •An Instant Replay mode. •New "signature moves" for star players. •Improved defense and passing controls and a foul shooting meter.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>jAFUs_nPjaU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ebd0df7-ba18-43f4-a705-6a7549b85c02.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/117805c2-7cfa-46a0-99a0-40e0086640ab.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a167dfc5-a8d4-436d-8235-f69b876564da.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95b10f07-6cc3-4b32-882b-d354808571bc.png</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>