<Game>
	<Name>Caesars Palace (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to the fast-paced casino capital of Las Vegas, Nevada -- home of the premier casino, Caesars Palace! Now you can sharpen your skills and practice your poker face in the privacy of your own home with your Sega Genesis and the CAESARS PALACE cartridge. Filled with the most popular games, CAESARS PALACE has everything a High Roller could ask for: Blackjack, Roulette, Craps, Keno, Slots, Video Poker, and Video Horse Racing!--From the Genesis Caesars Palace instruction manual.Overview::Caesars Palace is all about gambling, and the great thing about it is that you don't have to hate yourself for losing $5000 dollars. Caesars Palace contained 5 different games, and very detailed sound effects! This game made you feel like you were actually at the table, the odds were highly realistic! Another good add-on to this game was the videos to teach beginners how to play each game. A great game for the gambler in all of us.Controls:A Button: SelectB Button: CancelHints:$8 millionEnter 9CN6BXHZG3C8-YCG - Start with $9,999,999 -To start with $9,999,999 type in the password 9HS-TSHLH75QJTCG.http://www.consoleclassix.com/genesis/caesars_palace.htmlhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/home/915983.htmlCheat: Start with $1,000,000Start a new game and go to the Quickashier.  Move to the password button.  Enter the password: 8YX6BXGZ591SOTCG and start the game.  Find an ATM.  It says your name is Lucky and your balance is a cool $1,000,000!Cheat: Start with $1,000,000To start with $9,999,999 type in the password 9HS-TSHLH75QJTCG.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Card</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Interactive</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4303</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/915983-caesars-palace</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/caesars-palace/3030-1542/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4303-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14034/441742-caesarspalace_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/f/b/gfs_47717_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/2/b/gfs_47717_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/9/b/gfs_47717_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/8/b/gfs_47717_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/3/b/gfs_47717_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/e/b/gfs_47717_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/5/b/gfs_47717_1_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/8/a/gfs_47717_1_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/3/a/gfs_47717_1_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/9/7/gfs_47717_1_10.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RdTWmQi.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4303.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Once a player reaches a sufficient amount of funds, they can then go to the V.I.P. room and play more high stakes versions of these games to either win big or lose big. To add more realism, the player can also visit ATMs to draw more cash for playing in case they are running low on on-hand cash. It also has a password feature that will allow the player to pick up and continue their game at a later time.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35da43e0-0ad6-4938-8d4c-397e8e04c7b8.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fd584f5-da09-467d-a89d-1fd3788dd105.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Virgin Games</Publisher>
</game>