<Game>
	<Name>Chakan (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Chakan is a 2D action-platformer for both the Genesis and the Game Gear. The game was based on Robert A. Kraus' Chakan comic series.The Four Portals of the SupernaturalEarth - The realm of the 'Spider Queen'.Fire- The realm of the sadistic Elkenrod, Mistress of Spectres.Water - A realm of watery dangers. This level contains many levels including; Spiked Lizards, Squid, Giant-clawed Worms, and Demons. The boss of this level is The Mantis.Air- A castle in the air, the boss of this level is The Dragonfly King.Players are able to complete the portals in any order.Weapons:Balling Mallet - Used to bash through walls and boulders.Scythe - Used to combat enemies and slash through webs.Battle Axe - Used to battle creatures and break certain doors.Grappling Hooks - Used to grapple onto set locations.AlchemyThere are twelve types of alchemy:Temporarily blinds the enemy.Causes enemies to slow down.Allows players to throw bombs.Restores the skull bar.Arms the player with the Blue-sword.Arms the player with the Blue-Lightning Sword.Arms the player with the Orange Sword.Allow the player to jump higher.Arms the player with the Green-Lightning Sword.Reverses the hourglass.Creates a passages in certain locations.Shields the player from enemies.Cheat: All the Alchemy PowersStart the game than press the C button on both controllers.  Hold them down and hit reset.  You'll hear a sound when the title screen pops up.  Start the game again, hitting start to goto the alchemy screen, and push the pad on controller 2, left, right, up then down.  Push start on controller 2 for water alchemy, button a for earth alchemy, button b for fire alchemy and button c for air alchemy.Cheat: True EndingWait 15 minutes on the hourglass screen after defeating the final boss that appears after all levels are beaten, and you'll see the text "NOT THE END" appear for a few seconds before the game resets itself.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>LDiOtr5X81Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3891</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563316-chakan</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/chakan</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chakan/3030-11805/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3891-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3891-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80507-chakan-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3891-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35741-chakan-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35742-chakan-genesis-screenshot-the-story.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3891-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lTMoExK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3891.png</clearlogo1>
</game>