<Game>
	<Name>Championship Pro-Am (USA)</Name>
	<plot>If you like racing in simplistic circles, then I've got just the game for you: Championship Pro-Am. Developed by Rare and published by Tradewest, this game will make driving in straight lines a thing of the past. And in case you're wondering, it also happens to be quite a fun little title. Still, any bundle of joy is not without its poo, and the game has plenty of that, too. And so I ask: does the poo outweigh the good? Well, no. But it does come close.The game's premise is simple: you drive a car around something like 30 tracks, trying to finish in third place or better on each course so that you can advance to the next. The number of laps varies, as does the shape of a given course, but there are typically somewhere around three laps and there are only around six different course patterns.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/review/R72364.html</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Tradewest</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4310</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/925728-championship-pro-am</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/championship-pro-am/3030-24966/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4310-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/0/1/64901_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/5/8/gfs_61510_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/c/5/gfs_61510_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VAnM2sv.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4310.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Guide your radio controlled car to victory in this racing game. You have to beat your 3 opponents on 32 tracks while avoiding obstacles like water and oil puddles and collecting bonus items like better engines and tires. You can also collect a variety of weapons to blast your opponents out of the way. The Genesis version is basically the same game as the NES version with a few minor changes such as having 5 opponents instead of 3, spelling out CHAMPION instead of NINTENDO, and having enhanced graphics.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d973727b-82ce-46bc-8377-b18780b8fe6e.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/756661a0-b917-40a3-9a67-9db4429db3d8.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40d63a6b-3666-4a8b-98d7-afaa711b9810.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Tradewest</Publisher>
</game>