<Game>
	<Name>Chameleon Kid (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Wild Side is the newest game in town. All the kids are wild to play it. It's a machine that surrounds you with flame-belching, body-snatching monsters. Step inside and it's just you against the madness. It's fast, dangerous and almost impossible to beat. One other thing - it's a kid-eater! Until Kid Chameleon takes charge. He bursts open blocks, finds helmets and - Blam! - he transforms into a brick-smashing Berzerker! Crunch! He's a buzzing Micromax, hacking Maniaxe, or jet-powered Skycutter. By bashing blocks, he builds up superpowers for the monster-mash ahead! Crabuloids, Skull Chompers, Killer Slime! Kid Chameleon wipes 'em out with hair-raising leaps! He scrambles up walls, skates across ceilings and squeezes through escape holes. With more than 1,850 screens, 103 levels, and loads of secret paths, there's always a way out. And they all lead to the lair of the Elsewhere Evilmeister, Heady Metal!Cheat: Infinite Lives GlitchLose all your lives and in the last life, die and immediately press and hold start. If you did it correctly, the screen "resume play and give up" will appear. Choose "give up" and the number of lives disappears.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete Blue Lask Woods in under 20 seconds.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete any level without collecting any special items to get 5000 bonus points.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete a stage without being hurt by an enemy to earn 5000 bonus points.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsAt the end of Blue lake woods there is a series of blocks just above the flag. Jump to the last one and then press down and right, jump and special together. You will be warped to Plethora, the last level.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<rating>7.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>q0VMjLud9C0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2279</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586273-kid-chameleon</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2279-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2279-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/9/4/gfs_51620_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/4/gfs_51620_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2279-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2279.png</clearlogo1>
</game>