<Game>
	<Name>Chase H.Q. II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Similar to Chase H.Q. in some ways: same gameplay, same number of stages, and same objective. If you haven't heard of this game before, you basically drive on a freeway trying to catch up with five criminals who have committed felonies, but time is against you. If you catch up with the criminal's vehicle, you can ram into it to do some damage. If you do enough damage, the car malfunctions and you arrest the suspect. You can also use up to three turbo boosters that comes equipped with the car if you are far behind the suspect.However, what makes this game different is the fact that you can choose one of three vehicles to drive: a sports car, 4-wheel drive, and a semi truck, with each one of them having their advantages and disadvantages. For example, the truck may be slow in speed, but can do a massive amount of damage. The sports car, on the other hand, can perform at higher speeds, but has a poor attack efficiency. As well as passing cars, your task is made difficult by obstacles, such as barricades, on the freeway. Finally, some vehicles in the game will have someone shooting at you. And watch out for the helicopter that attempts to drop bombs on you.Cheat: Cheat CodesAt the title screen, press the following for the desired affect. It must be done quickly and you will get a sound confirmation.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Taito America Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>crZJn7gVJ1k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4311</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586101-chase-hq-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/chase-hq-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chase-hq-ii/3030-11492/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4311-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4311-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4311-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70375-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70376-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70377-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-the-taito-monitoring-system.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70378-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-select-your-vehicle.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70379-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-downtown.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70380-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-jumping.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70381-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-watch-out-for-the-barricades.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70382-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-inside-a-tunnel.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/70383-chase-h-q-ii-genesis-screenshot-spotted-the-yellow-sports-car.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4311-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CPFUEUg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4311.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The player takes control of three main vehicles. One of which is a modern stock sports car, a patrol sports car and a striped muscle car. Each level consists of one simple goal of racing to the end with the intent of defeating the villain vehicle, which has to be damaged enough to be taken down and the criminals taken into custody. Some villains have tricky tactics that make gameplay more challenging. Gameplay is also based on a point system.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76b957ae-2e5c-449d-a701-d9c1e71d4783.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff22c600-a50d-4a47-8d7c-e1f5ecc7e766.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/86871d7b-7358-4a9d-96fd-77acdf95dec9.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>