<Game>
	<Name>Chuck Rock (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Chuck Rock is a prehistoric-themed platformer starring the eponymous caveman Chuck on a quest to rescue his wife from a jealous rival. Chuck's main form of attack is a stomach bump with a limited range, but he is also able to take advantage of rocks littering the stages to attack enemies from afar. He can also use these rocks to create platforms to higher areas he cannot reach by jumping normally. While most dinosaurs are hostile some, like the wading brachiosaurs and certain pteranodons, will assist Chuck by taking him to new areas of the stage.UK developers Core Design originally created Chuck Rock for the Atari ST and Amiga computer platforms, and it was subsequently published on many home consoles of the era by Sony Imagesoft and Virgin Interactive in Europe and the US. It is perhaps best remembered for its rock n' roll theme tune. It was followed up with a direct sequel starring Chuck's son Chuck Jr., called Chuck Rock II: Son of Chuck, and BC Racers, a spin-off cart racer game.Cheat: Level SkipOn the title screen, press: A B right A C A down A B right A If done correctly, the caveman second to the right will grin. Now, start the game, enter the first level, and press and hold  A+B+C, all together. Release, hold down A, and press up. You'll skip to the next level, and you can perform the ''hold A press up'' code again to skip multiple levels if you wish.Cheat: Level CodesLevel 2: GJFKFN Level 3: PDPKKN Level 4: JWNTF Level 5: TSNFNVP </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>iGNUAUHTpJc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>7506</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586107-chuck-rock</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/chuck-rock</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chuck-rock/3030-2941/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2370453-genesis_chuckrock.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/7506-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/97022-chuck-rock-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66770-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66771-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-use-the-dinosaur-to-cross-water.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66772-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-chuck-rock-by-name-chuck-rock.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66773-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-use-bird-to-lift-you-along.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66774-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-big-legs.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66775-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-level-1-boss.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66776-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-ice-cave.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66777-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-sabre-tooth.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66778-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-scared-stiff.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66779-chuck-rock-genesis-screenshot-the-dinosaur-graveyard.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tPy1sJ5.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/7506.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Chuck Rock is your typical average cave man. He likes to spend his Sunday afternoons watching football and drinking beer. Unfortunately, his peaceful existence is interrupted one day when his wife, Ophelia Rock, is kidnapped by the village wierdo, Gary Gritter. So, Chuck is rather upset about this whole situation and you have to help him make things right. The game is a side-scrolling platformer. Chuck fights of a variety of dinosaurs using his belly-buster attack and a jump kick. Occasionally he has to pick up and throw rocks to defeat enemies and allow him to jump to greater heights.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/975fec83-490a-40da-87ea-81adfca9e064.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9c316ed-cb9c-4a7f-9f0e-b8b1245e7f9a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/64eae88f-39e5-4da1-9557-2324b235f31f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Virgin Games</Publisher>
</game>