<Game>
	<Name>College Slam (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:College Slam is an arcade style basketball game.Power-Ups!3: Increases your ability to make the three-point outside shot!D: Allows you to perform Monster Jams from anywhere on the court!S: Increases your overall speed to astounding levels!P: Increases your power to a degree you can hardly imagine!T: Provides you with temporary unlimited boost action!F: Causes you to be temporarily "on fire"!B: The bomb knocks over everyone on the court - except you!?: Randomly activates the effects of one of the other icons!R: Reverses the direction of the ball if it's in mid-shot!Z: Prevents your opponents from scoring by zapping your hoop with a flash of lightning!I: Causes your teammate to become invisible for a brief period of time!C: Causes the ball to chaotically bounce in random directions every time it hits the floor!W: Causes you to become a whirlwind that will knock over any player who comes in contact with you! [Note your controller will be affected such that you will keep moving in one direction until you press another direction on the control pad. If you are in possession of the ball, shooting or passing will neutralize the whirlwind.]Teams in College SlamAlabamaArizonaArkansasBoston CollegeCal BerkeleyCincinnatiConnecticutDukeFloridaFlorida StateGeorgetownGeorgiaGeorgia TechIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisiana State UniversityMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMichigan StateMissouriNebraskaNorth CarolinaNorth Carolina StateOhio StateOklahomaOklahoma StatePenn StatePurdueSt. John'sSouth CarolinaSyracuseTexasThe University of MemphisUCLAUNLVUSCVillanovaVirginiaWake ForestWisconsinCheat: Cheat CodesEnter these codes at the "Tonight's Matchup" screen:Cheat: Infinite Shot ClockGo in the options screen, then configure game. After that hold down A, B, and C, until the screen appears again. Go back into configure game, and you will be able to set the shot clock from 0 to the whole game. Have fun!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>687</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/915986-college-slam</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/college-slam</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/college-slam/3030-125/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/687-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/687-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/98517-college-slam-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280157-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-legal-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280158-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280159-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-main-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280160-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-team-select.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280161-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-player-select.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/280162-college-slam-genesis-screenshot-the-tip-off.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/786062-1142727417_00.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/786061-1142727399_00.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/786060-1142727375_00.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/786059-1142727356_00.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gq8BrWK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/687.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Each team starts out by picking any 2 out of 5 players to play with during the game. During timeouts, and at half-time, the player has a choice to make substitutions. When a player makes 2 baskets in a row, the announcer says "He's heating up", and if he makes 3 baskets in a row without the other team scoring, he says "He's on fire!", which makes it easier to score. In the season mode, the player can pick from 44 teams, and then play a 20 game season against quality competition. In the tournament mode, 16 teams compete for a chance to win the national championship. The player also has the ability to edit teams and players. The game itself is not realistic, as players can easily make full-courts shots and occasionally, players get struck by lightning as they dunk. The final score of the games are usually in the middle to high 100s.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b8d77273-b75b-4bc2-90d1-4551f085a961.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/506075d4-38a6-4afd-a51c-59a0b1441a5a.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>