<Game>
	<Name>Columns (World)</Name>
	<plot>Drift back to ancient Phoenicia and challenge yourself with Columns, a game favored by middle eastern merchants. In this mesmerizing pastime, tinker with your riches to align glittering jewels across, down, or diagonally. As you line up colors, the gems vanish and more sparklers drop from above. The challenge increases as the jewels fall more rapidly. You must quickly align them before the columns reach the top. You don't have to be a joystick whiz to excel, even at the hardest levels. Try Flash Columns and make a flashing jewel disappear before time runs out. Enjoy solitary games, or play with a friend. Imagine yourself on the warm Mediterranean coast, or drifting over a languid sea. Forget the passage of time, and tickle your mind with Columns, the brilliant game of strategy and skill.Cheat: Get an extra magic jewelColumns Extra Magic JewelsThere is a way to trick the game into giving you a second magic jewel. To do this you must set up the screen in a certain way. Have one row of the normal jewels stacked up almost to the top of the playfield. There must be vertical space for only two of the three jewels in the next block to come on the screen. Watch the "Next Block" preview box. When you see that the magic jewel block is next, get ready to quickly move it on top of your prepared stack. After the magic jewel eliminates the 'touching' color jewels, all of the remaining jewels will drop down as will the one magic jewel that was off the screen. This magic jewel will drop down and eliminate another group of colored jewels.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>htcKIzCK_2c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>465</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586114-columns</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/columns</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/columns/3030-5487/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/465-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/465-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/152808-columns-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80684-columns-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/466961-columns-genesis-screenshot-alternate-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/466947-columns-genesis-screenshot-the-tutorial-cinematic.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80683-columns-genesis-screenshot-first-piece.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80685-columns-genesis-screenshot-magic-jewel.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80686-columns-genesis-screenshot-scoring.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80687-columns-genesis-screenshot-near-to-lose.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80688-columns-genesis-screenshot-record-table.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/466962-columns-genesis-screenshot-single-player-menu-options-screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/466963-columns-genesis-screenshot-single-player-menu-options-screen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/465-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sgYpXmY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/465.png</clearlogo1>
</game>