<Game>
	<Name>Combat Cars (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Heat seeking missiles, anti-auto mines, slippery sludge slicks. This ain't your usual drive around the block. This is the most action-packed arcade racing game ever to hit the highways. You'll need every awesome enhancement your prize money can buy to win on all 24 grueling tracks. Whether it's rocky mountains, congested urban sprawl, gutsy harbor drives or shifty sand beaches, in this game only the strong survive. And Sunday drivers get wasted. Choose one of 8 mean machines for maximum adrenaline racing on 24 killer courses. Make a run for it by yourself, go head-to-head against a buddy in split-screen, or join forces for roadway domination. Boost your performance with extra turbo-thrusts, mega tires, amped-up engines and wicked power-ups.Cheat: Unlock All TracksGo to Exit in the Options menu end then enter the following code....  A + B + C + Start  If done correctly you should have all of the tracks unlockedCheat: Stage SkipNote*** this can only be done with a six button controllerCheat: Stage SkipChoose the head to head mode, and select your driver. Next, wait for the race preview screen to show up (the one with the best times etc.). Once there, press X to go back levels, and MODE to go forward levels. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3894</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/915987-combat-cars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/combat-cars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/combat-cars/3030-11952/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3894-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/195332-combat-cars-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/195334-combat-cars-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103678-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103671-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-top-scores.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103674-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103673-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103672-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-icy-level.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103675-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-the-characters.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103676-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-character-information.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103677-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-track-description.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103670-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-that-s-not-the-right-direction.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/103679-combat-cars-genesis-screenshot-walking-on-a-tight-line.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/cEvyRGu.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Combat Cars is a racing game in which the player not only competes with other cars, trying to outrun them, but also uses all kinds of weapons and gadgets to damage their opponents. In the beginning of the game, the player can choose one of the eight available characters. Each character has his/her own strengths and weaknesses (speed, car handling, etc.), as well as unique weapons. The weapons include a simple gun, glue spots they can leave to trap other cars, homing missile, and others. There are 24 different tracks available in the game. The player must complete them in a linear fashion, and once they run out of time, the game is over.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bcae4d74-3766-4b6f-859b-44db44ec76eb.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fc6a015-ac71-4405-aa6e-73ff2f141a76.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5acd814b-b278-4bcb-a4a4-9f3d906996b8.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3501259-ae80-452f-84fe-9dec366819e6.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Accolade</Publisher>
</game>