<Game>
	<Name>Curse (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Curse is a basic horizontal-scrolling shooter, one of the first released for the Megadrive, where one pilots a space fighter through deadly environments such as a mutated jungle, a ruined city, and an underground volcano. The game features five stages, and at several points in each stage, a larger boss enemy appears which must be destroyed to continue.There a variety of weapon power-ups to collect, each with three power levels. There is a spread shot that can cover nearly the entire screen, a bomb that explodes into shrapnel when it connects, and a twisting wide shot that can pass through environmental obstacles. There are also homing missiles, smart bombs, speed-ups, and an option that can be placed on any side of the ship. The ship also has a shield which can absorb damage from smaller bullets, meaning it can take a few hits before exploding unless it's hit by an enemy ship, part of the landscape or some special enemy weapons that just ignore the shield.Cheat: Level SelectTO execute level select, hit reset, then hold down button A and hit start.  This will bring you to the configuration mode, where you can pick the level you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Micronet Co. Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>UysuAyLBcFc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20311</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/567444-curse</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/curse</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/curse/3030-41031/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20311-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/0/3/28703_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/396119-curse-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/396120-curse-genesis-screenshot-starting-out.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/396121-curse-genesis-screenshot-shooting-at-the-enemy.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/396122-curse-genesis-screenshot-my-weapon-has-upgraded.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/396123-curse-genesis-screenshot-i-lost-all-my-lives-game-over.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/f/d/gfs_7400_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/6/0/gfs_7400_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jcfuDR2.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>You play as a ship that has to save an alien planet from destruction caused by a neighboring planet that had mysteriously changed from friend to enemy over the course of centuries.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0105ca90-5921-4021-a578-a513335e34e7.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5cb5a6e-e1ea-4686-ac2b-08dc2187c8a9.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/168c003f-fe45-4b42-94b0-26274fed3c37.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5b30d92-f845-4c5e-9545-f0b032a4c023.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>INTV</Publisher>
</game>