<Game>
	<Name>Cyber Police ESWAT (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>ESWAT is: the toughest fighting force alive! ESWAT means: Enhanced Special Weapons and Tactics! You're staring straight into the evil E.Y.E., a power-mad horde of vicious terrorists. But you are the ultimate crimebuster. Decimate their front lines with your lead-belching Gatling gun! Incinerate their mobs with your spinning flame thrower! Start as an ESWAT rookie and blast your way up to become an awesome supercop - more machine than man! Metal attack! Annihilate helicopters, machines, and maniac robots. Feel the heat while bulldozing crazed 'experiments.' Hear, see, and smell the danger when sewer ooze turns into man-hungry goo. Grapple with bionic monsters to face the final showdown! Stay glued to your weapons through 8 missions of grueling combat! You have the ultra-tech gear and the guts to survive! The ESWAT force is waiting. Hit the streets!Cheat: Level selectStart a game, the Hero and Mission screen appears. Now hold down A,B,C and press Left, Right, Up, Down on D-Pad. You are now able to select the level by pressing Left/Right.Cheat: Level selectTo enable the sound test, first beat the game. Then during the ending sequence, press and hold buttons A, B, C, Down, and Left. Keep holding these and press Start until the sound test screen appears.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/7/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>FEbUt7oR-kA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4361</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586161-eswat-city-under-siege</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/e-swat-cyber-police/3030-16898/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4361-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4361-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874145-eswat_cyber_police_4.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874144-eswat_cyber_police_3.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874143-eswat_cyber_police_2.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874142-eswat_cyber_police_1.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874141-eswat_cyber_police.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1987/874140-eswat_cyber_police_5.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/4/6/gfs_46728_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/9/6/gfs_46728_1_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/7/gfs_96191_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/7/gfs_96191_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4361-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>