<Game>
	<Name>Cyborg Justice (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>You are a member of the Galatic Unity Agency on routine patrol in deep space when your patrol ship is damaged after accidently passing through a meteor storm and starts to lose control, smashing into a nearby planet and blacking out.  The next thing you remember you are rummaging through scrap metal and welding together steel to make parts for weapons. You have become a cyborg slave in a munitions factory for the Cydrek Federation, a twisted machine with a human brain, unable to comprehend your situation, clouded by cybernetic programming until one day your human side finally starts to break through.  You remember everything and realize that the Cydrek Federation is building an army to take on the G.U.A. and you must stop it. You must take on the entire Federation using your new cybernetic body and stop them from taking over the universe.You can build up to 216 different combinations of cyborg body parts to rip, tear and burn your opponents in submission, even using the destroyed parts of your downed foes and putting them onto your body. You can also play in Arcade mode in which you take on wave after wave after wave of opponents until your cyborg is finally destroyed or even play co-op with a buddy.  The game features up to five levels from the plants surface, the Cydrek Command Center even a futuristic jungle.Cheat: Secret OptionsPress start, then quickly press C,B,B,C,C,A,C,B.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>5HPRXv-e9IE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3898</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586126-cyborg-justice</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/cyborg-justice</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/cyborg-justice/3030-3743/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3898-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3898-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/98571-cyborg-justice-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/3898-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289897-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-opening-sequence.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289898-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-crash-landing.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289899-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-turned-into-cyborg.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289901-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289900-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-battle-level-1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289902-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-cyborg-with-saw-arm.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289903-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-battle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289905-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-level-finished-statistics.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/289906-cyborg-justice-genesis-screenshot-battle-level-3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/m4JPzyO.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3898.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the near future, anarchy reigns supreme and nobody is safe. Cyborgs control the streets and they enforce their rules the only way they know how: through CYBORG JUSTICE. Now's your chance to create your very own cyborg and enter it in the ultimate fighting competition. You can mix and match parts for your cyborg to form a fighting machine that matches your fighting style.  There are 216 different cyborg possibilities in all, meaning you're sure to find one that fits your needs. Whether you plan to use weapons, hand-to-hand combat, or an even mix of the two, you'll have quite a fight on your hands once you step into the arena. And if you long for some human competition, challenge a friend to a duel so you can determine who can really deliver CYBORG JUSTICE.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ZtiXaUU0I2U</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/453d6e10-753e-4f45-bd3a-e478eec26707.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42490519-6cf7-488d-afea-56c2540c15cd.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/679d9fb5-35ad-464a-8e77-64c6eadae6b3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d8b6613e-9464-4f6d-8a69-aad77a7c2cc2.jpg</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>