<Game>
	<Name>Dangerous Seed (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>It is the 25th century, and the solar system has come under attack by an mysterious alien enemy known as Dangerous Seed. Human forces have been decimated, and the aliens' next target is Earth! The enemy draws closer to the frontline base on the moon by the hour, and the final line of defense for Earth, the fighter ship Moon Diver, has launched.Dangerous Seed is a vertical scrolling shooter converted from the 1989 Namco coin-op. The player controls the three-part fighter ship Moon Diver through 12 stages to confront the alien menace and secure peace in the solar system. Each of the three parts of the ship, Alpha, Beta, and Gamma, have their own properties which can be combined in various ways. Each type and combination has multiple shot types which can be powered up, and there are also options and bombs available which contribute to Moon Diver's extensive arsenal.Cheat: 99 LivesWhen demonstration mode begins, press Left, Left, Left, Up, Up, Right, Left, Right.Cheat: 99 LivesUp, Down, Left, Left, Right, Right, Up, Down and a chime will confirm a correct entry.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>aPdgjN000f0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20355</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586127-dangerous-seed</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/dangerous-seed</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dangerous-seed/3030-29829/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20355-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/137936-dangerous-seed-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/207364-dangerous-seed-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374986-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374987-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-i-can-enter-my-initials.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374988-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-stage-1-first-tube.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374989-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-starting-location.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374990-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-i-am-using-my-bomb-this.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374991-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-i-was-destroyed.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374992-dangerous-seed-genesis-screenshot-i-lost-all-my-lives-game.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8303/1252596-dangerous_seed_gen8.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8303/1252595-dangerous_seed_gen1.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8303/1252594-dangerous_seed_gen2.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/qgPCXsO.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Dangerous Seed (デンジャラスシード) is a 1989 arcade shoot-'em-up by Namco ported to the Sega Mega Drive in 1990. Both versions were released exclusively in Japan. The Moon Diver is a ship consisting of three sub-ships, sometimes called wings: Alpha, Beta, and Gamma. You must stop an alien invasion whose base is Danger Seed by going through several "tubes;" however before the game starts Beta and Gamma break off and you must begin with Alpha alone. A shoots a normal shot which can be rapidfired. B shoots a bomb (you have a limited supply of bombs). As you pass through each tube, your ship collects wings; use C to change the arrangement of wings. Powerups are collected as in most schmups.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c82ae64-2f0e-4a8c-94cf-1a66558a9ded.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c0a210c-94ee-4432-b65c-b2432743d8d0.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a922b9ad-31d3-424c-869d-63fb1d50170a.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>