<Game>
	<Name>Darwin 4081 (Japan, Korea)</Name>
	<plot>Lakya is a technologically-advanced civilization on a planet far from our own galaxy. The planet's inhabitants have unknowingly unleashed the planet's life force, Evol. As the Evol drifts from Lakya, it reaches a planet called Cokyo, whose inhabitants use it to attack and invade Lakya. Now, fighters from Lakya must fight back against the invading army by using the Evol themselves.Darwin 4081 is a vertical scrolling shooter based on the 1987 Data East coin-op Super Real Darwin. The main attraction of the game is the ability to evolve your ship into a wide variety of different forms, each with their own attack abilities, by collecting DNA dropped by enemies. Other powerups will increase you ship's speed, give you an option that follows your ship, or even increase the power of your smart bombs. The game features surreal futuristic art design fitting of its title.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/4/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>Obfa8XjLQiM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20354</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/579606-darwin-4081</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/darwin-4081</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20354-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/256459-darwin-4081-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389977-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389978-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389979-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-get-ready.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389980-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-firing-my-lasers-as-enemies.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389981-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-these-guys-can-t-be-shot-they.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389982-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-i-was-shot-and-killed-game.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389983-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-i-can-continue-up-to-five-times.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389984-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-my-lasers-are-upgraded.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389985-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-i-have-to-shoot-the-flying.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/389986-darwin-4081-genesis-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/faUKFjb.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Super Real Darwin is a 1987 arcade shoot-'em-up by Data East. Sega ported it to the Sega Mega Drive and released it in 1990 exclusively in Japan under the name Darwin 4081 (ダーウィン４０８１). The game controls like a regular shoot-'em-up: A and C shoot bullets, B drops bombs; there is rapidfire. However, unlike regular shoot-'em-ups where weapons are upgraded through powerups, your ship "evolves" to survive situations and get past obstacles. Evolution occurs with the Evol (small faces with an E on them) and B-Evol (darker Evols). Each pickup adds a new evolution state to the list. After a particular amount of time, one evolution wears off and the next evolution is chosen. The DNA powerup does provide a more permanent weapon upgrade, but will merely just make the existing weapons stronger. You can hold up to nine DNA powerups.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62b7139c-7b9a-4ac7-9486-d7ca9d1f08ab.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/908564f2-de2e-43ef-aa3d-9cc13fc78ba9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>