<Game>
	<Name>Deadly Moves (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Deadly Moves, alternatively known as Power Moves (SNES) or Power Athlete (in Japan), is a Fighter game inspired by Street Fighter II: The World Warrior. The game features Joe, an American martial artist, and a group of other fighters from across the globe. In the single-player, Joe is the only playable character, but all eight featured characters (besides the final boss, who is only playable in the Genesis version with a special password) are available in the multiplayer mode.CharactersJoe - American - The protagonist of the single-player mode and all-rounder fighter. Has a moveset similar to Ryu's from Street Fighter.Baraki - Kenya - An African native who fights like a beast. Resembles Blanka.Buoh - Japan - A large fighter in kabuki costume that is able to teleport and fight with his hair. Gaoluon - China - A nimble warrior that fights with a pair of curved knives.Nick - Spain - A flamboyant and agile matador, inspired by Vega.Reayon - Thai - A female fighter that resembles Chun Li.Vagnad - Russian - An enormous obsidian-skinned man. Resembles the X-Man Colossus.Warren - American (Hawaii) - A grappler type.Ranker - American - A strong martial artist and the boss of the game. Unavailable on the SNES version. Resembles Mayor Mike Haggar, except without the mustache.Cheat: Final Level with Full Power PasswordMPV XRPO JM7Cheat: Final Level with Full Power PasswordEnter the following code at the password screen....  Level 3: V3A - 5FTW - NHG Level 4: V3A - MFDK - 01A Level 5: HBV - MFD3 - 25H Level 6: IY5 - MFD4 - 046 Level 7: EVV - G93R - IQ7  Then you should go to your desired level</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kaneko USA, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4331</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586132-deadly-moves</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/deadly-moves</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/deadly-moves/3030-19025/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4331-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4331-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107428-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/374315-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-and-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107429-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107430-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107431-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-two-player-mode-character.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107432-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-one-player-mode-opponent-select.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107433-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-what-a-nice-girl-say-do-you.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107434-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-sea-scenery.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107435-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-japanese-temple-level.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107436-deadly-moves-genesis-screenshot-looks-like-a-victory-to-me.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4331.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You are Joe, a young American who has been secretly training to become a powerful fighter. One day, he meets an old martial artist who tells him he should travel all over the world to meet other teachers and to learn from them. During his travels, Joe encounters many other fighters, and has to become more and more skillful in order to prove that he is the greatest fighter in the world.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c2ace73b-e10a-4f12-952f-fe1e640cbcf1.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a37785a-4a55-43c2-aa7e-b3d0da9b4e6d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Kaneko</Publisher>
</game>