<Game>
	<Name>DEcapAttack (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In this game you play as Chuck D. Head, the product of a mad, but benevolent, scientist.  Chuck looks a lot like a mummy, except he is missing an important part: a head.  Fortunately, he is equipped with a set of eyes and a weird punching appendage in the middle of his chest. Chuck's weird features come in handy when, one day, this evil guy named Max D. Cap emerges from the underworld.  Max quickly takes over our world, and only Chuck can stop him.The gameplay in Decapattack is of the side-scrolling platformer variety.  You play through several colorful worlds, collect useful power up potions, and deliver a beat down to the ugly bosses.Cheat: Round SelectIn Options, move the cursor to Exit.  Now press right, left, left, right, right, right, left, left, A.  The Round Select text appears.  Set it to ON, and when you begin a game, the Round Select menu appears.Cheat: Always get extra lives in bonus roundGet all the coins and put them in the following channels and mash C as they reach the top.Cheat: Always get extra lives in bonus roundRound 1: Channel 2Round 2: Channel 5Round 3: Channel 3Round 4: Channel 5Cheat: Always get extra lives in bonus roundJump at one of the white segmented poles in game and land directly on top of it.As you boune on it the segments will turn red and you will get half a heart for each changed segment.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>4YpxkphszDo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4333</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586135-decapattack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/decapattack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/decap-attack/3030-5596/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4333-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4333-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28961-decapattack-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31255-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-chuck-s-strange-world.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31256-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31257-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-bust-up-the-statues-for-power.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31258-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-eventually-you-ll-find-a-skull.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31259-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-chuck-s-internal-punching-head.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31260-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-chuck-is-being-chased-by-a-giant.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/422690-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-the-inventory-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/422691-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-the-game-over-screen.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525062-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525063-decapattack-genesis-screenshot-the-second-boss-in-toad-al.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4333.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this game you play as Chuck D. Head, the product of a mad, but benevolent, scientist. Chuck looks a lot like a mummy, except he is missing an important part: a head. Fortunately, he is equipped with a set of eyes and a weird punching appendage in the middle of his chest. Chuck's weird features come in handy when, one day, this evil guy named Max D. Cap emerges from the underworld. Max quickly takes over our world, and only Chuck can stop him. The gameplay in Decapattack is of the side-scrolling platformer variety. You play through several colorful worlds, collect useful power up potions, and deliver a beat down to the ugly bosses.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/507c9654-c827-42d8-9811-e6f09d7c4c42.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b9c2299-0884-4673-97fb-771b08574b40.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e8aa088-4d29-4f43-a3ea-4bb2972520e0.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>