<Game>
	<Name>Demolition Man (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Demolition Man is a game based on the 1993 movie by the same name. As with the movie, the game takes place in a dystopian Los Angeles, in 1996. John Spartan is the countrys most fearsome cop and hunts his nemesis, Simon Phoenix. However in doing so, he kills several innocent civilians and both characters are sentenced to cryostasis rehabilitation where they will be brainwashed for 30 years. However the brainwashing does not go as planned and upon waking up, Phoenix goes on a new crime spree. However in 30 years the world has also changed and Los Angeles has become San Angeles, a utopian and violence-free society. As a remnant of a more violent past, police officer John Spartan is once again sent to capture Phoenix.Demolition Man is a fast-paced platform game, with some levels taking place in an overhead perspective (similar to Smash TV). As John Spartan, the player will spend most of his time shooting endless waves of "cryocons" released upon the antiseptic world of the future. The standard weapon can be upgraded with a shotgun and magnum, both with limited ammo. Additionally, various types of grenades can be collected, which are thrown independently of the firearm. Simon Phoenix appears as a boss character at the end of every level that is directly tied in with the movie.The Sega CD version of the game retains identical levels and gameplay, but adds digitized clips from the film to introduce levels and advance the plot.Cheat: Free livesPause the game and press C, A, B, A, Left. When you unpause the game you'll gain one life. You can repeat the code as much as you want before unpausing the game to gain one life for each time you press this combination.You can use also B,A,B,A, Left to get the same result.Cheat: Free livesPause the game then enter one of the following codes to get the desired effect:Cheat: Free livesAt the title screen, press A, C, Up, Right, Left. Then go to options and choose the level.Cheat: Free livesStart a regular game and pause it during gameplay. Then press: left, right, A, B, B. Unpause to skip to the next level.Cheat: Password to last level (easy).Set the game to Easy, then insert: GL9C92KGM</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4334</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/915989-demolition-man</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/demolition-man</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/demolition-man/3030-9607/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2371433-demolition_man_final.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/46/362280-demolitionmanbackcover.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99683-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99670-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99671-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-move-explanation.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99672-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99673-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-demolition-indeed.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99674-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99675-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-first-level.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99676-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-cut-scene.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99677-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-your-score.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/99678-demolition-man-genesis-screenshot-fire-level.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4334.png</clearlogo1>
</game>