<Game>
	<Name>Devilish - The Next Possession (USA)</Name>
	<plot>There was a once a happy time when princes and princesses could get together and take the 'live happily ever after' route without being accosted by devil-faced demons with names like &#172;I. Back when kids respected their elders and you could leave your house without locking the door, such couples had no fear from monstrosities with names that look like an ASCII hiccup randomly showing up and turning them into stone paddles.But those days have passed, and the unfortunate young couple in our tale fall foul to such a demoralising fate. Cursed to spend the rest of their lives looking like a slightly more solid version of Pong's infamous paddles (but with sex-identifying colour coding!), hope was lost. From the demon world came the chuckling of &#172;I, but from the heavens fell a solitary blue orb. The blue orb of hope and rapture!Hints:- Get 99 Lives -Enter the following code at the Title screen: A + B + C + Lefthttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/review/R102248.htmlCheat: Get 99 LivesEnter the following code at the Title screen....  A + B + C + Left  Then when you play the game you should have 99 Lives</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sage's Creation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>bwhJKcFJeJw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4336</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586137-devilish-the-next-possession</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4336-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/7/0/47270_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/4/d/gfs_22256_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/6/1/gfs_38863_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xv1JoOG.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4336.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Devilish" is different from other paddle games by letting you play with two paddles. The lower one behaves just like a usual paddle - you use it to prevent the ball from dropping down. The upper one can move and turn, allowing you to hit the ball from different angles and from different parts of the screen. You advance through levels by destroying bricks and enemies, going up until the level boss enemy appears.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01d44d78-797d-4bdf-8804-0f875f42a1d0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d09890ab-354a-425c-ba7c-745dc15be78a.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44bb9094-95b3-45a4-8340-2fe8f64952ce.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6cba77c-7941-4a4e-b16e-b852c894433d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79fc71d8-79d4-4067-8ca9-31f278af0747.png</snapshot3>
	<Publisher>Sages Creation</Publisher>
</game>