<Game>
	<Name>Devil Crash MD (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A totally awesome gothic chamber of horrors await you in this, the ultimate video pinball game. Incredible graphics and great action-packed playfields. Six bonus rounds and the chance to score one billion points - if you're good enough!Cheat: Hidden Options MenuEntering A+B+C+Start at the same time at any point in between the Sega Logo and the Title Screen will open a secret options menu that allows you to reconfigure the control configuration, choose between two ball speeds, and to access a sound test for sound FX and the remarkable BGMs.Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsEnter ONECRUSHME as your password and you'll receive 594,000,000 and 27 balls.Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsIn the Passwords screen enter THECRUSHL and then you'll receive 999,999,900 points, and you will also be able to see the end of the game. Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsEnter the following code at the Password screen....  OMAKEBGM? Fill in the ? with a number 0 - 4 to select track   Then when you play the game that song will always be the BGM Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsEnter at password screen.Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsTo start playing the game normally but with 7 balls instead of the usual amount of 2, enter the rather obvious password ''DEVILCRASH'', the original japanese name of the game. Cheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsEnter the following code at the Password screen....  6RENAXUEMW  Then when you play the game you should be in the final levelCheat: 594,000,000 points and 27 ballsEnter the following code at the Password screen....  UFELFO78TL  Then when you play the game you should have 13,000,000 points and 99 ballsCheat: Start ball at top screenImmediatley after you release the ball hold  up the right flipper. The ball will automatically go up to the top screen.  Cheat: Start ball at top screenThis also works for Devils Crash (MD)</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card, Pinball</genre>
	<Developer>TechnoSoft</Developer>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>WYj4papkEGQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4347</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586150-dragons-fury</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4347-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/3/0/8/47308_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/a/1/gfs_3178_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/2/gfs_57039_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/f/gfs_57039_2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4347.png</clearlogo1>
</game>