<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dragon Slayer: Eiyuu Densetsu II is the second game in the Dragon Slayer spin-off series The Legend of Heroes. It continues several years after where Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes left off with the son of the hero and heroine from the first game investigating an incident in the nearby mountains involving people in strange spacesuits. The game plays similarly to the first, with traditional turn-based battles and additional party members that can be recruited as the game progresses.Dragon Slayer: Eiyuu Densetsu II ("Eiyuu Densetsu" translates directly as Legend of Heroes) was originally released on the NEC PC-8801 and ported to the PC-9801, FM Towns, PC Engine, Super Famicom, Sega Mega Drive and MS-DOS. The Super Famicom version was published by Epoch and was compatible with the Barcode Battler system through an adapter peripheral that was sold separately. Several codes could be transferred via the device to unlock features in the game.Eiyuu Densetsu II marks the first true sequel from a game in the Dragon Slayer franchise, Nihon Falcom's RPG anthology series that changes settings and entire mechanics from game to game. The Legend of Heroes series would continue to receive many more sequels, including the Gagharv trilogy (The Legend of Heroes III, IV and V) and the Trails in the Sky trilogy (The Legend of Heroes VI, split into three separate games or "chapters"). Though The Legend of Heroes II: Prophecy of the Moonlight Witch was labelled as the second game in the series for its US title, it was simply renamed as such to avoid sequel confusion, like how Final Fantasy IV was renamed II for its US release due to several games being skipped. Dragon Slayer: Eiyuu Densetsu II has yet to receive an official English localization, unlike its predecessor and five immediate successors.		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20324</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570417-dragon-slayer-eiyuu-densetsu-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-slayer-eiyuu-densetsu-ii/3030-7005/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20324-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/7/4/31274_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86344-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86335-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86336-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-huh.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86337-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-here.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86338-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-prince.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86339-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-character.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86340-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-cemetery.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86341-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-world.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86342-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-fighting.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86343-dragon-slayer-the-legend-of-heroes-ii-genesis-screenshot-in.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes II (ドラゴンスレイヤー英雄伝説II) is the sequel to Dragon Slayer: Eiyuu Densetsu within the eponymous subseries (whether or not it is also part of the main Dragon Slayer series is unknown) released by Falcom in 1992 for the NEC PC-88. As with Eiyuu Densetsu, it was ported to a number of systems, including to the Sega Mega Drive in 1995 by Sega Falcom exclusively in Japan. The Dragon Slayer series would continue with Lord Monarch, which also saw an entry on the Mega Drive. However, with the next The Legend of Heroes game, Eiyuu Densetsu III: Shiroki Majou, Falcom decided to break the series away from Dragon Slayer. This third game was ported to the Sega Saturn in 1998.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea1b9649-2538-434b-b3ff-16cc08729d6a.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>