<Game>
	<Name>Dragon's Eye Plus - Shanghai III (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The ancient fascination of Mah-Jongg meets the cutting edge of video games in the most captivating strategy game to challenge the Western world - Shanghai II: Dragon's Eye. Calculate your moves! Beware the art of maneuver. An intricate ever-changing layout of ancient tiles marked with mysteriously eye-catching designs challenges your every move. Think before you make your move - it could be your last. Clear the board! Snap off matching pairs until the board is empty. Looks simple enough... but looks can be deceiving. The next tile you need may be buried five deep. Choose from 13 deceptively simple tile formations and 9 unshakably addictive tile sets with surprising animation, exciting sounds and enchanting musical themes. Master the basics, and then confront the ultimate challenge: Dragon's Eye!Cheat: Tournament PasswordsChoose "Resume Tournament Game" from the Title Screen and enter one of the following:</plot>
	<releasedate>2/11/1991</releasedate>
	<Developer>Home Data Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>cxFMtRuQ9Lw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20508</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586453-shanghai-ii-dragons-eye</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/dragons-eye-plus-shanghai-iii</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20508-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/0/5/5/48055_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413238-dragon-s-eye-plus-shanghai-iii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413239-dragon-s-eye-plus-shanghai-iii-genesis-screenshot-shanghai.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413240-dragon-s-eye-plus-shanghai-iii-genesis-screenshot-dragon-s.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/f/2/gfs_68202_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/f/gfs_68202_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Dragon's Eye Plus: Shanghai III (ドラゴンズアイ プラス 上海III) is a 1991 game by Home Data for the Sega Mega Drive released exclusively in Japan. It is a member of Activision's Shanghai series of mahjong solitaire games — to be precise, it is a port of the Japanese version of what the Western market got as Shanghai II: Dragon's Eye; the numbering discrepancy was because of a Japanese Shanghai II that had already been made. Activision were not happy with this version of the game, and instead produced their own Shanghai II: Dragon's Eye for the Western market.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1bf6cb9-9bc0-41ca-b879-2999ad814ea4.png</boxart3>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Home Data</Publisher>
</game>