<Game>
	<Name>Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:The story begins during the closing onslaught of a goblin siege upon Duke Barrik's castle.  In the dying seconds before the castle is overrun, it magically teleports to a new and strange land!  In a valley surrounded by sheer cliffs, it falls to a likely band of heroes to venture into the unknown in an attempt to find allies and preserve the kingdom and culture.Gameplay:The game follows the relatively straightforward rules of party system adventuring, with the benefit of the player being allowed to customize their party before the game begins.  Like many RPG games, your party members start out as mere weaklings surrounded by superior beasts and enemies.  Progression in the early stages of the game demands some time spent on grinding levels and improving inventory items.  Combat has two modes, depending upon the given situation:Out in the open (valley, swamp etc) battles are a strategic affair utilizing a combination of ranged, magic and direct melee attacks.  It becomes important here to have a well rounded party to effectively dispose of enemies.  Attacks are based on turns during this combat, for instance, once your party has attacked, the enemy will counter.  In dungeons/caves the combat moves towards real-time, requiring the player to cycle through attacks using the A or B buttons.  Each attack is followed by the next party member, with the ability to actively retreat or pursue enemies should it be necessary.  In both cases the attack ritual is the same, with a different attacks mapped to both A and B. Visual StyleIn normal adventuring mode, 70% of the screen shows your party in the world from a distorted isometric viewpoint.  The other 30% of the screen shows status bars and pictures of each member of your party including which attacks are mapped to A and B buttons.  During underground adventuring in dungeons/caves, the screen changes to include a notepad section that describes traps, smells, approaching enemies and items found.  This effectively limits the viewport down to about 25% of the screen which displays a 3D dungeon/cave.Characters:ClericProficient in both spell casting and fighting.  Many of their spells heal damage or negate adverse effects on party members.  FighterThe primary warriors of any party.  They generally have the most hit points and deal the most damage.  Fighters are great leaders to a party as they can absorb lots of damage, effectively protecting the other members.Magic-UserSpellcasters who have the lowest hit points yet can cause tremendous damage from range.  Magic-Users also have the ability to 'entangle' enemies effectively paralyzing them so they become vulnerable to melee attacks.ThiefSpecializing in stealth, sneaking up on opponents and removing traps.  Thieves are good in battle using ranged weapons such as bows and slingshots.DwarfA shorter, stockier version of the Fighter.  Dwarves receive as many hit points as Fighters and are just as good at dealing out damage.ElfCombining the skills of fighting and magic, elves are a good all rounder to any party.  They are neither as strong as Fighters, or as powerful as Magic-Users however.HalflingAn interesting combination of Fighter, Cleric and Thief, the Halflings can handle their own in a battle yet don't have the highest hit points, and they can also hide like a thief without some of the trap spotting abilities. Each character class can be male or female with the added ability to customize color, name and beginning stats. Critical ReceptionWhen released Electronics Gaming Monthly issued the scores of 4,7,4,7 adding, "...exceptional graphics for this type of game.  If you are into RPGs give this one a try you won't be disappointed".Cheat: Cheat ModeHold Start on controller two and quickly press Down, B, Right, Up, C, Left, A on controller one at the Sega logo when the game starts. A sound will confirm that you've entered it right. Begin playing the game and press Start to display the options screen. Use the ''Specials'' selection for a sound test and gold options.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>bl82Oj9L5-w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4330</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586590-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun/3030-314/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4330-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4330-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/126434-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125840-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125841-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125842-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125843-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125844-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125863-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125865-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125867-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125869-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/125870-dungeons-dragons-warriors-of-the-eternal-sun-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IKAQYMs.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Dungeon &amp; Dragons: Warriors of the Eternal Sun is set in the world of Mystara, a setting of the Dungeons &amp; Dragons game. The characters find themselves in a strange, red-hued world in which the horizon slopes upward in all directions, eventually vanishing into a crimson haze at the limits of sight. Their mission is to find and make allies in this new world or else the kingdom and its culture will perish. The player leads a party of four characters (either the default party or one that the player has created). Characters and races can be chosen from the normal D&amp;D options. The gameworld is viewed from an isometric perspective and the characters can roam around in realtime. Battles are turn based. Like most role-playing games, the gaming experience focuses on exploration, inventory management and character development.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c9446256-1aa4-4e91-b0de-99d4f98edf14.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e57f6b94-3352-463f-87ed-c402bc72f9d9.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a2106c4-c85d-490c-9f46-d36c9f364eac.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7fa0525e-3864-4d2e-8ff7-12060d9d2413.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ea059d0-974b-4d96-b74b-8572dc6b100c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/875f2f7e-70b2-48ba-8653-19a19cb3c597.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>