<Game>
	<Name>Dynamite Headdy (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dynamite Headdy is an action/platformer game developed by Treasure and published by Sega in 1994. Dynamite Headdy was released on the Wii Virtual console in July 2007.Story:The main character of Dynamite Headdy is the star puppet, Headdy. Upon arriving in North Town discovers that the evil puppet, King Dark Demon has come to select which peaceful toys he shall convert into His evil minions.Headdy is captured by the Toruzo-Kun and is thrown into a dust cargo to be destroyed, but Headdy escapes and sets off on an journey to defeat the evil King.Gameplay:During the course of the game, certain heads can be unlocked from HeadCase which allow for certain enemies to be defeated or access to special areas.HeadCase HeadsLotsa Heads - allows Headdy to fire three heads at once.Liberty Head - takes Headdy to the bonus stage.Head Trip - slows Headdy down and prevents him from jumping and attacking.Slammer Head - allows Headdy to do more damage.Pig Head - makes Headdy attack with projectiles out of his nose.War Head - shoots nearby enemies automatically.Protector Head - causes fireballs to surround Headdy that damage enemies.Spike Head - allows Headdy to climb walls.Empty Head - makes Headdy immune to enemy attacks.Super Head - makes Headdy faster, allows him to jump higher, and increases his attack range.Sleep Head - causes Headdy to fall asleep, this restores some health assuming no enemies are around.Pin Head - shrinks Headdy.Bomb Head - turns Headdy's head into a bomb that can destroy all ememies on screen or (if left undetached) destroy Headdy.Vacuum Head - makes Headdy's attacks inhales nearby items and enemies.Ticker Head - freezes enemies in time.Shooting Scene HeadsRocket Head - grants Headdy faster movement than the other flying heads and fires a laser that penetrates everything.Air Head - turns Headdy into a plane than fires three different dirrections and can face backwards.Feather Head - fires projectiles that are affected by gravity.Cheat: Hard Mode (or 1-hit death mode)At the title screen, press Start once, then leave the cursor on &amp;quot;Start Game.&amp;quot; Just like the stage select code, press C, A, Left, Right, B. You will hear headdy say &amp;quot;Nice&amp;quot; when you've entered the code correctly. Then press and HOLD START. Continues holding start until you see the &amp;quot;Opening Demo&amp;quot; scene appear. Now you can release the start button and continue as normal. Be warned, One hit is all it takes to kill you now. Cheat: Hard Mode (or 1-hit death mode)At the title screen select ''Options'' and press: C, A, Left, Right, B.  You will hear ''NICE'' when you've entered the code correctly.  Then press START to view the head animations.Cheat: Hard Mode (or 1-hit death mode)When the title screen appears, press START once. Leaving the cursor at Start Game, enter the code: C, A, LEFT, RIGHT, B. If you hear a sound, you've got it! Press START and you'll access the Stage Select! Just choose your level and stage. Then press START to play! (Note: This trick was done on an early version of the game. It may or may not work on later versions)Cheat: Extra Secret BonusDuring Scene 3-4 (Clothes Encounters), you can get a secret bonus point by waiting for the Wooden Dresser to put on the Bino head, and then knocking it off. However, if you do this at the right moment, you'll hear that you've gotten a secret bonus, but the Wooden Dresser's heart will remain pink. In this case, the Wooden Dresser will put on the Bino head again, allowing you to get a second secret bonus. If you got the other three secret bonuses in this stage, you'll see that the score will show that you got 5/4 secret bonuses. And if you get all the others in the game, the final score will show that you got 40/39.Cheat: Secret final sceneAfter the end credits has finished rolling you are prompted to enter a 4 digit secret code on a keypad. The valid code is different each time the game is played , complete the basket ball mini game four times while going through the game to determine your games secret code. </plot>
	<releasedate>5/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4351</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586154-dynamite-headdy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/dynamite-headdy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dynamite-headdy/3030-6927/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2370510-genesis_dynamiteheaddy_eu_cropped.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EDkl1Gn.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/VwNHltV.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80491-dynamite-headdy-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4351-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51158-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51159-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-secret-bonus.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51160-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-level-6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51161-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-party-time.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51162-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-end-level.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51163-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-spotlight-please.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51164-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-big-robot-attack.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51165-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-robot-cutscene.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/51166-dynamite-headdy-genesis-screenshot-walking-through-town.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4351-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6TPgzFz.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4351.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Hot-headed Headdy gets into some real head-banging to thwart the Dark Demon's devious deeds. This wacky headcase is up to his neck in surprises! Switch heads to match the job! Over 15 heads to choose from! Bash heavy objects with Slammer Head! Suck up foes with Vacuum Head! Stick it to your enemies with Spike Head! Headdy's spring-loaded head gets him where he's gotta go! Use it to swing over ledges, grab onto objects and shoot hoops in the basketball bonus round. Use your head to whiz through a radical variety of play! Action, shooting and strategy speed you on to a surprise ending!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/735ab4d7-cde5-458d-8c62-f7ee6d09bad8.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/036bada9-f2d2-4018-b38b-293351a13ea7.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77fec80b-ed67-4850-8b5c-c687ad1a36e1.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43096349-c39c-4258-8346-f3d6e61b90b8.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18eb563f-d06f-4c74-9601-df8cfa29fd9d.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c85e6a4d-db66-4121-ac0d-606fa842e520.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>