<Game>
	<Name>EA Hockey (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The only game to score with the NHL! Includes all 22 NHL teams and two All-Star teams - each skater modeled on 14 different attributes, such as scoring, skating, aggression, and rink awareness. All the fast-paced action of real hockey - superior skating, body checks, and ballistic slap shots. Watch out! Slashing, holding, and tripping will earn you some time in the penalty box - if the ref sees you! Slip one past the goalie and you light up the board - it takes sharp skills and skates to succeed in this league! This game has all the details down, including instant replay, scouting reports, realistic sounds - booing, cheering, clapping, and dynamic crowd reactions.Cheat: Championship PasswordsTo get to the championship with any team, enter the following at the passwords screen:Cheat: Championship Passwords To play as the New York Islanders against the San Jose Sharks in the Stanley Cup finals, enter the following at the password screen:Cheat: Championship PasswordsEnter these passwords at the password screen under Continue Playoffs to play as the Rangers in each round of the playoffs.Cheat: Championship PasswordsEnter these at the password screen: Note: The first team listed is the team you will be controllingCheat: Skate Through the StandsBegin a 2-player teammates game. Make sure that the penalites are on. Once your player is found to be an instigator of a fight, move away from the penalty box and proceed to bump the player into the boards. Your player will skate up and into the stands.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Park Place Productions</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4533</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586347-nhl-hockey</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ea-hockey/3030-32799/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4533-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4533-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2254853-eahockeyscreen3.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2254852-eahockeyscreen2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2254851-eahockeyscreen1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/0/0/gfs_67853_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/9/d/gfs_67853_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/C9mIask.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4533.png</clearlogo1>
</game>