<Game>
	<Name>EA Sports Double Header (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>EA HOCKEY: All the fast-paced action of real hockey - high-speed skating, body-checks, ballistic slap shots and fights! JOHN MADDEN FOOTBALL: All the hard-hitting action of real American Football! Block tackles, dive, jump, and 'sack' the quarterback! Featuring a 3D playfield and IsoVision passing camera.Cheat: At the first Option Screen, press B, A, C, A, C. If done correctly, you will hear Madden say something and if you move your team selection before ALL MADDEN, you will see the Carolina Panthers and the Jacksonville Jaguars.Cheat: At the Options Screen, press A, C, C, B, B. If done correctly, you will hear Madden say, ''BOOM!''. The coin toss is sped up heavily.Cheat: Enter the following password:Cheat: To make any opponent miss an extra point, purpously go offsides repeditly until the ball is placed on the goal line.  When the extra point is kicked from there, the kick will not be able to go high enough to get across the cross bar and the kick will always be missed.Cheat: To get to the championship with any team, enter the following at the passwords screen:Cheat:  To play as the New York Islanders against the San Jose Sharks in the Stanley Cup finals, enter the following at the password screen:Cheat: Enter these passwords at the password screen under Continue Playoffs to play as the Rangers in each round of the playoffs.Cheat: Enter these at the password screen: Note: The first team listed is the team you will be controllingCheat: Begin a 2-player teammates game. Make sure that the penalites are on. Once your player is found to be an instigator of a fight, move away from the penalty box and proceed to bump the player into the boards. Your player will skate up and into the stands.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20366</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/932570-ea-sports-double-header</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/ea-sports-double-header</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ea-sports-double-header/3030-9116/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20366-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/154979-ea-sports-double-header-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48179-ea-sports-double-header-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/143562-ea-sports-double-header-genesis-screenshot-game-selection.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/c/e/gfs_74742_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/5/3/gfs_74742_2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/8/3/gfs_74742_2_2.jpg</snapshot4>
</game>