<Game>
	<Name>Earnest Evans (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:Earnest Evans III embarks on his grandfather&#8217;s failed journey to discover three ancient idols that hold the power to destroy Earth. Opposing Earnest is another treasure hunter named Brady Tresidder who wants to obtain the idols so that he may use their power to rule the world. With his trusty whip at his side Earnest will encounter various exotic locales and characters on his journey to find the ancient idols.Critical ReceptionWhen the Genesis version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly issued the following scores, 6,7,5,7 adding, "...a nice combination of graphics, unknown paths and whip 'em out action, but none of its individual characteristics saves it from being slighty above average over all"Trivia:Earnest Evans is the first game in a trilogy, the other two being El Viento and Anneto Futatabi which didn't see a US release.Cheat: Skip Current LevelPause the game and then enter the following code....  Up - A - Down - B - Left - A - Right - B  Then when you un-pause the game you should go to the next level</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Renovation Products, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>XOXnW3UsSeo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4352</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570484-earnest-evans</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/earnest-evans</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/earnest-evans/3030-18018/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4352-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4352-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45347-earnest-evans-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108143-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108142-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-the-hero.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108141-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-falling-down-falling-down.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108144-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-i-ll-show-you-bad-scorpions.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108145-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-crouching-be-careful-spikes.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108146-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-climbing-a-rope.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108147-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-hey-that-hurts.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108148-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-no-platform-game-would-be.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108149-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-dead-at-the-bottom-of-the.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/108150-earnest-evans-genesis-screenshot-lava-very-dangerous.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4352-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4352.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The story of the game is connected to that of El Viento. Earnest Evans is a brave treasure hunter. His grandfather was a famous archaeologist who searched for three legendary idols in the 1930s. It was said that those idols could bring disaster upon the Earth if fallen into the wrong hands. But despite his efforts, he could never find even one of the idols. Now it's up to the grandson to continue his work, fifty years later. But the evil syndicate leader Brady Tressider has his own plans, and will do anything to stop Earnest... This is an action platform game in which you control Earnest Evans, armed with his trusty whip. The hero can jump, climb ropes, crouch, and crawl. There are plenty of obstacles on the levels (bottomless pits, spikes, crushing bridges, lava, etc.), as well as gangsters and monsters to dispose of.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4cac11a9-f855-4a0a-8ca1-1e254fcca19c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9405376-64f5-48c7-ae2d-9b29bc2ec0b6.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e58c0042-eced-4fd0-9185-c39dffbfa55e.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Renovation Products, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>