<Game>
	<Name>Earthworm Jim (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Earthworm Jim is a side-scroller shooter from Shiny Entertainment and the first game in their Earthworm Jim series. The player assumes the role of the eponymous annelid who is able to shoot in multiple directions with his space blaster, with the ultimate goal of saving the galaxy from Queen Slug-for-a-Butt. The game is best known for its surreal sense of humor and fluid animations.Earthworm Jim premiered in the October of 1994 for multiple platforms. It saw a sequel the subsequent year: Earthworm Jim 2. In 2010, Earthworm Jim received HD rereleases for modern consoles.Story:Jim was just an ordinary earthworm who, early one morning, was running from some crows when an indestructible, high-tech super suit (created by the evil genius Professor Monkey-for-a-Head) fell onto him from the sky and, by some wonderful coincidence, the opening of the suit landed on him, and in he went, transforming him into the amazing annelid we've all come to love. Then he took out his gun and exploded the crows who had been chasing him.The suit had been dropped by a space ship that was being attacked by Psy-Crow, an evil henchman for the Evil Queen Pulsating, Bloated, Festering, Sweaty, Pus-Filled, Malformed Slug-for-a-Butt (or Queen Slug-for-a-Butt in short). The suit was originally designed for her to help her take over the galaxy (...though she probably could never fit in it). Psy-Crow comes to earth to look for the suit but only finds the scorch marks made by the impact of the suit and the exploded crows. He radios Queen Slug-for-a-Butt and they talk about their evil plans for her sister, Princess What's-Her-Name (this game likes its hyphens). Unbeknownst to Psy-Crow, Earthworm Jim was hiding and heard everything. Mustering up some new-found courage, Jim decides to embark on a quest to rescue the beautiful princess.Gameplay:Jim begins his quest to rescue Princess What's-Her-Name in the game's first level, "New Junk City". There, Jim is introduced to concepts that will be seen throughout most of the course of the game. This includes the use of chains, rope, moss, etc. to climb horizontally, attempting to avoid the peril of landing on spikes, and swinging from hook to hook via Jim's head (using his worminess as a whip). Each level has its own unique gameplay elements to cope with as well. This level in particular includes obstacles such as bouncy piles of tires and zip-lines the player has to use to get Jim to his destination.Jim firing his blasterJim will almost immediately encounter baddies at the start of the game. His weapons include a little red blaster and his own earthworm body. Either weapon can be used almost at any time, though on occasion one can be more effective than the other (the gun can stun a crow, but it takes a little longer to kill than by just using the whip, which only takes a single lash. However, the crow must be at the right distance or it's ineffective). Jim's blaster has a full automatic fire rate although it's ammo is capped at 5000. Additional ammo can be picked up throughout the level (the little blaster symbols floating around). Should Jim run out of ammo, the blaster will recharge up to one hundred bullets by itself. There are also Mega Blaster bullets that can be found in a few places in every level. Each Mega Blaster upgrade is good for one shot, delivering a large, devastating beam that destroys any lower enemy with one touch.Though a platforming game at heart, each level has its own special twists to the formula, breaking up the run-and-gun-and-jump model to deliver on such things as riding hamsters or bungee jumping.PlanetsNew Junk CItyJim starts off his adventure in this junk yard which he must get through to defeat both Billy the Bin and New Junk City's owner, Chuck.Andy Asteroids?Jim jumps on his Pocket Rocket and races with Psy-Crow to the end of the level, avoiding asteroids along the way.Psy-CrowA level that the player only has to complete if Jim loses against Psy-Crow in the Andy Asteroids? level, Jim must have a one on one battle with the mad crow himself to continue.What The Heck?Planet heck is a strange hell-type planet. This is where Evil the Cat lives and where the player must defeat the likes of lawyers and an un-meltable snowman. The player must complete the level while listening to horrifying elevator music.Down the TubesDown the Tubes is an underwater level in which Jim must ride giant hamsters, knock over Bob the Killer GoldFish and complete the infamous tube race.Snot a problemMajor Mucus is out to get Jim! Compete with him in a 3 round battle in which Jim and him both bungee jump down to infested waters and fight by swinging into each other and seeing which cord breaks first.Level 5The 5th level takes place in Professor Monkey for a head's lab. Watch out though, Jim may just lose his suit, make sure to get it back.Who Turned Out The Lights?A hidden area found in Level 5 which is completely blacked out besides spotlights, the enemies' eyes and doors.For Pete's SakeJim has to escort a cute, tiny puppy named Peter through a level that consists of holes, tentacles and meteor showers. Peter is a small cute timid little dog, but when very frightened he becomes a raging monstrous Hulkish beast.Intestinal DistressThe level takes place in the intestines of a strange creature and at the end of the tunnel Jim must face off against Doc Duodenum. The level is missing from the SNES and PC versions of the game.ButtvilleIt's all come down to this, Jim is nearing the end of his journey! At the end of stage, prepare to face off against the appropriately named The Evil Queen Pulsating, Bloated, Festering, Sweaty, Stinky, Pus-filled, Malformed, Slug-for-a-Butt.Avatar AwardsThe XBLA version has 2 avatar awards to be earned.Earthworm Jim Suit - Complete a bonus level.Earthworm Jim T-Shirt - (Achievement: Bin Collector) Beat Billy the Bin in New Junk City.Soundtrack:Earthworm Jim has an awesome soundtrack which consists of -Banjo RaceSnot a ProblemParty TimeFallingWhat the HeckButtsvilleBass MixJunkitBos AnneildPsy-crowDarkworm RagSubmergedYou're the bestEnd themeCheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and enter: A + B, C, C, A, A, B, B, B + CCheat: Cheat MenuAny time during the game, pause it and press A and Left, B, B, A and Right, B, B, A.  Unpause the game, and the words 'Cheater!' will appear on the screen.  Up comes a menu which lets you select your level, give yourself infinite energy and check the map of any level.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: Down + C, B, A, A, A, A, B, CCheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: A + C, B, B, C, C, C, A, BCheat: Cheat MenuPause and enter the following: A + Up, B, A, C, A, A, C, BCheat: Cheat MenuAt any time, pause the game and press B and Up simultaneously, then press B, A, C, A, A, A, A.  You will hear Earthworm Jim say ''Cheater! Wheee Doggy!.''  When you unpause the game, you will see that you now have an extra life.  You can perform this code as many times as you want.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press A + C, A, B, C, B, C, A, C(2). Cheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press A + C, B(2), C(3), A, B. Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and enter: A, A, A, A, A, A, B, CCheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press Right + A, A(2), B, A, C, B, A. Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: A + B, A + B, C, A, Right, Right, Left, RightCheat: Cheat MenuButtville pasword on the Difficult setting. Redball, Cow, Atom, Atom, CowCheat: Cheat MenuBegin your game, take controller one and press START to pause at any point, Now press A, B, B, A, A+C, B+C, B+C, A+C. You'll skip to the next level.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: B, B, A, A, A, A, B, CCheat: Cheat Menu Pause the game and enter A,C,C,A,B,B,A,C.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press C + Up, A(2), C, A, B, C(2). Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: C, A, A, A, A, B, CCheat: Cheat MenuAt any time, pause the game and press C and Down simultaneously, then press A, B, C, A, B, A, C.  You will hear Earthworm Jim say ''Cheater! Plasma!.''  Now when you unpause the game, you will have nine plasma shots. You can do this as much as you want.Cheat: Cheat MenuWhen playing the first level, pause the game and press Left, Right, A, B, C, Left, Right, A.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game, and press A+C, A+B, C, C, B, B, A, A. You will hear Earthworm Jim yell ''Cheater'' and you will be brought to the ending scene of the game.Cheat: Cheat MenuPress START to pause then enter one of the following codes: Plasma Shot Weapon: C, A, B, C, A, B, A, C Earn one continue: A, B+Left, A, B, A, B, C, A Fill weapon to 1,000 rounds: A, B, B, B, C, A, C, C One free guy: B, B, C, C, A, A, A, ACheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press A + C, A + C, A + C, A, B, C, B, A. Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press: A + B, C, C, C, A, B, B, BCheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and enter: A + C, A, B, B, C, A, C, CCheat: Level SelectPause game play and enter one of the following codes to start game play at the corresponding level. Level Password  What the Heck? Press A, Right, A, C(2), Left, Right, A.   Snowman Press Right(3), A, C, Left, Right, B.   Evil the Cat Press Up, Down, Right, C(2), Left, Right, B.   Big Bruty Press C(3), Left(3), Right(2).   Down the Tubes Press Up, Down, Left(2), Up(3), Down.   Tube Race Press Up(2), Left(2), Down, Left, Up, C.   Snot a Problem Press C, B, C, Right(2), Left, A, B.   Snot a Problem 2 Press Up, B, C, Down(3), A, C.   Snot a Problem 3 Press A, Up, C, Up(2), Down, C, A.   Lab Press A, B(2), Down, Right(2), Left, Right.   Chicken Plummets Press A, B, C, Up, Down(3), Right.   Naked and Lovin' It Press C, A, C, Left, Right, Up, Down, Right.   For Pete's Sake Press A, B, C, A, B, A, Down, Right.   Andy Asteroids Press A, Left, A, C(3), B(2).   Andy Asteroids 2 Press C, Down, A(2), Down, B(2), Down.   Andy Asteroids 3 Press A, Down, Left, A, C(2), A, B.   Andy Asteroids 4 Press A, Down, A(2), C(2), A, B.   Andy Asteroids 5 Press A, Left, A, C(2), Down, Up, A.   Andy Asteroids 6 Press A, Right, A(2), Right, B, Up, A.   Intestinal Distress Press C(2), A, Right, Left, Right, B(2).   Who Turned Out the Lights Press A + C, B, Up, Left, Right(2), Left(2).   Who Turned Out the Lights 2 Press A, B, Up, B, Left, Right, C, Up.   Who Turned Out the Lights 3 Press A, B, C, Up, Left, A, Right(2).   Who Turned Out the Lights 4 Press A, C, Up, Left, C, Right, Left, B.   Who Turned Out the Lights 5 Press C, B, Up, Down, Left, Right(2), Left.   Queen of Buttville Press A, C, Left, Right, B, Left(2).   Buttville Helicopter Press B(2), Down(2), A, Right(2), Down.   Psycrow Press C, B, Up, Down(2), Right, Down, Right.   </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Playmates Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>49puptyIPVI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2894</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586155-earthworm-jim</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/earthworm-jim</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/earthworm-jim/3030-11133/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2894-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2894-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80512-earthworm-jim-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37589-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-funny-sega-logo-with-earthworm.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37590-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37591-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-level.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37592-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-careful-domestic-animals.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37593-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-crossing-an-abyss-hanging.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37594-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-this-cow-is-a-puzzle-figure.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37595-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-jumping-on-tires.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37596-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-frantic-battle-against-crows.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/117756-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-jim-has-fallen-to-the-death.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/117757-earthworm-jim-genesis-screenshot-andy-s-asteroids-recurrent.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2894-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8OABm0v.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The storyline involves many colorful characters. Jim (voiced by TenNapel) was at first an ordinary earthworm who did very earthworm-like things such as flee from crows and eat dirt. One day, in the space above Earth, the evil Psy-Crow had cornered a rebel spaceship pilot who had stolen an "Ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit" built by Professor Monkey-for-a-Head. The suit had been commissioned by the evil Queen Pulsating, Bloated, Festering, Sweaty, Pus-filled, Malformed, Slug-for-a-Butt so that she could further conquer the galaxy. In the ensuing space fight, the suit was dropped to Earth, and fell on Jim. By a stroke of luck, Jim managed to land within the collar of the suit, and it ended up mutating him into the large and intelligent (at least by earthworm standards) superhero he is today.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5b60ea36-65fb-4fbb-929b-0baac368dade.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06f2a187-e231-40eb-817d-fc13fa55b1e9.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c994020-e8fd-483b-9242-3ec37d255bb0.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>