<Game>
	<Name>Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ecco: The Tides of Time is a direct follow-up to the 1993 game, Ecco the Dolphin and developed by Novotrade International (now Appaloosa Interactive). The controls of the first game are identical to the second one, as with the difficulty. It includes all new puzzles such as a Scavenger hunt. There are also new powers, one of them includes Ecco changing into different animals such as a jellyfish, a seagull, a shark and a school of fish. With these new additions, many things from the original game came back. The health and air meter are back along with the Glyphs.Story:The story starts off where the last leaves off: The Vortex Queen is back and follows Ecco back to earth to begin a new hive. Ecco lost his powers from the Ast erite and after he encountered a dolphin with long fins named, Trellia, who was his descendant. She took Ecco to her present which was his future.In Ecco&#8217;s future, Dolphins evolved with telekinetic powers and the power to fly with helium sacks that were on them. The ocean had a mind of its own with &#8216;skyways&#8217; or waterways that floated trough the skies, which connected other parts of water on the earth. Ecco, who was exploring the future, then found the Asterite.When talking to the Asterite, it told Ecco that something was wrong. When Ecco used the time machine the world split into two. One which was a joyful future with flying dolphins, the other was a lifeless wasteland which was dried up by the vortex. Even though the Asterite was killed by the Vortex Queen not until later it was explained how it was talking to Ecco. It then sent him back to the present.Ecco pieced the Asterite together by bringing the globes that made up the creature. The last of the globes had been taken by the Vortex to the future; Ecco had to retrieve them before both he and Asterite could defeat the vortex. They both went to the vortex future that was full of bizarre machines and was much like the last levels of Ecco the Dolphin. Eventually Ecco found the Astrite&#8217;s last two globes and went back to the present.The Asterite was complete again and Ecco got all of his powers back again.Ecco then fought the Vortex Queen using the song to destroy her. Though she escaped to the Atlantean time machine, the Asterite told Ecco to destroy it; instead he uses it to and disappears in to the Tides of Time.Cheat: Debug MenuWhen you have control of Ecco and can pause, Try to pause while Ecco is facing you. Once Ecco is facing you, press A, B, C, B, C, A, C, A, and B.  If you entered the code correctly, a menu will pop up with all sorts of optionssuch as a sound test, level select, tempo, etc. This code can be entered as many times as you'd like, as long as the game is paused while Ecco is facing you. Cheat: Debug MenuTurn Ecco left or right and pause the game while Ecco is facing towards the screen. Press (A), (B), RIGHT, (A), (C), (A), DOWN, (A), (B), RIGHT, (A), and then unpause. You will now never die from lack of air or injuries.Cheat: EasymodeJust entering the word easy mode in the password screen would work as a password. This difference it caused was it made certain lvl's much easier to complete like jumping certain spots in the game where you could easily lose in normal mode where no longer there. I am surprised no one ever thought about trying this code. I would always try and figure out codes and just enetered it one day when I was 12 years old. 16 years have passed and no one ever brought it up.Cheat: Easymode   Crystal Springs = UEPMCVEB    Fault Zone = OZUNSKZA    Two Tides = KDKINTYA    Skyway = SZXHCLDB    Sky Tides = OZWIDLDB    Tube of Medusa = QSJRYHZA    Skylands = MULXRXEB    Fin To Feather = YCPAWEXA    Eagle's Bay = YCJPDNDB    Asterite's Cave = AOJRDZWA    Four Islands = UOYURFDB    Sea of Darkness = UQZWIIAB    Vents of Medusa = MMVSOPBB    Gateway = KDCGTAHB    Big Water = QQCQRDRA    Deep Ridge = UXQWJIZD    Hungry Ones = WBQHMIUE    Secret Cave = CHGTEYZE    Gravitorbox = UIXBGWXE    Globe Holder = SBFPWWJE    Dark Sea = MXURVMLA    Vortex Queen = OKIMTBPA    Home Bay = CSNCMRUA    Epilogue = CEWSXKPA    Fish City = SGTDYSPA    City of Forever = WSSXZKVACheat: Easymode@ = New level found only in Hard Mode Crystal Springs: WPHSAAFB Fault Zone: CRNPTFZA Two Tides: QUKGZZYA Skyway: MCMBPJDB Sky Tides: OZMRKIDB Tube of Medusa: ODFADPYA (@) Aqua Tubeway: KNHRKJYA Skylands: WXRDJYEB Fin to Feather: UQTFBRXA Eagle's Bay: QSNVMMDB Asterite's Cave: EGAQRVXA (@) Maze of Stone: EUTQQQWA Four Islands: CZVQNHCB Sea of Darkness: WFMYIDAB Vents of Medusa: SHWZZNBB Gateway: QKLLFPHB Moray Abyss: YCFSBRAB The Eye: AGNEXBTE Big Water: YCBXONIA Deep Ridge: UPODMUQD The Hungry Ones: YOHVUVLE Secret Cave: SPKHKISE Lunar Bay: WTHXKISE Black Clouds: USKIKDOE GraviatorBox: WNQWZMME Globe Holder: MIPGDOME (@) New Machine: GOSTCXJA Vortex Queen: OOSFBXAA Home Bay: QNSGAPGA Epilogue: AXBGKHBA Fish City: WKGETHCA City of Forever: WQHFTZHA ''Secret'' Password: AVQJTCBA Cheat: Hard ModeIn the starting area break the two shells above you, and then swim through the tunnel to start the game in hard mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0vAPLN1G-7Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4354</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586157-ecco-the-tides-of-time</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/ecco-the-tides-of-time</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ecco-the-tides-of-time/3030-15751/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2370522-genesis_eccothetidesoftime_eu_croppeds.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SWkxko0.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/133785-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4354-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4354-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33480-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33481-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33482-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-colored-fishes.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33483-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-jumping-high.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33485-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-into-the-depths-of.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33486-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-talking-to-a-friendly.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33487-ecco-the-tides-of-time-genesis-screenshot-beautiful-sky.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2763975-eccotides001.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Pn8TFTi.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4354.png</clearlogo1>
</game>