<Game>
	<Name>Ecco the Dolphin (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ecco the Dolphin (also known as Ecco) is an aquatic side-scrolling action-adventure game developed by Novotrade and published by Sega for the Genesis in Europe (on July 31, 1992), North America (on December 29, 1992), and Japan (on July 30, 1993).Players control a bottlenose dolphin named Ecco (unique to other dolphins for the six star markings on his forehead) as he embarks on a journey through the oceans, trying to figure out the whereabouts of his group (who were sucked up in a mysterious waterspout) while helping fellow dolphins along the way.Along with its unconventional gameplay mechanics (including a dedicated "sing" button for interaction and echolocation), the game is known for its extreme level of difficulty (which would be a staple for the main games of the series) and bizarre plot development (including time travel and alien abductions). It would later spawn a sequel (Ecco: The Tides of Time), a kid-friendly spin-off (Ecco Jr.), and a 3D reboot (Ecco the Dolphin: Defender of the Future).Along with downscaled ports to the Sega Master System and Game Gear, the game was ported to the Sega CD less than a year later. This version (known in Japan as Ecco the Dolphin CD) features a bonus set of levels and new soundtrack (using Redbook audio), and was later ported to the PC in Japan and North America (both in 1996, featuring new high-resolution sprites). The original game was digitally re-released for the Wii (via Virtual Console on November 27, 2006), Xbox 360 (via Xbox Live Arcade on August 15, 2007), PC (via Steam on June 1, 2010), and most iOS devices (on July 22, 2010), and was included in two compilations: Sega Genesis Collection (for the PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable), and Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection (for the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3).An enhanced port was made for the Nintendo 3DS (as 3D Ecco the Dolphin, part of Sega's 3D Classics remake series) and digitally released on the 3DS eShop on December 12, 2013 (June 26, 2013 in Japan). This version features stereoscopic 3D and a significantly-easier difficulty setting (adding invulnerability and unlimited air).Cheat: Enable the Super Cheat MenuBegin the game and move Ecco left and right.  Press Start to pause the game while Ecco is turning.  You have to pause it when Ecco is directly facing you.  When you do that, press Right, B, C, B, C, Down, C, Up.  If you did it right, a cheat menu that has options such as stage select, message test, sound test, and more, will appear.Cheat: Enable the Super Cheat MenuEnter the code SHARKFIN for infinite air and sonar.Cheat: Enable the Super Cheat MenuInput a valid password, then press Start, and wait for the screen that shows the name of the level you're currently in with your password.  Next, hold A and Start.  Keep hold of A and Start until Ecco appears on the screen.  Now press Start to unpause and you will be invincible.Cheat: Enable the Super Cheat MenuAJPPOWAX is the password for this levelCheat: Alternate Password EntryWhen you are in the "password entry" screen, you can enter these "please" codes to reach the corresponding levels. Cheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Last Fight: KNLMLMLCCheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Undercaves: UYNAINCC The Undercaves 2: DQDIACCI The Vents: FKWLACCACheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Lagoon: NDRBRIKR Ridge Water: HYAUGFLV Open Ocean: FNCQWBMTCheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Ice Zone: DWFFZBMV Hard Water Zone: QGDJRQLA Cold Water Zone: MCLFRQLWCheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Island Zone: UWXIOQLK Deep Water Zone: EILQOQLC The Marble Sea: XAKUQQLSCheat: Alternate Password EntryThe Library: FDGXQQLC Deep City: ZUVPQQLU City of Forever: AABBRQLUCheat: Alternate Password EntryJurassic Beach: PLABUNLT Pteranodon Pond: FQREUNLI Origin Beach: QXKIUNLXCheat: Alternate Password EntryTrilobite Circle: OBEMUNLX Dark Water: JNXPUNLA Deep Water 2: WSGAKNLCCheat: Alternate Password EntryCity of Forever 2: ZBPIGPLD The Tube: KUVEKMLK The Machine: SDDBKMLGCheat: Alternate Password EntryNVNAINCRCheat: Easy Password ListBy entering an even combination of A's and N's in different sequences for your password, you can gain access to a variety of levels within the game. Here's a list of password combinations and the levels they take you to:Cheat: Easy Password ListAANNNNAA: Deep CityNNNAANAA: The Marble SeaAAAANNNN: Origin BeachNNNNAAAA: Island ZoneNNNAAAAN: UndercavesAAAAAAAA: UndercavesNNNNNNNN: Welcome to The MachineAAANNNNA: Welcome to The MachineANANAANN: The VentsAANNAANN: The VentsNNAANNAA: Dark WaterNANANNAA: Dark WaterANNANNAA: Dark WaterANANANAN: Hard WaterNANANANA: Hard WaterAANNANAN: Hard WaterNNAANANA: Hard WaterCheat: Easy Password ListAll other combinations will not work, and will transport Ecco back to the starting screen of the game.Cheat: Easy Password ListCheat: Easy Password ListCheat: Easy Password ListCheat: Easy Password ListCheat: Easy Password List</plot>
	<releasedate>30/7/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>It_eOIPgCdE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2900</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563323-ecco-the-dolphin</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/ecco-the-dolphin</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ecco-the-dolphin/3030-9286/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/28/12125-ecco.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/imaBng1.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/d1w1yDS.jpg</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/198102-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33474-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33475-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2900-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2900-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2900-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2900-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ISPfG6O.png</banner1>
	<Notes>You are Ecco, a powerful young dolphin. A mysterious storm has swept your family from the sea. The search to find them will take you through vast underwater realms of treachery, beauty and adventure. Use your sonar to discover hidden caverns and unlock the secrets of crystal glyphs. Charge packs of bloodthirsty sharks. Dive deep... but don't linger too long, because you're a mammal and need air to breathe. In your quest, you'll discover that more than your family's safety is at stake. The fate of the whole world rests on your wits and fins. Explore over 25 giant levels of solving puzzles and fighting denizens of the sea. Knife through the waters, flip above the waves, with motions created from real dolphins.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/32e8fc71-8711-423c-bf63-ef012e606238.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d379ffb7-0a5c-4c49-a280-5ecae7beced4.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b49ab23-ce03-430f-a1c6-3bd78dbcfd6a.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43f9ca1c-ab39-4690-ae01-f9460aa4c597.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ccb6b72-9649-4ee7-ac8e-835b31e3812c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/874e14b2-3765-45f5-a080-b2c40f34c3fa.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90d2521f-47b8-4c3f-96f7-a7c64f424db9.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f261bc38-030e-4315-a986-56126d3c045d.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef58cbf3-b620-486c-98d2-7f796ce4286c.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4370a31-6261-441d-9036-beb113d3318f.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/448dfee1-5c46-47e4-8b74-3759b4cc171f.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a5d037f-e6eb-4ffb-8d55-e8a1a0c686cd.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>