<Game>
	<Name>Ecco the Dolphin II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Ecco is older, stronger and engulfed by dangers! The evil Vortex has shattered the mystical Asterite. Ecco and Trellia, a beautiful dolphin of the future, cross 100 million years of time to save the dolphins and all life on Earth! Ecco morphs! Charge a metasphere to become a shark with all its fighting power! Change into a seagull and fly! Safely swim past dangers as a jellyfish! Over 40 levels of spectacular aquatic adventure, with password save. Five levels of challenging 3-D travel, through the vast waters of the open ocean!Cheat: Debug MenuWhen you have control of Ecco and can pause, Try to pause while Ecco is facing you. Once Ecco is facing you, press A, B, C, B, C, A, C, A, and B.  If you entered the code correctly, a menu will pop up with all sorts of optionssuch as a sound test, level select, tempo, etc. This code can be entered as many times as you'd like, as long as the game is paused while Ecco is facing you. Cheat: Debug MenuTurn Ecco left or right and pause the game while Ecco is facing towards the screen. Press (A), (B), RIGHT, (A), (C), (A), DOWN, (A), (B), RIGHT, (A), and then unpause. You will now never die from lack of air or injuries.Cheat: EasymodeJust entering the word easy mode in the password screen would work as a password. This difference it caused was it made certain lvl's much easier to complete like jumping certain spots in the game where you could easily lose in normal mode where no longer there. I am surprised no one ever thought about trying this code. I would always try and figure out codes and just enetered it one day when I was 12 years old. 16 years have passed and no one ever brought it up.Cheat: Easymode   Crystal Springs = UEPMCVEB    Fault Zone = OZUNSKZA    Two Tides = KDKINTYA    Skyway = SZXHCLDB    Sky Tides = OZWIDLDB    Tube of Medusa = QSJRYHZA    Skylands = MULXRXEB    Fin To Feather = YCPAWEXA    Eagle's Bay = YCJPDNDB    Asterite's Cave = AOJRDZWA    Four Islands = UOYURFDB    Sea of Darkness = UQZWIIAB    Vents of Medusa = MMVSOPBB    Gateway = KDCGTAHB    Big Water = QQCQRDRA    Deep Ridge = UXQWJIZD    Hungry Ones = WBQHMIUE    Secret Cave = CHGTEYZE    Gravitorbox = UIXBGWXE    Globe Holder = SBFPWWJE    Dark Sea = MXURVMLA    Vortex Queen = OKIMTBPA    Home Bay = CSNCMRUA    Epilogue = CEWSXKPA    Fish City = SGTDYSPA    City of Forever = WSSXZKVACheat: Easymode@ = New level found only in Hard Mode Crystal Springs: WPHSAAFB Fault Zone: CRNPTFZA Two Tides: QUKGZZYA Skyway: MCMBPJDB Sky Tides: OZMRKIDB Tube of Medusa: ODFADPYA (@) Aqua Tubeway: KNHRKJYA Skylands: WXRDJYEB Fin to Feather: UQTFBRXA Eagle's Bay: QSNVMMDB Asterite's Cave: EGAQRVXA (@) Maze of Stone: EUTQQQWA Four Islands: CZVQNHCB Sea of Darkness: WFMYIDAB Vents of Medusa: SHWZZNBB Gateway: QKLLFPHB Moray Abyss: YCFSBRAB The Eye: AGNEXBTE Big Water: YCBXONIA Deep Ridge: UPODMUQD The Hungry Ones: YOHVUVLE Secret Cave: SPKHKISE Lunar Bay: WTHXKISE Black Clouds: USKIKDOE GraviatorBox: WNQWZMME Globe Holder: MIPGDOME (@) New Machine: GOSTCXJA Vortex Queen: OOSFBXAA Home Bay: QNSGAPGA Epilogue: AXBGKHBA Fish City: WKGETHCA City of Forever: WQHFTZHA ''Secret'' Password: AVQJTCBA Cheat: Hard ModeIn the starting area break the two shells above you, and then swim through the tunnel to start the game in hard mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Novotrade</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0vAPLN1G-7Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4354</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586157-ecco-the-tides-of-time</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/ecco-the-dolphin</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ecco-the-dolphin/3030-9286/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4354-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4354-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/d1w1yDS.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/198102-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4354-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4354-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2900-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33474-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33475-ecco-the-dolphin-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4354-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ISPfG6O.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4354.png</clearlogo1>
</game>