<Game>
	<Name>Empire of Steel (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>It is the age of steel. Mammoth battleships cruise the skies. Armored locomotives carry cannons the size of railway cars. Invincible fortresses float on air... and military might rules the day. The Motorhead Empire has conquered and enslaved most of the world. Only one hope remains... The Republic of Silverhead. Their Z-01 Zeppelin flying ship launches lethal aerial-mines. Their Striker airplane fires armor piercing missiles. Their Lightning Bomb will reduce Motorhead's flame-shooting juggernauts to crumbling hulks of burning metal. Enter a future that might have been. It's time to wage the war of the Steel Empire!Cheat: 100 ShipsGo to the Options menu and set up the options as follows: Difficulty - Hard Ships - 2 Continues - 1 Then select Sound 65 in Sound Test and press A. There won't be a sound, but when you start playing, you'll start with 99 ships.Cheat: 100 ShipsHold down B and press the Start button on the title screen. You should start on the second level now.Cheat: 100 ShipsHighlight ''Sound Test'' in the Options menu. Then press A to listen to the sounds in this order: Sound 1, Sound 1, Sound 9, Sound 2. A stage select option should appear at the bottom of the screen.Cheat: 100 ShipsPress C, A, C, A, Start, B on controller two at the ship select screen.Cheat: 100 ShipsGo to the Options menu and set up the options as follows: Difficulty - Hard Ships - 3 Continues - 2 Then select Sound 77 from Sound Test and press A. No sound will be heard, but when you start playing you can gain Level 20 firepower by pressing B on controller two.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Hot-B</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>eyvSpDCnsKc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4676</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586490-steel-empire</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/steel-empire/3030-11296/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4676-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4676-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4676-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648936-eos2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648935-eos4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648924-eos6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648923-eos5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648921-eos3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/19332/648919-eos1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/c/9/gfs_3606_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/a/gfs_88189_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/b/a/gfs_88189_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4676-1.jpg</fanart1>
</game>