<Game>
	<Name>ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:ESPN Sunday Night NFL is a football game based on the TV show of the same name, which aired on the ESPN when the game was out in 1994. It was released on the Super Nintendo, Genesis and the Sega CD. The game uses a vertical perspective common to football games of the era, using sprite scaling as the ball travels the field to zoom in and out on the players.The game has the NFL license, so the player can choose between twenty-eight teams present in the 1994 AFC and NFC leagues. The stats are approximate to the quality of the teams at the time, with certain teams vastly overpowering others in offense and defense. TeamsBuffalo BillsIndianapolis ColtsMiami DolphinsNew England PatriotsNew York JetsCincinnati BengalsCleveland BrownsHouston Oilers (now the Tennessee Titans)Pittsburgh SteelersDenver BroncosKansas City ChiefsLos Angeles Raiders (now the Oakland Raiders)San Diego ChargersSeattle SeahawksDallas CowboysNew York GiantsPhiladelphia EaglesArizona CardinalsWashington RedskinsChicago BearsDetroit LionsGreen Bay PackersMinnesota VikingsTampa Bay BuccaneersAtlanta FalconsLos Angeles Rams (now the St. Louis Rams)New Orleans SaintsSan Francisco 49ers</plot>
	<releasedate>23/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>4360</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586164-espn-sunday-night-nfl</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/espn-sunday-night-nfl</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/espn-sunday-night-nfl/3030-50378/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4360-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/193015-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/193016-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337555-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337556-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337557-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-choose-a-team.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337558-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-game-modes.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337559-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-weather-conditions.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337560-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-game-options.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337561-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-commentary.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337562-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-this-looks-like-it.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337563-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-more-team-comparisons.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/337564-espn-sunday-night-nfl-genesis-screenshot-the-coin-toss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4360.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>ESPN Sunday Night NFL was one of the many football games released back in the day. It features all 28 official NFL teams and their respective logos, but doesn't feature a license from the NFLPA, so there are no actual players names in the game. There are four different game modes to choose from: Playoffs, Single Game, Season and another season mode that lets the player act out the 1994 NFL season schedule.  It also had variable weather conditions that the players on the field would react to and a battery back-up to save games.  It also featured Chris Berman, who not only graced the front cover but also gives commentary as well.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2ae4255b-7a32-4135-9404-91e882a3f07d.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79f15b19-d299-4520-8c90-ed766ba79ad1.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>