<Game>
	<Name>ESWAT - City Under Siege (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:ESWAT: City Under Siege (JP: Cyber Justice: ESWAT) is a Sega Arcade side-scrolling shooter that was released to the Sega Genesis the following year with numerous tweaks. The original Arcade version was also converted for many home computers and consoles of the late 80s and early 90s. The Genesis version of ESWAT was also later added to the 2009 Sega compilation Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection as well as joining several other Genesis titles on Steam.ESWAT features the cop Duke Oda as he makes his way through the ranks of a futuristic police force, eventually donning the ESWAT power armor that turns him into an almost unstoppable crimefighter. Standing in his way is the terrorist organization E.Y.E., which is determined to bring down ESWAT at any cost with equivalent hi-tech gear.The game changes as the player progresses, evolving from the moderately underpowered patrolman to the ESWAT cyborg and adopting new weaponry and powers along the way. The game plays similarly to other Sega side-scrolling games of the era, such as Shinobi.Cheat: Level selectStart a game, the Hero and Mission screen appears. Now hold down A,B,C and press Left, Right, Up, Down on D-Pad. You are now able to select the level by pressing Left/Right.Cheat: Level selectTo enable the sound test, first beat the game. Then during the ending sequence, press and hold buttons A, B, C, Down, and Left. Keep holding these and press Start until the sound test screen appears.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/7/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>FEbUt7oR-kA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4361</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586161-eswat-city-under-siege</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/eswat-city-under-siege</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/eswat-city-under-siege/3030-29056/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4361-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4361-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80499-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67935-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67936-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67937-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-health-pick-up.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67938-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-enemies-fire-up-and.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67939-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-a-security-droid.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67940-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-the-first-boss.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67941-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-level-2-inside-cyber.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67942-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-hop-in-if-you-dare.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67943-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-enemies-on-moving.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67944-eswat-city-under-siege-genesis-screenshot-watch-out-for-droids.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/h4uWrt5.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The city is besieged by wanted criminals, and as a police officer it is your duty to stop them. The first criminals in the wanted list can be stopped with your service weapon an some fast reactions, but once you're facing the toughest criminals in town you'll need to use the cyber suit, which provides additional protection and higher firepower. Unlike other versions of this game, this Genesis cartridge doesn't follow the layout of the arcade game. The levels, rather than being linear, feature some platform elements, and the enemies in the first levels are no longer bank robbers or hit-men, but soldiers and robots instead. And the setting is no longer your typical American city, but a futuristic megalopolis.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/073e5598-5a7c-45f7-a475-ac9a09df4376.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4dbac7f0-9064-4971-8c1a-b59bb8370cc1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10d9ed39-e00e-46f4-8019-55dbe18769f7.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0c39057-0650-4b99-a6ad-92361f896c96.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb824f2d-7a86-4a10-96c3-6edcb29fc86a.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8865732f-be44-43cb-a334-56071ef59baf.jpg</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>