<Game>
	<Name>Ex-Ranza (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Engage in airborne combat with jump-jets and weapons of incredible power or link up with your cyber cycle for high speed ground attacks. Each step inches you closer to your goal and the fight of your life. You are Ranger X... A mysterious lone warrior who has risen from the ashes to return peace and justice to a failed society. Eight post-apocalyptic levels of high-intensity action! Monstrous mechanical bosses await your every move. Use jump-jets to attack by air or transform into the Super Cyber Cycle and roll to victory!Cheat: Cheat ModePause game play and press Up, Down, Up, Down, Up, Down, C, B, A, Right, Left. The music will resume to confirm correct code entry. Enter one of the following controller actions to enable the corresponding effect.  Level skip Press B.  Slow motion Press A. Press Start to return to normal speed. Cheat: Cheat ModeTo access debug mode of the ship in the cut-scene, when you see the WARNING sign flashing, press B + X + Z + Mode.Cheat: Cheat ModeEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  Up - Down - Up - Down - Up - Down - C - B - A - Right - Left  To skip to the next level just press BCheat: Cheat Mode During gameplay, pause the game then press U,D,U,D,U,D,C,A,R,L. Then prees A to go into slow motion.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/5/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Gau Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ZmkyHnh-lWM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>681</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586414-ranger-x</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ranger-x/3030-1421/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/2237979-586414_46772_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/681-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/544628-ranger_x_007a.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/544384-ranger_x_005.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/544383-ranger_x_004.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/544382-ranger_x_003.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542920-ranger_x_022.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542915-ranger_x_020.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542907-ranger_x_016.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542886-ranger_x_011.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542879-ranger_x_002.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1634/542878-ranger_x_0.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/681.png</clearlogo1>
</game>