<Game>
	<Name>F1 Circus MD (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>F1 Circus MD is a Sega Mega Drive video game using the vehicles and the basic regulations of the Formula One circuit. The "Circus" part of the title is actually a mistranslation of the word Circuit. The view is top-down which is considered a tricky view for most gamers[4]. Players must try to either win as many races as possible or achieve a podium finish. Every new Grand Prix at worldly destinations like the Canadian Grand Prix and the Japanese Grand Prix requires the player to learn new skills and new turns. The racing action consists of open wheel vehicles capable of going more than 200 miles per hour (321.8 kilometres per hour) on the long straight portions of the track.While loosely based on the 1991 Formula One season, the game uses drivers and racing teams with similar names to the officially licensed counterparts of that era. Career mode only permits racers to race up to eight seasons; retirement is mandatory after the eighth season. Preparing for each and every indvidual race requires setting up the right racing parts for the individual demands of that particular course (all of them are road courses with no oval courses as seen in the actual Formula One league). Team Lotus is considered to be the official co-sponsor of this video game along with its publisher Nichibutsu.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/F1_Circus_MDCheat: Sound Test MenuTo access the sound test menu, press and hold A + B + C + START at the title screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nichibutsu</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>9DhrYT-H93M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20370</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570407-f1-circus-md</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20370-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/5/7/31257_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/1/6/gfs_9814_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/8/b/gfs_9814_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/5/b/gfs_9814_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<Notes>F1 Circus MD (Ｆ１サーカスＭＤ) is a 1991 racing game by Nihon Bussan for the Sega Mega Drive in their F1 Circus series, which also contains a Mega CD game. The game is a typical Formula 1 racing game. In World Championship mode, you are limited to a predefined course set, but you may choose your team, lap count, vehicle specifics, etc. Races are presented in a top-down view. A accelerates, B breaks, Up shifts down, Down shifts up, and C opens a menu.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/350c8620-900d-4e2c-a394-01493047d8bf.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d166c84e-6fd8-40e9-afeb-7b4c8e04547e.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/156d6f51-b543-4a40-90f6-fc22dc57ed94.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15ea65cf-2bf3-4987-a0e4-cbdfc2ac1b1a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5b6a0536-a80c-4d8f-be17-5f4985cd9e56.jpg</snapshot6>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nihon Bussan</Publisher>
</game>