<Game>
	<Name>Fantasia (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:~ Runaway NotesShh! Mickey, the sorcerer's apprentice, is asleep in the master's dungeon. But not everything is quiet. A wicked wind from Bald Mountain creeps in, flicker's the candle flame, and--poof--the candle's out! What's the evil wind up to? The paper on the table rustles, but Mickey is deep, deep in a dream. The musical notes on the paper float away, captured by the win! Mickey, do something! And Mickey does? He follows the notes in his dream, rising into the air and drifting after them.  But is Mickey too late? The tricky wind scatters the notes throughout Fantasia. It drops a few in the master's workroom, and loses others in the ancient jungles and under the sea. Some notes fall into deep, dark caverns. Many of the notes are scattered about in the garden's and meadows, where mushrooms skip. And far, far into the land of Fantasia, even more of the notes drift among airy columns, between floating bubbles, flying horses, and hippo's dancing on their toes. Take care, Mickey. Magic is everywhere, ready to catch you in it's spell! You'll bump into marching brooms, waddling cauldrons, and poisonous dancing flowers. You'll be knocked into the ooze by the rumble of battling dinosaurs. Pterodactyls will flap around your head, and crocodiles will snap. You'll even travel high into space, where planets zoom and stars explode. On Bald Mountain, witches, imps, and wailing goblin heads will chase you through burning lava! Take along some magic spells of your own, and get more magic from the master's book. You must find the notes and bring them back, so the master's music can play again! ~Passage from the manual.     Worlds~ The Land of Fantasia The Water World- A wolrd full of scaly amphibians, skipping mushrooms, and dancing brooms.The Earth World- Set in a jungle full of dinosaurs, the level is also visited frequently by earthquakes.The Air World- Set in a beautiful sky garden.The Fire World- Enter Bald Mountain, and combat the witches and goblins. Bonus Rooms Wooden doors appear in special places. These lead Mickey to bonus rooms filled with magic items. Magic Items Magic items are all around. If Mickey can get them, they'll keep up his strength and earn bonus points. Cheat: A bunch of treasures right from the beginning...Just after the first stage of the game starts, go downstairs. Get the two enemies. Go right and two magic broomsticks will show up. Don't touch them. Instead, move to the very left and have them following you. Cheat: A bunch of treasures right from the beginning...Then kill the one at the front only.Cheat: A bunch of treasures right from the beginning...Go back upstairs. You will see there are three crystal balls and two stars--very valuable treasures in the game!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>qmGAZQahx5o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4369</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586174-fantasia</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/fantasia</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fantasia/3030-20273/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4369-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4369-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80490-fantasia-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210642-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210643-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210644-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210645-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-ready-to-do-some-music.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210646-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-starting-location.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210647-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-be-careful-of-those-brooms.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210705-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-the-front-layer-of-parallax-can.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/210704-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-going-to-heaven.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/646018-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-life-lost.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/646019-fantasia-genesis-screenshot-nice-lake.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hWvJQxi.jpg</banner1>
</game>