<Game>
	<Name>Fastest 1 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Fastest 1 is a Formula One racing game. The game doesn't have an official FIA license, but much like Human's Fire Pro Wrestling series, includes a number of recognizable fictionalized drivers, such as Ayrton Sesna and Satoru Inakajima. The game includes a world championship mode, where the player must start from the lowest rankings and win races to become the F1 world champion. There is also a battle mode where one or two players can race each other or against computer opponents, as well as a test run mode where the player can learn each course and try to set course records. There are a total of 16 different courses, which can be played in either dry, wet, or half-wet conditions, as well as a wide variety of vehicle settings that can be tweaked.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/6/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>1.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20372</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570405-fastest-1</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/fastest-1</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20372-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/5/8/31258_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/b/8/gfs_9208_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/5/gfs_9208_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/5/gfs_9208_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<Notes>Fastest 1 (ファステスト・ワン) is a 1991 racing game for the Sega Mega Drive by Human. It is seemingly similar to Human's Human Grand Prix series for the SNES. Renovation Products was set to release the game overseas as Speedway Pro Challenge, but the release was cancelled for unknown reasons. Box shots have been leaked to the Internet somehow. The game is a generic 3D racing game. B accelerates and Up and Down change gears.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a732d66-c3a0-41e4-bc11-0f69998dce11.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/128f0ab9-aba5-4b33-bb51-bde57763d47d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0ed018c-edcd-41a0-ba54-5d8a0fa01483.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96c1b8c7-9f4c-49bd-b9c6-9323a0fa06ed.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce90eafb-b01d-410b-80a2-30431d736b6c.jpg</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>Human</Publisher>
</game>