<Game>
	<Name>Fatal Rewind (USA, Europe) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>First prize is your life! It's a game show in the 21st century and you're the entertainment! Equip your armored body with high-tech weaponry. Scale the walls and avoid the rising acid as you make your dash for freedom. Dozens of Hostile Artificial Life Forms have targeted you for extermination. Watch your step, booby traps are everywhere! 12 levels of hot arcade action to climb, jump and blast your way through. Choose from over a dozen different weapons to strap onto your body suit. Fatal rewind - step in and re-direct sections of your previous escape attempts. 3 levels of difficulty - hard, harder and hardest!Gameplay::This game is a mixture between platformer and shoot'em up. It looks very similar to the popular computer video game Turrican. Apart from avoiding or shooting enemies moving in different patterns you must make your way from the bottom up to the level exit because after a few seconds toxic liquid will start to rise. At the beginning of each level you may display a map by pressing the Help key (Amiga version). You can jump, run, climb walls and use special weapons or items (keys to open certain gates) to master different sections of these levels. After you lose one life you see a replay and be able to continue at any point by pushing the fire button. You can fast-forward the replay by holding the F10 key pressed. This was a unique and convenient feature because like other Psygnosis titles the game has a high degree of difficulty.The Genesis version had 6 levels divided into two parts each. and is now available on the Sony PSP.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/home/586179.htmlhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fatal_RewindCheat: Level SelectTo access level select, during startup, when you see the Psygnosis logo, press and hold Up + Left + A + B + C + Start. Then go to options to select the level.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>478</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586179-fatal-rewind</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/killing-game-show</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fatal-rewind/3030-8582/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/478-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/478-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/162897-the-killing-game-show-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201015-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-the-us-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201034-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-euro-and-japanese.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201026-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-oh-and-did-i-mention.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201027-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-the-video-window.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201028-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-as-well-as-the-color.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201029-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-as-well-as-the-frame.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201030-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-yet-despite-that.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201031-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-the-intro-plays-in.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201032-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-i-wish-they-kept.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/201033-the-killing-game-show-genesis-screenshot-yeah-welcome-to-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4SooAnp.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/478.png</clearlogo1>
</game>