<Game>
	<Name>Fido Dido (USA) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Fido Dido is a hip line-art cartoon character animated into various situations. However Fido's animator has fallen asleep and because of that, there is trouble brewing inside of other drawings. Fido must enter each one of these strange worlds and use his laid back attitude to overcome obstacles and solve the problems.Gameplay::Fido Dido is a side-scrolling platform game. The player, controlling Fido Dido himself can move left and right, jump, pick up items and use them. If Fido is ever without items, the use button instead causes him to snap his fingers which can open doors and cause things to happen. Fido has an energy meter on the screen, enemies and hazards that touch him will deplete that meter. When it is gone, Fido Dido loses a life. Each level features a new and unique objective as well as items specific to that level.Hints:- Level passwords -ALLISFAIR   Level 2SOFTWAREWOLF   Level 3BONETOPICK   Level 4FEAROFFLYING   Level 5SINCORSWIM   Level 6YIPPEEAYEAY   View endinghttp://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/fido-didohttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/code/586181.html</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Kaneko</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>13675</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586181-fido-dido</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fido-dido/3030-14281/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/13675-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/2/gfs_38883_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/f/gfs_38883_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/f/gfs_38883_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/b/gfs_38883_3_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/b/gfs_38883_3_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Fido Dido is a game platform on the Megadrive. The player Fido worlds through drawings from the author. Each level has its own goals and its own objects that the player must make the best use to get rid of enemies and obstacles which stand in the way.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23a7cdfd-a787-414d-836a-1f7e9c4c0180.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc73937b-c91c-4795-be13-4860d05c932d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Kaneko</Publisher>
</game>