<Game>
	<Name>FIFA Soccer 97 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv)</Name>
	<plot>One of the early FIFA football games. It was released for the Genesis, SNES, Saturn, PlayStation and the PC. It was the first FIFA game to include polygonal players. In previous games 2D sprites had been used. It was also the first FIFA game to include a 5-a-side indoor football arena to compete in.David Ginola (a Newcastle United winger) featured on the cover of the European version's, and Bebeto (a Brazilian Striker) was on the cover for the American and Asian versions of the game.The first Nintendo 64 FIFA game FIFA 64 was based on this game.Features:Fifa 97 is the first game in the series to use polygonal players, as previously the games featured 2D players. Fifa 97 continues to use the virtual stadium system which was introduced in Fifa 96. Cheat: Max Out Create a Player StatsCreate a player and change his name to the following:Cheat: Top players available for transferIn the options menu, go to 'Transfer Players' and select the American team Los Angeles.  In the team are three strikers with 95 skill (J. Jacecko, G. Simmons, U. Mayer).  Transfer them to any team of your choice to make it a lot easier to score!  Also, check out Miami and New York for some other great players that you may not have heard of.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>ETklRFxhlc8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4373</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563324-fifa-soccer-97</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/fifa-soccer-97_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fifa-soccer-97/3030-3383/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4373-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4373-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54813-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37425-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-genesis-gold.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37426-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-match-select.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37427-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-world-cup.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37428-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-the-list-of-the-games-that.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37429-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-wow-all-the-israeli-stars.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37430-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-choosing-a-strategy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37431-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-game.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37432-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-throw-in.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37433-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-replay-just-like-tv.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37434-fifa-soccer-97-genesis-screenshot-goal-kick.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4373.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This iteration of the FIFA lineage includes commentary from John Motson with summaries from Andy Gray, with the between-match sections covered by Des Lynam. All player moves are from David Ginola using the MotionBlending technology. Full interactive replays are included. You can play a league or cup tournament, and practice your skills before playing. The game can be tailored to action or simulation style, with fouls, injuries and offsides available to toggle on or off. This version also includes a 6 vs 6 indoor play mode, and various multiplayer options</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2cf956d4-6328-4819-b449-4ef145746522.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b01b4f92-aae7-4869-a3c4-928dcec9c2c4.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d6d6822-e7c2-4f87-b4a9-a0a633a907bb.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>