<Game>
	<Name>Fix It Felix Jr.</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1986-06-18T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Fix-It Felix, Jr. is a platformer game in the Wreck-It Ralph universe. It takes place in Niceland, where Ralph, Felix, several Nicelanders and Q*Bert characters live.At the beginning of a game, Ralph climbs up a hotel, breaking windows as he goes. It is the player's job as Felix, to repair each window with his magical hammer, while avoiding bricks that fall off when Ralph punches, and Duck Hunt-inspired ducks that fly horizontally across the screen at random. On some screens, if the player waits long enough, a Nicelander will appear in a window to drop off a pie which Felix can collect for a period of invincibility and other effects depending on the version of the game. As the game progresses, the enemies become more numerous and faster, and there are more windows to repair. What's more, Ralph will smash and break windows that the player has already repaired, forcing them to go back and fix them. Higher levels introduce rather increasing numbers of randomly-placed obstacles such as purple flowerbeds which prevent Felix from jumping up or down between two windows. The versions made available online also feature open window shutters for blocking Felix horizontally, while the arcade version instead has a number of large piles of bricks fall between two windowsills and get stuck starting in the fifth round. Felix can jump over these brick piles to get across the row, but they will kill him if he steps into them or jumps into them from below.  The story of the game is that Ralph is destroying Niceland Apartments in retaliation for the Nicelanders bulldozing his hollow-stump home in the forest to build their apartment building and leaving him in the town dump. When Felix fixes every window on the screen, Ralph climbs higher and reveals more floors of broken windows. When Felix fixes the highest screen (with penthouse visible on the arcade version), a cutscene plays where the Nicelanders join Ralph and Felix on the roof and award Felix a medal (which floats down from behind a pair of parting clouds), a pie, and a kiss on the cheek. The Nicelanders then lift up Ralph and hurl him off the building into a mud puddle. Finally, Ralph comes back to try again in a new level.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a57f59c1-35da-4e6b-86cf-1e99ab545c5d.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aed0b451-45a8-46d0-9a62-0d3f42a914c6.jpg</boxart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1c2b3ffa-626a-486c-ac7a-bbf70c39c77f.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/efa346dd-4b95-4ef4-8ead-a5a514947514.jpg</snapshot1>
	<Rating>2.5</Rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Developer>Tobi Komi</Developer>
	<Publisher>Tobi Komi</Publisher>
</game>