<Game>
	<Name>Flashback (Europe) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>Planet Titan: Brave mutants, robots, anti-matter fields and the primitive inhabitants as you find your way through the jungle. New Washington: First recover your memory, then go undercover to earn money. Finally, buy a false ID if you want to sneak back on Earth. Death Tower: Climb the 8 floors of the Death Tower labyrinth. Avoid the deadly Replicants and win a free ticket to Earth. Earth: Big trouble! The authorities have discovered your false ID and send robot cops to capture you. Paradise Club: You discovered the aliens' plans, but somehow end up being captured and mysteriously transported through space. Planet Morphs: You materialized on their home planet. Now all you have to do is destroy the Morphs and live to tell about it!Cheat: Better weaponEnter the following at the password screen:Cheat: Better weaponEnter the following code at the Pasword screen....  Level 1: PIXEL Level 2: BETSY Level 3: PANCHO Level 4: STUDIO Level 5: TOHO Level 6: AKANE Level 7: INCBIN  Then you should go to your desired levelCheat: Better weapon At the password screen put in CYGNUS.Cheat: Better weaponEnter the following code at the Pasword screen....  Level 1: CLIO Level 2: ACRTC Level 3: BLOB Level 4: STUN Level 5: MIMOLO Level 6: HECTOR Level 7: KALIMA  Then you should go to your desired levelCheat: Better weaponEnter the following code at the Pasword screen....  Level 1: FALCON Level 2: DATA Level 3: MILORD Level 4: QUICKY Level 5: BIJOU Level 6: BUBBLE Level 7: CLIP  Then you should go to your diesired levelCheat: Better weaponEnter SANFRA as your code to view the ending of the game.Cheat: Better weapon When at any wall, turn away from it, hold A and the D-pad away from the wall, and then when Conrad runs, release A and press the D-pad towards the wall.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Delphine Software International</Developer>
	<rating>8.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>CMXJBS6n44M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4378</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586187-flashback-the-quest-for-identity</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/flashback-the-quest-for-identity/3030-1066/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4378-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4378-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/b/d/gfs_92659_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/d/d/gfs_57106_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4378-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4378.png</clearlogo1>
</game>