<Game>
	<Name>Flicky (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Flicky is a action platformer developed by Sega. The title was first released for arcade in 1984 and Sega Genesis in 1991.The game has been re-released In the Sonic Mega Collection for the GameCube (2002), the Sonic Mega Collection Plus for the Xbox and PlayStation 2 (2005); Sega Genesis Collection for PSP and PlayStation 2 (2006); Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection for Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 (2009); and on PC via Steam (2010).Gameplay:The player controls a bird named Flicky and the object of the game is to guide chicks to safety whilst avoiding a cat (Tiger) and a lizard (Iggy). Players can throw certain objects at Tiger and Iggy to kill them. There are 48 proper levels in the game and they are broken up with a mini-game in which Flicky must catch her chicks in a net as they are flung in the air by Tiger. Each main level wraps around.After finishing the 48 levels, it is possible to replay the game at a higher difficulty setting.Additional InformationFlickies are a species of bird that have appeared in a number of Sonic games most notably Sonic 3D Blast and Tails Adventure.The game was designed by Yoji Shii before he went on to found Artoon.PC System RequirementsMinimumOS: Windows&#174; XP or higherGraphics: 32MB or greater graphics cardDirectX&#174;: DirectX&#174; 9.0 or greaterHard Drive: 50MB free disc spaceCheat: Level SelectStart a new game, and then hold UP + (A) + (C) + START. When the ''Round 1'' screen appears, release all the buttons. Now you can press UP or DOWN to choose the round that you start on (up to 36).Cheat: Bikini GirlIf you complete the first 10 rounds of the game in under 20 seconds each and get a perfect score in each bonus round, you should then have over 240,000 points. After you get this feat, you will then see a window at the lower left corner of the screen with a girl in a bikini.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>9_jcUGPURt8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4379</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586188-flicky</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/flicky</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/flicky/3030-12914/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4379-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4379-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/89323-flicky-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151294-flicky-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151295-flicky-genesis-screenshot-explanations-about-the-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151301-flicky-genesis-screenshot-with-a-chicken-on-the-back-it-s.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151297-flicky-genesis-screenshot-hi-there-kitty-long-time-no-see.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151298-flicky-genesis-screenshot-hey-maybe-it-is-the-wrong-door.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151299-flicky-genesis-screenshot-a-level-with-an-elephant.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151300-flicky-genesis-screenshot-come-quick-little-guys.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151296-flicky-genesis-screenshot-this-is-a-bonus-round-it-appears.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151302-flicky-genesis-screenshot-go-get-em.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/151303-flicky-genesis-screenshot-a-fierce-battle-on-the-floor.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/liLScoo.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4379.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The feathers really start to fly when Flicky the Bluebird meets Tiger the treacherous cat and Iggy the instigating lizard in this zany, fun-filled arcade hit. See, it's like this: Tiger and Iggy are trying to trap the crazy Chirps. Tiger and Iggy will stop at nothing. So hop over them. Or fling anything handy at them—a tea cup, a flower pot, an apple. Then shuffle, scuttle and fly through maze after maze—dazzling ones, dark ones, silly ones, scary ones—gathering up Chirps as you go.  Lead as many Chirps as you can to safety. The more Chirps you rescue, the higher your score. And the closer you get to the BONUS ROUND where you catch catapulted Chirps with your net. So come join the fun. But don't count your chick-ens before you catch them...</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94715d19-83c9-4f0b-9445-f3798b30422d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d11b720b-468a-4070-82ee-e799e6b1b804.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b05c63a-5074-4bcd-b043-f2ac31a0a8a8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>