<Game>
	<Name>Gargoyles (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:Gargoyles the game actually doesn't have too much in common with the late cartoon it's based on. The player controls Goliath, (voiced by Keith David) leader of the Gargoyles Manhattan clan, on a journey to catch Demona and prevent her from using the Eye of Odin. There are virtually no connections to the television series's storyline. Only the aforementioned characters appear in any fashion. Most of the game takes place during the first century A.D. before the titular gargoyles are turned to stone for 1000 years to eventually be awakened in episode one of the show. As such, the player defends  Castle Wyvern against an army of vikings...and also giant, evil robots for some reason.  Like the show itself, the game targeted young teenagers and dealt with many mature story themes rarely seen in a side-scroller at the time.    The storyline is widely considered to be non-canon.   Gameplay:Gargoyles played similarly to most other 2-D action games of that era. The player was essentially moving from left to right on every level and there was an abundance of platforms to jump and enemies to attack. It is worth noting that Gargoyles is an incredibly tough game, even by the standards of that time and there was no continue/save system.  Reception: Gargoyles did not fare very well in terms of sales or critical reception. As a result, the planned SNES version of the game was never released.Cheat: Dedication ScreensPress START to pause game then press the following codes: Dedication Screen #1 (with floating spheres): A, B, RIGHT, A, C, A, DOWN+A then press START. Dedication Screen #2: A, B, RIGHT, A, C, A, DOWN+C Dedication Screen #3: A, B, RIGHT, A, C, A, DOWN+A, A, ACheat: Dedication ScreensDedication Screen #1 (Balls) -- B, A, Left, Left, B, A, Left, Left -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, Left, Left -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, B, A, Left -- C, A, Left, Left, A, B, B, B, B -- C, A, Left, Left, C, B, B, B, B -- C, A, Left, Left, Left, Left, Left, Left -- C, A, Left, Left, B, A, Left, Left Dedication Screen #2 (''Gargoyles'') -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, C -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, R -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, A -- C, A, Left, Left, C, C -- C, A, Left, Left, A, A, A -- C, A, Left, Left, A, C, C Dedication Screen #3 (Credits) -- A, B, C, A, B, C, A, B, C -- C, A, Left, Left, C, A, B, A, C -- C, A, Left, Left, A, B, B, B, C On the first dedication screen with the balls, you can also change the balls' pattern by tapping A, and you can pause/resume the balls' movement with Start. While the balls are paused, you can zoom in with Up and zoom out with Down.Cheat: Dedication ScreensPress START to pause and enter: A,B, RIGHT, A, C, A, DOWN, A, RIGHT, B, A. Unpause and your life bar will rise to 100%Cheat: Dedication ScreensPause the game and press A, B, Right, A, C, A, Down, A, B, and Right. Resume the game and press A to throw fireballs. Cheat: Dedication ScreensAnytime during the game, press Start, then press C, A, Left, Left, A, C, A, B, then press Start again. You can then fly when you hold A, B, and C.Cheat: Dedication ScreensPause the game and press A, B, Right, A, C, A, Down, A, B, Right, and Left. Collecting a shield will disable this code. Cheat: Dedication ScreensTo gain a Level Skip just press START to pause and enter: A,B, RIGHT, A, C, A, DOWN, A, B, RIGHT, A. You will skip to the next level.Cheat: Dedication ScreensPress A, B, and C at the same time then press STARTCheat: Dedication ScreensPause the game and press Down, Up, Left, Left, A, B, B, A, B, A, Left, Left, A, Down.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Buena Vista Interactive</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1937</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586203-gargoyles</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/gargoyles</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gargoyles/3030-352/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/1937-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/121685-gargoyles-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/121684-gargoyles-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290314-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290315-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-option-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290316-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290317-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-attacking.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290318-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-climbing-the-wall.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290319-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-avoiding-fire.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290320-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-flying.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290321-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-death.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/290322-gargoyles-genesis-screenshot-walking-on-a-wall.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15515/1338259-gargoyles_game.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aH8BAKL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/1937.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this game, players control Goliath, leader of the Manhattan Clan of gargoyles, in the years 1994 and 1995, as he seeks to put an end to a magical, corrupted talisman, the Eye of Odin, which can transform whoever comes to possess it.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a32b2ab8-4f9d-407d-b1ae-ef9a4940e52c.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e583845-dfa6-493e-965a-9dedf10d0654.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Disney Interactive</Publisher>
</game>