<Game>
	<Name>Garou Densetsu 2 - Aratanaru Tatakai (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The three lone wolves return to clash with new opponents in the 'Sultan of Slugs' Battle Royale. After a year in training, forging bodies of steel, Andy, Joe, and Terry take on the world. Fatal Fury 2!Special attacks explode with more action. 3D battles bring you to the next stage in the fighting game evolution. Easy maneuverability and realistic choreography.Cheat: Dipswitch ModeAfter your game is over and the Continue Screen is counting down, you can increase your continues up to nin by pressing UP, A, and B simultaneously. At the same time, press button C for every extra continue you want.Cheat: Dipswitch ModeTo play with Krauser, Laurence, Billy or Axel, on the Takara screen, do a ''Power Geiser'' inverted move + B (directional pad, down, down-right, right, down-right, left + B). If done right, you will hear a Krauser's voice. Now you can play in the survival, and v.s. mode. To Play in the arcade mode, on the select fighter screen, put the cursor on Mai, and press down + start and right.  Cheat: Dipswitch ModeComplete the game either with the normal or hard difficulty level without using a continue.Cheat: Dipswitch ModeHighlight the "Point" option in the "Control" section of the options menu for either player. Press and hold B and left until it reads 0.That player will now have to win 99,999 times to win (effectively making it impossible for them to win). This code works for either player, but only in versus mode. "1P" and "Survival" modes are unaffected.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Gaibrain</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>rsagnHYscPs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>975</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586177-fatal-fury-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/975-3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/975-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/7/a/gfs_3040_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/8/gfs_72254_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/0/8/gfs_72254_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/8/gfs_72254_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/a/8/gfs_72254_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/8/gfs_72254_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/8/gfs_72254_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/7/8/gfs_72254_1_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/a/9/gfs_72254_1_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/4/5/gfs_72254_2_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/975-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/975.png</clearlogo1>
</game>