<Game>
	<Name>Global Gladiators (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mick &amp; Mack as the Global Gladiators is a sequel to the NES game M.C. Kids. Global Gladiators is a side-scrolling platformer/shooter where players guide two characters through four different worlds. These worlds include Slime World, Mystical Forest, Toxi-Town and Arctic World. During each world, the player has to blast enemies with guns called GooShooters, that look similar to Super Soakers, except they shoot slimy projectiles. Each of these worlds consist of several sub-stages. The aim of each level is to collect a certain number of McDonald's Global Arches to advance to the next sub-stage. Also, during the game, the characters are guided by McDonalds mascot "Ronald McDonald"s its all recycled correctly.Story:Players control either Mick or Mack over 12 levels in 4 worlds (Slime World, Mystical Forest, Toxi-Town, and Arctic World). The mission is to clean up these levels of their enemies to hopefully progress to the single boss fight in the game.DevelopmentThe game was originally developed for the Sega Genesis/Mega Drive, but was later ported to the Sega Master System, Sega Game Gear and Commodore Amiga. The game was programmed by legendary developer David Perry, who would later go on to develop such games as Alladin, Earthworm Jim and Cool Spot, all of which would use the same engine as Global Gladiators. After the release of these games, David Perry's programming team would then go on to become Shiny Entertainment.Advertisements and MessagesMcDonald's famous "Golden Arch" logo.The game features abundant references to McDonald's brand restaurants, as well as a thorough environmentalist theme, given that players are fighting monsters made of pollution, going so far as to have a bonus stage in which players must collect falling garbage and throw it into the appropriate recycling bin (paper, plastic, or glass) whilst dodging falling anvils.Critical ReceptionWhen the Genesis version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly issued the following scores, 6,8,8,8 adding, "...An excellent action game with great graphics, excellent sounds, and solid game play. The animation is liquid smooth and the game play is as fast as Sonic in some areas. The graphics are highly detailed and the sounds feature voice and other digitized effects. Plenty of levels and hidden surprises!".In the same issue Mike Weigand gave the Game Gear edition the score of 7, writing "...huge levels and good control. Fans of the Genesis version should take a look".Cheat: Cheat MenuPress [C, B, A, Start] four times at the Sega logo to display the cheat menu screen.Cheat: Cheat MenuTo enable cheat mode, at the Virgin logo, quickly press A, B, C, B, A, C, A, B, C, B, A, C, Start. Upon correct entry, it should say CHEAT MOVE ACTIVATED below the logo.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause game play and press A three times, B three times, C four times, B, and then A.Cheat: Cheat MenuPause the game and press B, C, B, A, B, B, C, B, A, and B.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Kr21yKOCvxY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4502</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586316-mick-and-mack-as-the-global-gladiators</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/global-gladiators</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/global-gladiators/3030-3421/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4502-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4502-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90091-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90092-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-slimeworld.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90093-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-some-arches.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90094-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-falling.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90095-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-lost-a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90096-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-one-of.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90097-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-on-an-invisible.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90098-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-ronald.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90099-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-one-of.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/90100-mick-mack-as-the-global-gladiators-amiga-screenshot-this-dinosaur.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>