<Game>
	<Name>Goofy's Hysterical History Tour (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Goofy's Hysterical History Tour is a platformer developed by Imagineering and published by Absolute Entertainment for the Genesis.Story:Goofy takes up a job as the janitor of the Ludwig von Drake History Museum. Pete gets angry about this and tries to get Goofy fired. Pete goes on to take pieces of the museum exhibits and scatters them throughout different time periods. Goofy then sets out to recover and rebuild these exhibits before the museum opens the next morning.Gameplay:Players take control of Goofy as he sets out to recover the museum pieces. The game is a 2D sidescrolling platforming game which has players jumping, attacking enemies, and collecting items. Each level represents a different period in time such as the wild west or medieval times. Each level has a piece of a museum exhibit. Once all the pieces are collected Goofy will have to face Pete.Cheat: Level SelectAt the the main menu, highlight Options, hold A+B+C on the second controller, and press Start on the first controller. If done properly, you should see a new option, Exhibit, in the Options menu. Pressing Up on the second controller will cycle between its possible values.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4398</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586216-goofys-hysterical-history-tour</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/goofys-hysterical-history-tour</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/goofys-hysterical-history-tour/3030-30917/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4398-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/2/1/47521_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413241-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413242-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413243-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-level-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470342-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470343-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-the-help.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470344-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-an-enemy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470345-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-jumping.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470346-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-after-taking.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470347-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-some-enemies.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/470348-goofy-s-hysterical-history-tour-genesis-screenshot-these-blue.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4398.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Goofy's Hysterical History Tour, the player takes command of Goofy himself who gets his dream job as janitor at The Ludwig von Drake History Museum. However, his rival Pete is determined to get him fired and sabotages the exhibits and scatters pieces throughout various time periods. Armed with a new gadget, the Extend-O-Hand, Goofy must travel to the past and recover the pieces before the morning. The game is a platformer, where Goofy must travel through various stages ranging from Prehistoric times, Medieval times, Colonial America and the Wild West among many others, collecting items and power-ups and defeating Pete's henchmen using the Extend-O-Hand. After collecting all the pieces, Goofy then must face Pete himself.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0cbd1028-3c76-4f55-910c-85ca1804a1d5.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ebb909f1-2e28-4a9e-bbea-cb2dc066485c.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>