<Game>
	<Name>Gouketsuji Ichizoku (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Power Instinct (JP: Gouketuji Ichizoku, or "The Gouketuji Clan") is a competitive fighter game featuring eight different fighters, and one unplayable boss character. The fighters are competing to take control of the eponymous clan, who honors combat prowess above all else. The two daughters of the Clan, Otane and Oume, are favorites to win the tournament, but several other challengers across the globe intend to win the contest for their own reasons.Power Instinct is the first game in the Power Instinct series. It debuted in the Arcades in 1993 and was released on the SNES and Genesis the following year.CharactersOtane Goketsuji: An elderly woman and scion of the Gouketuji clan. Was threatened and abused endlessly by her older sister, Oume. Trained in secrecy for many years to surpass her, to the extent that she now has superhuman ability.Angela Belti: A physically imposing Italian strongwoman who follows her heart into dangerous situations.Annie Hamilton: A young English woman with a fondness for animals, which also feature in her specials.Keith Wayne: A cocky American martial artist and ex-gang member. He enters the tournament for his own pride, but falls in love with Annie and is determined to win her over.Reiji Oyama: An overly serious Japanese fighter who is focused purely on combat. Meant to be a parody of other overly serious martial arts, like Street Fighter 2's Ryu.Saizo Hattori: A mysterious ninja from Japan who keeps his face, and emotions, carefully hidden.Thin Nen: A Chinese Shaolin monk with mystical powers whose greed is insurmountable.White Buffalo: A Native American warrior who appreciates nature.Oume Goketsuji: An elderly woman, physically similar to Otane. Is considered one of the most powerful human beings alive due to her martial prowess and Goketsuji clan connections. Bitterly despises her younger sister Otane and is the final boss for the game (and is thus unplayable by any conventional means).Cheat: Play as Young OtaneMove the cursor to Story Mode at the title screen. While pressing Up, press Start and B at the same time. If the SEGA logo appears, the code has worked. Now, go to the character select screen on any mode, highlight Otane, and choose her while holding Start.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>ATLUS</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20332</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586391-power-instinct</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/power-instinct/3030-94/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20332-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/0/3/44403_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2756849-gouketuji+ichizoku+%28j%29_00000.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2756846-powerinstinct001.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2756844-power+instinct+%28u%29_00001.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2756843-power+instinct+%28u%29_00000.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/934466-powerinstinct.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13636/614181-power_instinct_00035.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13636/614180-power_instinct_00034.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13636/614178-power_instinct_00032.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13636/614177-power_instinct_00031.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13636/614175-power_instinct_00030.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Gouketsuji Ichizoku (豪血寺一族), called Power Instinct outside Japan, is a 1993 arcade fighting game by Atlus and the first in the long-running series of the same name. Atlus ported it to the Sega Mega Drive in 1994, releasing it exclusively in Japan. Plans were made to port the game to the US under the name Power Instinct, but were scrapped (however a US SNES version was released under this name). The game is a conventional fighter. A, B, and C each perform a different variation of each character's base attack, with various combinations possible with the D-pad.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2767437-cdfe-4dbb-a0ab-8acec7a80b16.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b86bf0fa-fa76-47df-ba8f-3ccfd70fbb06.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d267e82-54e2-4198-8c89-aad01b1d7c9f.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30f74a56-5c27-429d-b78e-d67c62f5d5c9.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>