<Game>
	<Name>Haunting Starring Polterguy (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:  The Haunting: Starring Polterguy is an action/simulation game that was originally released for the Sega Genesis in 1993. In it players take control of  Polterguy, a smart-ass, undead teenager who has nothing better to do than scare the crap out of the people.The object of the game is to scare the Sardini family by haunting different objects (which the game refers to as "fright 'ems") throughout their home. To haunt something Polterguy simply jumps into the object. Once an item is haunted it will cause an effect that will terrify anyone who is in the room. For example, if you haunt a bear rug the bear head will start growling, haunt a pile of dishes and they'll go flying across the room. Each time a family member encounters one of these hauntings they will get more and more scared until they can't take it anymore and run out of the house. Once all of the family members are scared out of their home they will move to a new house where you start the whole process over again.Being a ghost, Polterguy doesn't have health, he has   ecto. Ecto is a substance that Polterguy needs if he wants to stay in the real world and his supply of it is constantly depleting. After scaring a member of the family they will drop a puddle of ecto that will help to restore your supply. The amount of ecto in your possession can also be lowered if the family dog (the only character in the game that can see you) barks at you, or if Polterguy is attacked by other, malevolent ghosts who appear in the later houses. These spirits appear to be in cahoots with the dog, who can summon them at will in the final house. If you run out of ecto you are sent to the Underworld.If sent to the Underworld Polterguy must make his way through a grueling dungeon maze to collect ecto so that he may return to the living world. These dungeons are filled with enemies such as bats and skulls which can harm or even kill Polterguy. If he makes it to the exit, Polterguy returns to the Sardini household to continue The Haunting.After scaring the Sardinis from their fourth house Polterguy must defeat a final boss, a monstrous creature which is the true form of the family dog, to finish the game.The Sardini Family:  The Sardini Family   consists of five seperate characters, each with their own distinct personalities. Vito Sardini is the Father of the family; an uptight Italian businessman with a skeptical approach to the supernatural. Though this attitude clearly changes once Polterguy gets all up in his business.Flo Sardini is the Mother and matriarch of the household; a gruff, aggressive housewife who usually appears more angry at the fact that her house is being haunted than scared. Mimi Sardini is the Daughter of the family; a spoiled and arrogant girl eager to get one back on whoever is bothering her (including Polterguy). Tony Sardini is the Son of the family. All things considered, he is the most normal of all the personalities under the Sardini umbrella. He gets scared quite easily, and is angered a lot less than the other Sardinis. Last, and certainly not least, is The Family Dog, who is perhaps the most unique of all characters in the house for a few reasons. Firstly, he's the only living creature in the game that can detect Polterguy in the house, and second, his presence is reassuring to the Sardinis. When the dog barks at Polterguy, the ecto meter drops substantially, and the fear levels of any family members in the room go down. The dog is apparently a terrible monster in disguise, and when Polterguy scares the Sardinis out of town for good, it changes to its true form to get rid of Polterguy once and for all. Cheat: Level Skip &amp;amp; Extra PointsIn the first house, enter the grandfather clock in the dining room with A. While in the clock, press B, C, C, B. then A to exit the clock. You'll be in the second house with 15,000 more points. In the second house, enter the toilet in the Jacuzzi Room and press C, C, C, B. You'll be in the third house with 15,000 more points. In the third house, enter the garbage can in the garage. Press B, C, B, B and exit the garage. You'll be in the final house with 45,000 more points.Cheat: Level Skip &amp;amp; Extra PointsPause the game. Hold A, B, and C, then press Start. The music will be off. Do the code again to turn it back on.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_PPccBD4Rf0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>484</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586230-haunting-starring-polterguy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/haunting-starring-polterguy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/haunting-starring-polterguy/3030-15966/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/484-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/484-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/98299-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36582-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36583-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36584-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36585-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525591-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525592-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-all-members.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525593-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-the-game-has.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525594-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-easy-there.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525595-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-if-you-run.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/525596-haunting-starring-polterguy-genesis-screenshot-polterguy-serves.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BssRDAN.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/484.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Scare the evil, greedy Sardinis out of their houses by turning everyday household objects into something scary, funny or just plain gross. Or use your special spells to really send 'em shrieking. But you gotta hurry, 'cause your ectoplasm may run out! 16 megs of cool graphics, gross special effects and blood-curdling sounds. Unique 3/4 view perspective. Over 400 scary, funny or gross fright items, each causing something different to happen. Five special spells: Zom-B-Ize, Supr-Scare, Boo-Doo, Ecto-Xtra and Dog-Off. "Killer" dungeon with 12 different paths!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/400c5d63-9845-4c8f-9564-41448fdcf8b0.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7de6a91-406a-42f8-b572-b60bebd91dd3.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0640cf0-7fdc-43cd-82bc-61de4c24d83d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bacd8744-4b70-460a-bdfd-ff95428b6dbb.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>