<Game>
	<Name>Home Alone (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The blueprints screen allows you to booby trap the house in several different ways.In Home Alone the player takes on the role of Kevin McCallister, the protagonist of the movie. The goal of the game is to prevent the games villians, Harry and Marv, known collectively as The Wet Bandits, from looting the houses in the neighborhood. The player accomplishes this by causing &#8220;pain&#8221; to the burglars. This can be accomplished in one of two ways: booby traps and weapons. The first time Kevin enters each house he is given the chance to place traps. Kevin starts the game with a BB gun and can craft additional weapons, made from items found throughout the houses and the surrounding neighborhood. Weapons are made of three components: Platform; Operator; and Ammo.Kevin's just hanging out.There are several meters in the game. When outdoors, you are always provided with the Charge meter. As long as Kevin has &#8220;Charge&#8221;, he can boost the movement speed of his sled. This is especially useful when smashing through snowmen to reveal items or outrunning the bandit&#8217;s van to the next house. The Charge meter can be refilled by finding batteries. Indoors, you have three meters: Ammo; Loot; and Pain. Ammo depletes as Kevin uses his equipped weapon, and will automatically refill if he finds additional ammo for the equipped weapon. The Loot meter will fill as Harry and Marv empty the safes located around the house they currently occupy. Once the meter is filled, the house becomes &#8220;flooded&#8221;, in reference to the Wet Bandits calling card of clogging sinks and letting the water run. Pain will fill as the bandits encounter the traps that were previously laid out or as they are hit by Kevin&#8217;s weapons.If the bandits catch Kevin, they will hang him on a hook, but he can escape by wiggling in all directions. Some of the houses have a guard character that will attack any intruder, including Kevin.The game will end in a Game Over if the player in unsuccessful in stopping the Wet Bandits from &#8220;flooding&#8221; all of the houses. If the player is able to fend the Bandits off for the twenty minute time limit they will win the game.The game does have a higher difficulty that will unlock new items and weapons to be crafted.ItemsHome Alone features a weapon crafting system that lets you combine items you find around the neighborhood .Tire &#8211; Can be dropped indoors to help reach higher areasPepperBlow DryerBallBalloonsCoalsSnowballsRubber BandWireCanGlueMagnetCrossbowScoopTrapsTorchIceTarToysMarblesCheat: Freeze a BanditIn the Old House, go upstairs and stand in the bathtub. Wait until Marv or Harry comes and let them jump onto the tub, then quickly shoot them. Exit the tub and whoever you hit will start walking into the wall and will not move unless you touch them or leave the house. You can also get both in there if timed correctly.Cheat: Old House AtticAt the Old House, go to the top floor and into the bedroom, all the way on the right. Jump onto the bed, and place a tire. Jump on the tire to bounce Kevin onto the ledge. Place another tire and jump onto it to bounce Kevin into the attic. Up here are multiple items and the Wet Bandits cannot get up here. Watch out because like on the regular floors, Kevin can make holes in the roof and fall through.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>FF7cHSeTcvo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>487</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586236-home-alone</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/home-alone_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/home-alone/3030-50880/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2783599-8475908822-4225_.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/487-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/63345-home-alone-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159755-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159756-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-main-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159757-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-game-start.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159758-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-on-the-road.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159759-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-sliding-over-ice.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159764-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-entered-the-mansion.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159767-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-laying-traps.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159765-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-just-inside.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159769-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-falling-on-one-of-the-traps.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159766-home-alone-genesis-screenshot-weaponry.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/487-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QWZlPi9.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/487.png</clearlogo1>
</game>