<Game>
	<Name>Hua Mu Lan - Mulan (China) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>Hua Mu Lan: Mulan is an unlicensed action game by some unknown developer for the Sega Mega Drive made some unknown year. It is based on either the Chinese legend of Hua Mulan or the 1998 Disney film of the same name &#8212; which it steals art from, giving us a potential earliest release date. Some of its music is stolen from another unlicensed game, Chuanpu's 1996 Ya Se Chuan Shuo; whether or not the rest is also stolen has yet to be determined.Interestingly enough, the game has a story screen... in Chinese, English, Spanish, Portugese, and Arabic. The stories appear to be identical: during the Tang Dynasty, the Hun warlord Tan-Yu led his soldiers to seize the dynasty, and Tang conscripts all men to fight the oncoming forces. Hua Mulan, not wanting to see her old father fight, goes in to fight for him.The game is a typical platformer. B attacks and C jumps.</plot>
	<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	<thegamesdb_id>20499</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20499-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<Notes>Hua Mu Lan: Mulan is an unlicensed action game by some unknown developer for the Sega Mega Drive made some unknown year. It is based on either the Chinese legend of Hua Mulan or the 1998 Disney film of the same name — which it steals art from, giving us a potential earliest release date. Some of its music is stolen from another unlicensed game, Chuanpu's 1996 Ya Se Chuan Shuo; whether or not the rest is also stolen has yet to be determined. Interestingly enough, the game has a story screen... in Chinese, English, Spanish, Portugese, and Arabic. The stories appear to be identical: during the Tang Dynasty, the Hun warlord Tan-Yu led his soldiers to seize the dynasty, and Tang conscripts all men to fight the oncoming forces. Hua Mulan, not wanting to see her old father fight, goes in to fight for him. The game is a typical platformer. B attacks and C jumps.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d4127e6-18fb-4f2c-a31c-e0a4f57fac56.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8af69d1-33d2-4a8a-a04e-80a9a45bdb57.png</clearlogo1>
	<Developer>台灣三協資訊股份有限公司</Developer>
	<Publisher>X-Boy</Publisher>
</game>