<Game>
	<Name>Hurricanes (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Featuring in a children's TV cartoon, The Hurricanes are the most revered team in the World Soccer League. The Gorgons are desperate to beat them in a key match - so desperate that they have made it hard for the team to even get to the stadium. Taking control of one of their star players, you must trek through the jungle, mines and a temple to get them to the stadium on time.Soccer Kid seems like a logical game to 'influence' a license of a show about brilliant football players. Arc Developments agreed. The gameplay thus has a football used as a weapon against encroaching foes. There are ropes to move across, precise jumps to time, and traps to avoid.In The Hurricanes the ball sticks closely to the player's foot, even while he is jumping. It is only released when purposefully kicked, and replaced if it hits something or is lost. It can be flicked up while you are off the ground.The levels move from left to right but on several different vertical levels, and there is often more than 1 possible path, in a manner similar to Global Gladiators. Power-up tokens can be collected and traded in. Losing one of your 5 lives takes you back tot he last restart point - losing one of your continues takes you to the start of the world.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>EC - Early Childhood</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>KFgE8JARW14</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>17363</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586240-hurricanes</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/hurricanes</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hurricanes/3030-6810/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/17363-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/7/8/47578_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172084-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-copyright.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172086-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172087-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172088-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-club-crest.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172089-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-this-is-the-story-of-the-hurricanes.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172090-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-does-gianfranco-zola-play-for.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172091-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-what-we-can-expect-to-face.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172092-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-notice-the-token-woman-and-token.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172093-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-game-start.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172163-hurricanes-genesis-screenshot-ready-to-take-out-the-elephant.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/oU0zl0k.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Hurricanes is a 1994 platformer for various systems, including the Sega Mega Drive and Sega Game Gear, by U.S. Gold based on DiC's Hurricanes cartoon. The MD and GG versions were only released in Europe (a SNES port developed by Probe was released in the US). Each version has different levels. Instead of being a soccer simulator, the game is a platformer similar to Marko's Magic Football: you play as one of the players on the fictional Hurricanes football team as they use their football to destroy enemies through various platforming levels.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a02df86e-28ce-4fe0-a1bb-1879e112d417.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/feb428a4-b34e-4c97-8ea2-0b86a1aea4a9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold</Publisher>
</game>