<Game>
	<Name>Izzy's Quest for the Olympic Rings (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Izzy's Quest for the Olympic Rings is the official game of the mascot of the 1996 Olympic Games in Atlanta. As the name suggests, Izzy must find the five Olympic rings, hidden by the guardians so that Izzy does not take them to his world.The game plays a lot like Mario games; to eliminate an opponent Izzy must jump over his head. There are two jumps available, the ball jump suitable for height and the hurdle jump, suitable for distance. Both allow Izzy to clear an enemy, but the second harms  him.If Izzy is hit, then he must find three medals, or at the next hit he loses a life. There are some extra objects, like Olympic torches, and eggs that hatch either objects for bonus points, trampolines or  morph points to reach otherwise inaccessible areas or traps. Izzy can also morph into a glider, a baseball player, an archer or a rocket, among others, to overcome some sections of the levels.Graphics and sound remain faithful to the cartoony origins of the mascot.Cheat: Cheat CodesPress pause and enter one the following codes for the desired affect:Cheat: Cheat CodesWhen the title screen has finished loading (Start and Options text is displayed), enter this code: B, down, down, C, A, B, B.  If entered correctly, the hidden menu will instantly appear.Cheat: Level SelectIn the first stage, shortly after the second checkpoint is a hanging vine next to a stone platform.  Stand on the left edge of the stone platform, do a long jump (down + C), and aim for the tree canopy directly above the vine.  Keep holding C, and as you reach the height of the jump, begin holding A as well.  Continue to hold C + A while the invisible cannon rockets you through a hidden shortcut.  After the trip through the shortcut is complete, release the buttons and proceed to lose all your lives to get a Game Over.  Once back at the title screen, open Options and a level select is now available at the bottom.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4457</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/915992-izzys-quest-for-the-olympic-rings</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/izzys-quest-for-the-olympic-rings</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/izzys-quest-for-the-olympic-rings/3030-13750/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4457-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/0/1/50801_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149447-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149449-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149448-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-animations.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149450-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-giving.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149451-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-first.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149452-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-izzy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149453-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-three.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149454-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-izzy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149455-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-losing.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/149456-izzy-s-quest-for-the-olympic-rings-genesis-screenshot-finishing.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4457.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Izzy's Quest for the Olympic Rings is the official game of the mascot of the 1996 Olympic Games in Atlanta. As the name suggests, Izzy must find the five Olympic rings, hidden by the guardians so that Izzy does not take them to his world. The game plays a lot like Mario games; to eliminate an opponent Izzy must jump over his head. There are two jumps available, the ball jump suitable for height and the hurdle jump, suitable for distance. Both allow Izzy to clear an enemy, but the second harms him.If Izzy is hit, then he must find three medals, or at the next hit he loses a life. There are some extra objects, like Olympic torches, and eggs that hatch either objects for bonus points, trampolines or morph points to reach otherwise inaccessible areas or traps. Izzy can also morph into a glider, a baseball player, an archer or a rocket, among others, to overcome some sections of the levels.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7c2ec3b-8420-4377-81c4-b9ed3d6c3acd.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6dd8e7c9-be41-4463-b169-5614f2095048.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5a65c64-5790-4bea-815e-11ac229a8483.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold</Publisher>
</game>