<Game>
	<Name>James Pond II - Codename - Robocod (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:James Pond 2: Codename RoboCod is the second game in the James Pond series, which is also known as Super James Pond. It features the piscine special agent in a new mission at the North Pole. Unlike its free-form predecessor, James Pond 2 is a far more traditional side-scrolling platformer.The game was originally released on the Commodore Amiga, Atari ST and the Sega Genesis in 1991. They were followed with ports to the Amiga CD32, C64, Game Boy, Game Gear, Sega Master System and the Super Nintendo. It has recently received additional graphically enhanced ports for the Nintendo DS, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Network.There have been multiple publishers for the game. The SNES port alone has three: Victor Interactive Software published the game in Japan, American Softworks in the US and Ocean Software in Europe. EA, US Gold and others have published the game on other systems.Gameplay:James Pond 2: Codename Robocod is a side-scrolling platformer which is very similar in feel and gameplay to the early Super Mario Bros. games. The player takes on the role of James Pond; a walking fish with body armor who must free all of the Penguins and Toys that the evil Dr. Maybe has captured. In addition to the more traditional elements of platforming, the player has the ability to extend James' body vertically in order to reach platforms and items. He also has access to a number of vehicles throughout the game, such as cars, biplanes and a flying bath.Trivia:The UK version of the game contains one of the earliest known forms of in-game product placements with the Penguins in the game advertising the "Penguin" chocolate bar by McVities.The SNES version of the game was called Super James Pond in North America, whereas in other regions it was called Super James Pond 2.The Playstation, Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS versions of the game are re-makes rather than ports, with changes to music, level design and art, they are generally considered to be inferior games.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly's Mike Weigand revealed little in his short review of the SNES version of the game other than his review score of 5 out of ten. He wrote, "...James's ability to make himself tall is quite interesting, but that is really the only special thing about him". He suggested that fans of the franchise may prefer Aquatic Games.Cheat: Cheat MenuAt the title screen, hold A+C+Down+Left. Release the buttons after the screen goes black.Cheat: InvincibilityAt the hub level (the building), run right and stretch up onto a roof.  There are five objects a hammer, an apple, earth (a globe), a cake and a tap.  Collect them in the following order. Cake, Hammer, Earth, Apple, Tap. That spells C.H.E.A.T and James will become invincible for ten minutes.  YOu can do this everytime you return to the hub level. Cheat: InvincibilityEnable the Invincibility code first. Then pause game play and press A button 4 times. The game will resume at the exit. Note: Enabling this code may result in an impossible situation that may require a reset.  Cheat: InvincibilityTo refill your power meter, spell out the word ''power'' by picking up these items in the following order: penguin, oil can, wine glass, Earth and racket.Cheat: Invincibility Go to the far right end of level One, climb the tower on the roof, and walk to the left through the wall.Cheat: InvincibilityAt the sports level, spell out the word ''lives'' by picking up these items in this order: lips, ice cream, violin, Earth, snowman.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>IlfV9tKzW4M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2267</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586251-james-pond-ii-codename-robocod</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/james-pond-2-codename-robocod</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/james-pond-2-codename-robocod/3030-397/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2364821-snes_superjamespond.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2267-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79964-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180982-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-title-japanese.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40075-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40076-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40077-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-the-house.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40078-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-dropping-inside.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40079-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-side-scrolling.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40080-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-a-level-with.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40081-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-pond-can-hang.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40082-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-creme-cake.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40083-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-genesis-screenshot-upside-down.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/oUUD4pZ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2267.png</clearlogo1>
</game>