<Game>
	<Name>James Pond II (Japan, Korea)</Name>
	<plot>The sinister Dr. Maybe is back and only our slickest Special Agent, James Pond, can stop him. Special Agent Finnius Frog can help you get to those hard to reach places with his powerful jumping abilities. Explore more than 100 levels of outrageous fun! Win using an ocean of FI5H gadgets: suction boots, the fruit gun, X-ray specs, a thruster unit, spring boots and a clever fruit suit disguise. Use a special FI5H rocket pack to defeat Dr. Maybe! Fry over 40 different enemies under Dr. Maybe's control and avoid Maybe's mounted guns and missile launchers!Cheat: Level SelectEnter red cheese, yellow mouse, green cat, blue dog as a password, return to the main menu, highlight options, hold left+B, and press start.Cheat: Level SelectAt the main menu, highlight option, hold Left+B, and press start.Cheat: Infinite Rocket FuelAfter entering the usual cheat password - Red Cheese, Yellow Mouse, Green Cat, Blue Dog, add a Red Rocket for Infinite Rocket Fuel.Cheat: Cheat ModeAt the password screen, enter the following symbols: Red Cheese, Yellow Mouse, Green Cat, then Blue Dog. After that, add in any of these behind those symbols:  Red Fish for Invincibility  Red Book to have All Areas Unlocked  Red Star to start with five energy Red Skull to start with one energy and one life Red Teacup to have All Cheese Mines destroyed  Red Cupcake to have the gun always start with Homing Cupcakes Red Dog to always have the X-Ray Specs Then, leave the password screen by selecting the door icon, and start the game. Cheat: Cheat ModeDestroy all the cheese mines and stiltonium  machines to get the good ending.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Millenium Interactive</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>DMS0iWgAuQU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2267</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586250-james-pond-3-operation-starfish</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2267-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2267-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/5/gfs_46744_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/c/5/gfs_46744_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/5/gfs_46744_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/8/gfs_46744_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2267-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2267.png</clearlogo1>
</game>