<Game>
	<Name>James 'Buster' Douglas Knockout Boxing (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Featuring the short-lived heavyweight boxing champ of the world in 1990, James "Buster" Douglas, Knockout Boxing was a side-profile perspective boxing game for the Sega Genesis.  The game contained both instant action matches, as well as an in-depth (for the time) career mode, where players would build up their their newly created pugilist from palooka to world champion.  Using combinations of jabs, hooks, and uppercuts, the player navigates his boxer around the ring, seeking the knockout blow.  In between matches, player-created boxers improved their skills in four categories (hand speed, hitting power, stamina, defense) by selecting various training regimens available. Knockout Boxing climaxes with the player taking on Buster Douglas for the heavyweight championship.  As a part of the career mode, player-created boxers' skills would degrade over time, making late-career bouts difficult when facing the new fighters coming up just as the player had.  The player's career concludes with his retirement after 30 matches.Trivia:By inputting "THEBEAST" as the name of a player-created boxer, the player would be rewarded with a fully maxed-out fighter with green skin bearing a strong resemblance to The Incredible Hulk.Cheat: Sound TestTo enable the sound test, Press Start on the first player controller and choose either a 1 or 2 player game. Then, on controller 2, press C and Start at the same time.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4460</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586249-james-buster-douglas-knockout-boxing</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/james-buster-douglas-knockout-boxing/3030-5261/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4460-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14034/441233-buster_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/5/d/gfs_38921_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/8/d/gfs_38921_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/3/d/gfs_38921_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/f/6/gfs_88415_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/c/0/gfs_38921_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/1/0/gfs_38921_2_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/b/gfs_88415_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/b/gfs_88415_2_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/0/b/gfs_88415_2_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/b/gfs_88415_2_4.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4460.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Final Blow is an action game based around the sport of boxing. You can play the fighters in a sequence of knock-out competitions, (the computer versions also include a round-robin league). Rounds last one minute, with a short break in between them. As in the real sport, your aim is to knock your opponent down for 10 seconds, by gradually weakening him with a series of punches. You can block punches, to avoid them inflicting damage onto you. The ring is of a limited size, so players can be cornered, although the referee will intervene to break the boxers up if they become entangled in a stalemate position.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52c581bc-3273-4b6a-b4a3-641a696f5e09.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5697070d-d500-4d80-ba98-2c1731b0a8a1.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c8ebde4-3d1f-4f32-9a3a-c21a72ea2f07.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cb222eb-ff68-4f85-aeca-1372db961e3f.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/19fed109-2512-487f-9f8d-347034d15682.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>