<Game>
	<Name>Jammit (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jammit is a 1994 street basketball game from GTE Vantage Inc., where one player can enter a street basketball tournament, or two players can square off in a game of one-on-one. The game has three playable characters: Chill, Roxy (Jammit's lone female character) and Slade. The unselected characters serve as opponents.The single-player mode consists of a series of one-on-one hoops battles, involving $100, $200 or $300 wagers on each game. A combination of victories and earnings will unlock the game of Cutthroat; a victory in Cutthroat will prompt a game versus the game's boss (The Judge) at his home court (The Palace).Jammit is one of only a handful of games to feature an in-game Bass Boost option so that players can "turn on the bass back beat for the most happenin' music effects", according to the game's manual.Jammit also features a trash talk toggle; players can choose to play the game with no trash talk, some trash talk, or lots of trash talk.Gameplay:Jammit features a number of different play variations:One on One - First to 21, fouls enforced, losers' outs.Sweat - First to 21, fouls not enforced, winners' outs.2 Hot - First to 21, fouls enforced, losers' outs, and double points for shots made from the moving "X".Poison - First to 21, fouls enforced, losers' outs, and if a player scores 20 points (Poison), it is reduced to 13.Slams Only - First to 21, fouls not enforced, winners' outs, and only slam dunks count towards players' scores.In 2 It - First to 21, fouls enforced, winners' outs, and only shots made from the two moving "X"s count; a shot made when both moving "X"s overlap results in double points.Frenzy - First to 10, fouls not enforced, each player has a ball, and only shots made from the two moving "X"s count; a shot made when both moving "X"s overlap results in double points.Cutthroat - First to 21, fouls not enforced, winners' outs, two players against one, "Poison"-style rules where a score of 20 or 13 is reduced by ten points, and up to three free throws after a field goal.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1993</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586253-jammit</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/jammit</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jammit/3030-8577/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/1993-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213618-jammit-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213619-jammit-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98984-jammit-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98969-jammit-genesis-screenshot-choices.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98970-jammit-genesis-screenshot-choosing-your-player.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98971-jammit-genesis-screenshot-lots-of-various-game-modes.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98972-jammit-genesis-screenshot-betting.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98973-jammit-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-game.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98974-jammit-genesis-screenshot-shot-attempt.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98975-jammit-genesis-screenshot-nice-shot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98976-jammit-genesis-screenshot-expressive-score.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98977-jammit-genesis-screenshot-choosing-a-court.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/1993.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>As the name implies, this is strictly a basketball game. It has a black-basketball theme (as seen in a lot of odd American movies) and has a myriad of game options (one on one, group etc.). Also, it has a betting option, but other than that it's your typical run-of-the-mill basketball game.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c937a69c-d253-4ccb-8a1d-9be084c8bd18.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b27c6913-124d-43b7-8a91-4e202622aff4.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>GTE Vantage</Publisher>
</game>