<Game>
	<Name>Jelly Boy (Europe) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Jelly Boy was one of those "lost" Platformers of the SNES-era. By this, I mean it was a game of exceptional quality that got lost within the many, many poorly designed 2D Platformers that plagued that console generation. Subsequently this game, like Plok or Skyblazer or any decent non-Mario-affiliated platformer, went largely unnoticed by the general gaming public on release.Jelly Boy puts in the control of a jelly baby with morphing powers, sort of like if A Boy and His Blob merged together in some ungodly ritual. His quest is to find various items inside a weird factory so that the elevator doorman will allow him to go up and meet the dude in charge. Awesome music, polished graphics, a whole bunch of detailed levels and worlds and a bizarre sense of humor brighten up an otherwise generic platformer.Hints:- Password -For the game ending enter...9YYP25 LVRYPR XQP935 9W69YPhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/file/582923/48718http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/code/582923.htmlCheat: Cheat PasswordsEnter the following passwords for the desired affect. If entered correctly, it will say CHEAT ACTIVATED, otherwise it will scramble your password.Cheat: Cheat PasswordsFinal - Ending</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>F80kmUzwPIE</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/582923-jelly-boy</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/3/0/318530_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/6/e/gfs_22789_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/b/e/gfs_22789_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/0/e/gfs_22789_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/1/e/gfs_22789_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/e/gfs_22789_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/7/e/gfs_22789_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/e/gfs_22789_1_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/3/gfs_22789_2_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Jelly Boy is an unreleased Sega Mega Drive platform game. It was developed by Probe Software with the aim of being published by Ocean Software in February 1995. Electronic Arts are also credited. Jelly Boy on the Mega Drive was almost complete when it was axed for unknown reasons. Development is presumed to have taken place around 1994/1995 - a Game Boy version saw a release in PAL territories in 1994, with a similar Super Nintendo version being released in early 1995. No versions of the game have ever been released outside of PAL regions. It is entirely unrelated to another Super Nintendo game, Jelly Boy 2 which also wound up being cancelled - Jelly Boy 2 is actually a sequel to the Super Nintendo game Jerry Boy, known as Smart Ball outside of Japan. It is unknown why Jelly Boy was cancelled. Review copies were sent to the gaming press and a fully playable prototype has since been dumped and released online.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>F80kmUzwPIE</VideoURL1>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99b335dc-cd4d-4e54-8678-68ebbb0357c2.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d1f8835-1416-482c-aeaa-cb44d7f7019f.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>Ocean Software</Publisher>
</game>