<Game>
	<Name>Joshua & the Battle of Jericho (USA) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>You, Joshua, must lead God's people into the Land of promise. But watch out! There are falling rocks, soldiers, battering rams, and elite forces that will try to block your every move. Sounds challenging? You bet! God has given you the power. Weapons like the horn of Jericho, God speed, power-ups, secret exits, and other armor will help you in your quest. Conquer the Canaanites, Amorites, and Hittites as you collect silver and gold, race through deadly mazes, and defeat the enemies of God. So grab your sword and shield and step into the battlefield. The challenge awaits you!Cheat: Level PasswordsAt the initial screen for level one, use the Control Pad up and down to change the letters to those of the password, left and right goes between columns. Press A on the fourth column enters the password.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Educational</genre>
	<Developer>Wisdom Tree, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20359</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586265-joshua-and-the-battle-of-jericho</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/joshua-the-battle-of-jericho</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/joshua-the-battle-of-jericho/3030-8222/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20359-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/174716-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/174562-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163657-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163658-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-the-story.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163659-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-level-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163660-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-i-have-completed.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163661-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-bible-trivia.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163662-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-i-got-2-bibles.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163663-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-level-2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163664-joshua-the-battle-of-jericho-genesis-screenshot-level-3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5822/534616-josh_nes_screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5822/534615-josh_gen_screen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Crystal Mines is a 1989 unlicensed puzzle game for the NES by Color Dreams. When they established Wisdom Tree, they repackaged the game twice: in 1991 as Exodus: Journey to the Promised Land and in 1992 as Joshua &amp; The Battle of Jericho, with Joshua labeled a sequel to Exodus. These two versions would be remade for the Sega Mega Drive in 1993 and 1994, respectively. Though the games do have a TMSS check, they will only do the $A14000 write if they detect the region of the console they are running on as US — therefore, the games will only boot on either any US Mega Drive or on any other Model 1 Mega Drive without TMSS (making that a partly useless form of region lockout). Gameplay of both versions is identical: you are the main character (Moses or Joshua, respectively) and you must collect all the bags with M on them (Joshua: coins with $ on them) scattered throughout each maze. A and C shoot; you can hold them down for rapidfire. Shooting destroys blockades and enemies. Once all the M bags are gathered, find the exit to move on to the next level. In between each level, you must answer a bunch of questions related to the story of the Bible of the game's theme; getting them wrong appears to be inconsequential to the outcome of the game (this needs investigation).</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed0a16ef-d378-41f1-bbc3-182f6361758e.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5334c8ba-83ed-4398-875a-535cb664de4e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Wisdom Tree</Publisher>
</game>