<Game>
	<Name>JuJu Densetsu ~ Toki - Going Ape Spit (World)</Name>
	<plot>Go Ape WIth Toki! Dr. Stark, the evil genetic engineer, kidnaps your girlfriend then turns you into an ape. You've got to find her before it's too late. Open your mouth and let it fly! Scorch Stark's weird hordes with fireballs and laser blasts. Slog through disgusting ooze bogs, explore lush jungles, jump boiling lava pits, and swim beneath sparkling seas. Go wild! Score a super simian success on your way through this fantastic adventure!Cheat: All weaponsTo have all weapons, at the title screen, when the title animation stops moving, press A, A, A, A, Up, Down, B. You should get a confirmation sound. When in-game, press pause and hold C + Up / Down to pick a weapon.Cheat: All weaponsOn the game's title screenCheat: All weaponsTo change the level, at the title screen, when the title animation stops moving, presss Left, C, Down, B, Right, A, Up, you should hear a confirmation sound. When in-game, press pause then hold B and press Left, Right, Up and Down to choose the stage you want to change to. You can also press B + Start in the pause menu to restart the current level.Cheat: Stage 8 - 3 level skipTo skip to stage 8 - 3, reset the game. Don't touch the controls and the game will play by itself, after about 10 minutes it will start playing stage 8 - 3, a very dark level, and the game will pause. When it does, unpause it and you will instantly die and it will say 'Player 1 Time out!' You will now restart on level 8 - 3.When starting from this glitch you will always be playing the default settings, even if you change them. Normal difficulty, 3 continues and 3 lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Santos</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>IVg4lR722Rk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>717</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586548-toki-going-ape-spit</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/toki-going-ape-spit/3030-9823/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/717-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/717-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/717-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235553-0063.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235552-0061.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235551-0053.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235550-0047.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235549-0046.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235548-0039.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235547-0038.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235546-0036.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/1235545-0035.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6FXpagd.jpg</banner1>
</game>