<Game>
	<Name>Jungle Book, The (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Get down to the bare necessities of life... and escort Mowgli through the jungle to the safety of the human village. Fight the boggle-eyed snake, Kaa, and defeat Shere Khan the hungry tiger in this exciting adventure based on Disney's classic! It'll drive you ape crazy!Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuOn the first level, make Mowgli run all the way to the right until you get to the briar patch.  When you see Mowgli recoil at the edge of the place, you know you're in the right spot.  Jump into the canyon and pause the game right before you're about to fall to your death.  While the game is paused, press B, A, Down, C, Right, A, B, Left, A, Right, Down, B, A, Left, Left, C, Up, Right, Left.  As soon as you do that, the screen will change to the Debug Menu, which features level select and a host of other options such as invincibility.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo start right next to Baloo the bear, pause the game and press B, A, Left, Up, Up.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo change the color of the screen, pause the game and press A, B, B, A, C, A, B, B.  Eventually you will get to the last color, which is blood red.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter one of the following button combinations while the game is paused to display hidden developer messages.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  A - B - B - A - A - B - B - A  Then when you un-pause the game you should have added 10 seconds to your timeCheat: Activate the Debug MenuDuring play, pause the game and enter the following code:UP - UP - DOWN - DOWN - LEFT - RIGHT - LEFT - RIGHT - B - AYou should hear Mowgli cheer, and then when you press the start button, you are automatically given restored health, 99 units of every weapon, and a compass.On Hard mode, you don't normally get a compass. Using the code on Hard mode, however, will give you the compass, making it easier for you to make your way through the stage.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo be transported to the boss King Louie, pause the game and then press Left, Up, A, Left, Up, A.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo go to the Witch Doctor Monkeys, pause the game and then press Right, A, Down, B, A, Down.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  Up - Up - Down - Down - Left - Right - Left - Right - B - A  Then when you un-pause the game your health should be refilledCheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  B - A - A - B - B - A - A - B - A - - B - B - A - A - B - B - A  Then when you unpause the game you should go to the next levelCheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  A - C - A - C - A - C - A - C - B - B - B - B  Then when you un-pause the game you will go to the last levelCheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo start the game right next to Kaa the snake, pause the game and then press C, A, A, B, C, A, A.Cheat: Activate the Debug MenuEnter the following code at the Pause Screen....  Left - A - Right - Down - B - A - Left - Left - C - Right - Up - Down  Then when you un-pause the game the screen will be upside-downCheat: Activate the Debug MenuTo see the game's ending, pause the game and press B, A, Down, C, A, Right, Left, A, Right, Down.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>9Jw8RG9mx2k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1578</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586267-disneys-the-jungle-book</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/disneys-the-jungle-book__</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/1578-3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/1578-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/114109-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/1578-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35826-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-bagheera-the-black.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35827-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-maugly.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35828-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-the-tiger-shere.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35829-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35830-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-level.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35831-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-the-options-menu.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35832-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-mission-is-clear.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35833-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-monkey-business.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35834-disney-s-the-jungle-book-genesis-screenshot-one-of-those-crystals.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/1578-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/25iCDyj.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/1578.png</clearlogo1>
</game>