<Game>
	<Name>Jungle Strike (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jungle Strike is the follow up to Desert Strike and continues the story started in Desert Strike. Players command a variety of aircraft and ground units in order to stop Ibn Kilbaba, the son of General Kilbaba from Desert Strike and Carlos Ortega, the drug lord, who threaten the United States with nuclear weapons.Gameplay:The game plays from an isometric perspective and is broken down into specific missions that need to be accomplished on each level. These range from attacking certain locations to defending objectives. Should any of the objectives result in a failure, the player must restart the level from the beginning. Before each level, players choose a co-pilot to help them, which gives the players semi-automatic to automatic fire on the machine guns. During the missions, fuel, ammunition, and armor all  factor into the gameplay. Story:Ibn Kilbaba, the son of General Kilbaba from Desert Strike, plots his revenge against the United States by allying himself with Carlos Ortega, the drug lord, and announces his domiance by dropping a nuke on an island somewhere in the Pacific. STRIKE quickly send their top agent to secure the President and the surrounding D.C. area against terrorist attack. After securing the President, STRIKE moves to nullify Kilbaba's nuclear capability and control of specific regions. Being pushed back to the mountains, Kilbaba and the Drug Lord put up a strong resistance in their fortress, but are captured and taken back to the United States. However, both are able to escape following an attack on the Capitol. In the end, Kilbaba's escape in a gasoline truck is cut short and the Drug Lord is presumed dead after attempting to flee in a bus. With both leaders out of commission and a nuclear crisis averted in Washington D.C., the world is once again safe from fanatical leaders.Cheat: 23 Lives PasswordsInput these codes to start with 23 lives, and all but one co-pilot (wild Bill).Cheat: Campaign PasswordsEnter the following code at the Password Screen....  Campaign 2: RL6GYKBX6GG Campaign 3: 9V6CR9WNMCZ Campaign 4: XTMDR9WNMCJ Campaign 5: VNPDTL6HDB6 Campaign 6: WSDWHFKB7SS Campaign 7: THGR7NS6MCJ Campaign 8: 7GRSD9WT7SS Campaign 9: N4SF3X7NLMS  Then you should go to your desired campaignCheat: Campaign PasswordsEnter one of the following passwords to use any co-pilot in the corresponding levelCheat: Campaign PasswordsTo start on any level with 10 lives: 1 Sub Attack: RXVWT74S6KB 2 Training Ground: 9WT7NL6MHBV 3 Night Strike: X7NL4SHPG94 4 Puloso City: VL4S6MGCZVH 5 Snow Fortress: W6JB9TL4SYW 6 River Raid: TMHPGCFDYN3 7 Mountains: 7PGCZJYK34X 8 Return Home: NCZJFD3BR67 Cheat: Campaign PasswordsInsert: NCZJFD3BR67Cheat: Campaign PasswordsEnter BXYTNMGCYDB at the password screen. This code will also make most co-pilots available to you.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>fdJ8XtuJBuU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>536</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586268-jungle-strike</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/jungle-strike</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jungle-strike/3030-2180/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/536-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/536-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28964-jungle-strike-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/536-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31114-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-developer-info.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31107-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/153725-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31108-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-intro-sequence-madman-ibn.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/129521-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/153740-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-select-your-co-pilot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31109-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-protect-washington-d-c-from.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31110-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-reful-at-the-gas-station.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31111-jungle-strike-genesis-screenshot-bust-up-the-terrorist-operation.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KUTsXc4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/536.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Some time after Operation Desert Strike, Ibn Kilbaba, son of Kilbaba S.R, threatens to annihilate America. After his father was killed, the people who were under his control, sent his son running off, along with his father's money and nuclear weapons program. Kilbaba, more ruthless than his father, longs for revenge of his father's death and decides to shed the blood of those who killed him, the Americans. Already armed, Kilbaba hires Carlos Ortega to help him set up his Nuclear Weapons program, deep in South America. Carlos Ortega, the world's most notorious druglord, also yearns to seek revenge. With his own private army, armed with the most hi-tech weapons, he's ready to fight America at all costs.  Because of this threat, you're hired again to battle these two characters, following their paths in the jungles of South America. Armed with the Commache, numerous other vehicles, and destructive weapons, you must take out their private army. Blow up the enemy with your hellfires, hydras, chain guns. Use the watercraft to launch mines at enemy ships. Pull off a drive-by on the enemy with guns on the side. Take out the evil duo and forever rid this threat.....in the jungle!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>fdJ8XtuJBuU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5256562e-a007-421d-adb8-37623235f81e.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fb66b9d-3238-4f7c-9718-10a76c52ef25.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39d993b9-f632-46f2-a9dd-3c7ff651d029.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/54cfa3a4-f044-4bac-b23b-451b5e297e7c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>