<Game>
	<Name>Juuouki (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Enter a time when men were warriors and Gods ruled the world. A time of good against evil, a place of danger. Summoned by Zeus to rescue Athena, you will infiltrate the Underworld with the power to transform into mythical creatures with supernatural strength. Level 1: Become a savage Werewolf and use teeth and nails to shred your enemies to pieces. Capture 3 of the elusive Spirit Balls and you'll be transformed into a ferocious, fireball throwing Werewolf. Levels 2 &amp; 3: Take flight as Weredragon and use fiery force to fry the followers of Neff. Creep across slippery crevasses inside a deep cavern as the crafty Werebear. Levels 4 &amp; 5: Stalk the gates of the Underworld fortress as a man-eating Weretiger, a predator with no pity. Inside the inner sanctum call on Golden Werewolf's might to demolish Neff the demon - forever!Cheat: CodesEnter on the title screen:Cheat: CodesIf you got a Game Over and the game restart, at the title screen hold the A button and press START. You will be able to start back at the level where you last play instead of the first level.Cheat: Beat the game completion scene after beating the gameWhen the credits are being displayed on the screen after you have beaten the game, you can control your character to kick away the credited names.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/8/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>jFiTLTSwAgw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>118</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586022-altered-beast</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/118-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/118-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/118-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/6/3/gfs_46700_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/8/f/gfs_51618_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/118-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/118-g.jpg</banner1>
	<banner2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/118-g2.jpg</banner2>
	<banner3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/118-g3.jpg</banner3>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/118.png</clearlogo1>
</game>