<Game>
	<Name>Ka-Ge-Ki - Fists of Steel (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Kei is an incredibly powerful Japanese boxer. One day the Boss of the evil Kageki gang sees him in action. Impressed by Kei's pugilistic skills, the Boss asks him to be his right hand man in his organization. Kei, honorable guy that he is, boldly refuses. The Boss swears that he will not be spurned. A few days later, Kei's brother is beaten within an inch of his life. Knowing who is behind this brutal assault, Kei vows revenge.Gameplay::As Kei you must fight nine Kageki gang members and four underlings in a series of one-on-one fights before confronting the Boss himself. Your opponents vary in skill and abilities. For example: Ashpit is slow but can slap really hard, and Lizard is a dirty fighter who attacks using sandbags. As a boxer, your offensive moves are limited to a jab (left punch), a super jab (right punch), and a straight (right punch). You can also duck and jump. The action takes place in a garage, a gym, a machine room, a former night club, a fitness club, and other locations inside a high-rise building. Unlike most fighting games, Kageki is designed for only one player.Controls:Start: PauseD-Pad: Move character in all directionsA Button: JumpB Button: Jab, super jabC Button: Straight punchB &amp; C simultaneously: DuckReviewer: Brett Alan Weisshttp://www.allgame.com/game.php?id=12552</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sage's Creation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4475</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586271-ka-ge-ki-fists-of-steel</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/kageki-fists-of-steel</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kageki-fists-of-steel/3030-13412/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/3/30086/1044853-genkagekifistsofsteel.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4475-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/c/7/gfs_3333_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/f/gfs_73024_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/f/gfs_73024_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/6/f/gfs_73024_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/7/f/gfs_73024_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/f/gfs_73024_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/f/gfs_73024_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/a/f/gfs_73024_1_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/9/2/gfs_73024_2_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/4/2/gfs_73024_2_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4475.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ka•Ge•Ki is a slightly-angled 3rd person beat-'em-up set around underground fighting matches a la Pit-Fighter in which you must take down every member of a notorious biker gang. Each match begins with a showdown with several weaker henchmen and then moves on to next of the 9 gang members, who must be KO'd 3 times before moving on to the next round. The game allows you to move your character in any direction, provided he doesn't leave the confines of the arena, and allows you to attack via mostly a combination of button presses that also trigger dodges and parries depending on the button pressed. Graphics are 2D with a unique super-deformed design (stocky bodies with gigantic heads).</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a892faf1-a6f8-4b27-bed6-ce518c670ae5.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/353e716b-13bd-460a-8f88-58248fb9f7e8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sage's Creation</Publisher>
</game>