<Game>
	<Name>Kid Chameleon (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kid Chameleon, released in 1992, was a platformer for the Genesis which is well-known for its difficulty and length. The game contains 103 levels, varying wildly in difficulty and size, although the player is free to choose his own path through the game. The game was re-released as a part of Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection (360/PS3).Story:The story is a throwaway plot, like most platformers at the time. A new game at the arcade can simulate reality; everything is all fine and dandy until one of the bosses, Heady Metal, begins somehow imprisoning those who lose within the game. Players control a sunglasses-wearing kid, who has been called upon to venture into the game and defeat him.Gameplay:The game is a platformer that includes the concept of masks - powerups which enable all sorts of powers. One of these forms is a knight who can climb and break blocks beneath him by jumping, another is a hoverboarder who can change the direction of gravity. The levels are organized in such a way that these are required to pass through the game, often incorporating two separate paths based on which mask the player is wearing. The game includes four bosses - each manifestations of Heady Metal.Cheat: Infinite Lives GlitchLose all your lives and in the last life, die and immediately press and hold start. If you did it correctly, the screen "resume play and give up" will appear. Choose "give up" and the number of lives disappears.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete Blue Lask Woods in under 20 seconds.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete any level without collecting any special items to get 5000 bonus points.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsComplete a stage without being hurt by an enemy to earn 5000 bonus points.Cheat: 10,000 bonus pointsAt the end of Blue lake woods there is a series of blocks just above the flag. Jump to the last one and then press down and right, jump and special together. You will be warped to Plethora, the last level.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>q0VMjLud9C0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2279</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586273-kid-chameleon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/kid-chameleon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kid-chameleon/3030-11175/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2279-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2279-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9XfkNXA.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/17522-kid-chameleon-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2279-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40172-kid-chameleon-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40173-kid-chameleon-genesis-screenshot-the-hero.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ZpRKuGy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2279.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A new virtual reality arcade game arrived in town and every kid played it. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary until kids began to disappear. The game's boss, Heady Metal, had freed himself from his scripted AI. He was using his new freedom to kidnap every kid who could not beat the game, which was all of them, until now. A boy named Casey who calls himself "Kid Chameleon" enters the game and must defeat every level, every boss and Heady Metal himself if he wants to save the others.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>YtcbZ23szcI</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fa78d50-a948-44d5-9a7a-86893d92c85d.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11acac63-65b7-4adc-b60b-0f19203d244c.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b01472c3-bc78-496a-b5d1-ecf4f668f966.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/565dcad4-9a8f-4ffa-88a5-8215964dd281.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9db654dc-19e4-4833-848e-43a329d14070.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f5d1305-d16e-462d-b6f8-fa4dea64db04.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bbd9236a-3387-482a-a9df-9d7d3668a556.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22c893aa-a599-4fc7-bc62-813226cf7b3f.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0494c0c8-fc8c-492e-ae16-6e183e057cba.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90e1a567-b003-4a75-a8a4-94decac84743.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb3a8779-e58c-4567-8711-13b0ea2cd139.jpg</snapshot16>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>