<Game>
	<Name>King of the Monsters 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Alien super monsters have returned and are trying to invade Earth again! Now, Super Geon, Atomic Guy, and Cyber Woo must fight to retain control of the planet. Each one has special attacks and powers. Take on monsters that have unique abilities never seen before, including fire breath, aerial spins, and radioactive blasts. Challenge a friend, or have him help you out in the two-player option. Battle your way through seven levels of intense action in KING OF THE MONSTERS 2.Gameplay::The sequel to King of the Monsters, King of the Monsters 2 features more monsters, more levels, and a new type of character, the minor fighter aliens, who pester you as you do battle. As in the first game, you control a monster and you fight other monsters one at a time using methods from various wrestling and fighting games. The colorful variety of monsters includes Super Geon, a Godzilla look-alike; Atomic Guy, an armor-plated scientist; Cyber Woo, a super robot built for war; Huge Frogger, a reptilian alien; Eifflelyte, a fierce mutant warrior; Claw Head, a crabby fusion of an assortment of creatures; Beetle Master, a super insectoid; Aqua Slug, a slimy sea creature; and Lavicus, a levitating alien maker. While fighting monsters, you'll also have to ward off heavily armed humans who are trying to regain control of the Earth. They come at you in submarines, tanks, and fighter planes. As you work your way through the game, you'll fight in exotic locations such as the Grand Canyon, Tokyo, the desert, and France. A two-player mode allows you and a friend to each pick a monster and go at it head-to-head. The first player to win two rounds wins the game.Controls:A Button: PunchB Button: KickC Button: JumpD-Pad:Move monsterStart Button: Pausehttp://www.jjgames.com/product/5970http://www.allgame.com/game.php?id=12217Cheat: Debug ModeAt the SEGA logo, on Controller 2 press Up, Down, Up, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right. You will hear a sound when entered correctly. In the debug menu you can view monster animations and sprites. You can only use MODE button on Controller 1 to escape. In options you have more time limit options.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	<Developer>Takara</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>6.6</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>t4ZUsy9PluQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4479</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563329-king-of-the-monsters-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/king-of-the-monsters-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/king-of-the-monsters/3030-4625/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4479-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4479-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528715-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528716-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528717-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-quite-a-variety.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528718-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-vs-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528719-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-let-the-destruction.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528720-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-heavy-hit.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528721-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-strange-creatures.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528722-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-yeah.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528723-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-i-can-only-say-shocking.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/528724-king-of-the-monsters-2-genesis-screenshot-won-by-time-out.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QirW0gm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4479.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>King of the Monsters 2 on the Sega Genesis is a slightly different game than the original Neo Geo version. While the original let you play one of three different monsters to go through side-scrolling beat'em-up stages and fight (non-playable) monster as boss enemies, the Genesis version was re-worked into a one-on-one fighter similar to the first King of the Monsters game.  Apart from Farmardy, all characters from the Neo Geo version are playable. To win, the player must defeat all other monsters and a clone of the played monster in a fight. The matches take place in areas built from the original levels, and feature destroyable landscapes and secondary enemies, both of which can be smashed to gain points and power-ups.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/02066a64-e29d-4d39-86d3-20e582e94963.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70f47461-7b3e-47d0-9456-d35ba91c1eb0.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Takara</Publisher>
</game>