<Game>
	<Name>Langrisser II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>"Langrisser II" is a sequel to  Warsong (whose original title is Langrisser). The events of the game take place several years after those described in "Warsong". Gone is the benevolent kingdom of Baltia, and a new power has risen - the Rayguard Empire, led by Emperor Bernhart and his four generals. Recently, Bernhart ordered his army to attack the neighboring countries, obviously searching for something. This "something" might be none else but a legendary evil sword, that makes the one who wields undefeated. It is up to the noble knight Elwin and his friends to stop the Emperor!"Langrisser II" is a strategy RPG. The army is divided into soldier units and generals, who fight alone and who are usually stronger than a whole unit. Before the scenario begins, you must hire soldiers, buy weapons and items, etc. During the battle, if you come into contact with an enemy unit, an automatic battle sequence occurs. You can also cast healing spells on your units or offensive spells to hurt the enemy.The major difference between "Langrisser II" and its "remake",  Der Langrisser for SNES, is the absence of branching storyline in Genesis release.Cheat: Control Everyone and have limitless movesDuring battle: up left up right A left down B down right A B down right ACheat: Control Everyone and have limitless movesAt the load screen of the game. Highlight the save you want to play and press left, right, start, c.Cheat: Control Everyone and have limitless movesIn the screen where you see the hire troops, shop, etc. options... Press A, B, A, B, up, down, left, right, start, B. Now go to shop and you would get some pretty rare equipment. You have to buy them though.Cheat: Control Everyone and have limitless movesThis cheat is for unlocking the real secret shop in addition to the "Secret Shop Cheat". In the screen where you see the hire troops, shop, etc. options... Press B, Start, right, left, down, up, B, A, B, A, up, down, left, right, Start. Now go to shop and you will get all the items in the game, including items that you normally cannot get!! Of course, save your money to buy them.Cheat: Accessing the Sound Test MenuIn any battle screen, go to coordinates (1,1) and hold down B. If you are having trouble finding (1,1), the top left is (0,0). A screen should pop up. Use the up and down directionals to scroll through the sound and music selections.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>NCS Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>20730</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/564392-langrisser-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/langrisser-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/langrisser-ii/3030-11343/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20730-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20730-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86411-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-map-overview.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86412-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86413-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86414-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-introducing-the-characters.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86415-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-beautiful-view.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86416-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-story-background-before-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86417-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-your-main-character.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86418-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-preparations-before-battle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86419-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-area-map.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86420-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-options-before-the-actual.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/poxKSmi.jpg</banner1>
</game>