<Game>
	<Name>Langrisser (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The Dalsis Empire has laid seige upon the Castle of Baltia to seize the legendary sword WARSONG. In a desperate attempt, King Alfador sends his only son, Prince Garett, into the countryside, away from impending death. Now Garett must rally his allies from across the kingdom, and lead their valiant armies in a battle against the Empire to retrieve the sacred sword! But, time is running short! Command troops and choose your mission commanders. Unite with loyal allies and charge into campaigns that forge the destiny of a realm. Between you and the path to victory lie dangerous rogues, the steel of Dalsis, and a confrontation in the ultimate showdown against evil!Cheat: All Items (Japanese Version)When recruiting soldiers or equipping items Hold Up-Left + A + B and Garett must be highlighted as well. All items will be available except for warsong. Note: You lose all of your cash by doing this.Cheat: All Items (Japanese Version)To access the scenerio select: -Zoom the map out -Move the cursor to the top left corner -Move the cursor down one space and to the right one space -Press and hold the B Button until the Scenerio Select appears NOTE:  If you warp to a scenerio where a character first appeared, you may lose all expirence for that character.Cheat: All Items (Japanese Version)-Zoom the map in -Move the cursor to the top left corner  -Move the cursor down one space and to the right one space  -Press and hold the B Button until the Sound Test appears Cheat: Level-up exploitAfter stage 4 (Ambush in the forest), use the "stage select" cheat to return to stage 4. Mina will replace Sabra in your party, but will still spawn in as an NPC later. As the "party" Mina levels up to level 10, the NPC Mina will be promoted to the next class, and "party" Mina will remain a level 9 cleric. Level up "Party" Mina again, and NPC Mina will be promoted again. When the stage ends, Sabra will rejoin you, and NPC Mina (now Saint or higher) will replace Cleric Mina in your party.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/4/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>NCS</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>2m6pbTP5M7A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20729</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586591-warsong</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/langrisser-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/langrisser-ii/3030-11343/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20729-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20729-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86411-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-map-overview.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86412-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86413-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86414-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-introducing-the-characters.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86415-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-beautiful-view.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86416-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-story-background-before-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86417-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-your-main-character.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86418-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-preparations-before-battle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86419-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-area-map.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86420-langrisser-ii-genesis-screenshot-options-before-the-actual.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FRImKLl.jpg</banner1>
</game>