<Game>
	<Name>Light Crusader (Korea) (En,Ko)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Light Crusader is an         isometric        dungeon crawling RPG adventure, developed by the much loved game developer,       Treasure. The majority game takes place in a six floored dungeon where the player must solve a plethora of challenging skill based puzzles, as well as the traditional riddle. The majority of the puzzles are a case of frustrating      trial and error, involving movable explosives and     spike pits, as well as time control. The puzzles can be reset if gone wrong, however, by leaving and re-entering the room, thus the trial and error.On the combat side, it's the usual    hack and slash affair, the player can buy or find more powerful weapons and armor to make things easier, but also use and combine one of four magic types, earth, air,   water and fire. The player can combine all of these with each other to find some interesting unique spells, but use sparingly, as magic is limited, and is most useful during  boss fights.Cheat: Test, Test2 and Debug ModeTEST MODE: Pause the game, and go to MODE, uncheck all items, then press Down 8 times. This lets you view sprites, sound test, text messages amongst other things.TEST2 MODE: After activating TEST MODE above, pause the game and enter the new TEST option. Then press Up, A, Right, A, Left, A, Down, A. This lets you view rooms, errors, system info etc.DEBUG MODE: After activating TEST MODE and TEST2 MODE, kill yourself until you get Game Over. Now at the Load Select screen, there should be a new option called DEBUG. Here you can jump to any part of the game and use debug features in your inventory.Cheat: Secret RoomOn Level 4 there is a room where David and the zombies in the room appear to have doubles. This is apparently the reflection off of a giant mirror. After you kill the zombies jump up on a box in the center and push against the mirror. You will enter a secret room that contains a pendant.Cheat: Secret RoomOn B2, while on your way to the yellow orb, you'll come across a room with some rock columns and a corpse with a scroll piece next to it. In the next room will be 2 goblins and a floor button. Instead of going there straight away, stay in the room with the corpse and move over to the 2 columns attached to each other in the right corner of the room. Attacking the columns will reveal that these 2 are actually made of ice and will shatter. Behind is a switch that will open a secret passage to a room where you can pick up a device called 'Sextant'.Cheat: Secret RoomWith this item, you can always transport yourself instantly to any teleportation room you have discovered so far from any location in the game!</plot>
	<releasedate>26/5/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-I-V2cIU-6Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2575</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586289-light-crusader</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/light-crusader</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/light-crusader/3030-13920/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2370707-genesis_lightcrusader_cropped.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2575-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/58409-light-crusader-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2575-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86428-light-crusader-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86429-light-crusader-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5fyapR1.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2575.png</clearlogo1>
</game>