<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 95 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Madden NFL '95 is a football game for the 94/95 season of American Football presented by John Madden's virtual doppelganger. It is the The game takes the advancements of the prior games in the series and continues to tweak the rules, animations and graphics. The game features the NFL license and contains all 28 teams in the NFL at the time. The Genesis version also has the NFLPA license, allowing the use of real names for the athletes as well.The game would be followed by Madden NFL '96.Cheat: 1 Minute gameTo enable a 1 Minute game, press the following buttons in the Setup Menu: A, C, C, B, BCheat: 1 Minute gameAt the setup screenCheat: 1 Minute gameEnter the following code at the Game Set-Up screen....  B - A - C - A - C  You should now have the Jaguars and the PanthersCheat: Easily block puntsWhen the computer is forced to punt, select the "Punt Rush" formation, then take control of your fastest player and line him up on the left side of the field, just outside the leftmost offensive lineman. Remember to use the line of scrimmage glitch to your advantage and move him down a little bit.Cheat: Easily block puntsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll easily be able to use your superior speed to charge in and block the punt due to the running back in the punt formation never moving over to assist in the blocking scheme. It should be noted that while this glitch is practically identical to the glitch seen in Madden '94, you need to be much faster this time around to pull it off correctly.Cheat: Easily block puntsTake control of your fastest defender and line him up directly in between the offense's guard and center, but a hair above where they are standing. If done correctly, you will not be called offsides when the play begins. The line of scrimmage in Madden 95 is parallel to the feet of the offensive lineman as opposed to the ball, which is why you're able to line up so close to the offense in the first place.Cheat: Easily block puntsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll have plenty of time to blast your defender through the line untouched, and you'll be able to stop virtually every play in the game.Cheat: Easily block puntsAfter scoring a touchdown, you can use a very simple glitch to guarantee yourself an extra two points. Select Goal Line Halfback Lead Left.Cheat: Easily block puntsThe AI will always come out with their Field Goal block team and call an audible. Snap the ball while they're running around like idiots changing their defense around and you'll have a free path to the end zone every single time.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op, 1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>632</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/366824-madden-nfl-95</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/madden-nfl-95</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-95/3030-7715/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/632-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/632-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/85329-madden-nfl-95-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164307-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164308-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164309-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-select-if-you-will-be-home.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164310-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-welcome-to-dallas.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164311-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-call-it-in-the-air.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164312-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-choose.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164313-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-it-is-tails.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164314-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-the-kickoff.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164315-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-a-gain-of-6-yards.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/164316-madden-nfl-95-genesis-screenshot-select-your-play.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/632-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/632-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/632-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/632-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/632-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KwAXcos.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/632.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>John Madden's back in the 1995 version of Madden NFL. Play exhibition, Super Bowl, playoffs or full season with any of the 1994 teams or all Madden teams. This time around, you can select whether or not to include weather conditions, new player animations (high steppin', QB slides), a bigger field and over 100 injuries. Also includes windowless passing, all new Madden-designed strategies and team match-up that shows how your players stack up to the other team in their position.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04d5b6bf-4ae8-4e57-90bd-2df792140e92.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d93299f6-28ad-4717-a8a0-2d3a3bd3a9b1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8ebdd71-bca4-4c72-9fa9-8e18347d9f8f.png</clearlogo2>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>