<Game>
	<Name>Master of Weapon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The "7-Day War" -- seven days of nuclear winter -- have caused massive ecological shifts on Earth. The ground splits open, the oceans boil, and all living things on the planet begin to change...including humanity. Scientists create a computer to leave a seed and restore humanity, a computer known simply as "N", which is part of the top-secret Project Yukiwo. What is Project Yukiwo? None who know remain...Master of Weapon is a vertically-scrolling shooter based on the 1990 Taito arcade game. The player controls the fighter ship "N", shooting various biological enemies. Powerups are sparse, with only a handful of upgrades available from item pods. The player can fire in the air, as well as towards the ground to hit land-based enemies. There is also a special weapon which can be changed with powerups, but also takes time to recharge back to full stock. There are a total of nine "acts", and three difficulty settings.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/9/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20399</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570421-master-of-weapon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/master-of-weapon</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20399-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/7/8/31278_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416198-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416199-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416201-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-act-1-using-secondary.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416200-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-act-2-battling-a-large.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416202-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-act-3-fighting-enemies.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416203-master-of-weapon-genesis-screenshot-facing-the-act-3-boss.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/5/gfs_8867_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/8/gfs_8867_2_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Master of Weapon (マスターオブウエポン) is a 1989 arcade shoot-'em-up by Taito ported to the Sega Mega Drive exclusively in Japan in 1991. A shoots a gun and B drops bombs. These can be rapidfired, however enemies will only be killed by one or the other. C drops a bomb with a special weapon attached to it. Special weapons and upgrades are collected as powerups found in green capsules throughout each level; they last until you are killed. In Japan, Sega released a version of Tetris as a conversion kit for Master of Weapon cabinets for unknown reasons.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3821a8c-978f-475a-8e95-e8b8c1e00a58.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/477db255-9bda-4d00-9f0d-53894e9d3de6.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7189b20-a483-4760-8480-f21fc8784697.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/54daf5e5-7bd9-476f-8a23-c1974f9af416.jpg</snapshot10>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>