<Game>
	<Name>Mega Games 6 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Mega Games 6 is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Sega,which was released in Europe in 1995.Cheat: Cheat menu for Super Hang-OnAt the "new game password" screen, press A, B and C together. A cheat menu will appear and you can select the game difficulty, adjust the timer and change the language. There is also a sound test option on this menu.Cheat: Columns Extra Magic JewelsThere is a way to trick the game into giving you a second magic jewel. To do this you must set up the screen in a certain way. Have one row of the normal jewels stacked up almost to the top of the playfield. There must be vertical space for only two of the three jewels in the next block to come on the screen. Watch the "Next Block" preview box. When you see that the magic jewel block is next, get ready to quickly move it on top of your prepared stack. After the magic jewel eliminates the 'touching' color jewels, all of the remaining jewels will drop down as will the one magic jewel that was off the screen. This magic jewel will drop down and eliminate another group of colored jewels.Cheat: Start arcade mode. When you get to the character select screen, hold down+left and hit A+C+Start. Nothing really confirms the code except until you get game over. If you input it correctly, the next time you get Game Over, it should say you have 9 credits instead of 3.Cheat: Press Left,Left,B,B,B,C,C,C, Start at the title screen.Cheat: Go to the main menu. Hold down (A) + (B) + (C) + RIGHT on controller 2 while selecting Options on controller 1 (best if done with two people). You can now select how many lives you start with and which stage to start on.Cheat: When you get to the final boss playing 2-player mode, have one player choose ''yes'' and the other choose ''no''. You will be forced to duel against each other.Cheat: To get the Bad Ending, you must be playing as 2 players. You must also be in 2 player mode before Level 8 or else player 2 can't come into the game on Level 8. When both players reach Mr. X in the final room and he asks his question, make sure one player answers yes and the second answers no. Mr. X will have both players fight each other to the death. Have one player lose and choose game over. Afterwards, Mr. X will ask a second question. Be sure to answer NO to that question as well to trigger the final boss battle. When you beat him, you will become the Boss. NOTE: If you answer yes, you will again be shut back 2 levels and still not be ale to get the bad ending.Cheat: Enter the following code at the Title screen....  A + Start  Then a new menu should appear with many new optionsCheat: At the main menu, highlight Arcade Mode and enter the code.Cheat: These are passwords for SHO's career mode. You also start out with lots of money.Cheat: 5FZ09000300000 3FJJDO9D6FGDRLCheat: You can use this password in arcade mode to play with the best bike available.Cheat: If you want to earn 30,000 bonus points, make sure you end a level with eleven times more shurikens than the number of lives you have left.Cheat: One the second stage of level four,fire at the base of the first conveyer belt.A special Musashi symbol will appear.Hop onto the conveyor belt and let it carry you to the end.You lose a life but you gain 2.Keep doing this until you have as many lives as you want/need.Cheat: Go to the Options Screen, move the pointer up to Shurikins and set them to 00, wait about 30 seconds (without moving the pointer). You will here a sound and the ''00'' should change to an infinite symbol. Start the game and you will have unlimited Shurikins.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19841</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/929136-mega-games-6</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mega-games-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-games-3/3030-49565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/19841-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48517-mega-games-3-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48518-mega-games-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/214556-mega-games-3-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/3/6/gfs_68700_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/e/6/gfs_68700_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/5/6/gfs_68700_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/4/6/gfs_68700_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/f/6/gfs_68700_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/2/6/gfs_68700_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/9/6/gfs_68700_1_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/4/7/gfs_68700_1_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/f/7/gfs_68700_1_9.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Mega Games 6 is a compilation of six Sega Mega Drive games, distributed with some European Mega Drive II consoles in 1995. It is actually a combination of two previous pack-in games, Mega Games 1 and Mega Games 2. It would be followed by Mega Games 6 Vol. 2 and Mega Games 6 Vol. 3.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/58a7a5c7-403f-4de7-a262-e2d507f690e0.png</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>