<Game>
	<Name>Mega Games 6 Vol. 3 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This pack of six games was included with some Megadrive consoles and comprises the following titles:1. Alien Storm2. Columns3. Super Hang-On4. Super Monaco GP5. Super Thunder Blade6. World Cup Italia '90Cheat: Enter Options from the main menu.  Immediately press up, down, C, down, B, B, B, up, C.  Press Start to return to the main menu.  Enter Sound Test next.  Press Start to return to the main menu.  Enter Options again, and the Credits selection is now present.Cheat: Note:This glitch can only be used  while you are playing as the robot character scooter.Cheat: Whenever scooter loses all his energy and fis defeated use his special attack  move,  scooter will run back onto the screen and you will be able to control him again, despite having been killed earlier.Cheat: Columns Extra Magic JewelsThere is a way to trick the game into giving you a second magic jewel. To do this you must set up the screen in a certain way. Have one row of the normal jewels stacked up almost to the top of the playfield. There must be vertical space for only two of the three jewels in the next block to come on the screen. Watch the "Next Block" preview box. When you see that the magic jewel block is next, get ready to quickly move it on top of your prepared stack. After the magic jewel eliminates the 'touching' color jewels, all of the remaining jewels will drop down as will the one magic jewel that was off the screen. This magic jewel will drop down and eliminate another group of colored jewels.Cheat: Enter the following code at the Title screen....  A + Start  Then a new menu should appear with many new optionsCheat: At the main menu, highlight Arcade Mode and enter the code.Cheat: These are passwords for SHO's career mode. You also start out with lots of money.Cheat: 5FZ09000300000 3FJJDO9D6FGDRLCheat: You can use this password in arcade mode to play with the best bike available.Cheat: If you can't beat G. Ceara and want to stay in the Madonna team.Cheat: 8I00 6020 8C00 4000000O 0GD5 3627 BH4CFA89 E000 0000 004J0000 0000 2200 DFA7Cheat: In arcade mode, cross the finish line in the top three while pressing A,B and C. When your driver holds aloft his trophy, he holds up his head instead!Cheat: To start the game on Maddona Team enter the password below:  15G2 B3E4 DJ00 0000 000H 00J2 C4H7 658A B9DE FOH9 1000 0041 0000 0000 F200 71D7Cheat: Begin the game with hard difficulty.  Stay in the upper right or left corners and fire your weapon continuously in levels 1 through 3.Cheat: Enable the level select code and get a continue.  Highlight ''Option'' and hold A + B + C, and press Start.  A picture of a panda will appear on the ''Player'' selection to confirm the code.Cheat: Press these controller actions at the title screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Sports, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20501</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/929137-mega-games-6-vol-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mega-games-6-vol-3</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20501-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/9/4/69894_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/109447-mega-games-6-vol-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/236567-mega-games-6-vol-3-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-columns.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/236568-mega-games-6-vol-3-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-the-revenge.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/5/gfs_68701_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/a/5/gfs_68701_1_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/5/gfs_68701_1_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/0/5/gfs_68701_1_4.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/b/5/gfs_68701_1_5.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/6/5/gfs_68701_1_6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/d/5/gfs_68701_1_7.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/0/4/gfs_68701_1_8.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>