<Game>
	<Name>Mega Games 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Mega Games 2 is a games bundle that comprises the following games:1. Golden Axe2. Streets of Rage3. The Revenge of ShinobiThe bundle came with the MegaDrive II (and additionally Sonic the Hedgehog 2) and was not for sale separately.Cheat: Start arcade mode. When you get to the character select screen, hold down+left and hit A+C+Start. Nothing really confirms the code except until you get game over. If you input it correctly, the next time you get Game Over, it should say you have 9 credits instead of 3.Cheat: Press Left,Left,B,B,B,C,C,C, Start at the title screen.Cheat: Go to the main menu. Hold down (A) + (B) + (C) + RIGHT on controller 2 while selecting Options on controller 1 (best if done with two people). You can now select how many lives you start with and which stage to start on.Cheat: When you get to the final boss playing 2-player mode, have one player choose ''yes'' and the other choose ''no''. You will be forced to duel against each other.Cheat: To get the Bad Ending, you must be playing as 2 players. You must also be in 2 player mode before Level 8 or else player 2 can't come into the game on Level 8. When both players reach Mr. X in the final room and he asks his question, make sure one player answers yes and the second answers no. Mr. X will have both players fight each other to the death. Have one player lose and choose game over. Afterwards, Mr. X will ask a second question. Be sure to answer NO to that question as well to trigger the final boss battle. When you beat him, you will become the Boss. NOTE: If you answer yes, you will again be shut back 2 levels and still not be ale to get the bad ending.Cheat: If you want to earn 30,000 bonus points, make sure you end a level with eleven times more shurikens than the number of lives you have left.Cheat: One the second stage of level four,fire at the base of the first conveyer belt.A special Musashi symbol will appear.Hop onto the conveyor belt and let it carry you to the end.You lose a life but you gain 2.Keep doing this until you have as many lives as you want/need.Cheat: Go to the Options Screen, move the pointer up to Shurikins and set them to 00, wait about 30 seconds (without moving the pointer). You will here a sound and the ''00'' should change to an infinite symbol. Start the game and you will have unlimited Shurikins.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20401</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/927550-mega-games-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mega-games-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-games-2/3030-49564/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20401-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/30683-mega-games-2-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/30684-mega-games-2-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/143588-mega-games-2-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/e/b/gfs_66452_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/3/b/gfs_66452_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/8/b/gfs_66452_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/9/b/gfs_66452_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/7/6/gfs_66452_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/a/6/gfs_66452_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/0/6/gfs_66452_2_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/b/6/gfs_66452_2_5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/6/gfs_66452_2_6.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Mega Games 2 is a compilation released for the Sega Mega Drive only in Europe in 1993. It was the second of three similar compilations, and was only distributed with Sega Mega Drive II consoles. Games included: Golden Axe Streets of Rage The Revenge of Shinobi</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e3903d5-2a9f-4854-9ce3-82510e01ac55.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/183f45fd-9b69-4346-b5e2-c9d51741b43b.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>