<Game>
	<Name>Mega Games 3 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This pack of three was included with some Megadrive consoles and comprises the following games:1. Alien Storm2. Super Thunder Blade3. Super Monaco GPCheat: Enter Options from the main menu.  Immediately press up, down, C, down, B, B, B, up, C.  Press Start to return to the main menu.  Enter Sound Test next.  Press Start to return to the main menu.  Enter Options again, and the Credits selection is now present.Cheat: Note:This glitch can only be used  while you are playing as the robot character scooter.Cheat: Whenever scooter loses all his energy and fis defeated use his special attack  move,  scooter will run back onto the screen and you will be able to control him again, despite having been killed earlier.Cheat: If you can't beat G. Ceara and want to stay in the Madonna team.Cheat: 8I00 6020 8C00 4000000O 0GD5 3627 BH4CFA89 E000 0000 004J0000 0000 2200 DFA7Cheat: In arcade mode, cross the finish line in the top three while pressing A,B and C. When your driver holds aloft his trophy, he holds up his head instead!Cheat: To start the game on Maddona Team enter the password below:  15G2 B3E4 DJ00 0000 000H 00J2 C4H7 658A B9DE FOH9 1000 0041 0000 0000 F200 71D7Cheat: Begin the game with hard difficulty.  Stay in the upper right or left corners and fire your weapon continuously in levels 1 through 3.Cheat: Enable the level select code and get a continue.  Highlight ''Option'' and hold A + B + C, and press Start.  A picture of a panda will appear on the ''Player'' selection to confirm the code.Cheat: Press these controller actions at the title screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19854</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/927551-mega-games-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mega-games-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-games-3/3030-49565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/19854-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48517-mega-games-3-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48518-mega-games-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/214556-mega-games-3-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/8/gfs_66453_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/7/8/gfs_66453_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/8/gfs_66453_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/d/8/gfs_66453_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/6/8/gfs_66453_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/5/gfs_66453_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/e/5/gfs_66453_2_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/5/gfs_66453_2_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/4/5/gfs_66453_2_4.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Mega Games 3 is a compilation released for the Sega Mega Drive only in Europe in 1993. It was the last of three similar compilations, and was only distributed with Sega Mega Drive II consoles. Mega Games 3 contains 3 games: Alien Storm, Super Thunder Blade and Super Monaco.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/32a9b4cd-8f3d-44db-a88c-d344507dfa32.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e95d37cf-5c65-434b-80a9-212c111b2101.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>