<Game>
	<Name>Mega Games I (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Three times the action! SUPER HANG-ON: Countdown to excitement. Hang-On's back with two awesome races that are guaranteed to rev your engine. Whether you're racing against time as you beat a path across four continents, or battling guts with an opponent on a specially-designed circuit, there's no better thrill than the roar of your pipes as they beat a steady rhythm in sync with your fast-paced driving! WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP SOCCER: World Championship Soccer kicks off against an international set of stars for the prized World Championship. To win, you'll move swiftly through the qualifying rounds onto the final tournament where only the best are lined up for intense competition! COLUMNS: Drift back to ancient Phoenicia and challenge yourself with Columns, a game favored by middle eastern merchants. In this mesmerizing pastime, tinker with your riches to align glittering jewels across, down or diagonally.Cheat: Super Hang-On: Secret OptionsAt the Title Screen [I]simultaneosuly press A+Start[/I]. An options screen will appear. Cheat: Columns Extra Magic JewelsThere is a way to trick the game into giving you a second magic jewel. To do this you must set up the screen in a certain way. Have one row of the normal jewels stacked up almost to the top of the playfield. There must be vertical space for only two of the three jewels in the next block to come on the screen. Watch the "Next Block" preview box. When you see that the magic jewel block is next, get ready to quickly move it on top of your prepared stack. After the magic jewel eliminates the 'touching' color jewels, all of the remaining jewels will drop down as will the one magic jewel that was off the screen. This magic jewel will drop down and eliminate another group of colored jewels.Cheat: Enter the following code at the Title screen....  A + Start  Then a new menu should appear with many new optionsCheat: At the main menu, highlight Arcade Mode and enter the code.Cheat: These are passwords for SHO's career mode. You also start out with lots of money.Cheat: 5FZ09000300000 3FJJDO9D6FGDRLCheat: You can use this password in arcade mode to play with the best bike available.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/8/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19840</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586563-triple-score-3-games-in-1</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mega-games-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-games-3/3030-49565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/19840-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/19840-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48518-mega-games-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/214556-mega-games-3-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/2/e/gfs_66451_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/f/e/gfs_66451_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/4/e/gfs_66451_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/5/e/gfs_66451_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/e/gfs_66451_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/e/gfs_66451_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/e/gfs_66451_1_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/7/gfs_39076_2_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/7/7/gfs_39076_2_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/19840-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>