<Game>
	<Name>MegaPanel (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Megapanel is a tile-based puzzle game that plays like a mixture of Tetris Attack and a traditional sliding tile puzzle. Blocks rise from the bottom of a well, and the player must slide them around in order to create a row or column of three same-color blocks. This causes the group to clear, and potentially create chains from the blocks above falling. As the game continues, the number of blocks that must be cleared to continue as well as the speed at which the stack rises will both increase.The game includes three modes. First is training mode which explains the basics of the game. In this mode, a certain number of blocks must be cleared to complete the stage. Second is a "pin-up" mode for one player, where clearing blocks reveals parts of an image of a cute anime girl, the goal being to uncover the entire picture. Last is a two-player versus mode, where players compete to clear their blocks the fastest, and can send garbage blocks to their opponent and fill up their field. The game includes two difficulty settings, two versus modes, a sound test, and a unique mode that displays the entire game in sepia tone.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/11/1990</releasedate>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>bg886NnmMEg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20402</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/579861-mega-panel</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/megapanel</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20402-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/1/4/7/42147_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413264-megapanel-genesis-screenshot-title-menu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413265-megapanel-genesis-screenshot-exercise.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413266-megapanel-genesis-screenshot-pin-up.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/1/gfs_19535_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Megapanel (メガパネル) is a 1990 puzzle game developed and published by Namco (under their Namcot branding) for the Sega Mega Drive. Though initially released only in Japan, the game has made its way to the west through various compilations and consoles with built-in games. Megapanel is a sliding puzzle game similar to fifteen-tile puzzle games. The aim is to clear as many panels as possible before the pile reaches the top of the screen. In order to clear panels, three or more panels of the same color must be lined up together either vertically or horizontally. Use the D-pad to slide panels (each button indicates what direction to slide to, so the appropriate panel is automatically chosen) and A to bring the next row up immediately. A new life is awarded every 10000 points.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9edb72b-5a6d-4a43-bce2-6ebd847008ee.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3f2db65-936a-4455-ab19-5440124c7898.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a43d8ecc-51d0-4f42-8100-eda7277ae08f.jpg</snapshot5>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>