<Game>
	<Name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Differences Between VersionsWhile the Main ideas and premises are the same between the two versions, there are numerous differences between the them.There are certain characters that are only in one of the two versions (as shown below).In the Game Gear version, hitting the punch and kick simultaneously results in a separate move. This is not present is the Genesis version.In the Game Gear version, almost every character has a dive kick move executed by hitting the punch and kick buttons simultaneously while in the air. This is not present is the Genesis version.In the Game Gear Version, all special moves are executed with a Hadouken motion (Down, Down Toward, Toward), while the Genesis version also uses charge moves.In the story mode for the Game Gear version, the player fights a gambit of putty patrols followed by a brief battle with Goldar; Goldar disappears before his life bar can be fully drained. The level boss then appears. This format continues throughout the game. In the Genesis version, there are no enemies present before the stage boss.Characters:Red RangerBlue RangerYellow RangerMegazordDragonzord F. (Game Gear version only)GoldarKing Sphinx (Game Gear version only)Polluticorn (Game Gear version only)Black RangerPink RangerGreen RangerDragonzordputty patrol (Game Gear version only)Shell Shock (Game Gear version only)Nasty Knight (Game Gear version only)CyclopsisMinotaur (Genesis version only)Madam Woe (Genesis version only)Cheat: Play as the Evil Green Ranger in 2p BattlePress A+B+C repeatedly on the second player controller at the Banpresto Logo screen. If entered correctly, a voice will shout ''Power Rangers'' The ''Evil'' version of the Green Ranger should be selectable in the 2P Battle Mode.Cheat: Unlock Green RangerTo unlock Green Ranger, you need to defeat the Dragonzord enemy with Megazord in 1P Scenario Mode. After that, Green Ranger will be unlocked as a selectable character for the remainder of the game in 1P Scenario Mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>eWXvIf3w65A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4507</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/367025-mighty-morphin-power-rangers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mighty-morphin-power-rangers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mighty-morphin-power-rangers/3030-27004/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4507-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4507-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4507-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91917-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91918-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91919-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91920-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-starting-an-area.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91921-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-selecting-your.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91922-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-fighting-regular.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91923-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-nice-car.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91924-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-enemies-fall-from.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/91925-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-snes-screenshot-in-your-robotic.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4507-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/rykJQ6U.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers is a one-on-one competitive fighting game, featuring two different game modes: a Scenario Mode where the player competes against a series of CPU-controlled opponents, and a Battle Mode for two players. In the Scenario Mode, the matches consist of two segments: the player will fight against a regular-sized monster as one of the Rangers, and after the defeating the monster they will battle a giant version of it. Initially only the five original Rangers and the Megazord are available with the Green Ranger and Dragonzord being locked until they are defeated.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>jLnuNwpnpvI</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11bed074-0adf-42f6-9ba8-2c2f98344332.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a2b70f3-24f8-40f8-99a3-7fd5bea43202.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cc6ae03-abba-4131-bed1-df04ea522ec5.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f381cb8-1406-4221-963b-03504c4bae91.jpg</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>