<Game>
	<Name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Movie (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Long ago and far away, a legendary interdimensional being know as Zordon, came to the city of Angel Grove, to establish a vanguard in the never ending battle against evil. With the aid of his trusted assistant, Alpha 5, the noble master sought out six extraordinary teenagers and gave them power to transform into a superhuman fighting force. In time of great need, the young heroes could call upon colossal assault vehicles known as "Zords". While the identity of the six remain a guarded secret, their courageous exploits soon became the stuff of legend, earning them the title... The Mighty Morphin Power Rangers! This game plays much like the Mighty Morphin' Power Rangers game for the Super Nintendo. In other words, it is very nice. The graphics are great, good quality for the Genesis. The sounds and music are nice. Music from the TV Show is used when playing through different stages. The game-play is superb as well, fighting various enemies and giving you a good time to keep you going for a while. Give this a try if you're a fan of Power Rangers or platform games.Directions:In this game, you play through six stages of karate-kickin', mighty morphin' action! In the beginning, you can pick the ranger of your choice... There are six ones you can play as. Tommy the White Ranger, Rocky the Red Ranger, Adam the Black Ranger, Billy the Blue Ranger, Kimberly the Pink Ranger, and Aisha, the Yellow Ranger. In each stage, you must be able to make it through in the time given. You are usually encountered by a group of baddies, and you are given a starting time of 60 seconds. When you're able to beat them, the clock gives you more time. Power-ups might also be needed. In this case, Power Coins will be dropped when you defeat enemies. Each one gives a unique reward. There's also special attacks not listed in the Controls section. To run, tap the desired direction, left or right, twice. To attack when running, press B. When you hold B for a while, you can release it to unleash a more stronger attack. Press B repeatedly to do a combo attack.Controls:A Button: Special Move (WILL TAKE AWAY LIFE!)B Button: AttackC Button: JumpHints:- Power Coin Uses. -Mastodon Coin: Adds 1000 points to total Pterodactyl Coin: Restores one bar of Health Sabertooth Tiger Coin: Adds 3000 points Triceratops Coin: Restores half health bar Tyrannosaurus Coin: Adds 1 credit White Tiger Coin: Restores one full health barReviewer: LinkOfHyrulehttp://www.consoleclassix.com/genesis/mighty_morphin_power_rangers_the_movie.htmlCheat: Visual Selector, animation test and stage select menusOpen the Options screen, and follow these steps in order: set SE Test to C1, set Voice Test to E8, set Music Test to 82, and then press B.  You will enter the Visual Selector, a cutscene viewer.  For the next part of the cheat, exit the Visual Selector by pressing Start, and then repeat the whole process just described four more times.  After you've exited the Visual Selector for the fifth time, select Exit on the Options menu.  This opens up an animation test menu.  Finally, exit that screen and start a new game.  A menu appears where you can set the starting stage and toggle damage on and off.Cheat: Fight Lord ZedHit a large rock that is on Level 5 a few times in the background.  Then enter and get rid of the putties in that part. After coming out another rock will appear and hit it a few times and enter that rock to fight Lord Zed.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>6.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>g2hDnyAOYTM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4508</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586325-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie/3030-21927/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4508-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4508-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4508-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499533-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499534-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499531-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499532-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499535-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499536-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499552-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499539-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/499537-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-movie-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4508-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/rO7Yqgq.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers: The Movie is a side-scrolling beat-'em-up that can be played by up to two players, where the player can control both the Rangers themselves and their Zords (depending on the level). The game consists of six stages, with the first two stages and the final one covering events from the film, whereas Stage 3 to 5 are set before the events of the film and adapt key episodes from the TV show's second season (namely "White Light", "Ninja Encounter", and "Power Transfer"). The game's soundtrack, composed by Hikoshi Hashimoto, features hard rock arrangements of Ron Wasserman's original TV themes.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>oJdR5pgToo4</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a3a5bba-5bee-430b-a1e4-f55faac69829.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f0070404-c09b-4092-adb7-d956be11d097.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1dc80cd-b6aa-4b4f-bb4a-dcfdd8704e40.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f98a50dc-12ea-4dfc-bb6a-0565f7839d35.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/659f0dcd-7103-4b10-8f51-97c6fb4cb0ce.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>