<Game>
	<Name>Might and Magic - Gates to Another World (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Feel the Power, Experience the Magic! Lead your party of hand-picked adventurers into the enchanted Land of Varn. From dark, moldy caverns, through corridors of majestic castles, you'll travel in search of clues to unlock the Secret of the Inner Sanctum! Daring exploits of heroism and sorcery will keep you riveted for hours. Choose from a variety of extraordinary personalities, and lead them on an adventure of a lifetime. Over 250 weapons and items, and more than 92 mystical spells to use in your search for the Inner Sanctum. Battle legions of ravenous monsters as you travel through forests and islands shrouded in mystery!Cheat: Bypassing Mandaguals KeepThe road to the Luxus Palace is guarded by Mandagual's Keep, where you need to fight a fairly challenging battle to get past. You can bypass this fight completely by turning around and walking the road backwards; the keep only ''triggers'' if you face it. This allows you to get in the Luxus Palace far earlier and train up low level characters quickly on the Mystic Clowns in the back of the throne room. This same backwards walking trick can be used to bypass various other difficult encounters, but this is probably the most useful spot.Cheat: Bypassing Mandaguals KeepThere are a couple of places (dungeons) in the game where the casting of spells has been disabled to make the game harder to beat. You can overcome this limitation by sleeping. This is especially useful for using teleportation in these dungeons to get to a particular place in seconds!Cheat: Bypassing Mandaguals KeepThere's an in-game variable that stores every character's experience points. At some point, this variable maxes out and starts back from zero. If you can make a character have exactly the maximum number of experience points (one more and he/she would have zero), you can keep leveling up forever by continuously selecting to train at the training grounds (you may actually need a rapid-fire joypad if you intend to do this for a long time). If you do this long enough, you'll end up with super characters that have 65535 hit points, etc.Cheat: Bypassing Mandaguals KeepThe number of experience points you'll need to do that is way above anything you would ever reach by playing the game normally. The only possible way of earning that much experience is to use the "Loads of money and gems" trick many times, using all of that money to buy experience at:Lord Slayers Dungeon(Level 1) at 11,5Cheat: Extraordinary WeaponsSelect view character during the game, and when the 'view which?'prompt appears, push and hold in order, Left, A, C.  Release at the same time and you'll summon super characters who will trade you for extraordinary weapons.Cheat: Extraordinary WeaponsIf you want to obtain food 'magically,' go to the command screen , select 'share' and then pick 'food.' Repeat and you'll boost your supply considerably.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, First-Person</genre>
	<Developer>New World Computing</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4506</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586323-might-and-magic-gates-to-another-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world/3030-19917/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4506-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4506-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/202565-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93784-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93768-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93769-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93770-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93771-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93772-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93773-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93774-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93775-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93776-might-and-magic-ii-gates-to-another-world-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zPcBgYA.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Gates to Another World is the second installment in the Might and Magic series, and a sequel to Secret of the Inner Sanctum. Core gameplay is similar to it's predecessor, with the player creating a party of six characters and exploring vast first-person 3D environments, while fighting enemies in turn-based combat and leveling up. Unlike the first game, enemy encounters occur at set points rather than spawning randomly, though enemy type selection is still random.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7424c3f-10d6-49d0-828e-652f621c1dd7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/387bfcb5-82c3-4e11-83da-a535bfdecc00.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f57e2eba-70e6-4edb-b2d4-73f61a892fcd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>