<Game>
	<Name>Mike Ditka Power Football (USA, Europe) (Alt 1) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>He was one of the best tight ends the game has ever seen, he won a Super Bowl as the coach of the Chicago Bears, and now Mike Ditka has his own football game in the form of MIKE DITKA POWER FOOTBALL for the Sega Genesis. You'll find all kinds of unique and powerful options at your fingertips with this game: four different passing modes, the ability to make substitutions, 28 teams to choose from, and legendary referee Jim Tunney. As if that weren't enough, you'll also have more than 80 plays to choose from, and a unique behind-the-kicker perspective that makes field goal kicking a more integral part of the game. Strap on the pads and get ready for some hard-nosed football the way it should be played with MIKE DITKA POWER FOOTBALL.http://store.videogamecentral.com/genesisusedgames032.htmlCheat: Punt TrickOn offense, choose &amp;quot;punt&amp;quot; at the play selection screen; then, as your players are lining up on the field, press start and go to the &amp;quot;Substitutions&amp;quot; menu. Replace your punter with a fast player with a speed rating of 80 or more and return to the game. When the ball is snapped, head for the left or right sideline and take off running. When you get 15 or 20 yards past the line of scrimage, all of the players on the opposing team will freeze like ghostly statues. You can run all over the field and walk right through them.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Ballistic</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20503</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586326-mike-ditka-power-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mike-ditka-power-football/3030-29302/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/1201374-g07132o2s57.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/9/2/47792_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/e/d/gfs_38956_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/7/0/gfs_38956_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<Notes>Mike Ditka Power Football is an American football game for the Sega Mega Drive. It was released without a license from Sega.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/318022b0-2645-4922-a5b2-1f52d136f857.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26cab6cd-0e3d-46ec-8612-06b946f5ed2e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ballistic</Publisher>
</game>