<Game>
	<Name>Monster World IV (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Monster World IV was released in Japan on the Mega Drive in 1994 and is the final installment in the Wonder Boy spin-off Monster World series. Monster World IV was never released outside of Japan during the life of the Mega Drive/Genesis, however an English translation patch was released by DeJap Translations and Demiforce on May 29, 2001. Sega eventually created an official English version of Monster World IV which was released on the Wii's Virtual Console on May 10, 2012. The English version of Monster World IV was also included in the Sega Vintage Collection: Monster World on the Xbox 360 and it was released as a stand alone game on PSN.Story:Monster World IV follows the adventures of a young green haired girl named Asha. One day Asha is listening to the wind when she hears a faint call for help from the four elemental spirits, immediately she begins a journey to aid them. Along the way Asha befriends a genie and a small blue monster called Pepe as well as learns of an evil force approaching the kingdom of Rapadagna. Now with the help of her new friends Asha must rescue the four endangered spirits and save the kingdom from evil.Trivia:Jacket image drawn by Maki OhzoraOn June 22, 2012 the MW Official Fan page on Facebook posted an unreleased song from Monster World IV that was created for an "Ocean Stage" that was never made. The song, like the rest of the MW4 soundtrack, was composed by Jin Watanabe and a special jacket image was created for the song by the game's original artist Maki Ohzora.Monster World IV was originally going to let the player choose between playing as a boy or a girl. However the idea was scrapped due to space limitations on the game's ROM. The boy character was named Eusha, which means "brave man." The girl character eventually evolved into Asha and became the only playable character in the finished game.Cheat: Debug MenuWhen in-game, hold A + C + START on controller 2, then press B + START on controller 1. A new menu should appear, where you can teleport to any screen/room/door or change the characters position. Press B + START on controller 1 on the selection you want to go to. Press START to exit. Or hold A on controller 2, then press START on controller 1 to see the credits roll.Cheat: Lucky 7,777 GoldFarm gold from enemies, if your gold reaches 777, you will automatically be rewarded with an additional 7000 gold.Cheat: Debug ShopWhen you reach Rapadagna, do not talk to the sage at the entrance that lets you save. Go left and talk to one of the two guards to enter the castle courtyard. Head to the top right of the screen to enter a long, apparently empty screen with bushes in the background. Go towards the group of bushes on the right side of the screen; keep pressing up on the left side of them where they begin. You will eventually enter the Debug Shop, where you can buy debug equipment which is the same strength as Legendary equipment but with additional debug features. Every time you talk to him, he'll give you 9999 gold. Stock up on as much gold as you want, and then buy out all the equipment and he will disappear.Cheat: Debug ShopTo open the hidden sound test menu, at the title screen when New Game is selected. Press up, down, up, down, left, left, right, right. There is 53 sounds in total, press up/down to select them, and Start button to hear them.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>xnnrRfacZ6M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2649</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/581776-monster-world-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/monster-world-iv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/monster-world-iv/3030-3003/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2649-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2649-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/tAOfoRa.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/6jLjO4R.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/294589-monster-world-iv-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40417-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40418-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40419-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-asha-the-heroine.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40420-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-mission-clear.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40421-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-down-a-rope.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40422-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-treasure.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40423-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-peaceful-animals.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40424-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-and-citizens.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40425-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-fighting-green-things.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40426-monster-world-iv-genesis-screenshot-in-a-forest.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UCz9gFQ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2649.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Monster World IV is a sequel to Wonder Boy 5: Monster World 3. The player controls Asha, the green-haired girlfriend of Shion, the hero of the previous game. One day, Asha was standing on a cliff near her home village, and suddenly heard a mysterious voice calling for help. She decided to leave the village and to embark on an adventure to discover the identity of this mysterious person.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/328d1097-1f44-4875-a289-c122454d35a2.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26a1fbc7-9937-4e42-af01-48194879606f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>