<Game>
	<Name>Mugen Senshi Valis (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>What would you think if your best friend went on a date with the King of the Dark World - because she thought he was cute?! You'd think she'd been duped - and you'd be right. The fiendish King Rogles stands poised to conquer the other worlds of the universe: the Dream World of Queen Valia, and the Human World. Rogles and his five Dark Lords have taken the force of Yang from Queen Valia and sealed it into a Fantasm Jewel. Only a warrior with a heart perfectly balanced between Yin and Yang can wield the Sword of Valis against the encroaching darkness! Yuko, a young student from the Human World, is the chosen one - and you will control her. She is to become the greatest warrior in the universe, never suspecting that her most fearsome battle will not beagainst a Dark Lord, but against her closest friend from the Human World - the one she warned, 'Don't go out with him, he's the Dark...' But before she could finish, her friend ran off into The Darkness.Cheat: Max HP/MPThis requires 2 controllers. At any time during actual gameplay, Pause the game with controller 1, then, on controller 2, press right+a+b. This will fill up your HP/MP to the max. You can do this however many times you like. Alternative: If you don't have 2 controllers, you can still do the code. After pausing on controller 1, switch it with controller 2's port and then proceed with the rest of the code.Cheat: Max HP/MPAt the title screen, simultaneously press and hold A, B, C, Up, and Start. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Riot</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>zhfE-U47OqU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4707</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563353-valis</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4707-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4707-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/a/7/gfs_3428_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/7/7/gfs_3428_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/a/f/gfs_45487_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/7/f/gfs_45487_1_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/c/f/gfs_45487_1_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/d/f/gfs_45487_1_4.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/f/gfs_45487_1_5.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/f/gfs_45487_1_6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/0/f/gfs_45487_1_7.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/d/e/gfs_45487_1_8.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>