<Game>
	<Name>MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Our Solar System is under siege from Dire 51 - the MUSHA Team is the ONLY hope we've got! In the ultimate battle, you must blast the controlling Intellicomputer Dire 51 and regain control of the planets. You'll earn special weapons like the Vanishing Buster, Blazing Beam, and Defensive Detonator. Change weapons fast, or you'll be blown to oblivion. On the MUSHA Team, skill alone won't cut it. Your existence depends on quick reflexes and instincts! Do you have what it takes?Blazing features include 4 Mbit ROM, 7 levels, Weapon options and Selectable Firing Direction, Multiple Endings and 16-Bit Graphics!Cheat: Five Bonus LivesTo earn five bonus lives, pause the game and push Right, Down, Right, Down, Left, Up, Left, Up, B, C, A and than Start.Cheat: Five Bonus LivesTo fully power up your M.U.S.H.A., pause the game and push B, B, C, B, B, C, Up, Down and then A.Cheat: Five Bonus LivesWait for the SEGA logo to appear then press reset, repeat this 9 more times (for a total of 10 times). After the 10th time let the game go to the title screen, enter the Options menu while holding DOWN and LEFT on the control pad. You'll now be able to select rounds in the option mode.Cheat: Five Bonus LivesTo start with twenty options, pause the game then hit up, up, up, down, down, down, Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, C, C, B, A and then Start.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Compile</Developer>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>kDoac4j2E2g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4489</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586296-musha-metallic-uniframe-super-hybrid-armor</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4489-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4489-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/e/gfs_3458_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/f/3/gfs_57141_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/2/3/gfs_57141_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/9/3/gfs_57141_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/8/3/gfs_57141_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/3/3/gfs_57141_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/e/3/gfs_57141_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/5/3/gfs_57141_1_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/2/gfs_57141_1_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/2/gfs_57141_1_9.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/x7hIWoN.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4489.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Our Solar System is under siege from Dire 51 - the MUSHA Team is the only hope we've got! In the ultimate battle, you must blast the controlling intellicomputer Dire 51 and regain control of the planets. You'll earn special weapons like the Vanishing Buster, Blazing Beam, and Defensive Detonator. Change weapons fast, or you'll be blown to oblivion. Blazing features include 4 Mbit ROM, 7 levels, Weapon options and Selectable Firing Direction, Multiple Endings, and 16-bit graphics. On the MUSHA team, skill alone won't cut it, your existence depends on quick reflex and instinct! Do you have what it takes?</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70fb31e0-15f5-4e83-8c1f-476fcc3e97dc.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bef714b8-ecc6-494e-a7da-045b23550087.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d89b9698-9e7e-4691-958a-179c9014e133.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/68051848-f6ce-4418-a207-4d1f2e3dd041.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ef4294d-95d4-45a3-b758-f04c855f7a57.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0786fc46-9f0a-4ea3-8ca6-39f7b1755835.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/409c6849-d9d6-4fa4-b4b4-22ab708a8331.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39d49d2d-4167-416c-a1d9-19071041af80.png</snapshot15>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Seismic Software Inc.</Publisher>
</game>