<Game>
	<Name>NBA Live 96 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Game Boy Version The Game Boy version of NBA Live 96 was developed by    Tiertex Design Studios and published by   Black Pearl Software.  Modes   In NBA Live 96 on the Game Boy there are not only a few different modes  of play, but also a simulation or arcade style modifier for each one.  In addition to the game modes there is also the option to change the  difficulty and period length for each mode. The different modes of play  are:      Season Mode Screen Exhibition - Exhibition is a simple one on one game against the AI. Season - In season mode a team is first chosen. At that point the schedule window will come up and allows the player to play the current game, simulate the current game, make trades, or exit the season mode. Season mode plays much like it's console counterparts and features a password save system.Playoffs - Playoffs mode is basically a tournament mode where a team is chosen and the goal is to win the tournament.Enter Password - A password can be entered to continue progress made in the season mode.Cheat: Golf MinigameEnter in exhibition mode.  While highlighting a team, press UP until start new appears.  Press start and enter the code.  Press start again to startCheat: Secret PlayersEnter at player creation screen to unlock the character</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Co-Op, 1-4 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2251</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/366765-nba-live-96</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/nba-live-96</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-live-96/3030-20257/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2251-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2251-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/137260-nba-live-96-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40346-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40347-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40348-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-draft-there-are-two-new-teams.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40349-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-creating-a-player.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40350-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-playoff-standings.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40351-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-the-game-begins.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40352-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-introducing-the-players-no-close.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40353-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-wow-what-a-dunk.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40354-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-dramatic-situation.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/40355-nba-live-96-genesis-screenshot-three-pointer.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2251-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>New for NBA Live '96: New player animations - big blocks, tip-ins, tip-in slams, spin moves, crossover moves, two foot takeoff. New moves - one-on-one, spin dribble and crossover. Two new teams - the Vancouver Grizzlies and Toronto Raptors. Multi-Team Seasons for up to four players. Trade any player, any time. On-the-fly Playcalling, Animating Playbook and Shot Diagram screens for side-line strategies. All-Star game and the Draft for the ultimate NBA season realism.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a88244df-813d-46c7-b379-59ee298686c9.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6d32b84-0ded-424b-aa0b-6c0aff42955d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6ac41dd3-8cfb-49d8-bb77-4a0f6e55d1ec.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>