<Game>
	<Name>NCAA Final Four Basketball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>NCAA Final Four Basketball is a standard basketball-sim with a full NCAA license with 64 of the top Division 1-A teams including North Carolina, Florida State, Boston College, and Maryland to name a few.There are three modes of play to choose from: two Practice modes, one which shows the player the basic in's and outs of the game and another for free throw shooting, Exhibition and Tournament.  Along with these modes are the ability to change around options to play a game to the player's liking including changing the length of the game. A battery-backup lets the player save their games, stats and rosters.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Mindscape, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4523</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586342-ncaa-final-four-basketball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/ncaa-final-four-basketball</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4523-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/0/9/47809_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413300-ncaa-final-four-basketball-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413301-ncaa-final-four-basketball-genesis-screenshot-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413302-ncaa-final-four-basketball-genesis-screenshot-tip-off.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413303-ncaa-final-four-basketball-genesis-screenshot-shot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413304-ncaa-final-four-basketball-genesis-screenshot-free-throw.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/5/a/gfs_38970_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/c/7/gfs_38970_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5YtHJsK.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The first college basketball game for the Sega Genesis, NCAA Final Four Basketball features 64 NCAA Division I teams, five player support with the use of a multiplayer adapter, and three different play modes: Practice, Tournament and Exhibition. Exhibition is one game against any two teams of your choice, Practice Mode allows you to hone your skills without worrying about a pesky defense (it's just two players and the ball), and Tournament lets you pick one team with the goal of moving past the Regionals and into the Final Four. There's also a mode that involves practicing your three-point shooting skills, with a perspective just behind the player's head looking toward the basket.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/759fa8ca-1a4e-4f26-8b94-7919ff983190.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d16aed1f-8798-43f3-af1c-d7d555fad7d8.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Mindscape</Publisher>
</game>