<Game>
	<Name>New 3D Golf Simulation - Pebble Beach no Hatou (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Eighteen of the most dramatic and toughest holes in golf. Five exciting golfing options: Practice, Stroke Play, Skins Game, Match Play, and Tournament Play versus 48 top golfers. In-depth Golf features: Caddie Advice, Instant Replays, Complete Shot, Leader Board, and Hole Fly-bys.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>T&amp;E Soft</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>675</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586373-pebble-beach-golf-links</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/675-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/675-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/9/e/gfs_2183_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/0/3/gfs_2183_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/675.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>New 3D Golf Simulation: Pebble Beach no Hatou (ペブルビーチの波涛) is a 1992 golf game for the PC-98 by T&amp;E Soft in their New 3D Golf Simulation series which takes place at the Pebble Beach Golf Links golf course in California. T&amp;E Soft ported the game to the Sega Mega Drive in 1993 along with three other New 3D Golf Simulation games; however, unlike those three ports, this one did receive an international release under T&amp;E's equivalent True Golf Classics label as Pebble Beach Golf Links. It was later brought to the Sega Saturn; in Japan this version was called Pebble Beach Golf Links: Stadler ni Chousen (PEBBLE BEACH GOLF LINKS ～スタドラーに挑戦～). Despite being on a newer system, the game does not take particular advantage of the Saturn's features and continues to use the same rendering style as the entries on previous-generation machines. It does add an overhauled UI, more fluid player animations, and videos of professional golfer Craig Stadler (hence the Japanese name) giving suggestions before each hole.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>4</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d88416b5-7dc3-448c-a864-034f089be78f.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/718cd6eb-4aa6-4345-8571-0e7df4b13c25.jpg</snapshot3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>