<Game>
	<Name>NFL Quarterback Club 96 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The ultimate in football realism! All the teams! All the top quarterbacks! All the players that count! 80 yards of viewable field... send 'em deep! Drag tackles! Up and over dives! Want more realism? Buy a ticket! Control any NFL player on offense or defense. Perfect your gridiron skills in the exclusive Practice Mode. Over 800 plays including authentic QB signature plays! Build your own dream team with the custom player feature. Player, game, and full season stats... all the way to the super Bowl!Cheat: Lotsa codesTo enable these codes you must win the simulations. Once you've done that, turn on the Genesis and enter the desired code after the Sega screen appears but before the Acclaim screen appears.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op, 1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4529</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586344-nfl-quarterback-club-96</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/nfl-quarterback-club-96</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nfl-quarterback-club-96/3030-11504/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4529-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4529-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413319-nfl-quarterback-club-96-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413320-nfl-quarterback-club-96-genesis-screenshot-game-type.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413321-nfl-quarterback-club-96-genesis-screenshot-choose-play.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413322-nfl-quarterback-club-96-genesis-screenshot-quarterback.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413323-nfl-quarterback-club-96-genesis-screenshot-pass.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/8/c/gfs_49839_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/1/1/gfs_49839_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pkXi6Qg.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4529.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Popular NFL quarterbacks such as Troy Aikman, John Elway, Steve Young, Brett Favre and other NFL stars are featured in this officially licensed football simulation. You can play practice games or a full NFL season. You can skip the season and go straight to the Playoffs or match up the best of the best in Pro Bowl action. A Simulation Mode lets you participate in historical NFL situations, or you can customize your own unique game situations. In all there are more than 800 plays you can call, including authentic quarterback signature plays. All NFL teams are represented, and you can customize them any way you like, including switching players between teams. Other options and features include player substitutions, a no huddle offense, three different camera angles, penalties, three different clock speeds, weather conditions, player progress reports, replays and a pre-game show.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff30feb7-6699-4108-95ed-d867f2bf7620.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ec6031c-beee-4d4b-9549-b9fd939bd2a8.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88ff2986-8434-48db-974b-91f44fc424c5.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>