<Game>
	<Name>Ninja Gaiden (Japan) (Proto) [b]</Name>
	<plot>This version is an extremely loose translation of the original arcade game, and not a particularly good one. Like all side-scrolling beat-em-ups, it requires a lot of repetition and button-pounding in order to succeed.This one was actually news to me until very recently. It was never released in the U.S., but oddly enough, almost all of the in-game text is (extremely bad) English.The plot is completely different from the original NES game, and Ryu is a less likable character. He's been sent by his ninja master to America in order to hunt down a fellow ninja who has betrayed his clan and stolen the "Secret Scroll of Huma" (or Homa, depending on the given moment in the game).Not much of a plot, and not really much of a game. Much like the original arcade game, it gets tedious and boring rather quickly. The arcade game, however, had cool moves like the Phoenix Backflip and the ability to hang from overhead bars and swing. Ninja Gaiden for the Genesis offers no such respite from the tedium. The graphics are passable for the less-than-spectacular capabilities of the Genesis. There were several other games which had much better graphics and gameplay.This one probably stayed in Japan for a reason... worth a play or two if you can find it, but not worth any significant amount of money. If you're looking for a good beat-em-up on the Genesis, go get a Streets of Rage game. http://ninjagaiden.classicgaming.gamespy.com/ng-gen.html</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Unreleased</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>5bOONkDOYV8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18828</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/984767-ninja-gaiden</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/18828-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/18828-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18828-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18828-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/18828-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/c/9/gfs_153579_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/4/gfs_153579_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IBIzlWs.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sega even had a third project running, this time for the Mega Drive. Once again, the development was done by a third party. This time it seems to have been the mostly unknown developer called Opus, as in-game art and the sound engine used indicate. This game was never released, probably due to quality issues, but a beta copy was leaked and can be played on emulators nowadays. The game would have tried to build on the concept of the original arcade game, but feels to some degree more like a very bad approach to the Streets of Rage school of beat-em-ups. It is obvious that it either was in a rather early development stage, or Sega did right to pull the plug on this botched mess. The game features a lot of cut scenes, all of them in the finest Engrish. The chapter titles are in Japanese, though. The story doesn't make any sense, at least not in its presented state. Later in the game, you meet people you should know but don't, and about halfway through the game you get to know that your goal from the beginning was to rescue Ryu's kidnapped lady friend.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/858a3314-3ac8-4804-9abb-a573f2bf5dd8.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63b1d407-250c-4f1b-90c5-4c0c55154b33.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/657a23ab-6892-4702-9a89-2a7e561d8a2e.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6a7775e-ccdb-4f0b-887c-f4d56099aec7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<rating>2</rating>
</game>