<Game>
	<Name>Pac-Attack (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pac-Attack is a  Pac-Man spin-off, in the same vein as  Tetris and/or  Dr Mario. It is based somewhat on Namco's earlier game Cosmo Gang: The Puzzle, an Arcade and Super Famicom game released the previous year.Pac-Attack has been released on many different systems. The original version was released on the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis in late 1993, closely followed by the Game Boy and Game Gear versions. An enhanced port was released on the Philips CD-i with the name Pac-Panic. It has also been released in many Namco and Pac-Man compilations, and the SNES version was rereleased on the Wii's Virtual Console.Gameplay: Pac-Attack ScreenThe object of the game is to clear rows of blocks by getting them into straight lines; however, most of the falling puzzle pieces also have ghosts attached which take up valuable space where blocks could be stored. The solution to this problem is Pac-Man himself. Every once in a while a Pac-Man piece will fall, and all the ghosts on the board will turn blue. If the Pac-Man piece is situated in an area where he can easily catch any ghosts he will remove them from the grid.The game offers a standard "Normal Mode" in which the game plays out as described above, as well as a "Puzzle" mode in which the player is given a limited number of Pac-Man to eat the various ghosts.Critical ReceptionWhen the SNES version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly gave the review scores of 8,7,7,8 and 8 out of ten. Mike Weigand wrote, "No, don't laugh, just try it! This game looks like nothing but once you start playing you will not be able to stop! The three games are addictive, and the two-player competition will have you and a friend playing until you drop!".Cheat: Level PasswordsThis password will allow you to use a music test and some other options in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>MHFf7GWYh40</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>673</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586366-pac-attack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/pac-attack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-attack/3030-13943/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/673-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/673-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/113835-pac-attack-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166105-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166106-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166107-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-normal-mode-level-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469648-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-falling-blocks.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469649-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-ghosts-turn-blue-when-pac-man.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469650-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-pac-man-chomps-on-the-ghosts.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469651-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-ate-some-ghosts.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469653-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-game-over.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469654-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-records.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/469656-pac-attack-genesis-screenshot-password-screen-for-the-puzzle.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ps1FMr5.png</banner1>
	<Notes>On a Tetris-like board the player drops blocks consisting of Ghosts, Blocks, Pac-Men, and one Fairy (if your Fairy Meter is full) to the ground. The objective is to not let the blocks overflow, let Pac-Man eat the ghosts, and make lines to shorten the amount of blocks on the board. When Pac-Man eats a ghost, the Fairy Meter goes up. Once full, a fairy will eventually be dropped. Once the fairy comes to a stop by landing on anything, it waves its wand and every ghost in the eight lines below it will disappear, often resulting in numerous lines being completed and simplifying the board. Once the fairy disappears, the score bonus is given, and gameplay continues. Pac-Attack can also be played in 2-player mode. Player 1 must eat Blinky, while Player 2 must eat Sue, the purple ghost from Pac-Mania. As players eat ghosts and complete lines, they will drop ghosts on their opponent's board, messing up their board and bringing them closer to the top. This game can even be played in puzzle mode. The object of this mode is to smash all 100 stages. If you get a Game Over, all the regular blocks appear with red crosses on them, while Blinky and Sue over backwards laughing silently. However, you can try the level again.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f0166f3-f9b1-40d2-8104-3bef04c28cde.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d154498-432f-437f-89ec-f6d6727407dc.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd29fe8b-61a9-428c-951c-1b18324d7246.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a8b15c5-b11c-4589-b69e-2c15046fac93.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>