<Game>
	<Name>Pachinko Kuunyan (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Yokohama Pachi-Pachi Chinatown is an island where all the people love pachinko. One day, a mysterious evil panda decides he must have it, and steals it for himself, turning it into his own personal pachinko island, a place where anyone who enters can never leave. Chen is a man who loves pachinko, and one day he heads of to the famous pachinko parlors of Yokohama...and never returns. Fortune tells that very soon, the person who will stop the evils of this pachinko parlor will appear, and Chen's daughter, Ren, sets out on her 18th birthday for Yokohama, looking for her father.Pachinko Kuunyan is a pachinko RPG much like the Pachio-kun series. The player controls Ren as in a standard role-playing game, but rather than fighting battles, she can enter pachinko halls and play the machines. Each of the five cities has several pachinko halls, and Ren must empty out a certain number of machines before she can move on to the next city. If she runs out of balls, then the game is over.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Soft Vision International Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20417</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570403-pachinko-kuunyan</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/pachinko-kuunyan</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20417-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/5/5/31255_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421644-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421645-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-main-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421646-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-intro-before-game.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421647-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421648-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-starting-position.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/421649-pachinko-kuunyan-genesis-screenshot-talking-to-another-character.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/2/e/gfs_9937_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/3/gfs_9937_2_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Pachinko Kuunyan (パチンコクーニャン) is a 1992 pachinko game for the Sega Mega Drive by Soft Vision released exclusively in Japan. The game takes more of an adventure/RPG-type approach to presenting itself: you, as the main character, walk around in a top-view town containing both pachinko parlors (with machines you can go to and play) and other buildings.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cd6a278c-a773-4e86-a0e5-83ecd5c05f8b.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5502f4bb-8d40-4ba5-a2ab-f8c831bb40c6.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<Publisher>Soft Vision</Publisher>
</game>