<Game>
	<Name>Pele! (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Soccer, the most commonly played sport worldwide, has been brought to your living room via Pele for the Sega Genesis. Pele, the one-named soccer phenom on whom this game is named after, is widely considered the greatest of all time. You can play Pele alone or with a friend in exhibition matches or in a tournament. By yourself you can play in an 18-game season, or you can enter a practice mode, wherein you work on the fundamentals of the game.In the two-player mode, players must alternate playing one-player games until their two teams are matched up. There are forty teams, each of them represented by countries and cities from all around the globe. Features in this game that are also part of the sport of soccer itself include free kicks, penalty kicks, replays, roster substitutions, formation changes, goal kicks, throw ins, corner kicks, offsides, and game and team statistics.Trivia:Widely considered the greatest soccer player of all time, Pel? has scored more than 1,000 goals professionally.Controls:D-Pad: Move player, dribble.D-Pad + A Button: Scroll field, aim throw-ins, goal kicks, free kicks and corner kicks.D-Pad Left/Right: Curve ball left/right after a kick on offense.Start: Call time out.A Button: Chip ball, quick soft shot to goal, switch control to player nearest the ball on defense, switch player control while ball is in air.B Button: Pass to another player on offense, check player on defense, head the ball when ball is in air, throw-in pass.C Button: Bicycle kick when ball is in air, slide tackle, throw-in pass.C Button (tap): Punch out a low, hard kick.C Button (hold): Deliver a long, high kick.Reviewer: Brett Alan Weisshttp://www.allgame.com/game.php?id=14341</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>TbXc9PG7JRk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4552</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586374-pele</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/pel</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4552-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4552-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370148-pele-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370149-pele-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370150-pele-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370151-pele-genesis-screenshot-team-select.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370152-pele-genesis-screenshot-the-match-up.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370153-pele-genesis-screenshot-the-game-starts.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370154-pele-genesis-screenshot-running-with-the-ball.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370155-pele-genesis-screenshot-the-ball-is-kicked-at-the-goal.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370156-pele-genesis-screenshot-a-goal-is-scored.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/370157-pele-genesis-screenshot-celebrating-the-goal.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4552.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Pelé! is a soccer game that lets the player take control of soccer legend Edson Arantes do Nascimento (better known as Pelé, the games namesake). There are forty different international teams to choose from and the game has a two separate single player modes. In Practice the player chooses the teams and learns the basic fundamentals of the game. In Season, the player competes in an 18 game season in order to compete for the championship.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6dc7e37-b313-4f92-946a-e9e1e960c155.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7fca1e4f-bde4-463e-9910-ce6e536a8887.JPG</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f6c8b86-c56a-454d-bbd5-4e2eafc5016f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Accolade</Publisher>
</game>