<Game>
	<Name>Pink Goes to Hollywood (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pink Goes to Hollywood is a licensed platformer from Manley and Associates, which was published in Europe and the US by TecMagic and in Japan by Altron (where it was simply known as Pink Panther). The game follows the Pink Panther's adventures across numerous film sets in Hollywood, trying to find fame and fortune while eluding the tenacious Inspector Clouseau.The game was released on both the SNES and Genesis in late 1993. Critical ReceptionWhen the Genesis version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly gave the review scores of 7,7,7 and 7 out of ten. Danyon Carpenter wrote, "I was surprised by how good this game actually was. Although the character may not be the most modern around, Pink Panther still offers fans of side-scrolling action games some new surprises and a lot of technique. The idea of having movie sets for stages was cool and the music that goes with it is fitting. I would like to have seen more power-ups available, but as it stands, the game is decent".In the same issue of Electronic Gaming Monthly Mike Weigand reviewed the SNES version of the game giving it a 6 out of ten. He wrote, "The cool pink cat makes it to the home systems! However, you may be better off with the Genesis version of this one, because the SNES counterpart suffers from stiff control and unappealing levels".Curiously, as a part of the "Major Mike's Game Roundup" the review crew gave additional scores to the scores they had already given the Genesis version. Those scores are, 7,7,5 and 6 out of ten.Cheat: Cheat ModePress A and C on controller 1 and B on controller 2 immediately after you turn on your Genesis. You can now do any of the three cheats below.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>TecMagik Entertainment Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>vqxQ0nNjz2c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2489</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563335-pink-goes-to-hollywood</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/pink-goes-to-hollywood</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pink-goes-to-hollywood/3030-8302/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2489-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2489-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48038-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116883-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-main-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116885-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-main-game-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116886-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-pink-panther-flees.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116887-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-entering-the-first.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116888-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-avoiding-a-walking.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116889-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-hmm-i-thought-i.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116890-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-paparazzi-try-to.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116891-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-hello-there-fellow.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/496692-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-riding-a-flying.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/496693-pink-goes-to-hollywood-genesis-screenshot-this-onions-looks.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vwaBxar.png</banner1>
</game>