<Game>
	<Name>Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame (Europe) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Journey back to Persia in the swashbuckling sequel to he award winning Prince Of Persia. Prince of Persia 2 is alive with breathtakingly fluid animation and scenery so rich in colour and feeling it'll change you forever.- Life-like sword fighting, now against multiple opponents.- Journey through 5 exotic scenarios.- 15 treacherous new levels with even more traps and puzzles.- Stunning animations based on real life human modelsCheat: Level passwordsEnter the codes on the password screen to go to the level shown.</plot>
	<releasedate>Canceled </releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Microids</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>rJXP8HRowdA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>24135</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/665251-prince-of-persia-2-the-shadow-and-the-flame</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/24135-1.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/2/7/gfs_255846_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/f/7/gfs_255846_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/4/7/gfs_255846_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/5/7/gfs_255846_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/e/7/gfs_255846_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/3/7/gfs_255846_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/b/a/gfs_255846_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/6/a/gfs_255846_2_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/d/a/gfs_255846_2_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Prince of Persia 2: The Shadow and the Flame is the sequel to the 1989 hit Prince of Persia. Released for DOS computers in 1993, ports were made to the Apple Macintosh in 1994 and the Super Nintendo in 1995. A port to the Sega Mega Drive was planned for a 1996 release, but ultimately cancelled. Development of this port was handled by Microïds, and the game was to be published by Psygnosis. A prototype was dumped and released on 11 August 2006 by drx of Hidden-Palace.org, which dates back to 20 February 1995. Though more graphically accurate to the DOS original than the SNES port, it has poorer sound quality and various bugs. There is also less time to complete the game (75 minutes) and the HUD uses different colours.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/618f81bd-c651-442b-a0bc-a4881ff440ba.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d173d56f-8d39-4d21-bbf2-f29639bfdb70.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ccdeb77a-6be0-489b-b0cb-d58073a0d69c.png</snapshot11>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
</game>