<Game>
	<Name>Probotector (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Kickin' cyborg butt... That's what it's all about, dude. Jack into this game of genetic engineering gone bad. Real bad. It's five years after the mother of all wars ended - and things still aren't right. Your job is to fix it. The ever-popular Contra series makes its Sega Genesis debut with a pulse-pounding new storyline. At 16 megs, HARD CORPS pushes the technology to bring you over ten gut-wrenching levels with huge boss characters, great graphics and dynamic sound. Find high powered weapons such as the homing gun, crush gun, needle laser or mine setter. Do you think you can handle it? Trust me, you can't. You still here? Okay, then get ready for the fight of your life. Pick one of the four heroes and begin your search across many dark levels of doom. The ending changes, depending on the paths you choose - but every pass crosses boss characters that will blow you away. Literally!Cheat: Game Codes (Japanese version)Enter these at the main menuCheat: How to get the bad and best  endingGo though the game and don't go after dead eye joe, Fight to the end and not surrender, and when you get to the end of the 2nd to last level choose these:Cheat: Extra endingBefore battle with the zodiac boss, climb up the wall and talk to the weird guy. Agree, and you'll be in a hidden stage. Beat the stage for an extra ending with monkeys.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>-9YFtbCb3y0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6244</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563317-contra-hard-corps</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/6244-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/6244-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/9/gfs_45464_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/9/gfs_45464_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/b/9/gfs_45464_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/a/9/gfs_45464_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/9/gfs_45464_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/9/gfs_45464_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/7/9/gfs_45464_1_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/a/8/gfs_45464_1_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/1/8/gfs_45464_1_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/a/c/gfs_45464_1_10.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DYdTaQW.jpg</banner1>
</game>