<Game>
	<Name>Pulseman (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pulseman is a 2D platformer released exclusively for the Sega Mega Drive in 1994. It would later see a Europe and US release when it came to the Wii's Virtual Console in those territories in 2009. It is notable for being a pre-Pok&#233;mon release from studio Game Freak, and one of the few games they produced that wasn't released on a Nintendo console.The player controls the eponymous Pulseman: a superhero who is able to manipulate and take on the form of electricity. He can use this power to defeat enemies and traverse levels, zapping between nodes. His unique parentage, half human and half "C-Life" (a digital AI lifeform), means he can travel in and out of cyberspace, which makes up some of the game's stages.Cheat: Level SelectIn Sega logo, press (in joystick 2): A, B, C, C, B and A.Cheat: Level SelectAfter this, enter in Options and use the Map option.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>BtoBY2S2zzo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14961</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/580016-pulseman</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/pulseman</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pulseman/3030-3637/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/14961-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9287PLv.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/249162-pulseman-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/14961-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30578-pulseman-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30579-pulseman-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97878-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-strange-sega-logo.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97864-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-and-a-matching-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97865-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-nice-options-menu.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97866-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-the-hero.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97867-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-world-map.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97868-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-game-in-japan.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/97869-pulseman-genesis-screenshot-game-game-game.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Q2Q3Oxb.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The world is connected by a network of eight ultra computers and the self-conscious final computer "Saint Anne". In 1999, the young Doctor Yoshiyama has created an artificial intelligence in the ultra computer Amabilis in Japan, which became a "C-Life". He fell in love with the C-Life girl he had created, so he digitized himself on the computer to stay with her. Later, he combined his DNA with her program core, and their union resulted in the Half C-Life, half human boy called Pulseman. Pulseman's dual nature allows him to freely travel through the real world and cyberspace, and he can control electricity. In the year 2015, the mysterious Galaxy Gang led by Doc Waruyama starts a series of crimes across the world to conquer the galaxy. Pulseman uses his abilities to stop the evil ambition of Doc Waruyama.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0750458-be94-487d-9b61-587e1d8d59c0.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bb3eab9-e838-4ed1-9786-b91936e7c8ae.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>