<Game>
	<Name>Rainbow Islands Extra (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Rainbow Islands Extra is a conversion of the classic Taito coin-op Rainbow Islands. Included on the cartridge are conversions of both the original game and the reworked "Extra Version", in which the stages and bosses have been rearranged to be more challenging. As with the other versions, the game is set in the titular Rainbow Islands, where the two boys Bub and Bob (no longer small dragons as in Bubble Bobble) must free the islands from the evil monsters who have overrun them, by using the magical power of rainbows! In addition to both the Original and Extra modes, the game also includes three difficulty levels.Cheat: Start the game with virtually infinite livesIn the option menu, choose number of lives and select 0. Then you can start your game normally. When you died, instead of Game Over, you get a lot of extra lives like ??, ?! and other symbols in pair as your number of lives. However, it is not really unlimited. After you died a lot of times (about 400 times), your number of lives became 99, and when it reached 0, the game is over.</plot>
	<releasedate>5/10/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>FViHQf5v8Yo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20424</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/579725-rainbow-islands-extra</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/rainbow-islands-extra</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20424-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20424-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413595-rainbow-islands-extra-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413596-rainbow-islands-extra-genesis-screenshot-course.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413597-rainbow-islands-extra-genesis-screenshot-rainbow.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413598-rainbow-islands-extra-genesis-screenshot-too-many-rainbows.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/0/8/gfs_19934_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/9/5/gfs_19934_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<Notes>Rainbow Islands Extra (レインボーアイランド エキストラ) is a strange update to Rainbow Islands: The Story of Bubble Bobble 2, released by Taito for arcades in 1988 before being ported to the Sega Mega Drive in 1990 exclusively in Japan. Although it offers a port of the original Rainbow Islands, the default option is the "extra" mode, in which all the cute and colourful enemies found in the original game are replaced with enemies found in Taito's shoot-'em-up series, Darius. The music in extra mode has also been replaced with tunes from that game. The rules are otherwise the same as in the original - create rainbows to defeat enemies and reach the top of the screen. The story for both modes is the same: Bubby's friends have been captured and turned into Bubble Dragons by Super Skull Monsta [sic], and Bubby needs to save them by destroying the Super Skull Monsta's minions with rainbows and collecting Little Diamonds to get Magical Mirrors needed to break the spell. Rainbow Islands Extra was only released in Japan.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3adfb0ad-f2ae-4c4c-b7bd-7ba25cb6735b.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9121b75a-9de1-4fe8-a45a-fc88c417dcea.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>