<Game>
	<Name>Resq (Europe) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Good evening, Mr. Phelps. Your mission, should you decide to accept it, is to undertake a perilous rescue mission to the Adrianne star system. The planet has been laid waste by corporate raiders from the Wellmax company, who are even now going planetside to conduct a mopping-up operation for the few survivors hiding out in the city's tunnel system. Time is limited, so the decision to act must be made immediately. This tape will self-destruct in five seconds....Only the boys from Liverpool could pull off a funny little arcade game that manages to combine the best of both the platform and shooter genres. The attempts at humorous stabs of various financial personages and events is stilted, but it's still a fun game to play. It's a shame that Sony chose not to distribute it, because it sure is a neat little piece of work.http://www.genesisproject-online.com/Genesis/R/ResQ.htmlCheat: Hidden Sound TestEnter "MUSIC" at the password screen and hit Start to access a hidden sound test.Cheat: Hidden Sound TestEnter the codes on the password screen to go to the level shown.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Psygnosis</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>bUxAVRfwRHI</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/605272-resq</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/3/3/162633_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/1/3/gfs_178072_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/c/3/gfs_178072_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/7/3/gfs_178072_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/3/gfs_178072_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/d/3/gfs_178072_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/8/e/gfs_178072_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/5/e/gfs_178072_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/e/e/gfs_178072_2_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/f/e/gfs_178072_2_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/4/e/gfs_178072_2_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>ResQ is an unreleased Sega Mega Drive developed by Tempest Software and set to be published by Psygnosis. It is a 2D action game with both space ship and on-foot segments. Had it been released, ResQ would have been an exclusive title for the Mega Drive. Psygnosis cancelled ResQ very close to release for unknown reasons. It was reportedly programmed on 486 DOS PCs, with the artwork produced with Deluxe Paint II and III on Amiga 1200s. A prototype has since been unearthed, with an internal copyright date of 1993. Notably, ResQ's bonus stages are depicted as third-person on-the-rails shooting segments which involve primitive 3D polyons, similar to the Super Nintendo's Star Fox.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83e92747-5ac5-48fd-a075-260599a56466.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11ff78b2-4b94-4e90-81d4-65ef82141e04.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52a66432-419c-490d-b9e9-e2b996809701.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67423c23-9266-4cc1-84f5-612da2297e1b.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f2aedc50-f851-4f2b-af1b-6a13a2f1044a.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44041c42-7263-4e6f-9b20-9f9ec00e1ba2.jpg</snapshot15>
	<Publisher>Psygnosis</Publisher>
</game>