<Game>
	<Name>Revenge of Shinobi, The (USA, Europe) (Rev B)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Revenge of Shinobi (JP: The Super Shinobi) is a ninja action game from Sega and part of their Shinobi franchise, released exclusively for their fledgling Genesis console in 1989. The opposing ninja clan from the original  Shinobi, Zeed, has returned as Neo Zeed. They seek revenge on  Joe Musashi, wiping out his clan and kidnapping his fianc&#233;e.Gameplay:The game is a 2D  side-scrolling brawler. Joe is armed with  shuriken (though they resemble kunai) for distance attacks and ninja magic to handle difficult bosses. He is armed with the Ninjitsu, or quite simply, Ninja Magic. The game consists of differing difficulty levels, with the higher difficulty levels having more enemies, less ability to handle damage, and fewer lives to start with.NinjitsuSpecial techniques that the player can use that can cause massive damage, increase mobility, and provide invulnerability.Ikazuchi, the Art of ThunderJoe calls upon Thunder to surround him with its protection. While enveloped in Ikazuchi, Joe will not be injured and his Life Bar won't decrease. After taking several enemy hits, Ikazuchi fades away.Kariu, the Art of the Fire DragonAssume this jitsu to envelop Joe in a fire column, which then spits and travels, scorching every enemy it touches. Kariu is over when the fire columns disappear.Fushin, the Art of FloatingIncrease Joe's jumping prowess with this jitsu. When Joe assumes Fushin, his jumps and somersaults have maximum height and distance. Fushin stays with Joe until the scene ends, even if he assumes another jitsu.Mijin, the Art of PulverizingBy assuming Mijin Joe becomes a human explosion that destroys everything in its blast. Mijin is best used as a desperate last resort, when the life bar is short. Mihin takes a life, so the player must make sure they have at least one other life remaining.CratesInside crates the player will find a variety of items that can both help or hinder their progress.Power Pack: Increases Joe's strength and adds to his weapons. He throws his shuriken faster and more accurately, gains a lethal sword for combat, and applies the skill of Cross Guard, warding off enemy shuriken with his own.5 Shuriken: Joe gains five more throwing knives.20 Shuriken: Joe acquires twenty more throwing knives.Small Heart: Joe's Life Bar gains two small bars.Large Heart: Joe's Life Bar increases to full strength.Musashi: Joe gains an extra life.Ninjitsu: Ninjitsu (ninja magic) can be used again in the same life, even if Joe's used it already.Bomb: An explosive that detonates either when Joe touches it or its time runs down. Damages Joe if caught in its explosion.Legacy:The Revenge of Shinobi for some infamous instances of copyright infringement. The game had bosses who very closely resembled  Spider-Man,  Batman,  Godzilla and  The Terminator. All Bosses were altered or replaced in later versions of the game: In version 1.01 Batman was replaced by a bat-like mutant, in 1.02 Spiderman is re-designed to look more like the character (because Sega was developing  The Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin for the Genesis at the time) also the bat creature is removed from the battle entirely, and in 1.03 Godzilla is replaced by a skeletal dinosaur. The copyright issues have been a major reason why the game is not often included in Sega compilation discs. The  Virtual Console version has a totally unique version where Spider-Man had a palette swap, but identical abilities (this is due to the license for using Spider-Man was for only limited time, that license is now owned by  Activision).SEGA AGESAs part of the SEGA AGES Online initiative, the game hit Xbox Live Marketplace and PlayStation Network on May 23rd 2012 in Japan (by its Japanese title, The Super Shinobi). For the PlayStation 3, the title was released for &#165;600. For the Xbox 360, the title was released in a bundle with  Alex Kidd in Miracle World and  Super Hang-On for 800 MS Points.Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsIf you want to earn 30,000 bonus points, make sure you end a level with eleven times more shurikens than the number of lives you have left.Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsOne the second stage of level four,fire at the base of the first conveyer belt.A special Musashi symbol will appear.Hop onto the conveyor belt and let it carry you to the end.You lose a life but you gain 2.Keep doing this until you have as many lives as you want/need.Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsGo to the Options Screen, move the pointer up to Shurikins and set them to 00, wait about 30 seconds (without moving the pointer). You will here a sound and the ''00'' should change to an infinite symbol. Start the game and you will have unlimited Shurikins.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ClJZV2qCFJg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4673</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/519117-the-revenge-of-shinobi</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/revenge-of-shinobi</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-revenge-of-shinobi/3030-236/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4673-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4673-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KudLvAr.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/41KJSRs.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/l437hyv.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/sP2jLB5.png</boxart5>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80016-the-revenge-of-shinobi-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4673-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33576-the-revenge-of-shinobi-genesis-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33577-the-revenge-of-shinobi-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4673-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KEArsex.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4673.png</clearlogo1>
</game>