<Game>
	<Name>Revolution X (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Revolution X is an on-rails light-gun arcade shooter, developed and published by Midway. Its final prototype was released on May 23rd, 1994, followed by the official release the following month on June 16th.Story:In a dystopian future, the corporations have taken over. The New Order Nation (NON), lead by the villainous Mistress Helga, have waged war on the youth and have banned music, television, and video games. But the greatest injustice is that they have kidnapped Aerosmith! The player must defeat the NON with the power of music. Which means firing CDs at guys in yellow suits and motorcycle helmets, and giant glowing green skulls!Gameplay:This game is a standard rail shooter in which the player is led along a set path and must defeat enemies by aiming and shooting at them with the yellow button. The home versions were not light gun-compatible.Each stage has hidden rooms containing a member of Aerosmith. Rescuing all members of Aerosmith and collecting Aerosmith's winged logo after each rescue will unlock the game's best ending, consisting of a party with the band and a bonus room filled with loot and smoking hot babes.Trivia:The members of the band are hidden within the levels and if they are all found the player gets the proper canon ending.The songs Eat the Rich, Toys in the Attic, Sweet Emotion, and Walk this Way are looped throughout the game. Not the entire song, but rather a few seconds of each, over and over and over again.There were plans to make a Public Enemy version, but that game never came to fruition.The CD-ROM releases of Revolution X featured full-motion video sequences with members of the band informing the game's plot.Following a particularly large explosion, Steven Tyler will occasionally yell "Toasty!", an homage to Dan Forden's uppercut reward in Mortal Kombat II, which had an advertisement for Revolution X in its attract mode.		</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>1.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ipaiDnknENo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>668</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586418-revolution-x</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/revolution-x</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/revolution-x/3030-12829/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/668-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/668-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/217280-revolution-x-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76571-revolution-x-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76572-revolution-x-genesis-screenshot-helicopter-busting-action.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76573-revolution-x-genesis-screenshot-aerosmith-in-concert.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76574-revolution-x-genesis-screenshot-kidnapped.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76575-revolution-x-genesis-screenshot-the-high-resolution-video-scene.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/7/1/gfs_39012_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/a/1/gfs_39012_1_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/1/1/gfs_39012_1_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/0/1/gfs_39012_1_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/b/1/gfs_39012_1_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UmPZjIE.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/668.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The plot concerns a dystopian version of 1996 where an alliance of corrupt government and corporate military forces have taken control of the world in the guise of the "New Order Nation" (NON). The NON, with their vampish commander Mistress Helga (portrayed by Kerri Hoskins), have declared war on youth culture (anyone aged from 13 to 30) and have banned music, television and video games. At a gig in Los Angeles at 'Club X', complete with neon sign, Aerosmith are captured by NON troops once the player reached inside the theater and the game begins.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/17aa7b3b-6c12-4726-98bd-fa551cfe7b33.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ddcd5e8-249b-4660-99ec-3d572063aeb2.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bbbc6f0c-2aba-4c2a-a804-3c4f34b09969.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>