<Game>
	<Name>Rings of Power (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Rings of Power plays in an isometric view and has many RPG like qualities to it. The world is filled with NPCs (Non-Player Character) that the player must talk to, and get clues from. Just as in The Legend Of Zelda, most of the world is accessible from the start leaving the player free to explore, and discover, the world at their own will. Overview:Rings of Power was the second game created by developer Naughty Dog (Keef the Thief being first) and was published by Electronic Arts. In the game the player assumes the role of a young Sorcerer named Buc, who is tasked with gathering the eleven Rings Of Power to recreate the Rod of Creation, and defeat the evil god Void once and for all.The Rod Of Creation was broken in to two after a deadly battle between the holy god Nexus and Void. After the battle each god took a half of the Rod of Creation and created eleven rings, which were given to trusted members from each of the six guilds. Over time the Rings of Power were lost and the story became a legend, however the story was real, and news comes that Void is attempting to command a group of followers to recover the Rings of Power.The game begins at the Sorcerers Guild, where a traitor is revealed and attacks Buc's Sorcerer master Thalamus. To protect the students Thalamus casts them from the Guild and scatters them across the globe. Thalamus instructs Buc to gather a party of members from the other guilds, and find the Rings of Power before Void does. As Buc you must seek out and team up with the Knight Slash from the City of Division, the Necromancer Mortimer from the City of Blood, the Archer Feather from the City of Speed, the Conjurer Alexi from the City of Perfection, and the Enchanter Obliky from the City of Kaos.Together, you must gather each of the eleven Rings of Power and unite them before Void does to finally destroy him forever. The Rings of PowerThe eleven Rings of Power are as follows:The Ring of AdvancingThe Ring of BileThe Ring of BloodThe Ring of CallingThe Ring of DivisionThe Ring of IntuitionThe Ring of MutationThe Ring of PerfectionThe Ring of ThoughtThe Ring of VariationThe Ring of Will Nude CodeRings of Power is considered to be the first game to feature a nude code. The game opens with a Naughty Dog title sequence, in which a blonde woman in a t-shirt appears on the screen. The screen then pans to the right revealing the Naughty Dog character and the company logo. By holding down the buttons A, B, C and START, while also pressing the D-Pad DOWN RIGHT on a second controller as you turn on the Genesis, you will initiate the nude sequence. The same Naughty Dog title sequence appears, but the blonde woman will appear topless next to the Naughty Dog logo.Cheat: New Logo (Mature Audiences Only)To get an alternate Naughty Dog Games logo during the opening splash sequence, before you turn on you Genesis hold down A + B + C + Down-Right + Start, then turn your power on.Cheat: Refill any Chest.To Refill any chest you have opened, simply look at your map.  When you close the map, any chests you have opened will be closed and will have a random item inside.  Cheat: Teleport CheatView the map and press A C and Start on pad 2 together to teleport to wherever the cursor is.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>KeyiMImbPfA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4595</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586420-rings-of-power</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/rings-of-power</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rings-of-power/3030-13615/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4595-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/64326-rings-of-power-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/205679-rings-of-power-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87002-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-nice-company-logo-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87003-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87004-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87005-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-information-about-game-characters.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87006-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-intro-text-only.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87007-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-game.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87008-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-walking-through-an-alley.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87009-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-you-can-zoom-on-and-examine.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87010-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-will-you-pay.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/87011-rings-of-power-genesis-screenshot-battle.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/j82sTYA.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Band together six powerful magicians and search out the fabled Rings of Power to free your world. Interact and trade with inhabitants of thirty cities. Over 100 animated spells to choose from! Rings of Power is quite different from traditional console RPGs gameplay-wise, and is more similar to Western-style games such as Ultima series. You can freely wander through the huge isometric world, and are not obliged to follow any storyline except the main quest for the eleven rings. You can talk to NPCs about many topics, choose whom to fight, bribe people, etc. There is a day/night cycle which affects the behavior of characters. Unlike most RPGs, there are no weapons and armor in this game. The turn-based combat is entirely dependent on magic spells. On your journey you will encounter characters from several guilds, each proficient in his own type of magic, and make them join your party.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef5fa0b9-9e8f-43ae-bb21-584ab6b5c6f5.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d96f4cf-3f7a-46f8-91a5-4e8b210576fc.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db69a342-f9b3-468b-b6f3-932a9b8c7787.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>