<Game>
	<Name>Risky Woods (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Unusually for Electronic Arts in the early 90s, this was a platform -shooter game with little or no adventuring or strategy elements. The game scrolls sideways, and has sections where precision jumps are required, either to clear rivers or collect bonuses. You carry a dagger to deal with the enemies, and must avoid contact with them. When killed, they leave coins to be collected - these are spent in the shop sections. Death loses you most of your coins, but they can usually be retrieved if they land on solid ground - making it better to be killed in combat than by drowning.Cheat: Level SelectGet killed and make sure you have a high score.  Put in EOA as a name, and when you select options, you can choose which level you want to start on!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>NJvhUTT6UHM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4596</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586422-risky-woods</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/risky-woods</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/risky-woods/3030-3898/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4596-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4596-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/65236-risky-woods-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37648-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37645-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-the-quest-s-map.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37646-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-stage-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37649-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-knife-throwing-is-the-basic.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37647-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-amidst-the-action.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37650-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-collecting-coins-give-you-armour.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37651-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-time-out.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/37644-risky-woods-genesis-screenshot-game-over.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/1/gfs_3024_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/b/b/gfs_82758_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4596.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The ancient monks, who preserve the wisdom of the Lost Lands, have been frozen in stone. Young Rohan must plunge into the Risky Woods to release them. Only then can wisdom triumph once again. Most of Risky Woods involves Rohan running, jumping ledges and fighting monsters while freeing the monks from stone. At every third stage lay a boss, usually some gigantic floating insect that throws fireballs. Both the monsters in the levels as well as these insect bosses drop coins, though bosses drop considerably more. These coins can be used after each level to buy weaponry upgrades and extra life energy. During the game, a number of other elements present themselves, such as evil monks who were also trapped in stone. Freeing them will cost you and even hurt you; they can be distinguished from regular stone monks by how their stone looks. However, some later levels switch which monks are trapped in what color of statue, which can be quite disorienting at first. The secondary objective of each level is to pass through multiple "Eye-Key" gates. The player has two find two halves of an Eye-Key object, then use the completed Eye-Key to pass through these gates, otherwise the gate will send the player back in the level to find the missing key again, at the cost of half the player's life energy. Continues may be found during the game, but only two are given in the entirety of the game. Once those continues are used up, that's game over and the player has to restart the game. The final level leads to a castle in which we must defeat Draxos, and upon which we are given a short animation and game over sequence.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc21017c-a50f-449d-96f2-ff0095e8d684.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38232dc8-f08f-47a1-9bf1-21bda1e25776.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e20a18a-2c16-4924-b8c5-c5849eb13f6e.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>