<Game>
	<Name>Risk (USA)</Name>
	<plot>You're the General, so defend your countries, capture new territories, occupy vast continents... and keep building your armies so you can conquer the world! Fast Setup: Touch one button and the computer deploys your troops. Computer Intelligence: Battle your friends or the A.I. of 6 computer enemies. Fast Play: Pick the classic attack or a computer fight to the finish. Arcade Competition: Where your skill determines the outcome of the attack! Battlefield Sound Effects and Music: Bringing the battlefield to life!Directions:Use your stradegy skills to conquer the world!Controls:  A Button: ChooseB Button: BackC Button: NoneStart Button: Start/End TurnHints:- Don't Spread Yourself Too Thin - To make the best use out of your turn, remember that you only need one victory to get a card. Don't make so many attacks in one turn that your territories end up with just one or two battalions on them. It'll just make it easier for an opponent to come behind you and take them.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/home/586421.htmlhttp://www.consoleclassix.com/genesis/risk.html</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Parker Bros</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>683</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586421-risk</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/risk/3030-43952/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/683-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/683-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/8/gfs_39015_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/8/gfs_39015_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/8/gfs_39015_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/8/gfs_39015_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/2/5/gfs_39015_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/f/5/gfs_39015_2_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/4/5/gfs_39015_2_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/5/5/gfs_39015_2_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ylVAib7.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Players attempt to capture territories from other players by rolling higher die numbers. The game is won when one player has managed to occupy every territory.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90709c03-0e84-4f0f-a646-a17c1b70370d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ac66224-52be-4e3c-90b7-2c64759b6b6b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Parker Brothers</Publisher>
</game>