<Game>
	<Name>Road Rash 3 (USA) (Alpha)</Name>
	<plot>The Rash is back in the latest, nastiest, baddest race game for your Genesis. This time there's five NEW weapons, including the cattle-prod and crow bar. NEW race tracks take you across the globe, from the Aussie Outback to nighttime urban Japan. NEW modes raise the ante with the other Rashers while the NEW digitized graphics and interactive obstacles charge NEW life into the gameplay!Directions:Race against others on motorcycles. Punch, kick, and hit others with a weapon to push you closer to first place. The higher your rank, the better the pay you get! Avoid crashing into cars, and watch out for cops, or you will get busted!Gameplay::Following the previous two Road Rash games, the player has conquered the US illegal motorcycle championship. But why settle for that when one can take over the World; racing in the peaceful streets of the UK, dodging the animals in Kenya, blaze through the night in Japan or jump in the hilly circuits in Italy?Keeping the same spirit of the previous two games, Road Rash 3 adds all new digitized sprites (based on the 32-bit remake released an year earlier), bike upgrades, more weapons and meaner police. Most other aspects of the game remain unchanged: the player starts on the lowest division with a small amount of cash and a slow, hard to handle bike. To get more money (and get a faster bike) the player must beat as many of the other 15 racers to the finish line, using all means possible, even kicking and punching them into knockout. By clearing (finishing on the top three spots) all five races on a level, the player advances to the next, where opponents are faster and tougher, the police is more active and a longer race.As for new gameplay elements in the final title in the series released for Sega's 16-bit console, bikes can also be improved by choosing cheaper upgrades (instead of simply buying new ones) such as tires (less skidding), engine (improves acceleration and top speed), suspension (allows better control while landing after jumps) and body (bike takes more hits before turning into smoking metal). Instead on relying on simple motorbike patrols, the police now has helicopters at their disposal (which try to land on the player) and patrol cars, which attempt to block the path of the bike, forcing it to stop or collide to get a bust. To make things easier (or harder), new weapons were added, some of which allow the carrier to stun an opponent for a few seconds, making him the perfect victim for an incoming vehicle. Also new, if the player finishes the race with a weapon, carries it to the next race.Each track has it's own features: in the UK, cars drive left on a rainy day, in Australia and Kenya animals wander into the road, in Brazil bikers can get themselves a close-encounter with a car on a crossing, in Italy the hills allow a lot of air-time for light and speedy bikes, Germany, where the icy roads and sharp turns make a deadly combination and finally in Japan the race goes during the night under the neon lights.Controls:  A Button: BrakeB Button: AccelerateC Button: punch/kicks if holding c and down/uses weaponX Button: N/AY Button: N/AZ Button: N/AStart Button: Starts game/Pauses gameMode Button: N/AHints:- Level 5, Wild Thing 2000, lots of Cash -Enter The Following Password at the password Screen:R7EF TU0RThe ''0'' is a Zero, not The Letter O.- Level Codes, loads of money, Wild Thing 2000 -Enter these codes at the password screen for $300,000 and the Wild Thing 2000:Level 1: 8CKE 1U0MLevel 2: 8CKE 2U0NLevel 3: 8CKE 3U0OLevel 4: 8CKE 4U0PLevel 5: 8CKE 5U0QNote: Most of the 0's are the number, but the O at the very end of the Level 3 code is the letter.- Super Password -Enter the following code at the Password Screen....15S9 - PU03Then when you play the game you will have $200 000 and the Wild Thing 2000- Cheat Mode - To go to Level 3 with the DMG 1000, $20000 in your pocket, and a range of weapons, press ABRACADABRA on the title screen (where R is Right and D is Down). If put in correctly then a police siren will go off.- Difficult Games - Enter the below codes at the "Game Options" screen:K000 100MLevel 1, $100, Perro 125K000 200NLevel 2, $100, Perro 125K000 300OLevel 3, $100, Perro 125K000 400PLevel 4, $100, Perro 125K000 500QLevel 5, $100, Perro 125- Various and Final Level Passwords -Enter the following passwords at the password screen...DDEF PU0F - Start game at Level 1 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 CashDDEF QU0G - Start game at Level 2 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 CashDDEF RU0H - Start game at Level 3 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 CashDDEF SU0I - Start game at Level 4 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 CashDDEF TU0J - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 CashDDEF TUUD - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 Cash/Final Race at BrazilDDEF TURA - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 Cash/Final Race at ItalyDDEF TUFU - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 Cash/Final Race at JapanDDEF TUN6 - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 Cash/Final Race at KenyaDDEF TUTG - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/Max.Upgrades/305,660 Cash/Final Race at U.K.http://www.consoleclassix.com/genesis/road_rash_3.htmlhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/code/586427.htmlhttp://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/road-rash-3-tour-de-forceCheat: Cheat ModeTo go to Level 3 with the DMG 1000, $20000 in your pocket, and a range of weapons, press ABRACADABRA on the title screen (where R is Right and D is Down).  If put in correctly then a police siren will go off.Cheat: Cheat ModeTo start with a fully upgraded Bike and $1,000 in extra cash, at the title screen, on Control Pad 2, press Up, Down, Down, Right.Cheat: Cheat ModeTo start on Level 2 with $1,500 in extra cash, at the title screen, on Control Pad 2, press Down, Up, Left, Left.Cheat: Cheat ModeAt the title screen on controller 2 press B, Left, Up, Right, then press Start.  You will start with $3330, on level 3, and you'll get Wild Thing 2000 (fastest bike in the game).Cheat: Difficult GamesEnter the below codes at the "Game Options" screen:Cheat: Difficult GamesEnter the following passwords at the password screen...</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>DAprFOGApsQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4599</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586427-road-rash-iii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/road-rash-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/road-rash-ii/3030-7144/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4599-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4599-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/75043-road-rash-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4599-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63475-road-rash-3-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63476-road-rash-3-genesis-screenshot-the-bike-shop-buy-a-new-type.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63477-road-rash-3-genesis-screenshot-select-a-racing-track-there.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kae77wg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4599.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Rash is back in the latest, nastiest, baddest race game for your Genesis. This time there's five NEW weapons, including the cattle-prod and crow bar. NEW race tracks take you across the globe, from the Aussie Outback to nighttime urban Japan. NEW modes raise the ante with the other Rashers while the NEW digitized graphics and interactive obstacles charge NEW life into the gameplay!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>XYXAStghIaM</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8ad91aa-840c-4c37-852a-7a0b349ae83a.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d696296f-b0e8-4c54-a23c-d2de7a1cd45e.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ecd6959d-b2e7-4da3-861d-88306ce48899.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01088145-778c-408c-b7bd-c806d592e59b.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>