<Game>
	<Name>Road Rash II (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Road Rash II is a motorcycle-racing video game developed and published by Electronic Arts. Players participate in violent, illegal street races to win championships and earn money, which is used to repair your motorcycle, pay bail, or buy new motorcycles. The game was released on July 22, 1993.Gameplay:The gameplay in Road Rash II is presented in a third-person view, with the camera directly behind the player. The objective of the game is to beat other racers to the finish line and avoid both obstacles and police officers. The player starts off with just their fists for protection, but other racers may have weapons at their disposal, which may then be stolen by the player. Getting hit by weapons or crashing into obstacles will have your health bar deplete. When you run out of health, your motorcycle breaks down and the race is over. If you crash or if you stop completely while a police officer is chasing you, you will be arrested and taken to the police station, where you will be charged a fee before being released. If you run out of money to repair your bike or pay your police fee, the game is over.Cheat CodesVarious Level and Final Level PasswordsEnter the following passwords at the Password Screen in the Options menu.    EVVU 1U09 - Start game at Level 1 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash EVVU 2U0A - Start game at Level 2 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash EVVU 3U0B - Start game at Level 3 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash EVVU 4U0C - Start game at Level 4 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash EVVU 5U0D - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash EVVU 5UUJ - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash/Final Race in Alaska EVVU 5UTG - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash/Final Race in Hawaii EVVU 5URM - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash/Final Race in Tennessee EVVU 5UNQ - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash/Final Race in Arizona EVVU 5UF2 - Start game at Level 5 with Wild Thing 2000/327,670 Cash/Final Race in Vermont  Difficult GamesEnter the following passwords at the Password Screen in the Options menu.    001K 110N - Level 1, $100, Shuriken 400 001K 210O - Level 2, $100, Shuriken 400 001K 310P - Level 3, $100, Shuriken 400 001K 410Q - Level 4, $100, Shuriken 400 001K 510R - Level 5, $100, Shuriken 400  Cheat: Start With Any BikeChoose a two-player head-to-head game and choose a bike from the shop. Go back to the Game Select menu and choose the two-player ''Take Turns'' mode. Then pick a one-player game and press Start. Now you should be able to pick any bike from the shop.Cheat: Start With Any BikeTo get the hidden bike, known as the Wild Thing, hold Up, A and C on the title screen.  Press start to enter the Race Select screen, then release the buttons.  You will start the first race with the Wild Thing.Cheat: Difficult GamesPut the following codes as your password on the options screen:Cheat: Difficult GamesEnter the following passwords at the password screen...</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Qdi_PL7v3Tg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>734</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586426-road-rash-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/road-rash-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/road-rash-ii/3030-7144/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2371394-genesis_roadrash2_2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/734-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/17646-road-rash-ii-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142046-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142047-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/466975-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-setting-your-name.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175240-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-cruising-around-tennessee.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175241-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-race-in-vermont.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175242-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-i-m-as-clueless-as-you-are.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175243-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-i-did-nothing-other-than-speeding.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175244-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-several-bikes-are-available.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175245-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-track-selection.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/175246-road-rash-ii-genesis-screenshot-arizona.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jLPQnFU.png</banner1>
</game>