<Game>
	<Name>Scooby-Doo Mystery (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Sega Genesis version of the game was a point and click adventure game based around the hit TV show about a bunch of kids and their talking dog who drive around in a stoner van and solve mysteries. It features two episodes where Scooby and Shaggy are on their own to solve the mysteries solo. You control Shaggy while Scooby accompanies you everywhere that you go. Scooby will sometimes give you hints by pointing at objects you may need, or places of interest. You search through each locations to find items and clues that will help you solve each mystery. The game was surprisingly fun and captured the charm of the show rather well.The Super Nintendo version of the game was a platformer game based around searching through different locales for clues to solve the mystery. You controlled Scooby and Shaggy, who would search different rooms for various items, and could sniff out hidden ones. Shaggy could speak to members of the gang to do accomplish different goals.Daphne would give scooby snacks to decrease Shaggy and Scooby's fright meter.Fred would give the blueprints to consturct the traps to catch the villian.Velma would determine if item were clues, and award the player 200 points for every clue item.Plot:Each episode involves the gang driving to a reportedly haunted locale and trying to figure out what, or who, is behind all the ruckus. In both cases Shaggy and Scooby end up being the only ones left to solve the mystery. Whether Shaggy tokes or not is not important here, he needs a clear mind in order to solve both mysteries and save the day.Episodes (Genesis Version)Blake's Hotel - A hotel that is run by Daphne's uncle Blake, who invites the group over for a weekend stay. Upon arrival they learn that an ancient chieftain is scaring away all of the customers.Ha Ha Carnival - A practically abandoned Carnival. Eventually Fred, Daphne, and Velma go missing and a phantom clown seems to be behind it all.Episodes (SNES Version)Spooky Shipwreck - an abandoned ship named the Red Cyanis is being haunted by the One-Eyed Matt.Ha Ha Carnival - the amusement park is being haunted by an evil clown.Abandoned Ranch/Swamp - A tar monster is running amok on a ranch scaring away any visitor.Blake's Hotel - a house owned by Daphnie's uncle is haunted by Count Bagosi.Cheats (SNES Version)Level 2 - (Deserted Circus) -TDBKSRQLevel 3 - (Abandoned Ranch/Swamp) - XLWPMTCLevel 4 - (Haunted House) - NBKSDLVCredits - SPNNRCheat: Debug ModeAt the main menu selection screen, press A, B, A, C, A, B, Left, Right, A, B, Left You will hear a Scooby-Doo chuckle when entered correctly. Now pause the game, and you can choose which room you are in, and also see all the items.Cheat: Ending passwordsBlake's Hotel Chapter D*OX% AZY%# YM*UV NTKSH !MCLE %TU!T SOJZH E#TSO JZHE# TSOJY (Use the medallion with the hook to see the ending.) Ha Ha Carnival Chapter CN?NE L*QG* UM*I* IFEJC HW*++ PN%XW *++PN %XW*+ +PN%X W*++P (Just use the dart with the ball to see the ending.)Cheat: Ending passwordsAfter selecting Blake's Hotel, go to Continue Blake's Hotel and on the password screen enter:"SCOOBYDOOSHAG(with 1 G)YANDTHEGANG without taking in mind the following letters. The result is always the same: this cheat takes you a little before the end of the game, outside the house. There are quite the paradoxes (having items which are behind a locked cabinet for example, or the totem pole not being on the ground etc.) Scooby is also with Shaggy, while another Scooby is being chased by the Chieftain. Check out ALL of the strange going on-s. ;)</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.|Sun Corporation of America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>weHFbWPSl5U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4611</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586443-scooby-doo-mystery</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/scooby-doo-mystery</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/scooby-doo-mystery/3030-17638/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4611-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74241-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-copyright-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74229-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74230-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-the-first-mystery-is.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74231-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-the-gang-on-there-way.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74232-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-the-lobby-of-the-hotel.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74233-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-the-chef-wont-let-you.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74235-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-have-a-conversation.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74234-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-game-progress-is-restored.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74236-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-its-cold-outside-this.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/74238-scooby-doo-mystery-genesis-screenshot-the-monster-of-the-story.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4611-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4611-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4611-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/l0BeizQ.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Scooby-Doo Mystery is a point-and-click (or point-and-press button rather) adventure featuring two playable episodes of a typical scooby-doo cartoon. Blake's Hotel - Daphne's Uncle Blake has invited the gang over to his hotel for a ski weekend. Upon reaching the hotel they learn that the ghost of the Ancient Chieftan is scaring all the customers away, as he isnt happy about a hotel being built on his burial grounds. Soon Uncle Blake is kidnapped, and its up to Scooby and Shaggy to find clues and hunt this ghost down. Ha Ha Carnival - The gang arrives at an almost-deserted carvinal, looking for some fun. Soon enough Fred, Daphne and Velma get trapped in a pond when they go out in one of the rides. Not only that, someone has broken the rollercoaster tracks. Then an evil looking phantom clown has Scooby and Shaggy being chased all around the carnival. Another mystery for the pair to solve.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36f5e1a4-0bd9-48fb-a27a-e079a86f3ddb.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab82d14b-9574-4e00-ac67-ef1dd910b2c1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c1ac6b2-243e-4455-9cab-f5067442dbc5.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5e8304e-edbf-4a74-a36e-e4b69aeb338c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>