<Game>
	<Name>Senjou no Ookami II ~ Mercs (World)</Name>
	<plot>Terrorists have their job and you've got yours: CRUSH 'EM ALL! They've kidnapped a former President, and the MERCS are going in for the rescue. Punch through their coastal defenses, snatch enemy weapons and gain firepower. Pick up machine guns, bazookas and heavy artilery as you advance through the smoke of burning metal. Power up a flame thrower, and good-bye, Charlie! Push through a non-stop barrage of lead, grenades, heat seeking missiles and attack choppers. Hijack tanks and gunboats. Shred 'em with their own weapons! They messed with your country - now you're gonna make 'em scream!Cheat: Faster and Smarter EnemiesAt the options screen, highlight Original Mode, then hold A, B, C, and then press Start.Cheat: Faster and Smarter EnemiesAt the Sega logo, on controller 2 hold d-pad left + down, A, B, C and keep holding until the next screen.  The round select will appear when starting a new game.Cheat: Hidden areas shown.If you beat Mercs on original mode (not the arcade version) you will see in the end that they will show you where all the hidden areas are in game for each level on original mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<rating>7.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>_2bR0dP_zb4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4501</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586313-mercs</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4501-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4501-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4501-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4501-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/3/gfs_82948_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/f/b/gfs_120313_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/e/gfs_82948_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/6/6/gfs_120313_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/b/6/gfs_120313_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/0/6/gfs_120313_2_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4501.png</clearlogo1>
</game>