<Game>
	<Name>Sensible Soccer - International Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:International Sensible Soccer is the third iteration of Sensible Software's highly acclaimed top-down soccer series Sensible Soccer. Like the previous game, Sensible Soccer 92/93, it includes several incremental gameplay improvements as well as a few new features. In this case, a new international content mode - the World Cup - and referee sprites that can be seen on the pitch.Also, like Sensible Soccer 92/93, it was made accessible to a number of consoles as well as the Atari ST and Amiga computers. It was released on Genesis, SNES, Atari Jaguar and Amiga CD32 - the Jaguar hosting the only US release. 		</plot>
	<releasedate>31/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20450</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/international-sensible-soccer/3030-16250/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20450-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/f0EuHio.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sensible Soccer: International Edition or International Sensible Soccer is an entry in the Sensible Soccer series of football games and was released for the Sega Mega Drive in 1994. It acts as an update to the Mega Drive version of Sensible Soccer and like this game, remained exclusive to Europe. The game was marked as a limited edition release, and features teams, groups, and players from the 1994 FIFA World Cup. It is otherwise almost exactly the same game, right down to the menus.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f2e1cec8-6e56-4142-843a-4101be4853f0.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84ea8e84-8592-445c-9ee5-8585b7e66014.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7bd7401f-7cca-4900-b4ca-87b7f171a840.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3bce6484-db31-4e08-8a44-d43e37035e5f.jpg</snapshot2>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<Developer>Sensible Software</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>