<Game>
	<Name>Shadowrun (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to 2050, chummer.Shadowrun is an action RPG of epic proportions. You take on the role of Joshua, a Shadowrunner out to discover who murdered his brother. Along the way you get into street brawls, deadly gunfights, run the Matrix, slip into and out of the MegaCorps, explore the wild wilderness and deal with every low-life mage and high-tech cyber Street Samurai in Seattle.Shadowrun was based on the FASA RPG of the same name, and while real-time, modeled every rule from the paper system, from character stats to experience to combat to weapons and equipment.The game used an overhead view for physical combat, and a third person "POV" when on Matrix runs. It allowed two other characters to join your party either temporarily or "for life" however long that may be...Cheat: Cheat MenuEnter the following code at the Title Screen....  A - B - B - A - C - A - B  Then fo into the pocket secratary, below the Save/Load is a blank line. Go into that option and you can unlock some awesome cheatsCheat: Lower Shadowrunner Hiring Costs at No RiskComplete a moderate or advanced Shadowrun that requires you to collect payment from the Johnson you contracted with. Then hire a shadowrunner for the short-term BEFORE collecting your payment. Upon receiving payment, the game will treat your hired shadowrunner like he/she successfully completed the contract with you, and will lower his/her hiring price anyway.Cheat: Easy Stolen Package Corp RunStolen packages are always randomly located in safes in corporate buildings. Each time you exit and reenter a corp building, the package relocates to a different safe.Cheat: Easy Stolen Package Corp RunThat said, always take the Corp Run that requires you to retrieve a stolen package from Lone Star Security. The Lone Star building has a safe right next to the exit. Enter, check the safe, exit the building, and repeat the procedure until the package appears in that safe. It is the easiest Corp Run in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>2uz5XcKWtBM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1306</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/366854-shadowrun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/shadowrun</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shadowrun/3030-21710/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/1306-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/1306-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/73598-shadowrun-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27974-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-shadowrun-s-sega-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27975-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-shadowrun-s-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27976-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-choose-to-be-a-street-samurai.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27977-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-or-a-decker.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27978-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-or-a-shaman.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27979-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-opening-cinematic-over-seattle.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27980-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-opening-cinematic-surprise-ambush.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27981-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-running-in-seattle.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27982-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-running-in-redmond-barrens.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/27987-shadowrun-genesis-screenshot-meeting-mr-johnson.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4ydSkci.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The year is 2058. Following an event known as the Awakening, magic has returned into the world. Native American shamans and elves reclaimed a vast area known as Salish-Shidhe, located around the free city of Seattle. A small team of shadowrunners - mercenaries working for powerful corporations - is brutally attacked in the wilderness. The massacre is captured in video and broadcast in the news. One of the slain shadowrunners, Michael, had a brother named Joshua. Arriving in Seattle, Joshua begins to investigate his brother's death. He must find out who killed Michael, and what was the nature of the shadowrun job he was carrying out. The Genesis version of Shadowrun is a darker and grittier version of the universe. While still heavily based on William Gibson's Neuromancer, the story revolves around the murder of the protagonist's brother. Shadowrun for the Genesis is a more open ended game than its counterpart on the SNES.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/31a69cd7-f299-43c1-aa60-c9b6f20ca923.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/403710d2-bef7-4fed-8e71-bb45f8cf9f74.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2432a0a4-83d5-4cc8-a6e2-89da0631ce76.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76a09010-df50-47d0-b699-227cffc098b1.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50171842-d847-488c-bace-b3ab50f557d5.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ac3c184f-f012-4f25-8092-fe463feb2cc4.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1de9eff2-690b-4690-916b-e57b73562041.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04719ac7-642b-4c14-83f5-92e0cb6e8a9e.png</snapshot16>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>