<Game>
	<Name>Shaq-Fu (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shaq Fu is a 2D fighting game developed by Delphine and published by EA for the Sega Genesis and Super Nintendo Entertainment System in 1994.The game follows professional basketball player Shaquille "Shaq" O'Neal, who must use the deadly arts of Shaqido in a mystical alternate dimension to rescue a mysterious boy from an army of servants loyal to an evil, powerful mummy known as Sett-Ra. He must be quick, so he can go back to a charity basketball game in downtown Tokyo!Despite the game's smooth animation and crisp graphics, the game was widely panned for its difficult controls, inconsistent hit detection, and silly concept. The SNES version was also known for having less features than its Genesis counterpart (including five less playable fighters and three less stages).It was ported to the Amiga (in Europe only, developed by The Dome and published by Ocean), Sega Game Gear (developed by Tiertex and published by EA), and Game Boy (developed by Unexpected Development and published by Black Pearl) a year later. Ocean was also the sole publisher of the SNES version in Europe.Characters:For details on the characters, see the guide.Cheat: Blood ModeEnter the following code at the Options ScreenCheat: Blood ModeAt the Options screen, choose the fighter you wish to use in Story Mode by picking a number in the Music Test as follows: 1=Mephis, 2=Sett, 3=Nezu, 4=Kaori, 5=Beast, 6=Auroch, 7=Voodoo, 8=Colonel, 9=Diesel, 10=Leotsu, 11=Rajah, 12=Shaq Then press Up, Down, B, Left, Right, B while still at the Options screen. The screen should flash if you did it correctly.Cheat: Third Bonus StageIn Story Mode, head to the rightmost trees above Kaori's Catwalk Falls (essentialy, the top right corner of the landmark) and press Start. There, you will reach a bonus stage, in which you must smash a number of skeletons before the time runs out. Getting a perfect score will earn you an extra continue.Cheat: Third Bonus StageIn Story mode, after opening up the path to the Second World, head under South Gate until you cannot move any farther (You should be at the southern-most tip of the Second World), press the C button, and you will be treated to a Bonus fight -- a purple and black version of Sett. Like the Beast bonus fight in the First World, this battle does not have any dialogue and has no relevance to the plot.Cheat: Unlock bonus fightWhen in the ''Story'' level, go to the right-hand corner of Gargoyle's Peak. A set of stairs is there, which is leading to the Cliff, and move Shaq down these stairs, until he reaches the black door. Then, press Start, you'll face a blue version of ''Beast''. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>1.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>690</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/562309-shaq-fu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/shaq-fu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shaq-fu/3030-4855/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/690-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/690-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/280238-shaq-fu-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95356-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95355-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95357-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-duel-mode.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95358-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-preparing.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95359-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-fighting-at-the-north-gate.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95360-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-you-are-knocked-out.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95361-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-teasing-continue-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95362-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-near-the-castle-wall-shaq-is-about.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95363-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-nice-violet-level.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/95364-shaq-fu-genesis-screenshot-the-little-guy-is-called-leotsu.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AG55Ftl.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/690.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the game's storyline, Shaquille O'Neal wanders into a kung fu dojo while heading to a charity basketball game in Tokyo, Japan. There, he stumbles into another dimension, where he must rescue a young boy named Nezu from the evil mummy Sett-Ra.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>4xmzIXm62NA</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0dac2d71-cad4-475f-85b6-f90bc65b8257.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6520dde1-6202-4a1c-beb2-b38ad97651a1.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1d08bf4-526c-48c5-8e4c-4cdc6cd5f5bb.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>