<Game>
	<Name>Shinobi III - Return of the Ninja Master (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shinobi III: Return of Shinobi is the second of two Shinobi games developed for the Sega Genesis (known in Japan as Super Shinobi), but despite its numeral is actually the seventh game in the Shinobi series. It was also the last game to feature recurring Shinobi protagonist Joe Musashi until the 2002 Shinobi for PS2.The game saw multiple rereleases. It became available via the Sega Genesis Collection (PS2/PSP) and Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection (360/PS3) compilations; the emulated version that appears on the latter was eventually added to Steam. Shinobi III was also added to the Wii's Virtual Console, to iOS and to the 3DS eShop. After the adventures in  Revenge of Shinobi, it seemed like Joe Musashi, finally destroyed the evil criminal empire Neo Zeed. However, Neo Zeed decided to remain low until years later. Now the empire is once again on the rise, and it's up to the powerful Shinobi to finally destroy Neo Zeed for good.Cheat: InvincibilityChoose BMG selection on the options menu, then, press B to select the following songs in order. Cheat: InvincibilitySet the amout of shurikens to 0 on the options menu, Set the sounds effects option to Shuriken. Highlight the shurikens option and keep it there and the 0 will change into the symbol for infinity. Cheat: 6 Button ModeThis cheat makes it possible to play the game with a new 6 Button controller scheme. You need a 6 button controller plugged into port 1 and any regular controller in port 2.Highlight "Options" on the main menu. Normally when you're in the Options menu, it says "Options" at the top, with an S on the end.Highlight Options but don't go into it yet. On Controller 1, hold the Mode button and on Controller 2, hold UP on the D-Pad and the C Button. With all these buttons held down, press Start on controller 1.Now you're in the Options menu, it now just says "Option" at the top without an S. This means 6 Button mode is on. This is what each button does.A is the Block button.B is a Melee attack.C is JumpX uses Ninjitsu magicY and Z throw ShurikensThis allows you to use Melee move at any time rather than at close range or when out of Shurikens.Enjoy!Cheat: 6 Button ModeComplete a level without throwing any shurikens to get 30,000 bonus points.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>uNGbAStPXZc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>120</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586455-shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master/3030-16074/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/120-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/120-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SWGtTd6.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HXCLnUM.jpg</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/74912-shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35782-shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35783-shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master-genesis-screenshot-didn.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/120-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WNl807q.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/120.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Neo Zeed is threatening the world once more. The evil crime syndicate - thought to have been vanquished two years earlier - has returned, headed by a man known only as the Shadow Master. Joe Musashi has felt their presence, and descends from the lonely mountaintops of Japan to face his nemesis once more. As the Shinobi, stronger than steel and faster than a whirlwind, the last keeper of the Oboro Ninjitsu techniques, only he can stop Neo Zeed.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c758fea-6af3-4c64-970b-c0f9d3f7a0c1.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62c912b5-687b-47c3-92d8-33b3fe6a3ebb.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73dbaaf0-41d8-44b2-8fc3-2d4ffc0fc45a.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04f24d08-f7c3-4471-b037-26ab43c93ab9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3911759-0d48-4ee2-a999-702bf8a52c6b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92148036-6cc5-4deb-8af3-51453784623f.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/825980df-62cc-4e5c-9a16-5839887660d9.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c65f7725-e5ae-4365-9934-e261ee96eeb5.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82e527cf-ce4f-4337-bbaa-168ccf6b36ed.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a258b49-c2f7-4681-9516-bf44b8bad2fc.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93cc0f5c-3134-489c-b659-d5353cfedd25.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f7fc8f4e-0aa3-4f9a-b24e-0a128e6c2969.jpg</snapshot18>
	<snapshot19>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a445898-cb5a-4556-8f5f-bf13c28f5d78.jpg</snapshot19>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>