<Game>
	<Name>Shining Force II (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shining Force 2 opens following the thief Slade as he attempts to steal two precious jewels from an ancient shrine. Unbeknown to him these jewels are actually the seal on Zeon, the Devil King, and by stealing them he has let a great evil forth upon the world.In the kingdom of Granseal stands the Tower of the Ancients. The king of Granseal is attacked by an unleashed devil and it falls upon Sir Astral and his pupils, led by the protagonist Bowie, to investigate the attack and the strange occurrences at the Tower. Bowie, the other students of Sir Astral and the mysterious Phoenix Peter will form the basis of the Shining Force; their mission will take them across the world and pit their forces against Zeon's in an attempt to seal him away once again.The Shining ForceThe game is focused on a team of warriors known as the Shining Force. There are several different classes in the game, but they fall under the general areas of melee combat, ranged combat, and magical combat. As they level up they will learn new abilities and more powerful versions of their current abilities, but for the most part they will be increasing in attack, defense, hit points, magic points, and other standard RPG statistical categories.Most characters will also have the ability to be promoted (at level 20 and beyond) to some upgraded class as well; the promoted classes bring even more powerful attacks and abilities to the force. In some cases promotion may even completely change a character's focus, for instance the priest can be promoted to a master monk which is much more powerful physically but loses many of its healing powers. However, when a unit is promoted it will become level 1 in it's new class. This penalty is somewhat mitigated by waiting until later levels to promote the character, but at the same time the promotion classes are much more powerful in some cases, so the decision is a tough one for the player.BattlesBattles in Shining Force 2 involve tactical missions in which 12 (or fewer) members of the player's party face off against a group of enemies. The goal is simple: either defeat all the enemies or their leader. However, players have to be careful, as they will lose if the leader, Bowie, is killed. Unlike most tactical RPGs, there is no game over. Players will be revived in the last church they have visited and given the opportunity to fight the battle again with any experience or items that were earned before being defeated.Combat takes place in standard tactical RPG fashion. The battle occurs on a grid of squares and each character occupies a single square with the exception of some of the most powerful characters in the game. Each character will get the chance to move and perform an action on their turn. The amount of movement is dictated by the characters class and the terrain they are fighting on. After moving there are four actions:AttackAttacking allows the chosen character to enter combat with the enemy. There are two basic types of attacks: melee and ranged. Melee attacks may be made against enemies that are adjacent to the character. Ranged attacks can attack enemies that are two, three, or even more spaces away from the attacking character, but generally cannot be preformed against enemies that are directly adjacent. Some weapons, like spears, allow the character to make melee or ranged attack, but they are generally short ranged. MagicMagic spells generally have a larger range similar to ranged attacks. Generally as the magic attack gets more powerful it also has a larger area of effect, as well as a higher cost. Spells range from elemental magic to summoning to healing magic and death magic.ItemsEach character can carry four items at any given time. Most character use a melee weapon so effectively each character has three spots for items. Most of the time these will be healing items such as healing seeds or antidotes, but since the characters lack a communal item storage, anything that the player wishes to carry must be carried by a character in the force. In battle items are generally used on the characters holding them or someone adjacent, but items like Healing Rain will affect all friendly characters.Stand ByThe last command is to stand by which ends the character's turn. Leading the ForceIn between battles the game takes many cues from standard RPG traditions. As Bowie the player will explore towns, talk to NPCs, buy items, and generally manage the force.The ChurchMost towns have a local church which provides several essential services to the Shining Force. At the church, the player canremove curses or poisons from force membersrevive members that have fallen in battle. Note that if Bowie dies he is automatically revived, as is Peter, the phoenix.promote members to a new class if they are between levels 20 and 40save the gameHeadquartersA headquarters is available in one city which allows players to manage who will appear in the battle party. Players are given the ability to do this outside of the headquarters within a few battles of the party growing beyond the maximum party size. This mobile headquarters also has the ability to store additional items and access them between encounters.Differences from Shining ForceWhile Shining Force 2 is a sequel to the original game the stories are not directly related, but they are in some way connected by  Shining Force Gaiden: Final Conflct for the Game Gear.There are several other differences:The game is no longer broken into chapters. This allows for a lot more exploration and allows players to go back to areas earlier in the game.The interface is vastly improved.There is more breadth in the character classes.Cheat: Secret Configuration ModeWhile the Sega logo is on screen enter the following:Cheat: Secret Configuration ModeWhen the witch asks you to select your file, select a file already beaten (or set a file with the config code) and hold Up and Start and press A.Cheat: Random numbers arent randomTrying to get that spell to always hit or get that +4 on all your power up items, but you just can't seem to get the random to work for you?  Well I discovered the counter to the random number generator is the number of steps taken.Cheat: Random numbers arent randomSay you save your game and use an item for a stat increase.  Well if its not what you wanted, reload and take one more step befor using it.  The pattern I noticed was something like 2, 3, 2, 3, 3, 2, 4.   Thus taking 5 steps gave me my +4.  This works for spells that don't hit very often. Fun with desoul.Cheat: Boost L2 level up TrickWhen one of your characters learns the spell Boost and gets it to level 2, use it and make sure you get your ENTIRE party in range. This will give 49 Exp. to the one who casted Boost L2 REGUARDLESS of what level anybody may be in (which is, like killing a formitable monster that might be much stronger than you). Then, when the Boost effect wears off, you can repeat this sequence and easily get to level 99!Cheat: Boost L2 level up TrickAfter selecting the name for the main character, hold [START] as you choose "End."  Another name screen will pop up for another character and you get to name everyone else.Cheat: Boost L2 level up TrickGive a healer any HP restoring item (I.e. Medical Herb), and use it on themself. This will garner a quick 10 experience points for the healer. If you don't have herbs, use Heal 1 until you run out of MP. You could possibly have Heal 4 and Blast 4 for Sarah before you even finish the first battle in the game if you do it right. Also, if you use Aura and have 3 or more people in the targeted range, the healer will get 25 experience for their effort. If you use Detox on one, the healer will only get 5 experience. Make sure to do this trick if you want easy victories.Cheat: Boost L2 level up TrickThere is one more battle you can do once the game is completed. Once you've defeated Zeon, watched the end credits, and reached the ''FIN'' screen with the two jewels, wait for about 2 mins. A message will appear that says ''and more...''. press a button and you will begin a special battle with all of the old greater devils.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-X0RYtCqrcI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>184</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563341-shining-force-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/shining-force-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shining-force-ii/3030-14528/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2525246-box_sforce2.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/184-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/43794-shining-force-ii-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/184-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33451-shining-force-ii-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33452-shining-force-ii-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/184-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/184-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/184-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/184-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/184-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0qlHcbr.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/184.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Shining Force II is a tactical role-playing game. The player assumes the role of the Shining Force leader, Bowie. When not in combat, the player can explore towns and other locales, talk with people, and set the members and equipment of the army. Some towns have a headquarters where the player can inspect and talk with his allies. While roaming through town or moving throughout the world, one can find both visible and hidden treasures and interact with certain objects. Each ally unit is represented by a character with a background and personality. Some of these characters are hidden, requiring specific events to occur before they will join the force. Each ally unit also has a class, which defines the abilities for that unit. These abilities range from what type of weapons they can use to what kind of spells they can learn. Units can become stronger by fighting enemies and performing various actions which gives them experience points (EXP), which allow them to gain levels. Once a unit reaches level 20, that character has the ability to advance to more powerful class through promotion. Some characters have two different classes they may be promoted to, one of which is only accessible using a special hidden item. Battles take place on a square grid, and each unit occupies a single square. Battle is turn-based. Each turn, a character can move and perform one action: either attack, cast a spell, or use an item. Some commands, such as equipping or dropping an item during the turn, do not count as actions. The battle is won if all enemies are defeated, or if the enemy commander is defeated. If Bowie is defeated in combat or withdraws, the battle is lost and the player is returned to the nearest town, where he can recover his allies and fight the same battle again.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/567fc4a3-92fd-47a6-bdd1-79d12cb9837e.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7a83f94-d6d2-4abc-9539-550a899ef3a3.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df34d661-ab6b-48da-a720-de6b09cda35e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94255c61-ab5d-4e66-9f2d-4d1ccb58b4db.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f98beca1-b158-4598-aaad-569320683b78.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6cd6426f-a60d-4388-91db-83a67929c76b.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ca4aa9f6-7210-4e23-a9af-d534ab61290a.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/091cbb30-c4bb-46ae-862f-b01f1a90e7d4.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bfb7c5a-e6d1-4912-9415-13361f72e83f.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b3fc192-f770-4b87-b70e-f1d1bf80e535.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0089a6a7-ed73-4874-8e9f-3901b47f3cd4.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>