<Game>
	<Name>Shura no Mon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Tsukumo Mutsu, a young student of Karate, has come to the city seeking the Jinmukan dojo, looking for a challenge to prove himself. He's gotten lost, but a young girl helps him out. She happens to be the granddaughter of the head of the dojo, and doesn't want him to get involved with the place, but Tsukumo insists on continuing regardless. He walks right in, and takes on the first guy in a karate gi he comes across...Shura no Mon is a so-called "command action" game based on the manga by Masatoshi Kawahara. The player controls Tsukumo by selecting commands from a list, using different attacks and defensive maneuvers at the appropriate time, with the results shown via brief animated sequences. Between bouts, lightly-animated visual scenes progress the story. The plot closely follows the first arc from the manga, starting with Tsukumo's arrival at the legendary Jinmukan dojo.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/8/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20446</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570434-shura-no-mon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/shura-no-mon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shura-no-mon/3030-32027/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20446-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/9/6/31296_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413453-shura-no-mon-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413454-shura-no-mon-genesis-screenshot-menu-based-or-command-action.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/413455-shura-no-mon-genesis-screenshot-fighting-animation.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/f/6/gfs_8685_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Shura no Mon (修羅の門) is a 1992 strategic fighting game by Sega for the Sega Mega Drive based around Kodansha's Shura no Mon manga. The game is a menu-driven fighting game. You can move around the field while a meter on the left side of the screen rises — this shows your attack charge level. Once your attack is powerful enough, hit C to open a menu of attacks, which you navigate to make an attack. A and B do something; exactly what is unknown.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6deb9dac-9200-4c30-b943-4b008f6133cd.png</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>