<Game>
	<Name>Skitchin' (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Skitchin' is a 1994 combat and stunt racing game from Electronic Arts.Gameplay:The gameplay is very similar to Road Rash and even uses the same software engine.There are six ways to earn cash in this game...1. Race Bonus- This happens when you finish in the top five of any race.2. Thrash Bonus- You earn $5 every time you knockdown an opponent.3. Warp Bonus- This is awarded every time a player warps through the appropriate roadside billboard.4. Trick Bonus- This includes flips, spins and grabs and the money varies depending on the trick.5. Skitchin' Bonus- You earn $1 for every car the skitch.6. Cop Bonus- You earn $1 for every second you skitch a cop car.With the money you earn, you pay for entry fees into the races and replace your equipment. If you run out of money, the game is over. Equipment includes wheels, skates, elbow and knee pads, wrist guards and gloves. There are five varying levels of equipment, economy being the cheapest and worst, and professional being the most expensive and best.Cities featured in the game include (In order of appearance) Vancouver, Denver, San Diego, Seattle, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Washington D.C., Toronto, Detroit, Chicago, Miami and New York City.Each city has a bonus round containing special items and weapons that is unlocked depending on whether a player finishes the course quickly, thrashes several racers, or bones out (successfully completes several different tricks):Vancouver: SpeedDenver: Bone OutSan Diego: ThrashSeattle: SpeedSan Francisco: Bone OutLos Angeles: Thrash (King of the Bus - skitch and thrash for the entire level)Washington, D.C.: Bone OutToronto: SpeedDetroit: ThrashChicago: Bone OutMiami: SpeedNew York City: None (final city)Cheat: PasswordsAt the Warning screen (the one telling you the implications of Skitchin' in real life) press the following combination: B, A, Down, A, Start, Start. This will allow you to enter special codes at the Password screen.Cheat: PasswordsOn the warning screen press B, A, Down, A, Start, StartOn the main menu select password with eith the A,B or C button, but not with StartAfter typing in the password, use the Start button to confirm</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>gaTQ2b9Wypc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4618</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586462-skitchin</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/skitchin</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/skitchin/3030-18512/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4618-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4618-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/39166-skitchin-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138874-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-all-those-warnings-just-made-me.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138867-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138868-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138869-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-the-shop.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138870-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-pre-race-introduction.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138871-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-game-start.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138872-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-ouch-dudes.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138873-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-building-up-some-speed.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138866-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-big-jump.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/138876-skitchin-genesis-screenshot-the-camera-pans-away-as-i-ve-had.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0dGuC8Z.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4618.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You rollerblade (inline skate) down the road, grabbing tows from passing cars. Grab weapons to beat back your opponents. Race from city to city to earn money. Buy better skates, weapons, and protection with your winnings. This game is clearly derived both in technology and in design from the hit Road Rash series, and was released during the great rollerblading boom of the early-to-mid nineties.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fe7d32f-5468-4669-a23b-2eda1e3112e7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d7d5b34-9deb-49f0-a60f-55fb27c289af.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5be5e81-7bde-4b77-bd0f-0b520edc4141.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>