<Game>
	<Name>Slap Fight MD (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>At first glance, Slap Fight MD is a direct conversion of the 1986 arcade classic Slap Fight from Toaplan and Taito, featuring a faithful conversion of the original title with several difficulty settings, as well as both original and arranged soundtracks. However, also included on the cartridge is a completely new sequel with all-new stages, bosses, graphics, and music. The basic gameplay is identical: a vertically-scrolling shooter where power-ups cycle through a list to choose from, and it is possible to construct massively-wide ships with incredible firepower. Slap Fight MD also adds the ability to jettison your ship's power-ups causing a massive screen-filling explosion that can potentially save your life.Cheat: MutekiPause the game, then push Right, Left, Right, Down, Up, Down, Left. You will hear a sound.Effects:-You will be invincible.-During the game, hold B and push C to select between weapons.-Pause, hold Right and push Start to skip areas.-Pause, hold Down and push Start to lose a life.-Pause, hold Up and hold Start to speed up the game (until you let go of the buttons)Cheat: MutekiGo into the options screen and push A B and C at the same timeCheat: Instant livesGet over 9930000 points. From now on whenever you shoot something you will get an extra life.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/6/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tengen Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20451</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570423-slap-fight</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/slap-fight-md</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20451-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/8/5/31285_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/77178-slap-fight-md-genesis-screenshot-normal-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/77176-slap-fight-md-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-first-level.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/77177-slap-fight-md-genesis-screenshot-pick-up-stars-to-buy-powerups.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/77179-slap-fight-md-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-in-special-mode.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/77175-slap-fight-md-genesis-screenshot-slap-fight-special-mode.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/e/0/gfs_9961_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/7/d/gfs_9961_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/a/d/gfs_9961_2_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Slap Fight MD (スラップファイト) is a 1993 shoot-'em-up game developed by Toaplan and MNM Software for the Sega Mega Drive and published by Tengen exclusively in Japan and South Korea. Two games are available: a port of Toaplan's 1986 arcade shoot-'em-up Slap Fight with the choice to use either remastered music or the original sound, and a separate game called Slap Fight MD, that has the same gameplay mechanics but new art, levels, weapons, and music (composed by Yuzo Koshiro). The option to switch between Slap Fight and Slap Fight MD is in the Options menu under "Game Mode," with Normal enabling Slap Fight and Special enabling Slap Fight MD.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66011f0f-889f-4b74-81f4-cdbb14f2301e.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88407603-f830-445a-b909-10f44c3af375.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6efbcd4a-ec82-48c2-bfda-2f1a1a042053.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>Tengen</Publisher>
</game>