<Game>
	<Name>Sonic Compilation ~ Sonic Classics (World) (v1.1)</Name>
	<plot>Sonic Classics is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Sega,which was released in Europe in 1995.Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2Enter the level select cheat. At the sound test menu in the level select screen, play the following tracks: 4, 1, 2 and then 6. Now simply select any level. All the chaos emeralds are now in your possesion, meaning you can become Super Sonic by collecting at least 50 rings and jumping, and you do not have to worry about doing any of the bonus rounds.Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2At the title screen, enter the following code: Up, C, down, C, left, C, right, C, then hold A+C and press the start button. When the game starts, their should be lots of numbers which mess up the score and time words in the top left corner of the screen. B changed Sonic into an object, C will plant the object onto the screen and A will change the object. Press B again to change back to Sonic.Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2Enable the level select code, and at the level select screen there is a sound test option. Play tracks 1, 9, 9, 2, 1, 1, 2, and then 4. Select the level you want to play, but hold down A then press start. Screen coordinates will appear instead of a score and the number of objects displayed will appear instead of the time remaining. Press B to change Sonic into an object, press C to plant an object on the screen and press A to cycle through available objects. Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2NOTE: This code does not work properly when playing the game as Tails alone.Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2Chose Sonic 2 and go to options, then play sounds 19, 65, 09, 17 in that order. then press start and hold down A.  When you get to the title scrren press staat and the level select will be there!!!Cheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2At the title screen in Sonic 1, press Up, Down, Left, and Right.  You should hear a sound confirming it.  Then press and hold A and press StartCheat: All emeralds code for Sonic 2At the title screen, enter the following code: Up, up, up, down, down, down then up. This changes Tails' name to Miles. Enter the code again to change the name back to what it was before.Cheat: Stage 2: Frankly - RRRH Stage 3: Humpty - CPCG Stage 4: Coconuts - RCHY Stage 5: Davy Sproket - CBBP Stage 6: Sqweel - CRCP Stage 7: Dynamight - PYRB Stage 8: Grounder - YGPH Stage 9: Spike - YPHB Stage 10: Sir Fuzzy Logik - RYCH Stage 11: Dragon Breath - GPBC Stage 12: Scratch - RHHY Stage 13: Dr. Robotnik - YHBBCheat: 2 Frankly RRRH GCYY 3 Humpty CPCG YPCP 4 Coconuts RCHY BGCB  5 Davy Sproket RPGG 6 Sqweel YYCG 7 Dynamight PCBB 8 Grounder CYHY  9 Spike PBBG 10 Sir Fuzzy Logik CGRY 11 Dragon Breath BYYH  12 Scratch GCCB 13 Dr. Robotnik HCPH Cheat: Stage 2: Frankly - BBGY  Stage 3: Humpty - GYGC  Stage 4: Coconuts - PPRH  Stage 5: Davy Sproket - GRPB  Stage 6: Sqweel - PCGY  Stage 7: Dynamight - BPGH  Stage 8: Grounder - CPHY  Stage 9: Spike - PGHC  Stage 10: Sir Fuzzy Logik - GBYH  Stage 11: Dragon Breath - GPHR  Stage 12: Scratch - RGHB  Stage 13: Dr. Robotnik - RRCY Cheat: Enter these passwords after selecting &amp;quot;Continue&amp;quot; to skip ahead to the desired level.Cheat: R = Red BeanY = Yellow BeanG = Green BeanB = Blue BeanP = Purple BeanC = Clear (Garbage) BeanH = Has Bean (the little orange fellow)Cheat: At the Title Screen, press (A), (B), or (C) on controller 1 to make the ''e'', ''a'', and ''n'' in ''Mean'' jump. Press (A), (B), or (C) on controller 2 to make the ''e'', ''a'', and ''n'' in ''Bean'' jump.Cheat: Use this code provided, then go to sound select, and select sounds 9F for the ending or 9E for the creditsCheat: When you ride the green block accross a sea of lave, there are a couple of big blocks in front of you with rings on. If you hold the D-PAD DOWN button, Sonic will crouch. The green block will go underneath the blocks, but sonic will remain on it, and pass through the walls. Note that this ONLY WORKS WHILE CROUCHINGCheat: Using the level select cheat, scroll down and select "Special Stage".  Upon completion on the stage, you will receive a chaos emerald, and begin playing your game on the first stage.  At this point, RESET the game via the RESET button on your Genesis, re-enter the level select code, and repeat the process.  You will enter the next Special Stage level, and have a chance to earn the 2nd Emerald.  You can repeat this process over and over until you have all 6 Chaos Emeralds.  However, once you have all six, do NOT reset the system and select a level, or else you will lose them all.Cheat: Press up, up, up, down, down, down, up at the title screen Cheat: Go to the Options menu from the title screen, and then while there go to Sound Select and play sound number 7E. You'll notice that the game music had stopped. Now start the game and you'll be able to play the game without any music and sounds.Cheat: Weird trick, but you can play this game in slow motion. First, enter the level select code, found somewhere in the list of all other codes. Then start your game in any level. When you start, press pause. Then hold down B button and try to do anything with Sonic. The game will play in slow motion as long as you hold down the B button.Cheat: In Oil Ocean Zone, if you manage to take a hit and end up landing in one of those green-and-gold checkered cannons, you'll fall right out, but you'll be moving at twice your normal speed as well as jumping twice your normal height(with twice as much gravity).  A good place for doing this would be in Oil Ocean Zone, Act 2, near the first set of pop-tops and cannons.  Just jump into the semi-hidden bed of spikes on the right and land in the cannon.Cheat: Note:  Moving at twice normal velocity can often get you stuck in a wall.  Also, this wears off if you Super Spin Dash or Spin Dash.  It also only lasts for that Act.Cheat: Normally, when you turn into super sonic you lose tails behind you all the time.  Well, after you put in the debug cheat and have started a level (preferrably Emerald Hill), turn yourself into a box and place it somewhere on the floor WHILE you are super sonic. It should be a switch places box. Hit it and you will see tails will have a permanent invincible circle around him. He will stay like this through the whole level, he will keep up with super sonic or even out run him. A very fun glitch for 2 players.Cheat: If you beat the Death Egg with Tails you get the Tails ending.Cheat: Go to the sound test (not the one on the level select) and put in 19, 65, 09, 17, 01, 01, 02, 04 (press A after each one). There won't be a confirmation sound. Start the game by pressing Start on the first option (character select) and you should have 14 continues.Cheat: First, you enter the stage select code, shown above. Then you go into the Special Stage in the stage select menu. Every time you finish the special stage press reset and go back to the special stage. Keep doing this until you get the sixth emerald. Then you don't press reset. It will just zap you with your six emeralds into emerald hill. Get the last emerald on Emerald Hill get  50  rings and jump to be super sonic. Be careful to not run out of rings or else you will change into Sonic again. The rings start dissapearing when you are Super sonic.Cheat: First, enable the level select cheat and the debug mode which are available here. For this to work, you must choose Sonic and Tails as the players. After entering the codes, choose any stage from the level select menu(preferrably stage 1) As soon as you can move Sonic, hold down, and press C(don't let go of down on the D-pad). This will activate Sonic's spin; Tails will copy the Sonic spin also. Press the B button and Sonic will become the Debug cursor.(Tails will be locked in the sonic spin move). Press A until you(the debug cursor), displays an enemy sprite, like the monkey or that bee robot. Now that the debug cursor displays an enemy sprite, move the debug cursor to where Tails is, and repeatedly tap C. This will produce enemies where Tails is, and since Tails is locked in the sonic spin move, he will destroy the enemies. As Tails destroys enemies in this position, press C more until the score for destroying an enemy increases from 100 to 8000 to a 1up. Once you have enough 1ups, press B again to revert to Sonic.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4624</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/581774-sonic-classics</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sonic-classics</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4624-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4624-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54792-sonic-classics-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/143156-sonic-classics-genesis-screenshot-game-selection-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/5/gfs_36383_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/5/gfs_36383_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/7/5/gfs_36383_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/6/5/gfs_36383_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/na94lrO.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4624.png</clearlogo1>
</game>