<Game>
	<Name>Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Knuckles the Echidna is now in your control.Sonic &amp; Knuckles is a 2D action platformer developed by Sonic Team (with assistance from Sega Technical Institute, which would be the last Sonic game they contributed to) and published by Sega for the Sega Genesis on October 18, 1994.The direct sequel to Sonic the Hedgehog 3, Sonic &amp; Knuckles continues the story of Sonic the Hedgehog, who must venture deeper through Angel Island to track down Dr. Robotnik (whose orbital weapon, the Death Egg, crashed back down to the floating island). Along the way, he is still being pursued by Knuckles the Echidna who, still believing that Sonic is planning to steal the island's Master Emerald, hinders his progress and is still hiding the Chaos Emeralds around the floating island.While Miles "Tails" Prower is no longer a playable character (or companion), players can now play through the game as Knuckles (previously only playable in Sonic the Hedgehog 3's Competition Mode), in which he is less agile than Sonic (and cannot use the special jumping powers of elemental shields), but has the unique abilities to glide through air, climb walls, and punch out certain obstacles (as well as having to face more difficult boss battles as an added challenge). He has his own side-story, taking place after the main campaign, in which a surviving badnik (the EggRobo) takes Dr. Robotnik's place in finding the Master Emerald (though it is not sure, until the end of the game, who the main antagonist is).The unique Sonic &amp; Knuckles cartridge, with Sonic the Hedgehog 3 locked on top of it.Sonic &amp; Knuckles is the only Sega Genesis game to utilize special "lock-on technology" (in which the unique game cartridge features its own Sega Genesis cartridge slot at the top, similar to the Game Genie accessory), so that the game can access data from certain other Genesis games. This allows players to play through Sonic the Hedgehog 2 as Knuckles (complete with his unique abilities), and allows players to combine both Sonic the Hedgehog 3 and Sonic &amp; Knuckles into one "complete" game with special features.Ports and CompilationsThe game was later ported (alongside Sonic the Hedgehog 3) by Sega to PC (running Windows 95 and up) as Sonic &amp; Knuckles Collection (published by Sega for Japan in 1997 and Expert for North America in 1999). The game retains the same gameplay as the Sega Genesis version, but the music was re-done in MIDI format. It also includes the option to play Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles (both games locked-on) and also includes a Sonic-themed screensaver.Sega compilations that include both Sonic &amp; Knuckles and all of its lock-on functionality (as separate modes) include Sonic Jam (on July 31, 1997 for the Saturn), Sonic Mega Collection (on November 10, 2002 for the GameCube), and Sonic Mega Collection Plus (for the PlayStation 2 and Xbox on November 2, 2004 and for the PC on March 9, 2007). Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection (for the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 on February 10, 2009) includes the game but none of the lock-on functionality. Sonic Classics Collection (for the Nintendo DS on March 2, 2010 in Europe only) includes the game and both the Sonic the Hedgehog 2 and Sonic the Hedgehog 3 functionality.The game has been ported and digitally released on the Wii (via Wii Virtual Console on September 9, 2009) and Xbox 360 (via Xbox Live Arcade on February 15, 2010). Both releases are programmed so that if the owner has downloaded this and any of the three Sonic games originally required for lock-on functionality, he/she can play that Sonic game as if it was going through the Sonic &amp; Knuckles lock-on technology.Gameplay:In Sonic &amp; Knuckles, players control either Sonic the Hedgehog or Knuckles the Echidna as they navigate through 6-8 levels (known as "Zones", split into different "Acts") to track down Dr. Robotnik (in Sonic's campaign) or the lone EggRobo (in Knuckles's campaign). Players must dodge dangerous obstacles (such as spikes and bottomless pits) and plow through enemies (with attacks such as the rolling jump) to reach the end of each Act.ZonesLike Sonic the Hedgehog 3, each main level (known as Zones) are split into two unique sections (known as Acts), each act with a unique setting (such as Sandopolis Zone starting out in the vast desert and ending up inside a haunted pyramid) and music. The first act ends with one or more mini-bosses to fight and the second act ends with a boss to fight.Hidden Palace Zone and Sky Sanctuary Zone have only one "act" and both serve as two "acts" to one "level". Both are heavily shortened and modified for Knuckles's campaign (the first as a simple transition and the second as the Knuckles's final boss battle). Death Egg Zone and Doomsday Zone cannot be played as Knuckles. Doomsday Zone can only be played as Super Sonic (or Hyper Sonic in Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles) and has only one "act", serving as the Sonic's final boss battle.In Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles, all of the Sonic &amp; Knuckles levels appear immediately after all of the Sonic the Hedgehog 3 levels.Mushroom Hill ZoneFlying Battery ZoneSandopolis ZoneLava Reef ZoneHidden Palace ZoneSky Sanctuary ZoneDeath Egg Zone (Sonic Only)Doomsday Zone (Super/Hyper Sonic Only)Lock-On TechnologyUsing the game's special "lock-on technology", players can access special modes and features by putting any Sega Genesis cartridge on the cartridge's additional cartridge slot.Booting up the game without any cartridge locked-on plays Sonic &amp; Knuckles normally. With most cartridges locked-on, the game shows up a special "No Way!" screen (in which players can play a secret random pre-generated Special Stage by pressing all buttons simultaneously). Blue SphereThe screen that appears after locking on Sonic the Hedgehog.With Sonic the Hedgehog locked-on, one of the message in the "No Way!" screen changes to "No Way?" and pressing all buttons simultaneously unlocks a deeper Special Stage game (known as "Get Blue Spheres!" or, retroactively, as "Blue Sphere"). Players can play a series of pre-generated Special Stage levels (up to 134,217,728 configurations of varying difficulty) and keep track of their progress using a 12-digit numerical password.Earning a "Perfect" in the stage (by collecting all possible rings) skips ahead 10 stages. Players start at level 1 and can change the password before entering the stage (including passwords given out after completing a Special Stage with any other cartridge).There were plans to make Knuckles playable in Sonic the Hedgehog, but the concept was later scrapped because of issues with Knuckles's abilities in the game's levels. Knuckles the Echidna in Sonic the Hedgehog 2Knuckles in Emerald Hill Zone, the first level of Sonic the Hedgehog 2.With Sonic the Hedgehog 2 locked-on, players can play Knuckles the Echidna in Sonic the Hedgehog 2, in which they can play through the entirety of Sonic the Hedgehog 2 as Knuckles. Knuckles retains all of his abilities, and the game adds some new hidden items (that makes use of Knuckles's abilities). Two-player mode (including Time Trials mode) is disabled.Sonic 3 &amp; KnucklesKnuckles in Angel Island Zone, the first level of Sonic the Hedgehog 3.With Sonic the Hedgehog 3 locked-on, players can play Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles, which combines both games into one "complete" game (with the Sonic the Hedgehog 3 campaign leading to the Sonic &amp; Knuckles campaign in one long story). With this setup, players can play the Sonic the Hedgehog 3 campaign as Knuckles (complete with branching paths, due to his abilities, and a harder EggRobo boss at the end of each zone), play through the Sonic &amp; Knuckles campaign as Tails (or as Sonic with Tails), and save their progress in the Sonic &amp; Knuckles campaign (complete with more save slots).In addition, players who reach the Sonic &amp; Knuckles campaign with all seven Chaos Emeralds can trade them for the ability to collect seven Super Emeralds (Chaos Emeralds powered-up by the Master Emerald). When they have all seven Super Emeralds, they can transform into Hyper Sonic (who, in addition to the abilities as Super Sonic, gains the ability to perform a mid-air dash that flashes the screen, clearing all enemies on the screen), Hyper Knuckles (who, in addition to the abilities as Super Knuckles, triggers a earthquake when clinging on to a wall, clearing all enemies on the screen), or Super Tails (who has the abilities of Super Sonic as well as being surrounded by four super-powered Flickies that automatically charge at enemies on the screen).Cheat: Debug mode and all Emeralds (locked-on to Sonic 2)First activate and go to the Stage Select. Play the tracks in Sound Test with button B in this order:  01 09 09 04 01 00 01 08  This enables the Debug code, you should hear a ring chime if the code is entered correctly. start the selected level with A+start.  To get all 7 Chaos Emeralds, input this code the same way:  01 06 07 07 07 02 01 06  You should hear the Emerald chime. note: this code may not work without the Debug codeCheat: Debug mode and all Emeralds (locked-on to Sonic 2)While playing sonic 3 and knuckles press Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up in the mushroom hill zone, while on one of the pully things. (Just like level select in normal Sonic and Knuckles.) I think you have to do the level select code first.Cheat: Debug mode and all Emeralds (locked-on to Sonic 2)Start a game and go to Angel Island Zone Act 1.  Go to one of the swings that you hang from and grab on.  While Sonic is swinging, press Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up.  You will hear a ring if you entered the code correctly.  Pause the game and press A to take you back to the title screen.  Press Down twice to find the newly unlocked Sound Test menu.  Enter it, where you can play all of the sounds/music in the game and warp to any level. Cheat: Blue Spheres PasswordsLock-On Sonic 1 or Sonic Classics, at the No Way! screen press A + B + C. The screen will now say ''Get Blue Spheres!''. At the bottom of the screen is a Code Number Password, change it to any of the fallowing passwords and press Start to activate it.Cheat: Walk through wallsOn levels that allow you to travel upwards or downwards greatly as you progress as Sonic, go to an area where Knuckles' path starts. Hold down and wait for the screen to drop, then jump (do not spindash). If done correctly at a area that will cause this, the screen will shift and scroll in a loop back to you. During this time, you are free to walk through walls. This can also be done in select areas of levels where there is no path for Knuckles.Cheat: Bonus game trickPut a game other than Sonic 2 or 3 in the top of the Sonic &amp; Knuckles cartridge. Then, when it shows the picture of the trio and the message at the top, press A, B, and C simultaneously to play Bonus Games.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)1. Enter the level select code by pressing Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up on the swinging vines in Angel Island.  Press Start then A to restart the game.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)2. Enter the Level Select area (Sound Test) and select Mushroom Hill Zone Act 1Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)3. From here, grab on to the pully levers and press Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up.  Press Start then A.  From this point forward, push and hold down buttons A, B, and CCheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)4. Enter Sound Test again.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)5. Select a stage of your choice.  Once the Zone and Act title dissapear, you may release A, B, and C.  There are a few differences in button layout now.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)A: (Normal Mode)Makes Sonic jump normally.  (Debug Mode)Duplicates the selected item.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)B: Toggles between Normal Mode and Debug ModeCheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)C: (Normal Mode)Reverses Gravity.  (Debug Mode)Toggles through the level\\\'s templates.Cheat: Debug Mode (Locked-On to Sonic 3)In Mushroom Hill Zone, while hanging off one of the pulling machines, press left three times, right three times, and up three times. You should hear the ring sound. Pause and press A to be taken to the title screen. Highlight either Sonic or knuckles as your character, and press start while holding A. The menu shows all levels in the game, but some are specific to a certain character, so you can't play those if you picked an incompatible character. Any time you want to exit and select a different level, just repeat the code from right after the pulling machine part.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>EaD7pJWCAJI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20943</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586468-sonic-and-knuckles</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sonic-knuckles</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sonic-knuckles/3030-18115/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20943-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/733-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/49609-sonic-knuckles-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20943-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30837-sonic-knuckles-genesis-screenshot-flying-battery.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30838-sonic-knuckles-genesis-screenshot-sandopolis.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30839-sonic-knuckles-genesis-screenshot-knuckles-is-also-a-playable.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30840-sonic-knuckles-genesis-screenshot-lava-reef.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/20943-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kgPcJnI.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/20943.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When Sonic 3 is locked-on to the original Sonic the Hedgehog or Sonic Compilation via Lock-On Technology, the result is a deceptive "No Way!" screen. However, by pressing the A, B and C buttons together players can access Special Stage levels, commonly known as the "Blue Sphere" levels. Levels can be accessed by inputting a twelve digit code, every number combination a different variation of a Special Stage level.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/916f6e99-1305-4c56-978f-54aa7edf1d60.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/585ecbc0-20de-49e0-92da-f39297d756d5.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>