<Game>
	<Name>Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World)</Name>
	<plot>Placing the first Sonic game, or most other Genesis/Mega Drive games, into the Sonic &amp; Knuckles cartridge will display a screen                              depicting Sonic, Tails, Knuckles and Robotnik underneath scrolling text that repeats "No way? No way!". By pressing the A, B and C buttons together, a minigame based on the Chaos Emerald bonus levels is unlocked, called "Blue Sphere". There are over 100 million unique levels. The last level, "Special Stage", repeats itself once the level is beaten. Only by locking the original Sonic the Hedgehog or Sonic Compilation in the Sonic &amp; Knuckles cart can one play through all the stages. The other Genesis/Mega Drive games will only play one level each, which will infinitely repeat. Despite being near randomly generated, the levels are playable for the most part, even if many bits and pieces of levels get recycled. On another note, some levels may be nearly impossible to complete while others are not as difficult.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sonic_&amp;_KnucklesCheat: Alternate DebugEnter at soundtest ''19, 65, 09, 17'', then press A + start, then when sonic and tails pop up, press A + Start to go to the level select screen. On the sound test area, enter ''01 09 09 02 01 01 02 04'' and then press A + Start. This is an alternate debug to the others.Cheat: Alternate DebugPress up, up, up, down, down, down, up at the title screen Cheat: Alternate DebugFirst enter the level select code (Mentioned above).Now,go to sound test option,and play the following tunes-1,9,9,2,1,1,2,4-It should make a ring sound when track 4 is played to signify you've entered it correctly,now select the stage you want to go to,and press start while holding A until the stage starts,and you'll have debug activated.Here are the controls---- B-Turn Debug on/off A-Switch object C-Put down object selected Pressing A while the game is paused will cause the game to reset.Cheat: Alternate DebugAt the title screen, press Up, Up, Up, Down, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right.  Then, hold A and press Start to be taken to the level select menu.Cheat: Alternate DebugAt the title screen, select Options. Highlight Sound Test then play the following music and sounds: 19, 65, 09 and 17. You will hear a ring-collecting sound for correct code entry. Then press START to return to the title screen. Highlight 1-Player, hold the A Button and press START. You are directed to Level Select Screen. Choose a level then press START to begin.Cheat: Alternate DebugGo to the Options menu from the title screen, and then while there go to Sound Select and play sound number 7E. You'll notice that the game music had stopped. Now start the game and you'll be able to play the game without any music and sounds.Cheat: Alternate DebugWeird trick, but you can play this game in slow motion. First, enter the level select code, found somewhere in the list of all other codes. Then start your game in any level. When you start, press pause. Then hold down B button and try to do anything with Sonic. The game will play in slow motion as long as you hold down the B button.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayFor all those who like to play honest instead of cheating all those Chaos Emeralds together, there's an alternate - yet simple - way to become Super Sonic in Emerald Hill Zone 1. It involves some serious work, however:Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate way1. Complete the special stages as you would usually do and collect as many emeralds as you want.2. Press RESET.3. Start a new game USING THE OPTIONS MENU! This is crucial! Otherwise your emeralds are gone for good!4. Continue collecting the emeralds, if you don't have them all, yet and repeat point two and three until you got them all.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayIf you did everything correctly, after your last reset you should have all the emeralds from the very beginning and without using any code ever thus making Super Sonic available from the very beginning.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayThis has been tested and confirmed with the PAL version of Sonic 2 playing on a PAL Megadrive II.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayIn Oil Ocean Zone, if you manage to take a hit and end up landing in one of those green-and-gold checkered cannons, you'll fall right out, but you'll be moving at twice your normal speed as well as jumping twice your normal height(with twice as much gravity).  A good place for doing this would be in Oil Ocean Zone, Act 2, near the first set of pop-tops and cannons.  Just jump into the semi-hidden bed of spikes on the right and land in the cannon.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayNote:  Moving at twice normal velocity can often get you stuck in a wall.  Also, this wears off if you Super Spin Dash or Spin Dash.  It also only lasts for that Act.Cheat: Becoming Super Sonic in Emerald Hill - an alternate wayNormally, when you turn into super sonic you lose tails behind you all the time.  Well, after you put in the debug cheat and have started a level (preferrably Emerald Hill), turn yourself into a box and place it somewhere on the floor WHILE you are super sonic. It should be a switch places box. Hit it and you will see tails will have a permanent invincible circle around him. He will stay like this through the whole level, he will keep up with super sonic or even out run him. A very fun glitch for 2 players.Cheat: Secret Tails endingIf you beat the Death Egg with Tails you get the Tails ending.Cheat: 14 ContinuesGo to the sound test (not the one on the level select) and put in 19, 65, 09, 17, 01, 01, 02, 04 (press A after each one). There won't be a confirmation sound. Start the game by pressing Start on the first option (character select) and you should have 14 continues.Cheat: 14 ContinuesThis code only works for Sonic. First, do the Level Select cheat. In the Level Select menu, go to Sound Test and hear the sounds 04, 01, 02, 06 in this order. If done correctly, you'll hear a Chao Emerald sound effect. Now, select any stage from this menu and not only you'll be able to turn into Super Sonic with 50 rings but also you'll get Sonic's second ending after beating Death Egg Zone.Cheat: 14 ContinuesFirst activate and go to the Stage Select. Play the tracks in Sound Test with button B in this order:  01 09 09 04 01 00 01 08  This enables the Debug code, you should hear a ring chime if the code is entered correctly. start the selected level with A+start.  To get all 7 Chaos Emeralds, input this code the same way:  01 06 07 07 07 02 01 06  You should hear the Emerald chime. note: this code may not work without the Debug code  Cheat: 14 ContinuesFirst, head to the [I]Options[/I] menu from the title screen, and then into the [I]Sound Select[/I] menu from there. Play the following sounds in this order:19650917After that, press the [I]C[/I] button and then [I]Start[/I]. You will be taken back to the title screen. Now, when you see Sonic and Tails (Mils) appear on the screen, press and hold [I]A[/I] and press [I]Start[/I] while holding [I]A[/I] to be taken to the Level Select menu.From this menu, enter the [I]Sound Test[/I] feature, and play the following sounds in this order:04010206If done correctly, you will hear a familiar tune, confirming the [I]Super Sonic[/I] code was done correctly. Exit this menu and start the game as normal. Once you collect a minumu of 50 coins in any level, Jump (Press [I]A[/I]) to activate the Super Sonic code.Cheat: 14 ContinuesFirst, you enter the stage select code, shown above. Then you go into the Special Stage in the stage select menu. Every time you finish the special stage press reset and go back to the special stage. Keep doing this until you get the sixth emerald. Then you don't press reset. It will just zap you with your six emeralds into emerald hill. Get the last emerald on Emerald Hill get  50  rings and jump to be super sonic. Be careful to not run out of rings or else you will change into Sonic again. The rings start dissapearing when you are Super sonic.Cheat: 14 ContinuesFirst, enable the level select cheat and the debug mode which are available here. For this to work, you must choose Sonic and Tails as the players. After entering the codes, choose any stage from the level select menu(preferrably stage 1) As soon as you can move Sonic, hold down, and press C(don't let go of down on the D-pad). This will activate Sonic's spin; Tails will copy the Sonic spin also. Press the B button and Sonic will become the Debug cursor.(Tails will be locked in the sonic spin move). Press A until you(the debug cursor), displays an enemy sprite, like the monkey or that bee robot. Now that the debug cursor displays an enemy sprite, move the debug cursor to where Tails is, and repeatedly tap C. This will produce enemies where Tails is, and since Tails is locked in the sonic spin move, he will destroy the enemies. As Tails destroys enemies in this position, press C more until the score for destroying an enemy increases from 100 to 8000 to a 1up. Once you have enough 1ups, press B again to revert to Sonic.Cheat: 14 ContinuesFirst, go to the [I]Options[/I] menu from the main screen. From here, head to the [I]Sound Select[/I] menu and play the following sounds in the order they are placed below:19650917Once you have played each one (1 time only), press the [I]C[/I] button and then press [I]Start[/I] to be brought back to the title screen. Now, when you see Sonic and Tails (Miles) appear on screen, hold down the [I]A[/I] button and press [I]Start[/I] while holding [I]A[/I] to finish off the code. You will be brought to a menu where you have access to play any level in the game, whether you've completed the level you wish to play or not.Cheat: 14 ContinuesActivate level select and hold C while selecting a stage to darken the level.  The effect wears off when you die or when you beat the level.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VzcVOXpf740</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20944</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563343-sonic-the-hedgehog-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sonic-the-hedgehog-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sonic-the-hedgehog-2/3030-1662/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20944-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TCvbLsq.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/136254-sonic-the-hedgehog-2-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20944-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26970-sonic-the-hedgehog-2-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26972-sonic-the-hedgehog-2-genesis-screenshot-two-player-mode.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/20944-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7PPFHkc.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/20944.png</clearlogo1>
</game>