<Game>
	<Name>Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3 (World)</Name>
	<plot>Placing the first Sonic game, or most other Genesis/Mega Drive games, into the Sonic &amp; Knuckles cartridge will display a screen                              depicting Sonic, Tails, Knuckles and Robotnik underneath scrolling text that repeats "No way? No way!". By pressing the A, B and C buttons together, a minigame based on the Chaos Emerald bonus levels is unlocked, called "Blue Sphere". There are over 100 million unique levels. The last level, "Special Stage", repeats itself once the level is beaten. Only by locking the original Sonic the Hedgehog or Sonic Compilation in the Sonic &amp; Knuckles cart can one play through all the stages. The other Genesis/Mega Drive games will only play one level each, which will infinitely repeat. Despite being near randomly generated, the levels are playable for the most part, even if many bits and pieces of levels get recycled. On another note, some levels may be nearly impossible to complete while others are not as difficult.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sonic_&amp;_KnucklesCheat: Level SelectWhen the "SEGA" screen fades, quickly press Up-up-down-down-up-up-up-up.  If you have done this right, you should be able to scroll down to "Sound Test" below "Competition".  The ups and downs are very difficult in the short amount of time provided, but with practice, it is pretty easy.Cheat: Level SelectStart a game and go to Angel Island Zone Act 1.  Go to one of the swings that you hang from and grab on.  While Sonic is swinging, press Left, Left, Left, Right, Right, Right, Up, Up, Up.  You will hear a ring if you entered the code correctly.  Pause the game and press A to take you back to the title screen.  Press Down twice to find the newly unlocked Sound Test menu.  Enter it, where you can play all of the sounds/music in the game and warp to any level. Cheat: Level SelectEnter the following code in any stage while Debug Mode is enteredCheat: Access level select using Sonic 2To do this, you must have a copy of Sonic the Hedgehog 2.  activate sonic 2's level select (sound test: 19, 65, 9, 17)Now, without turning the system off, remove the cartidge, and insert the Sonic 3 Cartridge. Reset the Genesis console, keeping the A button held down at all times. On the title screen, press down untill you see sound test.Success! you now have an easy (but different) way to access the level select and sound test!Cheat: Access level select using Sonic 2If you are afrade of this damaging your games, please, don't try it. I have never had any game be damaged by this trick.Cheat: Access level select using Sonic 2BONUS: If you look at the level Icons, you will see the icons from sonic 2. If you look carefully, you will see the Icon for Hidden Palace Zone, a level that was "removed" from Sonic 2!Cheat: Access level select using Sonic 2Cheat: Access level select using Sonic 2Make your way to the end of Act 1 of Hydrocity Zone (Zone 2). When facing the mini-boss, keep yourself underwater until the water warning music plays. Then jump out of the water.  The game should now be playing the mini-boss music from Sonic and Knuckles, which wasn't out at the time (the music was evidently included in Sonic 3 to make the backwards compatibility feature easier).Cheat: Access level select using Sonic 2In the Icecap Zone Act 1, when you come to a wall that only Knuckles can bust through, Hold the Down button until sonic or tails looks down, and the screen pans all the way down.  Then Press up and jump at the same time.  The screen will start to rotate, walk in the direction of the wall and you will walk right thru it.  This only works on Act 1 of The Icecap Zone.Cheat: 100000 PointsManage to beat a stage at with your time at exactly 9:59 and you'll net yourself an easy 100000 points. Cheat: 100000 PointsWhen playing a level after enabling the level select cheat, pause the game, then press the C button to advance the game by one frame.Cheat: 100000 PointsOn the level select menu, play sounds 01, 03, 05, 07. Highlight Special Stage 2 and press A + Start.Cheat: 100000 PointsGet up to Launch Base Zone.  Sound any of the alarms, so that the Kamikaze birds come after you.  Charge up a Super Sonic Dash in between the alarm, but do not let go of the button.  The birds will continually crash into you.  After about 30 seconds, you will have gained enough points to get an extra life.  Continue the process for as many lives as you want.Cheat: 100000 PointsWhen you have done the level select cheat go to the Stage Select screen and choose the special zone for playing Blue Sphere. Select Knuckles as your character and start, when you quit and go back to Stage Select and choose a stage, you'll be Knuckles without having to use the Sonic and Knuckles add on.Cheat: 100000 PointsWhen playing any level which you have accesed using the cheat menu , pause the game and hold down B. Whilst B is held down , the game will play in slow motion mode. Cheat: 100000 PointsAfter entering the level select and debug code, you can use the debug to turn yourself into Super Sonic without getting all of the Chaos Emeralds. With the Debug On, go into any level and press Button B to turn yourself into a ring. Then press A to turn yourself into a monitor. Now, press button C to duplicate the monitor, and then B again to change back into Sonic. Jump on the monitor and you will become Super Sonic.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>eiXvuw6OJTk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20945</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586472-sonic-the-hedgehog-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sonic-the-hedgehog-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sonic-the-hedgehog-3/3030-4628/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20945-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/z2TB4Qc.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79776-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20945-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20945-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20945-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/20945-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30690-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/357870-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-when-inserted-in-a.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30691-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-knuckles-takes-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30692-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-hydro-city.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30693-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-marble-gardens.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/30694-sonic-the-hedgehog-3-genesis-screenshot-sonic-vs-tarzan.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/20945-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VrEcuDQ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/20945.png</clearlogo1>
</game>