<Game>
	<Name>Sonic Eraser (Japan) (SegaNet)</Name>
	<plot>Sonic Eraser is a puzzle game very similar to Columns that features Sega mascot Sonic the Hedgehog. Pieces in different arrangements drop into a well; if two or more matching pieces touch, they disappear and the above pieces fall to take their place. There are four different single-player game modes:1. Round: Each stage starts with pieces in the well already. There are several spinning green pieces, which must all be destroyed to finish the stage.2. Normal: A standard endless mode in which the game speed continually rises as matches are made.3. Doubt: No white-colored blocks will appear in the drop formations, but often a random block in the formation will change to a white block after it is placed.4. Block: Similar to Normal mode, but blocks will not fall out of formation until a match is made, allowing for impressive clear combos.These modes can be played either single player or two-player simultaneous on separate fields. There is also a versus mode for one or two players, in which creating a combo of three or more clears will attack the opposing player, which causes them to lose control of their pieces for a short time.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/935096-sonic-eraser</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sonic-eraser</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sonic-eraser/3030-23076/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/429/517350-sonic_eraser__j__1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418650-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-the-game-starts-with-the-logo.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418651-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-following-that-it-merges-with.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418652-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-instructions-are-mostly-japanese.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418653-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-more-of-the-mainly-japanese.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418654-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-wow-all-english-caught-me.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418656-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-the-puzzle-is-very-easy-and.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418657-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-basically-the-whole-thing.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418660-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-when-sonic-gets-attacked-however.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418661-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-when-the-player-wins-the-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/418662-sonic-eraser-genesis-screenshot-then-sonic-will-run-off-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Sonic Eraser (ソニックイレイザー) is a 1991 puzzle game that was downloadable for players that had Sega Game Toshokan, an online game downloading service for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan. Because the service is now long defunct, the game was unknown to much of the Sonic community for a time. The game was later released in 2004 on Sega of Japan's website, and it received more widespread attention as it was noticed by English-speaking Sonic fans this time around.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ac99eb2-fb8a-42b9-b604-9c24bf7a150d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/247f8960-041d-429f-b47b-1ff55eccda08.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9318dbf1-1903-48d1-88ed-a87925cf479f.jpg</snapshot12>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>