<Game>
	<Name>Spirou (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Spirou is an obscure 2D side-scrolling platformer designed by Infogrames based on a popular Belgian comic. Spirou is a bumbling bellboy who looks like he could be Tintin's younger brother. In Spirou, you task is to rescue the world-famous scientist Count Champaignac from the clutches of an evil organization intent on using his latest invention to take over the world. Both games has colorful cartoony graphics with fluid animation and incorporates funny antics. The game is similar to Pitfall, Jungle Book, or any of Infogrames' other licensed cartoon platformers (most notably the Tintin series)  The game was released on the PC and Snes as well as the original Gameboy. There was a Game Gear version being developed but was abandoned.Cheat: Debug ModeAt the Infogrames logo, enter the code.  As you press each button, it must be held down until the code is fully entered.  The Sega sound effect will play to confirm success.  During gameplay, hold A and press Start to enter the debug menu.Cheat: Level PasswordOn the main menu, select Password and enter the following password.Note: The picture order for each slot is: Spirou, Fantasio, Spip, Count Champignac, and Cyanida.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames Europe SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19527</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/924703-spirou</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/spirou</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spirou/3030-16845/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/19527-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/19527-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/200057-spirou-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/19527-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94093-spirou-genesis-screenshot-nice-sega-logo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94084-spirou-genesis-screenshot-language-select.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94085-spirou-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94087-spirou-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94088-spirou-genesis-screenshot-spirou-the-herou.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94086-spirou-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94089-spirou-genesis-screenshot-starting-a-level.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94090-spirou-genesis-screenshot-on-the-street.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/94092-spirou-genesis-screenshot-nice-view.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/19527.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Just as he is about to present his inventions to a scientific research symposium in New York, Count Champignac is kidnapped by Cyanida. The evil robot has but one aim, to rule the world. There's not a moment to lose. Spirou will have to scour the streets, subways and skyscrapers of New York and fly to Palombia, a marshy jungle full of surprise... good and bad...</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/840b8d69-9820-45ec-9199-ce27612f747f.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e531ff97-46c3-4107-b7f0-23bf07b1e61d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7da27344-5299-42ed-bee3-f0ef20f932f6.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Infogrames</Publisher>
</game>