<Game>
	<Name>Squirrel King (China) (Unl)</Name>
	<plot>Apparently this is a hack of the Chinese original Super Mario Bros for Mega Drive which was a bloody awful game.  What I can tell you though is that Squirrel King is actually pretty good.  Graphics throughout the game are of a high standard, especially for a Chinese original game.  Sound is also pretty decent.  This game really holds it's own in the playability department.  Everything is just so smooth as if it was an officially produced game.  Animation on the enemies can be a bit dodgy at times or even no existent but that won't throw you off the enjoyment.The idea of the game is pretty simple, just get from start to finish avoiding the enemies and stuff they throw at you.  Throughout the levels you'll also find items that you can pick up to throw at the enemy as well as finding hidden power ups or life icons.  The levels are challenging enough to keep you coming back for more and don't seem to suffer from any unreachable areas that many games of this type do.  Boss battle I found though a a little tedious but that's just me.  All in all, Squirrel King is a very good Chinese unlicensed game.http://www.segagagadomain.com/megadrive4/squirrel.htmCheat: 99 ContinuesTo get 99 continues, when at the continue screen countdown, press and hold B + C + Down + Start.Cheat: 99 ContinuesReset the game and press and hold A + C + Right. At the bottom left of the screen, a 01 should appear, press C to increase the level. Press A + B + Up + Start to view the ending, or at the character select screen, press B + C + Left + Start for infinite health.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Gamtec</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>k5iR_Y-UHGk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20509</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/702050-squirrel-king</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20509-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/1/3/267713_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/a/0/gfs_302800_2_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/7/0/gfs_302800_2_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/c/0/gfs_302800_2_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/0/gfs_302800_2_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/0/gfs_302800_2_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/b/0/gfs_302800_2_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/0/gfs_302800_2_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/d/1/gfs_302800_2_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/6/1/gfs_302800_2_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/4/3/gfs_302800_2_10.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Squirrel King is an unlicensed platform game developed for the Sega Mega Drive. It was published and developed by Gamtec, and therefore its origin is Taiwan. Squirrel King is extremely similar to Capcom's Chip 'N Dale: Rescue Rangers and it sequel, Chip 'N Dale: Rescue Rangers 2 for the NES, to the point where the player actually plays as two characters named "Chip" and "Dale" (though they look slightly different to their Disney counterparts). C jumps, B picks up and throws crates, and A allows Chip or Dale to throw fireballs, assuming they have some in their inventory. Squirrel King is the basis for another unlicensed title, Super Mario World, also for the Mega Drive,but developed by Chuanpu and possibly published by Ming Super Chip Electronic.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48f5e344-b149-4938-a499-3a8cf7d9900a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b7c8fc5-976c-4612-a45b-29d509904473.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5fe3fee-8a21-475b-81e5-a320d6324b89.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67c6ef78-c349-4f80-b967-b35468cfb476.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/854f42a5-5cff-46c8-9cfe-08a35c33ceba.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eec3f2e5-da8d-49bc-9edf-2227fdfe0663.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Gamtec</Publisher>
</game>