<Game>
	<Name>Steel Empire (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Steel Empire is a horizontal shooter for the Sega Genesis. It's one of the consoles first successful shooters. The game takes place in a war torn world, where flying aerial fortresses and zeppelin battleships, control the skies and the world. You are part of the resistance fighting to over throw an evil military empire, known as the "Steel Empire". While invading enemy territory with a giant airship, you take control of two aerial fighters. You pick between a small, compact fighter. The compact fighter is good for destroying land enemies. You also can pick a zeppelin fighter. The zeppelin is a big, easy, target, but it's massive fire power is good for fighting air enemies.The gameplay is different than most shooters. In Steel Empire, your ships have health meters, and the game has a level up system, where you collectexperience icons to level up your ships fire power. You can also use massive electro-bombs that do full screen damage. Each stage has a mid-boss battle and a end boss battle. The game contains lives and continues, but the amount you get depends on the difficulty setting you chose.The game has a 1940s World War II type of theme. The game begins with a classic movie reel count down, and the non-gameplay screens are done in a classic movie reel flicker. Keeping with the theme, is a decent soundtrack that mirrors the classic war movies of the 1940s.Years later the classic shooter would get re-released for the Game Boy Advance.Cheat: 100 ShipsGo to the Options menu and set up the options as follows: Difficulty - Hard Ships - 2 Continues - 1 Then select Sound 65 in Sound Test and press A. There won't be a sound, but when you start playing, you'll start with 99 ships.Cheat: 100 ShipsHold down B and press the Start button on the title screen. You should start on the second level now.Cheat: 100 ShipsHighlight ''Sound Test'' in the Options menu. Then press A to listen to the sounds in this order: Sound 1, Sound 1, Sound 9, Sound 2. A stage select option should appear at the bottom of the screen.Cheat: 100 ShipsPress C, A, C, A, Start, B on controller two at the ship select screen.Cheat: 100 ShipsGo to the Options menu and set up the options as follows: Difficulty - Hard Ships - 3 Continues - 2 Then select Sound 77 from Sound Test and press A. No sound will be heard, but when you start playing you can gain Level 20 firepower by pressing B on controller two.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Flying Edge, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>eyvSpDCnsKc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4676</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586490-steel-empire</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/steel-empire</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/steel-empire/3030-11296/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4676-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4676-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/130420-the-steel-empire-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4676-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215758-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215759-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215760-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-choosing-a-ship.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215761-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-the-first-stage.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215762-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-a-large-battleship.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215763-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-using-a-lightning-bomb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215764-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-the-first-end-boss.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215765-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-every-level-is-preceeded.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/215766-the-steel-empire-genesis-screenshot-falling-rocks.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4676-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lzgyarQ.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Steel Empire (originally released as Koutetsu Teikoku in Japan, and otherwise known in various English materials as The Steel Empire or Empire of Steel), is a side-scrolling shoot 'em up video game released on the Sega Genesis / Mega Drive home consoles in 1992, and was later ported to the Nintendo Game Boy Advance in 2004. Steel Empire is notable amongst shoot 'em up games for its unique aesthetic designs. Mostly low-tech in nature, with it being set in the late-19th century of an alternate world, the game's aircraft, weaponry, powerups, environments, enemies and bosses are heavily stylized adding strong steampunk elements to the style, themes and visuals of the game. Steam power, propeller-based aircraft, biplanes, dirigibles and heavily-armored steam trains with giant cannons play large roles in the game's protagonists and opponents.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f62b75ab-b61c-47e6-b4d2-6d3efc999ee4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e11b0841-5701-46b3-a322-37944d3910f1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc57cbc9-bf1b-46f6-af80-d4e4e9d77851.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d2646758-ba76-46a7-8bf0-465f69603ed2.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Flying Edge</Publisher>
</game>