<Game>
	<Name>Story of Thor, The (Korea)</Name>
	<plot>"You're Prince Ali, and you've decided to take a stand against the evil that has permeated your island of Oasis. Your goal is to release the power of the four Wild Spirits, which will halt the resurrection of a maniacal sorcerer while also saving your empire. As you wander the island in search of evil, you can use your weapons, as well as your feet and fists, to bring the enemy down.There are also Hidden Super Moves to discover, which will make you an unstoppable force. As you progress, you'll be challenged by a myriad of puzzles that will lead you to the bosses at the end of each level, so be sure to save some of your strength for those battles. If you're successful, Oasis will remain a tranquil island; and failure means the end of your empire!"The colors and textures of this game are pretty awesome. Over all it looks great. The animation is smooth and enemies give a terrific yell when you defeat them. The music is pretty good, though your basic RPG music. There are plenty of different items to make game play interesting and the worlds are creative and fun to explore.Directions:This is a fun RPG that has a lot of action. You start in a village that will be attacked. Start by defending the village, and then talk to the nearby villagers, by pressing B. If you look at your map, there will be a flag marking where you should go next.Attacking is not too difficult. Just tap B continuously to attack with a series of stabs and kicks, or hold down B to do a backhand attack with your knife. Later on, you can obtain different weapons as well as items by defeating enemies and opening treasure chests. To open a treasure chest chest hit it with your sword. To pick up new items press B when you are next to them.As with other RPGs, as you proceed further in your adventure you will gain experience points and learn new skills from defeating monsters and enemies.You can pick up various weapons throughout the game. They will be stored in your weapons menu. To change weapons press Start and then access the weapons menu by pressing B. Choose the weapon you wish to use and then press B again. Some weapons have a limited number of times you can use them. This will be shown next to the name of the weapon beneath the menu.Any items you find, like food, will be kept in your items menu where you can access them and use them. Just select the one you want to use and press B. To exit press A or C, not Start. If you press Start again while over an item you will drop that item. You will have a limited amount of time to pick it back up before it vanishes. Weapons are the same. A bit of information about each item will appear near the bottom of the screen.In the status screen your Rank (level or how much experience you have), H.P. (hit points or health), S.P. (Spirit Points), and Kills will be listed.You can find different kinds of spirits throughout the game in temples or dungeons. These guys will help you out. To summon a spirit just fire your light ball at the appropriate thing. I.E. to summon a fire spirit, fire it at a flame.Controls:A Button: Exit Menu or MapB Button: Attack/TalkC Button Tap: JumpHold Down: CrouchX Button: View MapY Button: Select WeaponZ Button: Select ItemStart Button: Main Menu of weapons, status, etc.Hints:- Listening to People -Talk to and listen to people to get advice on what to do next, especially main characters (such as the king and queen). Reviewer: fallenrain http://www.consoleclassix.com/genesis/beyond_oasis.htmlCheat: Best Players ScreenTo view the best players screen (which is firstly seen on completion of the game), press B + Start at the title screen.Cheat: Best Players ScreenAt the title screen, press and hold Down + Right + Start to view the demonstration.Cheat: Best Players ScreenTo instantly switch from your Alt. Knife to the weapon currently selected in the weapons menu and vice versa without needing to open the weapons menu up, hold Mode and press B. Please note that this command requires a 6-button controller.Cheat: Best Players ScreenThese codes require a six button controller.  Before proceeding, make sure that on the Diary screen with the 4 save slots it highlights an empty save slot by default.  On the title screen, hold the buttons listed in the cheat and keep them held as you press Start twice (once to open the Diary screen, the second to begin a new game)  A sound effect will confirm success.  For the area select and dialog viewer code, hold the MODE button as you open the save screen during gameplay to access the area list.  To access the dialog viewer, hold X and Z, and then press A or C to close the menu you just opened.  With X and Z still held, walk up to a NPC and press B to talk.  The game will now cycle through the story text.Cheat: Best Players ScreenAt the Diary (save select) screen, press B + Start to access the game's sound test screen.Cheat: Secret IslandNOTE: This will only work after you have the Warp Device. Go to the seashore on the lower west side of the map. Use Shade's Doppelganger to locate the invisible silver crack (the warp), then use your Warp Device to open up the warp. You'll then be transported to a secret island located on upper west side of the map. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>H40274WHGhI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20573</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586061-beyond-oasis</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/beyond-oasis/3030-211/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20573-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/0/9/5/47095_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/a/a/gfs_46707_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/1/b/gfs_69401_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/c/b/gfs_69401_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/3/7/gfs_46707_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/8/6/gfs_69401_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/5/6/gfs_69401_2_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3FVQ9Ii.jpg</banner1>
</game>