<Game>
	<Name>Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Most everyone familiar with electronic games has heard of Street Fighter II - the most famous beat-em-up series ever. Basically you get a bunch of fighters together (12 in this case) and get them to punch, kick, bite and thump the bejesus out of each other then you're close.Here yet another slightly different version of the game turns up - this time on the Genesis. Special Champion Edition is similar in most respects to the original Street Fighter II (which never turned up on the Genesis anyway) except that all 12 characters are selectable from the get-go (the boss characters were originally locked) and the game engine has been revamped.Cheat: Choose Same Character Twice in Group ModeGo to group mode. Where it has the 2 modes to choose from, on Controller 2, press Down,Z,Up,X,A,Y,B,C.  You should here Chun Li say her voice as if she was doing her whirlwind kick.  It can also be done by using controller 2 and pressing Down,C,Up,A,A,B,B,C.Cheat: Choose Same Character Twice in Group ModeWhen the Capcom logo fades, the building will show up with the Street Fighter II logo.  When the screen stops going up and you can see the logo, on a 6 button controller, press   Down, Z, Up, X, A, Y, B, C.  If right, you should here a short Zangief sound.  It can also be done on a 3 button controller by pressing Down, C, Up, A, A, B, B, CCheat: Choose Same Character Twice in Group ModePress Down+Z, Up+X, A, Y, B,C. Now you can only use special moves when fighting.Cheat: Special EndingBeat the game in Champion or Hyper mode with any character on 7-star difficulty or higher.Cheat: Alternate Character ColorsWhen picking a character, press Start to select him/her. He/she will have an alternate colored uniform/shorts/etc.Cheat: Alternate Character ColorsAfter choosing your fighter, when the plane flies to the next location, press and hold Start to bring up the controls. You can then change your controls as you see fit.Cheat: Alternate Character ColorsComplete the game with any character with the difficulty level on 4 or higher. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>cKQXc2Xupgs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5543</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586494-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5543-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5543-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/17640-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93663-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93664-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93665-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93666-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93667-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93668-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93669-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93670-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93671-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93672-street-fighter-ii-special-champion-edition-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5543-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/neSGRCT.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5543.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This version of Street Fighter II is similar in most aspects to the original, save that all 12 characters are selectable from the get-go (the boss characters were originally locked), and the game engine has been revamped.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18deca60-9870-481e-a7cb-d8f4d4f8d34f.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/59828071-e856-4c6f-845d-a736797672b4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e001e8af-9ee6-468c-bca2-e78115004ebc.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70b9732e-12c3-459d-bc97-654ae1f0c334.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80ca9a93-690d-4f20-9fb2-7ee573956998.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45a28b74-f760-4d32-95d9-2703114c4f3f.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>