<Game>
	<Name>Super Kick Off (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Super Kick Off is an enhanced developed version of the popular football game developed by Dino Dini for consoles. It includes 40 teams (16 national and 24 club), along the ability to edit club team names and shirts and player names and looks. Game modes include friendlies, Domestic League and Cup  (composed by eight English teams), European League (16 European teams) and International cup (eight team tournament). Training allows to practice free kicks, penalties or to pass, shoot and dribble without opposition. Players can compete head to head, or play cooperatively against the computer in the same team. Other game options include player speed, wind and grass cut, along the typical half length, offside rules, extra time and difficulty setting. All changes, from team edits to options, are stored in the cartridge internal memory.About the game itself, it was one of the most popular of the time, featuring a top-down view  with the ball not sticking to the players' feet being the most prominent gameplay feature.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20533</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/933967-super-kick-off</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-kick-off</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-kick-off/3030-14503/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20533-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/61630-super-kick-off-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/61631-super-kick-off-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159560-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159561-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-menus-here-the-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159562-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-options-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159563-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-knowing-where-each-player.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159564-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-player-editor-names-and.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159565-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-kit-editor-sadly-any-kind.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159566-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-competitions.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159567-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-european-92-sort-of.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159568-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-even-with-all-effort-to.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159569-super-kick-off-genesis-screenshot-flipping-the-coin.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Super Kick Off is a football game for the Sega Mega Drive, Sega Master System and Sega Game Gear, released exclusively in Europe and Brazil. It is considered by many to be a version of Kick Off 2, previously released for the Commodore Amiga (and ported to the Amstrad CPC, Atari ST and Commodore 64). Kick Off 2 was originally programmed by Dino Dini for Anco Games, with the console adaptations being handled by Tiertex. From a franchise perspective, Super Kick Off would be followed by the controversial Kick Off 3: European Challenge. However, Dino Dini, who had no involvement in Kick Off 3 would go on to form his own company and produce the Amiga/IBM PC game Goal!, which shares similar gameplay. Goal! also arrived on the Mega Drive, in the updated form of Dino Dini's Soccer.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49529298-2eff-4a70-8636-8a3f2b79446c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e8ec0ebf-faf7-427f-8392-ca5a235e5714.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9c73351-e06b-4916-94fe-58cb78661e4a.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold</Publisher>
</game>