<Game>
	<Name>Super League (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>It's batter-up and time for Tommy Lasorda's version of Pro-Ball. Whether you're infield or outfield, at the plate or on the mound, stealing bases or catching fly-balls, the competition is hot and you're even hotter now that you're playing with a big leaguer like Lasorda. And you've got control. Curve balls, fastballs or sliders are some of the wind-ups you'll pitch to outwit your batter. But be prepared when he connects, you'll have to think fast to make your players perform like a well-oiled machine. Are you up for a single, double, or even triple play? It all depends on how you throw the ball. But don't worry, you'll get your chance at bat. This is a race for the Pennant, so you better hope Tommy's on your side. Now take your pick, choose your line-up and let's play ball!Cheat: Redo a StrikeoutIn order to redo a strikeout you need to press Start to pause the game before the pitcher receives the ball back from the catcher. After pausing the game, press C to restart the game. Now the same batter who struckout earlier will still be batting, but he will only have 2 strikes on him.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/10/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<rating>4.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>718</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586551-tommy-lasorda-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tommy-lasorda-baseball/3030-11264/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/718-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/718-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/a/gfs_93651_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/7/gfs_93651_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/7/gfs_93651_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/7/gfs_93651_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
</game>