<Game>
	<Name>Super Hydlide (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A long time ago, evil descended upon the peaceful people of Hydlide. Old legends tell of a lone brave hero who saved Hydlide from the imminent threat of doom - the evil demon Varalys. Since then, the people of Hydlide have lived through centuries of peace. But one dark evening, a huge column of fire exploded out of the depths of Hydlide. The next morning, strange doors began to appear from nowhere. Many who were curious entered these doors, but were never seen again. From that day on, unusual events and disasters began to take place. Huge cracks opened in the ground, scarring the beautiful lands, floods wiped out entire villages. And then the monsters came. The Hydlide council feared that the same evil in the legends was back again. A wise old oracle predicted the second coming of evil. He also spoke of a young man who could save Hydlide from the grave danger. This young man is you...Super Hydlide continues the tradition of action RPGs started with the original Hydlide for NES. You can choose to play as one of the four character classes: Warrior, Thief, Priest, and Monk. In combat, you use melee or long-ranged weapons or cast magic spells in real time. There is an internal clock in the game that makes it necessary for you to sleep periodically to regain your strength. You also have to eat from time to time, otherwise your hit points will gradually decrease.Cheat: Free ExperienceIn the City of the Forest (the start town), there's a lake at the centre of the town with a bridge going across it.Go to the bottom edge of the lake, directly left of the bridge and "use" any unit of money - don't worry, you'll keep it.Exit the menu and check the ground to get 30 Experience points.  Repeat as much as you like.Cheat: Free ExperienceGo left from the City of the Forest to a small building to unlcock the Sound Test.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Seismic Software Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>4644</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586505-super-hydlide</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-hydlide</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hydlide-3/3030-15921/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2747467-2117741114-48196.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4644-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/96443-super-hydlide-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73694-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/522772-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-japanese-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73695-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73696-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-get-ready-hero.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73697-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-choosing-one-of-the-character.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73698-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-in-a-town.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73699-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-menu.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73700-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-buying-wepaons-and-armor.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73701-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-talking-to-townpeople.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/73702-super-hydlide-genesis-screenshot-your-stats.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Vum2dv2.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4644.png</clearlogo1>
</game>