<Game>
	<Name>Super Daisenryaku (Japan) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>Super Daisenryaku is one of the many titles in SystemSoft's long-running war strategy series. The game mechanics are based on Daisenryaku II, but many of the 35 included maps are unique to this release, including several based on Phantasy Star. There is no scenario mode, and any of the included maps can be played. Some maps are for two players, some for four, and any map can be played with any combination of human and computer players.The game is played on a large map made up of hexagonal spaces, each of which is a specific type of terrain. Each player controls a number of units, which each take up one space on the grid. Different units have different strengths and weaknesses toward other units, which are also affected by the terrain. Each player controls a capital, and the goal is to capture the other players' capitals.Cheat: Hidden Units and Secret Super UnitsAt any unit producing hex such as Capital and any adjacent hex, Factory, City, Airport, Sea Port within a 5 hex area originating from Capital.For hidden units, you only have to enter the code once, and it is unlocked for the rest of the game.Not all nation have hidden units, but the most likely ones are USA, USSR, W.German, Britain, France.As for secret units, it can be produced by any nation, but you got to re-enter to code each time you want to produce it. And you got to choose the relevant unit producing hex for entering the code, for example, planes/helicopter only at airport, and ninja at city or capital.Cheat: Hidden Units and Secret Super UnitsAt the screen where you load the map, load the map first, then highlight the "Load" option.Cheat: Hidden Units and Secret Super UnitsAt the loading map screen, load any map first, then highlight the "Load" option,</plot>
	<releasedate>29/4/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>20534</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/579435-super-daisenryaku</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-daisenryaku</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-daisenryaku/3030-33738/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/5/59247/1676773-superd88.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/1/4/41714_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416209-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416210-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-map-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416212-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-strategy-grid.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416211-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-planes-vs-troops.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416213-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-planes-vs-planes.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/416214-super-daisenryaku-genesis-screenshot-planes-vs-a-ship.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/c/1/gfs_19600_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/c/gfs_19600_2_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/8/c/gfs_19600_2_2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/3/c/gfs_19600_2_3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Super Daisenryaku (スーパー大戦略) is a 1988 World War II simulation game for NEC's PC-88 and PC-98 computers by SystemSoft in their Daisenryaku series of WWII sims. Sega ported it to the Sega Mega Drive in 1989, putting in a new soundtrack supposedly composed by Tokuhiko Uwabo. Not only was it never released outside Japan, but it does not fully implement TMSS, meaning it will only work on early Model 1 Mega Drives. The Mega Drive would receive a sequel, Advanced Daisenryaku, which not only does work on all Mega Drives, but also contained Mega Modem support.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/350f30e5-2479-4a04-b577-2fdae13610d5.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>