<Game>
	<Name>Super Shinobi II, The (Japan, Korea)</Name>
	<plot>The Shinobi master of stealth and the lethal ninja arts is back, bigger and deadlier than ever! Joe Musashi's sworn enemy, the Neo Zeed, grips the city in a vicious crime ring. Shadow Master, a super ninja cloned from Joe's own bloodline, controls the Zeed's savage army of bio-ninja. Musashi has no choice but to annihilate them all!Cheat: InvincibilityChoose BMG selection on the options menu, then, press B to select the following songs in order. Cheat: InvincibilitySet the amout of shurikens to 0 on the options menu, Set the sounds effects option to Shuriken. Highlight the shurikens option and keep it there and the 0 will change into the symbol for infinity. Cheat: 6 Button ModeThis cheat makes it possible to play the game with a new 6 Button controller scheme. You need a 6 button controller plugged into port 1 and any regular controller in port 2.Highlight "Options" on the main menu. Normally when you're in the Options menu, it says "Options" at the top, with an S on the end.Highlight Options but don't go into it yet. On Controller 1, hold the Mode button and on Controller 2, hold UP on the D-Pad and the C Button. With all these buttons held down, press Start on controller 1.Now you're in the Options menu, it now just says "Option" at the top without an S. This means 6 Button mode is on. This is what each button does.A is the Block button.B is a Melee attack.C is JumpX uses Ninjitsu magicY and Z throw ShurikensThis allows you to use Melee move at any time rather than at close range or when out of Shurikens.Enjoy!Cheat: 6 Button ModeComplete a level without throwing any shurikens to get 30,000 bonus points.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/7/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Megasoft (Japan)</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>uNGbAStPXZc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>120</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586455-shinobi-iii-return-of-the-ninja-master</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-revenge-of-shinobi/3030-236/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/120-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/120-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/2/gfs_51622_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/2/gfs_51622_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/120-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/120-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/120.png</clearlogo1>
</game>