<Game>
	<Name>Super Shinobi, The (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>You are Musashi, master ninja. You are one of the mystic warriors, who see and know all things. You are deadly! Now you must destroy the vicious army of Neo Zeed. If you fail, then Naoko, their beautiful prisoner, dies! Attack with a ninja sword and crossed daggers! Somersault over fences while hurling deadly knives! Ward off bullets, Death Stars, and junked cars by leaping, twisting, and kicking! The Neo Zeed are masters of disguise. But you are a master of Shinobi, the art of stealth. You'll stalk the Neo Zeed through 24 treacherous scenes, while they stalk you! Battle ninja, musclemen, deadly lasers, and the diabolical Boss! Outfight Kung Fu gangs and armies of machine gunners. The Neo Zeed is almost unstoppable, but you have a secret weapon - ninja magic!Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsIf you want to earn 30,000 bonus points, make sure you end a level with eleven times more shurikens than the number of lives you have left.Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsOne the second stage of level four,fire at the base of the first conveyer belt.A special Musashi symbol will appear.Hop onto the conveyor belt and let it carry you to the end.You lose a life but you gain 2.Keep doing this until you have as many lives as you want/need.Cheat: 30,000 Bonus PointsGo to the Options Screen, move the pointer up to Shurikins and set them to 00, wait about 30 seconds (without moving the pointer). You will here a sound and the ''00'' should change to an infinite symbol. Start the game and you will have unlimited Shurikins.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ClJZV2qCFJg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20722</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/519117-the-revenge-of-shinobi</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-revenge-of-shinobi/3030-236/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20722-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/20722-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/120-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/b/e/gfs_44401_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/e/gfs_44401_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>