<Game>
	<Name>Super Street Fighter II (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers is the fourth iteration of Capcom's genre-defining Street Fighter II originally released in the Arcades in 1993 on Capcom's new CP System II board. It follows Champion Edition (which first allowed players to play as the four Grand Masters Sagat, Balrog, Vega and M. Bison) and Turbo: Hyper Fighting (which increased the speed and balanced the game further). The most notable addition are four brand new characters: Cammy, Deejay, T.Hawk and Fei Long. It would eventually be followed by Super Street Fighter II Turbo Edition, considered the definitive Super Street Fighter II.Gameplay:This remake of  Street Fighter II featured a new scoring system that kept track of combos, first attacks, and reversals. Additionally, four new characters join the returning twelve characters from the original. Super Street Fighter II is also the first game in the SFII series to give full move sets to the boss characters. Previously in Street Fighter II: Champion Edition and Street Fighter II: Turbo, whilst the four boss characters were available, they did not have different animations for some punches and kicks. Although this was expected for Balrog (being a boxer), it was unusual to see a character doing a punch when pressing a kick button, or vice-versa.Aside from the bosses' added moves, some of the main characters' moves were adjusted in some ways. For example, the differences between Ken and Ryu became more defined - Ryu focusing on deadlier fireballs, and Ken's fierce Dragon Punch being able to set opponents on fire.CriticismFor all the additions and improvements Super Street Fighter II makes over  Street Fighter II: Turbo, its biggest failing is arguably that it does not include the same degree of speed that made Street Fighter II: Turbo such a hit. It is perhaps for this very reason that, in most cases, this game is overlooked in preference to its follow-up -  Super Street Fighter II: Turbo.Characters:Returning charactersSSFII featured four new characters Ryu Ken Masters E. Honda Chun-Li Blanka Zangief Guile Dhalsim Balrog Sagat Vega M. BisonNew characters Cammy Dee Jay Fei Long T. HawkCheat: Choose the same characterGet eight of the same fighter in the Group Battle Mode of Super SF II. Choose Group from the title screen. Now, at the Battle Mode Select Screen, enter the following sequence on controller two: A, B, A, B, A, B, B, A. Now select the number of characters to be eight in one of the mode and then go to the selection screen. Each player may now choose up to eight charactersCheat: Easily reach to M.BisonWhen playing the arcade or story mode have another controller plugged in  , during the fight press the start button on the 2nd controller so it well appear like a new challenger wants to fight you, then choose the character tha you were about to fight for the secnd player , and you'll have a match hat appears to be a versus mach but if player 1 wins you'll progress further to the next opponent . Do these steps until you reach M.Bison.Note: This will not work when you fight M.Bison , you'll have to fight him on your own.Cheat: Hidden ArtworkSet the difficulty to 7 or 8 stars and clear Super mode without losing a round. After the credits, a Cammy artwork will show up beside a Super SFII logo.A Dee Jay artwork is also available, when clearing Super mode set to Expert on the same difficulty settings and without losing a continue. Cheat: Hidden ArtworkCheat: Speed Up Computer BattlesAt the title screen, choose Tournament. In the Tournament Battle Screen, highlight the word END. Press START. All of the matches will be fought by computer opponents. Press a button to speed up the match.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>iQ3bbvUkx-U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2585</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586509-super-street-fighter-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-street-fighter-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-street-fighter-ii/3030-6665/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2585-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2585-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/136216-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118705-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118704-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-options-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118703-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-player-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468150-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-blanka-vs-dee-jay.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468151-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-the-insults-after.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468152-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-vs-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468153-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-feilong-fights.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468154-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-ha-do-ken.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635189-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-vega-vs-cammy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635190-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-claw-s-attack-is.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2585-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2585.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>is a head-to-head fighting game produced by Capcom originally released as a coin-operated arcade game in 1993. It is the fourth game in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games, following Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting. In addition to refining and balancing the existing character roster from the previous installments, Super Street Fighter II also introduced four new characters. It was also the first game to be developed on Capcom's CP System II hardware, which permitted more sophisticated graphics and audio over the original CP System hardware, used by the previous versions of Street Fighter II.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>AeHuR5pMmzA</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7eb6c78e-4f5a-42e5-bd33-6834cebc742c.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb632c7e-5e08-4b67-a3e7-8a831def047c.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/68170615-1057-4ed2-bf49-6c28327be0c0.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>