<Game>
	<Name>Super Thunder Blade (Japan) (Launch Cart)</Name>
	<plot>Super Thunder Blade was the console exclusive sequel to the 1987 arcade game Thunder Blade.This game was recently featured on the Sega Genesis Collection for the Playstation 2 and Playstation Portable, and Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection for the Xbox 360 and Playstation 3Overview:~ Super Thunder Blade (Genesis/Megadrive)Weathered and damaged, Thunder Blade returned victorious from it's last mission against the renegade troops. But, this was not to be its last flight.Reorganized with mega amount of devastating military electronics and weapons, the renegade troops have once again focused their sights on dominating the free world. From a secret power base in the East, they unleash their deadly troops who will take to land, sea and air powerfully armed.But so are you. From the cockpit of this modified bird, you've got a start-of-the-art defence system at your fingertips. An aerodynamically designed alloy body flies up to 523 kph while a 20 mm Gatling Gun fires up to 4,800 shots a minute. A computer-aided flight system takes you through even the most hostile environments. Don't worry, you're firing cannons and dropping air-to-surface AATM missiles from your skids, so there's no stopping you and the greatest chopper in the sky.~Passage from the manual.Stages (Levels)~ (Genesis/Megadrive)-- The following will describe the enemies faced in each level, respectively:STAGE 1-Hind-Ge- The main offensive force which attacks in formations.Frogger-Ba- A jet fighter with variable wings for high dogfighting capabilities in low altitudes.Merkava Mark IV- A battle tank with anti-aircraft missiles.Maneater Sub-commander- A large tank with a high-power Maser Cannon on its turret. It also fires anti-aircraft missiles.Seaminer Commander- Large aircraft carrier. Destroys the missile launchers on the side of the craft.STAGE 2-Fuji Sub-Commander- Attack aircraft with Gatling Guns.Land-Buster Commander- Strategic tank with nuclear engine. It moves with immense horsepower.STAGE 3-Murmansk Class- High-Speed warship.Aqua-Lyzer Sub-Commander- Nuclear submarine especially developed for guerilla attack.U-JAC-001 Commander- Secretly developed space aircraft.STAGE 4-Sigma-01 Sub-Commander and Sigma-02 Sub-Commander- 25 feet of mechanical armour for the infantry and operated by the soldiers riding in their cockpits. They fire machine guns and missiles.Final target is the guerilla basement.Bonus Points &amp; Earning Extra Helicopters~ (Genesis/Megadrive)BONUS POINTS- At the end of each stage, bonus points are awarded on the number of enemies defeated and the time elapsed during the stage. A Bonus screen will appear and indicate time required to earn a Time Bonus and number of enemies defeated to earn Defeat Bonus.EARNING EXTRA HELICOPTERS- The player will be given an extra Super Thunder Blade when they earn more than 500,000 points. After that, they'll be given an additional helicopter every time they earn over 1,000,000 points.Cheat: Avoid Enemy FireBegin the game with hard difficulty.  Stay in the upper right or left corners and fire your weapon continuously in levels 1 through 3.Cheat: Avoid Enemy FireEnable the level select code and get a continue.  Highlight ''Option'' and hold A + B + C, and press Start.  A picture of a panda will appear on the ''Player'' selection to confirm the code.Cheat: Avoid Enemy FirePress these controller actions at the title screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>xO0SlFSJWCY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>704</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586510-super-thunder-blade</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-thunder-blade</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-thunder-blade/3030-234/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/20737/762396-super_thunder_blade.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/704-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/74623-super-thunder-blade-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93985-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93971-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93972-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93973-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-ohh-fresh-air.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93974-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-enemies-appear.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93975-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-dead.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93976-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-too-many-tanks.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93977-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-my-score.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93978-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-level-2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93979-super-thunder-blade-genesis-screenshot-desert.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6cSsO9K.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Once known only as Thunder Blade, the ASH-002 is back in action as Super Thunder Blade, model ASH-091B. As part of the Air Force Special Operation Troop, you and Super Thunder Blade must take control of its state-of-the-art artillery to defeat the renegade guerilla armies with plans to dominate the world!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>xO0SlFSJWCY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb6f8e1b-af87-4a57-b392-fc78cd19b813.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/120a3520-a022-489d-96c4-dd99aecc4ea0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5ec6661e-832f-457b-9f9a-235caddb4b5e.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/586ec7cf-e583-4eaf-a6cf-f8e744e02f90.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b57f58b2-e5eb-4d48-93f9-6af8e1cb35f1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ac91f2b-3659-4a99-aec6-35cda68db9be.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a13a304-2260-4462-9007-fc4068c2d882.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98e450a3-3a23-49f8-ae75-bb621f9c7de1.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>