<Game>
	<Name>Super High Impact (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This isn't just football; it's SUPER HIGH IMPACT! It'a all the fast-paced action of the bone-crunching arcade smash! Quick-Action play selections get you into the action before you can say 'WICKED HIT!' Choose from 18 hard-charging teams and over 30 plays, from a red-dog blitz to a never-say-die superfly! 'YER TOAST' if the HIT-O-METER rates your tackle 'DWEEB', but you can settle the score the ol' fashioned way with an all-out team brawl. When you're tired of watching football from the sidelines... get into the button-pounding arcade action of SUPER HIGH IMPACT!Cheat: Extra Time OutAfter running out of regular time outs, pause the game and press A to call a extra time. Cheat: Easily block kicksWhen the computer is going for a field goal or extra point, take control of one of the defensive players all the way in the back of the field goal block formation. When the ball is snapped, run at the long snapper, then turbo at the kicker and jump. The glitch comes in the form is the long snapper never bothering to try blocking you, and you'll be able to block virtually any kick with ease.Cheat: Easily block kicksWhen on defense, pick the Suicide defense and take control of either one of the two nose guards. Hold down the Turbo button and direction yourself at the quarterback before the ball is even snapped. On virtually every single play, you'll blast through the line and nail the quarterback before he can even move regardless of whether or not the play is a run or pass, simply because the offensive line never bothers to block you when this trick is performed.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Arena Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>703</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586504-super-high-impact</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-high-impact</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-high-impact/3030-1243/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/703-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/703-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/98593-super-high-impact-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291613-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291614-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291615-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291616-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-team-select.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291617-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-kick-off.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291618-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-before-the-snap.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291619-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-first-down-on-pass.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291620-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-incomplete-pass.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291621-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-choosing-play.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/291623-super-high-impact-genesis-screenshot-fight.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8lSirS6.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/703.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super High Impact was one of the most hard hitting football games before the NFL Blitz series was created, with 18 teams and over 30 plays per team. The console versions are based on the Midway arcade series of the same name. The game has a Hit-O-Meter which often leads to massive brawls. Based on the arcade smash hit back in the days, featuring the three famous words: EAT THIS!!!, FIGHT!!!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2caa6a96-cea4-41a1-8e08-2a6a7203e4ce.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b2efc2a-89c7-4542-b897-4e7e83fceab3.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Arena Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>