<Game>
	<Name>Super Street Fighter II - The New Challengers (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>It's SUPER STREET FIGHTER II! Featuring four all-new fighters and 16 challengers in total! New moves with improved animation. Time Challenge, Score Challenge, and Tournament battle modes. Loaded with 40 megs of fighting power!Gameplay::This is the sequel to the super hit Street Fighter II Turbo and Street Fighter II Championship games for the SNES and Genesis. This port of the arcade game featured all 4 new characters and stages making a total of 16 playable. The game was packed into massive 32Meg and 40Meg cartridges for the SNES and Genesis. Featured many multiplayer modes in addition to the single player mode. There was the returning elimination group battle where you and a group of people played until one person was the champ. The Point Battle where the person with the most points wins. Newer modes included Tournament where you had an 8 man double elimination tournament. Finally the Challenge mode, where you tried to get the most points on a CPU opponent or beat them real fast trying to surpass records.Hints:- Choose the same character -Get eight of the same fighter in the Group Battle Mode of Super SF II. Choose Group from the title screen. Now, at the Battle Mode Select Screen, enter the following sequence on controller two: A, B, A, B, A, B, B, A. Now select the number of characters to be eight in one of the mode and then go to the selection screen. Each player may now choose up to eight characters- Speed Up Computer Battles -At the title screen, choose Tournament. In the Tournament Battle Screen, highlight the word END. Press START. All of the matches will be fought by computer opponents. Press a button to speed up the match.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/home/586509.htmlhttp://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/super-street-fighter-ii</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>iQ3bbvUkx-U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2585</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586509-super-street-fighter-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/121177/1748664-super_street_fighter_ii__flyer_.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2585-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/136216-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118705-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118704-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-options-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/118703-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-player-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468150-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-blanka-vs-dee-jay.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468151-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-the-insults-after.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468152-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-vs-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468153-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-feilong-fights.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/468154-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-ha-do-ken.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635189-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-vega-vs-cammy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635190-super-street-fighter-ii-genesis-screenshot-claw-s-attack-is.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2585-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iEP3Les.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2585.png</clearlogo1>
</game>