<Game>
	<Name>Sword of Vermilion (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Evil threatens the world of Vermilion. Armies of the evil Tsarkon march in conquest. All hearts look to you. From your beginnings in the humble village of Wyclif, you must search the world for the 8 rings of good. On the long road ahead you'll face treacherous governors and beasts ten times your size! You'll travel to 14 towns and battle through 14 first-person dungeons where every corner can mean death. Choose from dozens of swords and shields. Prepare to face the archmonsters, forked tails and hideous eyes of Tsarkon's minions. Talk with townspeople to learn the secrets of the caves. Be ready for hundreds of hours of adventure gameplay. Save up to three different games with battery backup. Over 30 spells and 20 special items - use them with care. At last, armed with the Sword of Vermilion, you're ready to meet Tsarkon in the final struggle!Cheat: Test MenuDuring any time during the game, [I]simultaneously press and hold the A, B and C buttons and  press Start on controller 2[/I]. A test menu should appear with [I]Input, Sound and C.R.T[/I] tests. And when you exit, it will send you back to the Sega logo screen.Cheat: Super Strength/ Virtual InvincibilityFor this cheat, you need a cursed weapon/suit of armor. Also, having Rafael's Stick helps save some cash, but you don't absolutely need it. Also, if you want the effects to be permanent, your level has to be maxed at 31. Cheat: Super Strength/ Virtual InvincibilityEquip the cursed weapon/armor. Now, either use Rafael's Stick or talk to a priest to remove the curse. Your strength or armor class (depending on what you equipped that was cursed) will go down. Keep re-equipping and removing the cursed item until your Strength/Armor Class goes to a ridiculous #, like 9999 or something like that. Now, re-equip your most powerful weapon/armor, and you'll either kill enemies in one hit guaranteed (Super Strength), or take only 1 damage from any attack from any enemy, including bosses (Invincibility)Cheat: Quick CashIn Keltwick, when Bearwulf gives you the dungeon key to get to Malaga, sell it. It's worth 1000 kims and Bearwulf has an unlimited amount of them. Just go back, talk to him and he'll say ''Did you lose the key? I have another one.'' He'll give it to you, and you can repeat the process as much as you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>rMuO77A9f8s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>705</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586515-sword-of-vermilion</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/sword-of-vermilion</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sword-of-vermilion/3030-13695/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/705-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/705-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45796-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36229-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/522773-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-japanese-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36228-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-choosing-a-name.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36230-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-in-a-town.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36231-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36232-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-statistics-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36233-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-at-home.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36234-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-oh-good-to-know.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36235-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-in-a-bar.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36236-sword-of-vermilion-genesis-screenshot-traveling-1st-person.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7lkLAGJ.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sword of Vermilion is about the son of Erik, king of Excalabria, who takes on a quest of revenge to defeat Tsarkon and free the world of Vermilion from evil. In the town of Excalabria the people went about their business, and tended to the fields. One day, vicious fighting broke out everywhere as the army from Cartahena, led by the wizard-king Tsarkon, swarmed all over the town. The townsmen were overwhelmed, and the castle of King Erik V collapsed. Erik V summoned his bravest, strongest and most faithful warrior, Blade, and gave him his infant son and an ancient family heirloom, the Ring of Wisdom. Erik ordered Blade to save himself and the child while the castle burned. Blade traveled to a small village named Wyclif, where he settled down and raised the child as his own son. Eighteen years later, the son of Erik begins his quest. The quest consists of travelling to towns and villages, battling creatures to gain experience and finding items such as swords, shields and armour, as well as many other items such as Herbs and Candles. Boss monsters take the form of larger, stronger creatures which are integral to the story. Fighting Boss Monsters takes place on a side on view of the battle where magic cannot be used. The titular Sword of Vermilion is the most powerful weapon at the end of the game.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4f8ac83b-6fd6-4462-84a1-79fe9634c86d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d19bc2fb-4c82-42a5-aa0a-e9e62acde9ba.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea74936d-104f-4f82-8d0c-70b64bea31f6.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c91abd8-f6eb-408b-89ad-286068424d19.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b71ff5f-b07c-42bb-aeb2-d787eb95b8b6.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e134c5b-4032-4edd-8ba5-002c381be37f.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>