<Game>
	<Name>Target Earth (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Target Earth is a side-scrolling mecha combat game for the Sega Genesis. It was developed by NCS Corporation and released in North America in 1990.Story:In Target Earth, a band of outcasts who left Earth have become cyborgs, and they are returning with a vengeance. As Rex, a pilot for Earth, the player must fight against the cyborg invasion and put a stop to the war.Gameplay:Target Earth features two types of play. For ground based missions, the game plays very much like a 2D platformer. Enemies will attack from side to side as well as by air. The space-based levels are similar to side scrolling shoot'em ups like R-Type. With every enemy the player kills, they earn ports that can be spent on weapon upgrades. Bonus weapons can be unlocked at the end of each mission depending on player performance. The game does not feature any sort of collectable health power-up. Instead, the player's health regenerates over time.	Cheat: All WeaponsDo not collect any bonus weapons or destroy anything except the ship at the end of the first level. Your score after the level is completed should be more than 2,800 points.Cheat: All WeaponsPress A + C + (Left or Right) on the second controller at the logo screen. Use the D-pad, A, and C to change the size and rotation of the logo. Cheat: All WeaponsDurind the game press Start on controller two and you should be invincibleCheat: All WeaponsBegin playing the game and get past level 2. After it's over, enter the options screen and press Start. A woman will appear and say ''Continue Up'' to confirm correct code entry. This may be repeated at any time if your lives have dropped below three.Cheat: All WeaponsWait until the first green alien appears on the right side of the screen in the first level. Press Start on controller two. One player can control the normal robot while the other player controls the enemy robot.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1990</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>DreamWorks</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>zpUyZ9DnXFg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>708</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586520-target-earth</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/target-earth</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/target-earth/3030-12475/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/708-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/708-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/135242-target-earth-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161722-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-us.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161720-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-title-screen-jpn.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161721-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-game-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161809-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-developer-logo.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161811-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161812-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-scores-page.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161813-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-level-1-intro.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161814-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-setting-the-scene.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161816-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-configuring-your-ship.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161817-target-earth-genesis-screenshot-among-the-first-wave.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/X7O7otj.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Target Earth is about Earth's outcasts, who have become Cyborgs, returning from space to attack the civilization that remained behind. The Earth Defense League fights to defend Earth in a galactic war. The battle begins on Ganymede. The game alternates between battles in space, on planets, on the earth and inside enemy outposts. Fighting for the OPTOF (Outer Planet Treaty Organization Force),you pilot the Assault Suit Valken 2. Your enemy is the Daess.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/de6a5995-38d0-43aa-aac0-2831f9dabf20.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6726f3ab-fc35-4c60-be87-20db50f43608.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>DreamWorks</Publisher>
</game>