<Game>
	<Name>Taz-Mania (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Taz-Mania is a 2D platformer based on the TV animation of the same name. Taz is tasked with crossing various 2D platformer stages, using his cyclone spin and voracious appetite to his advantage. The game was released on all three Sega platforms of the era: The Sega Master System, Sega Genesis and Sega Game Gear.It is not to be confused with the Super Nintendo Taz-Mania, which is a combative racing game with a different developer that was released the following year.Plot:Taz 's father telling the giant seabird tale.After being told by his father the tale of a lost valley, where there were giant seabirds that could laid eggs big enough that could feed Tazmanian devils for a year. Taz decides to go on a quest to find one of the giant eggs himself, on the prospect of potentially making the biggest omelet in the world!Gameplay:Taz-Mania is 2D side scrolling platformer/adventure game, where players control the famous Tasmanian Devil across several different stages, including factories, an ice level, a mine and many more.Those chili peppers sure are hot!Taz can use his famous Spin to attack enemies and knock them out of the screen, travel faster and jump farther , he is also able to perform several actions as carrying objects to reach ledges, and even a fire breath attack. Taz can also eat many of the items found through the stages, some like chili peppers will give beneficial abilities like the aforementioned fire breath, while others like bombs will give the old Tasmanian Devil less pleasant effects.The Sega Mega Drive/Genesis version was also one of the first to feature a tagged soundtrack, meaning that the music in the game would react to players actions, something that was considered innovative at the time.Cheat: InvincibilityPause the game and then press B. When you unpause it, you will be invincible.Cheat: InvincibilityPress Start to pause the game, and then press A, B, and C at the same time to go to the next level.Cheat: InvincibilityAt the title screen, hold A, B, and C on both controllers while pressing Start on controller one.  If you do it correctly, you will hear a chime.  Now start the game.  Pause the game and press A in order to have your health meter refilled when you unpause the game.  If you press B while the game is paused, you will get partial invincibility.  Press C while it's paused in order to view the number of the current stage, which you can change by pressing Left or Right.  Change to a different stage number if you want to be warped to that stage when you unpause the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2288</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586522-taz-mania</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/taz-mania</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/taz-mania/3030-4894/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2288-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2288-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/134873-taz-mania-sega-master-system-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2288-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127563-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127554-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-1-plains.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127555-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-man-eating-plants.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127556-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-2-jungle.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127557-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-2-jungle-boss.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127558-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-3-caves.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127559-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-4-ruins.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127560-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-extra-lives.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/127561-taz-mania-sega-master-system-screenshot-stage-4-ruins-boss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2288-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QgOtDWr.png</banner1>
	<Notes>One evening, Taz's father is telling an intriguing tale. Somewhere on Tazmania is a Lost Valley, and in that valley nests a huge seabird, so huge that one of it's eggs could feed a family for a year! Just think of the omelette one of those could make! Thus Taz becomes fascinated and leaves in search of one of those eggs before his Dad has even finished the story...</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9637524-9e27-4f88-8abb-bc2a20b67fb0.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c9f3b99-0a24-410f-9cbc-48e5572c6ba4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3938fe90-9464-424e-84d9-96c7f1e156c2.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a70b1168-9e32-4f56-9c93-11c8d1bb2e5d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cd4ff33-0e38-4203-9e39-afad6d0934a0.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>