<Game>
	<Name>Tecmo Super Bowl III - Final Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Provided the most in depth  TECMO football action ever. All 30 NFL teams and their rosters are included in the game, and a new free agency system makes the game like your own personal league. Updated graphics and player photos made this installment of the popular series shine above its previous incarnations. Complete stats, audibles, and tournament-style play spice things up, while the addition of Passing and Superstar modes deliver a needed increase in gameplay to the aging TECMO Super Bowl series. You call all of the plays, changing your defensive formations and offensive lineups to match your opponents' moves. With dive plays, touchbacks, and more, this is a classic football game that installed many of the gameplay elements seen in many of today's football games.The game also featured player injuries. Occasionally, a player would be injured, and would have to sit out a game or two.  However, the game did not have any method of classifying the injuries, or how long they would affect the player.  However, it was still a step towards the more realistic football simulations of the present day.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op, 1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>gxLuxStChvA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4657</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586527-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition/3030-17931/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4657-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121878-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121876-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121877-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121875-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-it-was.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121879-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121880-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-creating.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121881-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-you.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121882-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-team.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121883-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-team.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/121884-tecmo-super-bowl-iii-final-edition-genesis-screenshot-player.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/S792Ifc.png</banner1>
	<Notes>A late entry in what was once the premiere football simulation, TSB III has updated rosters and teams for the 1994-1995 season and is licensed by both the NFL and the Players group. Features real NFLP players and photos, the real NFL schedule, and weekly standings. You can change defensive and offensive formations, create your own Pro Bowl, fake punts and field goals, go for the two point conversion, and call audibles. Updates to the game itself include new cinema screens, superstar mode, free agency system, improved graphics, larger field simulation, passing modes, and improved speech and music. Horizontal scrolling. Also features battery back-up.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b88ec4ef-be7b-4a4c-bddf-0f41215cf418.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b22835b5-3e39-4d01-838d-cfa1f259aee5.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>