<Game>
	<Name>Teddy Boy Blues (Japan) (SegaNet)</Name>
	<plot>Teddy Boy Blues is an updated conversion of the 1985 Sega coin-op action platformer. While the basic premise is similar to the Master System version -- each stage contains a number of enemy generators, and enemies must be shot and collected before they take a portion of the time meter -- this version of the game has several differences. The graphics have been redrawn to take advantage of the more powerful hardware and the Yohko Ishino tie-in has been removed. There are also several new stages throughout the game, though many of the original game's stages are also present.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/951935-teddy-boy-blues</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/teddy-boy-blues</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teddy-boy/3030-16551/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2363096-sms_teddyboy_au.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420290-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420291-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-get-ready-for-round-1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420292-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-jumping.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420293-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-shot-an-enemy.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420294-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-about-to-shoot-an-enemy.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420295-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-collect-the-smaller-versions.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420296-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-if-the-small-enemy-isn.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420297-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-got-killed.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420298-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-shooting-barriers-to-destroy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/420299-teddy-boy-blues-genesis-screenshot-the-number-on-the-clock.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Teddy Boy Blues (テディボーイブルース) is a 1985 game for the Sega System 1 by Sega. The game was endorsed by Japanese singer Yohko Ishino, whose song of the same name was both the source of its title and the music in the background. (Consequently, the game is incorrectly known as Teddy Boy Blues: Yohko Ishino to many English speakers.) In this game, you play as a kid who must destroy boxes from which enemies come out. You have two buttons: one to shoot your gun with and one to jump with. Shots from your gun may be used to "destroy" enemies (they become items that can be collected for points), destroy barricades (which are always blue), and (with enough hits) destroy the boxes, which resemble dice counting down the number of hits needed to destroy them. Once all the enemies and boxes are destroyed, the level is complete. A port to the SG-1000 Mark III was released in Japan as a launch title for the console (along with Hang-On). It was subsequently released overseas on the Sega Master System, renamed Teddy Boy, which is the same except that the main theme song was changed due to licensing issues. TecToy also released an alternate version only in Brazil called Geraldinho, featuring an edited main character based on the titular protagonist of the popular comic strip. A port to the Sega Mega Drive was released in 1991 exclusively in Japan on the Sega Game Toshokan service. A port to the Sega Mega-CD as part of SING!! Sega Game Music presented by B.B. Queens was also released.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/978d70f4-46e5-4007-924e-c755b3446bec.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba30652d-cef3-4506-ab51-8c84dffa86a5.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/857194b3-2631-4637-b5c5-f7f306003c8b.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/59fcfd8d-22c0-48f0-992b-2d4a498463fb.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>