<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles - Tournament Fighters (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Trash the surf board and heave the 'za. It's a whole new breed of Turtles and they're fixated on fighting. We're dead serious, Tournament Fighters takes dude-on-dude demolition to new heights of intensity with 4 modes of pain-producing battles, deadly warriors, secret arenas, astounding graphics and sound effects that'll make you cringe! Clash with Krang-created clones of the Turtles, Casey Jones, April O'Neil, Ray Filet and Sisyphus, plus bosses Triceraton, Krang's Android and Karai. There's flying body presses, knee drops, head butts, rocket punches, elbow smashes, somersault throws, you'll feel and inflict them all. And the settings include Magma Ocean Planet, Jungle Planet, and every other bizarre corner of Dimension X!Cheat: Skip to bosses without losing continuesTo bypass fighting everybody and get to the boss trio without losing continues start a 1P game.  When the screen changes to the space map have controller 2 enter the game for a 2P game.  Have player 2 choose a character and select that person's home planet. Leonardo - Bio Planet Michaelangelo - Mirage Planet Donatello - Futuristic City Planet Rapheal - Magma Ocean Planet April O'Neil - Spaceship Casey Jones - Ice Planet Ray Fillet - Ocean Planet Sisyphus - Jungle Planet You can beat up a defenseless second player and the game will give you credit for defeating that character in the tournament lineup.  After you beat all eight defenseless fighters on their home stages the game will begin with the boss matches and you'll have kept all your continues.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>6.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>qzOO2DqDnmQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4661</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586528-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters/3030-4896/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4661-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4661-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/2koUbLL.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/188674-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4661-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4661-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4661-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/4661-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93896-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93885-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93886-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93887-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93888-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/93889-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters-genesis-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4661-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2ZGojTT.png</banner1>
</game>