<Game>
	<Name>Terminator, The (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Terminator is a side-scrolling shooter based on the 1984 movie The Terminator. The player assumes the role of Kyle Reese, and must repel multiple robots in the distant future before travelling back in time to protect a vulnerable Sarah Connor from a single T-800 unit.There are actually three versions of this game from three different developers, but each follows a very similar blueprint: each game features Kyle in the lead, each features side-scrolling shooter gameplay and each follows the same events as the movie.Radical Entertainment created the NES version, originally released in late 1992.Probe Software developed the 1992 Sega version, which was released on the Master System, Game Gear and Genesis. Virgin Interactive, which also published the Sega games, developed the revamped Sega CD version the following year.Mindscape, Inc. produced the 1993 SNES version of The Terminator.Cheat: Cinema Scene SelectAt the Options menu, hold the C button and press: Right, Left Release C. Choose the Sound Test option and you'll find a new option called Cinema Sequences.Cheat: Cinema Scene SelectEnable the secret menu. Now hold B and press left,right,right,left. The arrow should change to a square.Cheat: Cinema Scene SelectEnable the secret menu. Now hold the d-pad left and press b,c,b,c. The arrow should change to a square. now start the game. The level select menu should pop up.Cheat: Cinema Scene SelectHiglight the start game option. Hold the D-pad right. While holding d-pad right, press B, C, B, B. The pointer should change into a square. Now press start.Cheat: Cinema Scene SelectEnter the following code at the Title screen....  Start, then quickly press Up  You should see the opening cinema without the words</plot>
	<releasedate>23/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>h2AKOzKRKCg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4677</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586529-the-terminator</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/terminator_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-terminator/3030-10713/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4677-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4677-2.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/17513-the-terminator-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92917-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92914-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92915-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92916-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-fighting-a-big-machine-guy.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92913-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-fighting-lots-of-paratroopers.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92918-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-climbing-down.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92919-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-expressive-game-over-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/369366-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-the-streets.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/369367-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-kyle-vs-the-terminator.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/369368-the-terminator-genesis-screenshot-you-must-find-and-save-sarah.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4677-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vi5Kz3Q.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4677.png</clearlogo1>
</game>