<Game>
	<Name>The Adventures of Batman & Robin</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1995-02-10T00:00:00-08:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>The Mega Drive/Genesis version, developed by Clockwork Tortoise and published by Sega, is a run 'n' gun where both Batman and Robin must stop Mr. Freeze, who plans to freeze Gotham City. In order to keep the duo busy, he also frees the Joker, Two-Face and the Mad Hatter, each one with their own agenda. The Joker celebrates his birthday wreaking havoc in Gotham and stealing diamonds, Two-Face tries to take over the city from above, and Mad Hatter is creating a robot army in his surreal lair. The game can be played by two players simultaneously; one player with Batman, and the other with Robin. Both characters are identical in terms of playability, and both use batarangs, bolas, or shirukens in long-range attacks, while using melee attacks at short range. There are four levels consisting of several stages, mostly of a straight left-to-right traverse to the end where the boss awaits. In some levels the game switches to a side-scrolling shooter, in which the players must control the Batwings. The game is regarded as being extremely difficult to complete, and also known for showcasing some of the most impressive special effects on the Mega Drive/Genesis. It also features a soundtrack by Jesper Kyd. This accounts for the relatively high quality of Kyd's compositions, as well as the fairly simple FM synthesized nature of the game's sound effects.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL>8bWAwSRQ7fA</VideoURL>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e2c07389-b1ca-4230-b49b-18bc2f16af8a.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxback2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85888945-95a8-4472-b350-9ecbc88ac9ea.jpg</boxback2>
	<boxback3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dcc50642-f517-4f2b-8ed7-73653a2d4ea2.jpg</boxback3>
	<boxback4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f83464d5-c09d-400e-8ce8-84742cf65ba5.jpg</boxback4>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a84de5b-e48f-40e0-adb3-5c0068195139.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/097928f3-9841-49cb-8deb-6e3a5f0b5da6.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eba81914-6eea-498b-a409-17b6fc8d61c5.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7278169c-cadc-463f-b3fb-500dd34c0682.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e75869cf-febc-4110-848b-49ef73bf61e9.png</clearlogo1>
	<fanart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f892dcd5-145d-457a-b4c4-dce7f513b222.jpg</fanart1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23b80a38-f0a6-4df1-89dd-4c8eb01d1d67.jpg</snapshot1>
	<Rating>3.75</Rating>
	<WikipediaURL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Adventures_of_Batman_%26_Robin_(video_game)</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Action</Genre>
	<Developer>Clockwork Tortoise</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>