<Game>
	<Name>Theme Park (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Theme Park is a simulation management game in which the player attempts to build a famous and financially successful theme park. In order to do so, they have to purchase new rides, restaurants and other amenities as well as hiring park staff and keeping abreast of concerns like litter, bored people waiting in lines and squeezing the maximum amount of profit from their parks.Theme Park made its debut on the PC (via MS-DOS) and Amiga home computers. It would eventually be ported to Sega Genesis, Super Nintendo, Atari Jaguar and CD-based systems like the Amiga CD32, PlayStation, Sega Saturn and 3DO. The MS-DOS CD version featured Full Motion Videos of some of the rides.The game was also remade for the Nintendo DS in 2009 by EA Japan and on iOS around the same time. The PlayStation version was later rereleased on the PlayStation Network. Theme Park was followed by two sequels: Sim Theme Park/Theme Park World and Theme Park Inc/SimCoaster.Gameplay:World map screen showing different plots of land available for purchase.Like most management games, Theme Park starts the player off with a plot of land that they have to develop. The player can build many things found commonly at an amusement park, such as roller coasters and Ferris wheels, all of which can attract more customers. Players are able to set prices, hire new staff and generally maintain the plot. The aim of the game is to make the theme park as valuable as possible so that it can be sold and a new plot can be bought somewhere else in the world. The player then starts to make a new theme park and the process is repeated.Cheat: Australia and lotsa cashGo to the password screen and enter the following. Name: zarkon Password: pan6caa85t9Cheat: Australia and lotsa cashFor a cool $33,000,000, go to the Password screen, enter your name as DST, and enter the password 5AKCQSEBDS4.Cheat: Australia and lotsa cashTo get unlimited money in all aspects of this game, go to the password screen.  Enter your name as: ''ZARKON'' (without quotes) and Enter your password as: ''8AAACAA9999'' (also without quotes).Cheat: Blank ThemeAs soon as loading up Theme Park game, leave it for 30-45 minutes as the game will cycles through various Theme Park examples. Eventually a blank theme park should become available where you have a lot of cash and visitors will also have loads to spend.Cheat: Blank ThemeMake a hook a duck and change the prize vaule to 400, the price per game to the max (998) and the chance of winning to 100%. Now everytime somebody plays they always spend more than they win, and wining make them happier too. this works with other sideshows too.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VAncsZV-bJI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4679</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563349-theme-park</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/theme-park</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/theme-park/3030-6562/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4679-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4679-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/93982-theme-park-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92907-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92904-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92905-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92906-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-area-information.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92903-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-getting-started.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92908-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-building-the-first-road.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92909-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-various-stuff-to-place.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92910-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-finances.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92911-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-they-are-coming-they-are-coming.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92912-theme-park-genesis-screenshot-demolish-a-tree.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QRh0ltR.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4679.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dominating the exciting world of Theme Park ownership is your goal in this strategy game from Bullfrog. The first task is to set up your rides within the available land, structuring convenient paths and queues and ideally leaving some space for bigger rides once they become available, and include some lakes and trees to increase the park's allure. Rides range from Teacups and Haunted Houses to the biggest most elaborate roller-coaster you can design, and water rides that loop around other rides. Shops must also be included, so that the visitors can buy food, drinks and souvenirs - the cunning player will combine salt, sugar and caffeine settings to maximize consumer interest. Staff must be hired to keep everything running smoothly, and they will only work for what they consider a fair rate of pay.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>kO8Y5sdQCAU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8676803a-710e-49c5-91f1-cf5723ef62b7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/356f8637-b027-4022-bd70-374c8e8c1578.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b9d0354-34db-4692-b7a4-3f46370e06c1.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3c176dd3-fa40-4e93-9096-bea56720b861.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Bullfrog Productions</Publisher>
</game>