<Game>
	<Name>TinHead (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Once, there was peace in the Galaxy.Grim Squidge changed all that. The mad, intergalactic goblin escaped from the insane asylum on Centaurus IV and is now loose. Using his fiendish talents of invention, he created a spaceship to suck all the stars out of the Galaxy and trap them in crystal globes. And he did it, too! He then scattered the globes throughout a number of nearby worlds. Now, the whole Galaxy is threatened by a horrible Cosmic Void which will happen son if the stars aren't returned to their proper place.Enter Tinhead, Defender of the Edge of the Galaxy!Our friendly little metal-head just happened to be nearby in his remote space station when the nasty Squidge cruised by. Hearing the stars' cry for help. he know he's the only one who can save the Galaxy by stopping Grim Squidge's diabolical plan. Packing his trusty Bounce Blaster and with the aid of any add-on vehicles he may find, Tinhead must overcome the pesky creatures on four weird worlds. By collecting the stars and defeating the crazed goblin, he can restore order to the Galaxy.`Taken straight out of the Genesis manual`Cheat: Level PasswordsGo to Enter Password from the main menu to input them. You will see Password Accepted if entered correctly.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Ballistic</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>85Jepvltjbs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4684</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586541-tinhead</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/tinhead</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tinhead/3030-468/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4684-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4684-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/280236-tinhead-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147942-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-company-logo.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147943-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-title-scren.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147944-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147945-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147946-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-plot-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147947-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-game-start.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147948-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-climbing-via-some-platforms.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147949-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-something-to-shoot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/147950-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-that-crystal-s-looking-menacing.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/148041-tinhead-genesis-screenshot-the-green-vents-drop-shots-down.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4684.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Once there was peace in the Galaxy. Then the evil Grim Squidge stole all the stars, threatening to hurl the Galaxy into a horrible Cosmic Void. Who will save the stars before it's too late? Tinhead, Defender of the Edge of the Galaxy of course! Lead, slide, hop, fly and shoot your way through the wacky worlds and super-tricky challenging levels as you guide Tinhead ti free the stars. Take on pesky spinning Krystals, relentless flying Saw-Sirs and hordes of mega-tough bosses. Grab radical power-ups and zany vehicles like Batteries, Hyper-Hoppers and Rocket Packs to help Tinhead through each weird, monster-jammed world. 4 tin-tillating worlds with 24 super challenging levels. Unique pause-and-scroll to see the action offscreen. 3-way shooting power to blast the baddies. Dozens of power-ups and hidden bonus areas.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ee1ca82-12c7-43f3-90fa-abf65d116217.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe81f45c-8f7a-4738-8b4d-30c0369bb802.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Ballistic</Publisher>
</game>