<Game>
	<Name>TNN Bass Tournament of Champions (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:TNN Bass Tournament of Champions is a fishing game developed by both Gaps (SNES version) and Imagitec Design (Genesis version). The game was published in the US (both platforms) by American Softworks Corporation while the Japanese Super Famicom version was published by King Records.The US version is endorsed by TNN, a.k.a. the The Nashville Network. The TV network, renamed to Spike after 2000, was well known for hosting fishing shows. The Japanese SFC version, where the TNN license wouldn't translate, is instead endorsed specifically by Larry Nixon, a professional angler. The Nippon Bass Club also shares an endorsement credit.Platform DifferencesThe SNES and Genesis versions of the game were developed by different developers despite using the same name. While the two versions of the game have the same branding and same basic premise, they play slightly different and look quite different.	</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>American Softworks</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>4686</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586545-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions/3030-28300/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4686-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4686-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576679-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576680-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576681-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-music.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576682-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-setting.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576683-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576684-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-overview.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576685-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576686-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-casting.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576687-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-i-haven.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/576688-tnn-bass-tournament-of-champions-genesis-screenshot-tournament.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Starting at 7.30 in the morning, the player has until 4PM to take a boat on the lake and fish for bass to beat competitors. The boat can be steered freely using a top-down view until an appropriate spot has been found by checking the lowrance monitor. The game then switches to a first-person view, also showing the fisher from a side-view on a separate part of the screen, and it is possible to look around in the environment. Casting is done using a power meter to determine the distance. As the bait sinks, a monitor can be checked for nearby fish. There are also visual clues through splashing water. The player can check the depth and reel in when needed. When a fish has been caught, it becomes a sensitive play with the line tension to make sure it does not snap shown through the side-view of the fisher. At the end of the day the boat can go back to the weighing area to determine the results. Money earned in the tournaments can be used to acquire new spin reels, bait reels, boats, lines and lures.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a60b5c05-fa5f-42d2-8cf4-44968aaff3e7.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6c6aa92-1cfd-4344-9fbc-ed28d63e894a.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>American Softworks</Publisher>
</game>