<Game>
	<Name>Tommy Lasorda Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This was the first 16-bit baseball cart on the market. Play alone or with a friend. Choose from any of the 26 major league teams. The game uses all of the real-life city names, but the stats and player names are fictional.Once on the field, game play follows standard baseball rules. The password feature enables you to take your team all the way through a season to the World Series. The game also tracks all of the other teams in the league simultaneously.Batters in the game are rated according to batting average, home runs, running speed, and fielding and throwing ability. Pitchers are rated by ERA, curve-throwing ability, stamina, top throwing speed, and the distance a hit pitch will travel. All the ratings make this game a challenge to your managerial ability as well as your gaming skill because you're calling the shots from the dugout.The option screen enables you to decide how tough your computer opponent will be. You can play a pitcher's duel, a batter's slug fest, or a normal game. Decide whether there'll be fielding errors and determine how the wind will affect the hit balls. This game covers about every detail, right down to umps who shout "safe" or "out."Cheat: Redo a StrikeoutIn order to redo a strikeout you need to press Start to pause the game before the pitcher receives the ball back from the catcher. After pausing the game, press C to restart the game. Now the same batter who struckout earlier will still be batting, but he will only have 2 strikes on him.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>718</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586551-tommy-lasorda-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/tommy-lasorda-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tommy-lasorda-baseball/3030-11264/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/718-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/718-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/34054-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50011-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/680076-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-japanese-european.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50012-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50013-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-team-select.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50014-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-scoreboard.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50015-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-up-at-bat.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50016-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-pitching.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50017-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-single.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50018-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-leftfielder-s.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/50019-tommy-lasorda-baseball-genesis-screenshot-off-the-wall.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>It's batter-up and time for Tommy Lasorda's version of Pro-Ball. Whether you're infield or outfield, at the plate or on the mound, stealing bases or catching fly-balls, the competition is hot and you're even hotter now that you're playing with a big leaguer like Lasorda. And you've got control. Curve balls, fastballs or sliders are some of the wind-ups you'll pitch to outwit your batter. But be prepared when he connects, you'll have to think fast to make your players perform like a well-oiled machine. Are you up for a single, double, or even triple play? It all depends on how you throw the ball. But don't worry, you'll get your chance at bat. This is a race for the Pennant, so you better hope Tommy's on your side. Now take your pick, choose your line-up and let's play ball!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1f5078e-0fae-4ba6-a3b0-9cad8ce20d7f.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8240fa94-af5b-4c72-bff3-e87c9f2d136e.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed969770-c72d-4a57-9717-7790c3440c71.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9da1979f-af60-4029-a4e0-c4942a27d8c5.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>