<Game>
	<Name>Traysia (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In "Traysia", you control a young man named Roy, who lives in the town Johanna. All his life Roy has been dreaming about leaving the town and going to explore faraway lands. Now, finally, his chance has come. His uncle, a travelling merchant, is going on a journey, and Roy decides to leave with him. His girlfriend Traysia gives him a pendant, to remind him of her... will Roy be able to escape from all the dangers that await him on his long journey and to see Traysia again?The game is a party-based RPG with randomly encountered enemies. The combat is somewhat similar to early  Ultima games. When an enemy appears, you enter a battle screen on which your party is positioned in the lower part, the enemies in the upper part. You can attack if you are close enough to the enemy, otherwise you'll just move towards him. Magic spells should be cast to an appropriate direction to hurt the enemy.Cheat: Unlimited goldBegin game play and reach the Town Of Adventures and successfully complete the treasure game. Leave the Labyrinth and speak to the thief to collect the prize of 20,000 gold. Talk to the thief again without leaving the building to collect another 20,000 in gold. Repeat this to accumulate an unlimited amount of gold.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Renovation Products, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>719</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586560-traysia</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/traysia</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/traysia/3030-10121/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/719-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/719-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/249263-traysia-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86575-traysia-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86574-traysia-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86573-traysia-genesis-screenshot-good-bye-traysia.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86576-traysia-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-game.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86577-traysia-genesis-screenshot-a-regular-house.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86578-traysia-genesis-screenshot-character-information.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86579-traysia-genesis-screenshot-tavern.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86580-traysia-genesis-screenshot-in-a-church.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86581-traysia-genesis-screenshot-wilderness-area.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86582-traysia-genesis-screenshot-river-cave.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In Traysia the player controls a young man named Roy, who lives in the town Johanna. All his life Roy has been dreaming about leaving the town and going to explore faraway lands. Now, finally, his chance has come. His uncle, a travelling merchant, is going on a journey, and Roy decides to leave with him. His girlfriend Traysia gives him a pendant, to remind him of her... will Roy be able to escape from all the dangers that await him on his long journey and to see Traysia again?</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/27daf352-ace4-4a48-9cc5-baa3a7b95b51.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01485046-2fd2-465c-9fb6-aec4cdd3af9c.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Renovation</Publisher>
</game>