<Game>
	<Name>Triple Score- 3 Games In 1</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1992-10-01T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Triple Score: 3 Games in 1 collects three previously released games in one cartridge: Super Hang-On (1989), World Championship Soccer (1989) and Columns (1990). The sequel to Hang-On for the arcade and for the Master System (Sega's 8-bit platform), Super Hang-On is a motorcycle racing game that takes you across Africa, Asia, America and Europe. Each course has multiple stages. To advance, you must reach various checkpoints within the allotted time limits. Your score increases as you race on-track. If you veer off-track or have a collision, your score will temporarily stop increasing. In addition to the aforementioned Arcade Mode, Super Hang-On features a special Original Mode exclusive to the Genesis. This mode of play features a different circuit and more options. With the money you'll earn from winning or placing in races, you can hire a mechanic and buy better parts (such as mufflers, brakes and frames) to upgrade your bike. The next game on the cartridge, World Championship Soccer, features 24 international teams battling for a spot in the Final Tournament. Each team is ranked according to skill from one to five. Individual players are rated according to speed, kicking strength, tackling strength and accuracy. When selecting a team, you must choose 11 starters from a roster of 16. If you don't want to enter the tournament, you can play a special one or two-player Test Match, which consists of a single game of soccer. If a game ends in a tie, the winner will be determined by a series of penalty kicks. The penalty kick screen puts you behind the kicker while the rest of the action in World Championship Soccer features an overhead view. Last but not least is Columns, a Tetris-like game that takes you out of the world of sports and into the ancient land of Phoenicia. Originated among the Phoenician merchants, Columns has you arranging columns of rainbow-colored jewels (three jewels per column) that drop one by one from the top of the playfield. Your objective is to line up like-colored jewels horizontally, vertically, or diagonally in order to make the jewels in that row disappear. If the columns pile up to the top of the playfield, the game will end. In addition to the standard game of Columns, you can play Flash Columns in which you must make a flashing jewel disappear before time runs out. Also, two players can play Doubles (alternating on one field of play) or split-screen mode (two separate games going at once).</Plot>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/97d806f4-bdf9-4221-95ff-6c612c502efd.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxback2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d114f69-74b0-4499-a14f-5f227db09c61.jpg</boxback2>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7dd0ab2f-83c4-438d-86bb-814fd6a2d771.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef763106-f152-4526-bf37-a54f53a10a12.jpg</boxart2>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33839b23-2042-4a43-b962-6ede755f9a0b.png</media1>
	<WikipediaURL>https://segaretro.org/Mega_Games_I</WikipediaURL>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Genre>Puzzle; Racing; Sports</Genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>