<Game>
	<Name>Valis (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Yuko Asou is an ordinary Japanese teenager with an ordinary life - until one day she is attacked by a monster on the street. Out of nowhere, a sword appears in her hands. She fights the monsters who have suddenly invaded the city, and is summoned to the parallel world known as Vecanti, which is ruled by a cruel tyrant named Rogles, whose actions disrupt the balance of the the worlds. Wielding the legendary Valis sword, Yuko must defeat Rogles and restore the balance.Valis has the same story and basic genre (platform action) as the  original first game in the  series; however, it is a different game with different locations, regular enemies and bosses, new cut scenes, etc.  Defeating the numerous enemies populating the game world requires precise usage of jumping and ducking abilities, and attack timing. Yuko can jump very high and attack while jumping. Various power-ups are scattered through the game, many of which enhance the performance of Yuko's sword. Acting as a melee weapon in the beginning, it can be customized with power-ups and turn into a medium-range weapon, firing shots at the enemies - with proper power-ups, also in different directions. Boss enemies typically have different attack patterns and require different strategies to defeat them.Cheat: Max HP/MPThis requires 2 controllers. At any time during actual gameplay, Pause the game with controller 1, then, on controller 2, press right+a+b. This will fill up your HP/MP to the max. You can do this however many times you like. Alternative: If you don't have 2 controllers, you can still do the code. After pausing on controller 1, switch it with controller 2's port and then proceed with the rest of the code.Cheat: Max HP/MPAt the title screen, simultaneously press and hold A, B, C, Up, and Start. </plot>
	<releasedate>15/8/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Renovation Products, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>zhfE-U47OqU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4707</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563353-valis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/valis</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4707-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4707-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45795-valis-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33609-valis-genesis-screenshot-she-was-just-a-simple-schoolgirl.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33610-valis-genesis-screenshot-the-long-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33611-valis-genesis-screenshot-yuko-the-heroine.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33612-valis-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33613-valis-genesis-screenshot-reiko.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33614-valis-genesis-screenshot-don-t-hate-me-cause-i-m-beautiful.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33618-valis-genesis-screenshot-oh-no-indeed.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33616-valis-genesis-screenshot-starting-the-game-and-facing-more.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33619-valis-genesis-screenshot-come-and-get-me-sucker.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/33620-valis-genesis-screenshot-over-the-roofs-of-the-modern-city.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wMHALxk.png</banner1>
	<Notes>What would you think if your best friend went on a date with the King of the Dark World - because she thought he was cute?! You'd think she'd been duped - and you'd be right. The fiendish King Rogles stands poised to conquer the other worlds of the universe: the Dream World of Queen Valia, and the Human World. Rogles and his five Dark Lords have taken the force of Yang from Queen Valia and sealed it into a Fantasm Jewel. Only a warrior with a heart perfectly balanced between Yin and Yang can wield the Sword of Valis against the encroaching darkness! Yuko, a young student from the Human World, is the chosen one - and you will control her. She is to become the greatest warrior in the universe, never suspecting that her most fearsome battle will not be against a Dark Lord, but against her closest friend from the Human World - the one she warned, "Don't go out with him, he's the Dark..." But before she could finish, her friend ran off into The Darkness.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>F_0CUZhuWi8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab141d63-b0f6-4a3c-b742-2040dc2fdfe8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/afb7ffda-ac0b-467f-b30c-9d7227c74bb2.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88ed05d1-9245-4f52-a394-f6a354f6608a.png</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Renovation</Publisher>
</game>