<Game>
	<Name>Vampire Killer (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Time refuses to forget the Belmont family's horrifying, bloody destiny. And in 1917 two of its descendants are summoned by fate into epic battle. Their enemy? The most evil incarnation of Castlevania legacy to ever rise from the grave, the vampiress Countess Bartley. This spine-tingling, 6-stage fear-fest overflows with graphic sights and sounds from your worst nightmares. As John Morris, the whip wielding vampire hunter, or Eric Lecarde, master lanceman, you'll pursue the demonic Countess all across Europe before she resurrects Dracula for a final reign of global terror. Alas, her trail of doom is laden with zombies, hideous mutants, grotesque giants, ghouls and ghastly creatures. Taste the sweat dripping into your mouth as you try rescuing yourself from diabolical traps. Feel the torturous strain on every muscle as you wield again and again sacred weapon power-ups such as Holy Water, the Battle Axe, the Crystal Blade Boomerang and the Mirror of Truth. But in the end, make sure you've saved enough strength to scream!Cheat: Alternate Music With Final UpgradesEnter the options menu. Set 05 as the BGM (background music) and 073 as the SE (sound effects) selections. Press Start to begin game play.  Now once you fully upgrade your whip/ spear alternate tracks will play.  These tracks include: Vampire Killer, Bloody TearsCheat: Alternate Music With Final UpgradesIf you don't want to beat the game to unlock the Expert Mode, just press: up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A on the title screen. If done correctly, you'll hear a sound.Cheat: Level passwordsStage 2Empty Axe Bird EmptyBird Empty Bird EmptyJewel Empty bird axeaxe Empty axe axe Stage 3axe bird jewel axeEmpty Empty Empty jewelaxe Empty bird EmptyBird axe axe axeStage 4Empty bird Empty birdbird Empty bird Emptyaxe Empty  bird Emptyaxe Empty jewel axeStage 5axe axe jewel jewelEmpty Empty Empty jewelEmpty bird bird jewelbird axe jewel axestage 6axe axe Empty jewelEmpty bird Empty jewelEmpty axe bird jewelbird axe Empty EmptyCheat: Level passwordsEnter password on title screenCheat: Level passwordsEnter the following passwords at the PASSWORD screen...01. Start game at Stage 2/Atlantis Shrine, Greece with John Morris/Expert ModeAxe/Bird/Axe/EmptyJewel/Empty/Bird/JewelEmpty/Jewel/Bird/BirdBird/Axe/Axe/Empty02. Start game at Stage 3/Ruins of the Castle Dracula, Romania with John Morris/Expert ModeAxe/Axe/Jewel/JewelBird/Empty/Axe/EmptyBird/Empty/Bird/JewelAxe/Axe/Jewel/Axe03. Start game at Stage 4/The Leaning Tower of Pisa, Italy with John Morris/Expert ModeAxe/Axe/Empty/JewelBird/Bird/Axe/EmptyBird/Bird/Bird/JewelAxe/Axe/Empty/Empty04. Start game at Stage 5/The Munitions Factory, Germany with John Morris/Expert ModeEmpty/Bird/Jewel/BirdEmpty/Empty/Bird/AxeBird/Axe/Empty/AxeEmpty/Empty/Axe/Empty05. Start game at Stage 6/Versailles Palace, France with John Morris/Expert ModeAxe/Axe/Jewel/EmptyJewel/Bird/Axe/BirdBird/Jewel/Axe/BirdJewel/Axe/Axe/Empty06. Start game at Stage 2/Atlantis Shrine, Greece with Eric LeCarde/Expert ModeEmpty/Bird/Jewel/EmptyJewel/Empty/Bird/JewelBird/Empty/Bird/EmptyBird/Empty/Bird/Axe07. Start game at Stage 3/Ruins of the Castle Dracula, Romania with Eric LeCarde/Expert ModeAxe/Bird/Jewel/BirdAxe/Empty/Bird/AxeBird/Bird/Empty/JewelEmpty/Axe/Bird/Axe08. Start game at Stage 4/The Leaning Tower of Pisa, Italy with Eric LeCarde/Expert ModeEmpty/Axe/Axe/AxeJewel/Bird/Axe/BirdBird/Axe/Axe/EmptyJewel/Empty/Empty/Axe09. Start game at Stage 5/The Munitions Factory, Germany with Eric LeCarde/Expert ModeEmpty/Bird/Bird/BirdJewel/Empty/Bird/JewelBird/Jewel/Bird/EmptyBird/Empty/Jewel/Empty10. Start game at Stage 6/Versailles Palace, France with Eric LeCarde/Expert ModeEmpty/Bird/Axe/EmptyJewel/Empty/Bird/JewelAxe/Empty/Bird/EmptyBird/Empty/Jewel/AxeCheat: Bypass region restrictionTo bypass region restrictions, hold down the A button as you turn on the console.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6uf5lN435hw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2619</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563315-castlevania-bloodlines</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2619-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2619-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2619-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/1/8/gfs_2344_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/c/8/gfs_2344_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2619-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2619-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2619-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2619-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2619.png</clearlogo1>
</game>