<Game>
	<Name>Vapor Trail (USA)</Name>
	<plot>It's 1999, the terrorist organization "DAGGER" has taken down the communication system that provides communication for the world's military bases. The terrorists are now in control of the satellite communication network, and they threaten to destroy the world's greatest cities with nuclear bombs. The group is only prepared to cancel their threats when the world's leaders are ready to give their power to DAGGER.As a counter-offense, a special forces air unit is called in by the president of the USA. The air unit's code name: "Vapor Trail". The world's last hope lies in your hands now...The game is a vertically scrolling shoot 'em up. You can choose between 3 planes; the fast but weak plane: Seylen. The mediocre all around: Silph; and the slow but very strong: Valkyrie.During the game you can pick up various items. These items include: Speed-up, power-up and extra lives. An extra useful feature is the spin-dash which makes you invulnerable for a few seconds. For this feature you have to wait until your power is restored to full by waiting some time. You also get more than one boss per level.Cheat: Level SelectGo to options and set the options to PLAYER 5, MUSIC TEST 10, VOICE TEST 03, and play a voice test sound once. At the fighter select screen, hold the following button on Control Pad Two whilst selecting a fighter for the desired level:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Renovation Products, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>PR6xIJUToJ4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4708</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586577-vapor-trail</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/vapor-trail</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/vapor-trail/3030-23424/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4708-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4708-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/120266-vapor-trail-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320992-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-intro-cut-scene.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320993-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320994-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320995-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320996-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-select-a-plane.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320997-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-using-the-invulnerability-move.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320998-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-various-enemies.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/320999-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-flying-above-a-parking-lot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/321000-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-tons-of-tanks.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/321001-vapor-trail-genesis-screenshot-a-boss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9tBVdmL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4708.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game is a vertically scrolling shoot 'em up. You can choose between 3 planes; the fast but weak plane: Seylen. The mediocre all around: Silph; and the slow but very strong: Valkyrie. During the game you can pick up various items. These items include: Speed-up, power-up and extra lives. An extra useful feature is the spin-dash which makes you invulnerable for a few seconds. For this feature you have to wait until your power is restored to full by waiting some time. You also get more than one boss per level.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7146fcbc-6a42-4258-b5a1-e6c8b4d97f78.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9af40978-9111-4eb2-8a21-e7586ec7d4e3.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Renovation products</Publisher>
</game>