<Game>
	<Name>Vermilion (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Evil threatens the world of Vermilion. Armies of the evil Tsarkon march in conquest. All hearts look to you. From your beginnings in the humble village of Wyclif, you must search the world for the 8 rings of good. On the long road ahead you'll face treacherous governors and beasts ten times your size! You'll travel to 14 towns and battle through 14 first-person dungeons where every corner can mean death. Choose from dozens of swords and shields. Prepare to face the archmonsters, forked tails and hideous eyes of Tsarkon's minions. Talk with townspeople to learn the secrets of the caves. Be ready for hundreds of hours of adventure gameplay. Save up to three different games with battery backup. Over 30 spells and 20 special items - use them with care. At last, armed with the Sword of Vermilion, you're ready to meet Tsarkon in the final struggle!Cheat: Test MenuDuring any time during the game, [I]simultaneously press and hold the A, B and C buttons and  press Start on controller 2[/I]. A test menu should appear with [I]Input, Sound and C.R.T[/I] tests. And when you exit, it will send you back to the Sega logo screen.Cheat: Super Strength/ Virtual InvincibilityFor this cheat, you need a cursed weapon/suit of armor. Also, having Rafael's Stick helps save some cash, but you don't absolutely need it. Also, if you want the effects to be permanent, your level has to be maxed at 31. Cheat: Super Strength/ Virtual InvincibilityEquip the cursed weapon/armor. Now, either use Rafael's Stick or talk to a priest to remove the curse. Your strength or armor class (depending on what you equipped that was cursed) will go down. Keep re-equipping and removing the cursed item until your Strength/Armor Class goes to a ridiculous #, like 9999 or something like that. Now, re-equip your most powerful weapon/armor, and you'll either kill enemies in one hit guaranteed (Super Strength), or take only 1 damage from any attack from any enemy, including bosses (Invincibility)Cheat: Quick CashIn Keltwick, when Bearwulf gives you the dungeon key to get to Malaga, sell it. It's worth 1000 kims and Bearwulf has an unlimited amount of them. Just go back, talk to him and he'll say ''Did you lose the key? I have another one.'' He'll give it to you, and you can repeat the process as much as you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/12/1989</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sega AM2</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.1</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>rMuO77A9f8s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>705</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586515-sword-of-vermilion</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/705-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/705-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/2/3/gfs_46802_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/f/3/gfs_46802_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/4/3/gfs_46802_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/5/3/gfs_46802_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/3/gfs_46802_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/b/e/gfs_46802_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/6/e/gfs_46802_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/e/gfs_46802_2_3.jpg</snapshot8>
</game>