<Game>
	<Name>Verytex (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Humanity has long since advanced into space, and colonies have been established on many planets, but humanity has yet to contact any alien life. However, an emergency signal has come from the planet Shirakusa. During a colonization survey, contact was lost with the battleship Aphrodite. As a member of the elite Verytex squad, you are sent to investigate.Verytex is a vertically scrolling space shooter with vague organic themes. There are six stages and three different weapon types: Normal Shot, a standard multidirectional cannon; Beam Laser, a powerful forward-shooting weapon; and Boomerang Laser, a wide-range forward shot. Each weapon type can be upgraded to three increasing levels of power. Also available are homing missiles, which are also upgradeable, as well as smart bombs and shield pickups.Cheat: Extra LivesPause the game, then while holding down press start for each extra life you want.Cheat: Extra LivesPause the game, then hold right and press start for each extra shield you want.Cheat: Extra LivesHold A + B + C + Start</plot>
	<releasedate>5/4/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Asmik Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>L7FvNbS5MgY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20436</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586578-verytex</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/verytex</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/verytex/3030-40883/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20436-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/119101-verytex-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323006-verytex-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323007-verytex-genesis-screenshot-act-1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323008-verytex-genesis-screenshot-a-wave-of-enemies.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323009-verytex-genesis-screenshot-an-enemy-exploding.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323010-verytex-genesis-screenshot-collecting-a-weapon-power-up.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323011-verytex-genesis-screenshot-shooting-a-powered-up-weapon.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323012-verytex-genesis-screenshot-letting-off-a-bomb-clears-the-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323013-verytex-genesis-screenshot-flying-with-the-shield-power-up.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323014-verytex-genesis-screenshot-fighting-off-a-midsized-enemy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/323015-verytex-genesis-screenshot-a-boss-battle.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Verytex (ヴェリテックス) is a 1991 shoot-'em-up game by Asmik for the Sega Mega Drive released exclusively in Japan. Humans have developed the ability to colonize other planets and have started doing so with great success as no extraterrestrial life has been found. One day, however, the armed forces of the prosperous planet Syracuse have turned on its people for no apparent reason, and it is up to you and the Verytex fighter to stop them and find out why. A shoots (you have rapidfire). B drops bombs (you have a limited supply, but you can get up to 6 by collecting items with the letter B on them). C changes the speed of the ship (there are three available speeds, the current speed is shown in the HUD), and the charge generated at the back of your ship can be used to destroy close-by enemies. Powerups are collected as usual. There are three weapons available (each identified by a different color): the default "yellow" weapon that shoots normal bullets, the "blue" weapon that shoots boomerang-shaped bullets which are weak but very spread, and the "red" weapon that shoots a very powerful concentrated laser but only can shoot forwards. Collecting the same kind of weapon the ship currently has will level up it. Two more power-ups are available: one with the letter "M" that makes the ship shoot missiles alongside the current weapon (up to 7 at any given time on screen) and one with the letter "S" with gives the player a shield that can last several hits.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48b313d5-a613-4912-9c4d-1db8f8f6275e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49493c6a-435d-466c-a0e1-3d43900939c6.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b74a4a03-0c52-45ce-8c10-929df525ccdd.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cf03ebdb-a38d-4b7f-97e9-3f1a5d0a81c8.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dce2029c-87b2-491e-b66b-2caaad480172.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d6e7f00-db7a-452d-982c-35433ce82653.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Asmik</Publisher>
</game>