<Game>
	<Name>Virtua Fighter 2 (Korea)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Released in 1994, running in high resolution at an impressive 60 frames per second, Virtua Fighter 2 was release on Sega's Model-2 hardware in arcades. Adding to the original roster two fighters with unique fighting styles, Shun-Di, master of drunken kung fu and Lion Rafale, master of praying mantis kung fu. In Q4 of 1995, Virtua Fighter 2 was ported to Sega Saturn, and in the years to follow was release on multiple platforms including Sega Genesis (1996, as a 2D fighter), PC (1997), and ten years later, the Wii's Virtual Console (2007). It was Sega of Japan's biggest hit, being their first title to hit one million in sales in Japan for Sega of Japan. It is widely regarded as one of the 5 best titles in the history of the Saturn platform.Characters:   Akira Yuki   Sarah Bryant   Wolf Hawkfield   Dural   Jacky Bryant   Kage-Maru    Jeffry McWild    Lau Chan    Pai Chan    Shun Di*    Lion Rafale** New to the title.Virtua Fighter 2.1 Released only in Japan, Virtua Fighter 2.1 featured enhanced graphics, slightly tweaked gameplay and a re-designed Dural as a playable fighter.  This version was also released as part of the  Sega Ages 2500 collection. The European release has, under the Options tab, the ability to choose between versions 2.0 and 2.1, however the manual makes no reference to Dural. The changes are listed as follows: Expert Mode addedJacky's Crescent and Sweep attack levels corrected Akira's long-range dashing elbow corrected to dashing elbow with foot position changeShun's long range sweep is corrected to sweep without foot position changeWolf's punches and elbow attacks addedCertain moves no longer knock an opponent down. It is also more difficult to back away from an opponent (the pause between steps is slightly longer). Cheat: Different CostumesTo play in a character's different costumes, Hold UP and then select your character with the A button or C button. or Hold DOWN and select your character with the A button or C button or Start button.Cheat: Different CostumesPress Down, Up, Right, and A + Left at the Character Selection Screen for 99 seconds of time.Cheat: Different CostumesEnter the options screen,then highlight the ''Exit'' selection, and tap Left until the hidden options are displayedCheat: Different CostumesHold B while highlighting player 1's life selection at the Options screen, until the message ''No Damage'' appears. Then press Start.Cheat: Different CostumesJust highlight Akira if using controller one or Jacky if using controller two. Then press Left and then Right on the D-Pad. Repeat this a few times and Dural should then appear as a selectable character. Now you can use him as your character in the game!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8SWz2V4e0D4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4710</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586580-virtua-fighter-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/virtua-fighter-2_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/virtua-fighter-2/3030-41/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/13/139866/2595079-16193501.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4710-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/69348-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81617-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81616-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-character-select-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81615-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-jeffry-vs-jacky.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81618-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-pai-takes-out-wolf.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81619-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-and-rubs-it-in.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/81620-virtua-fighter-2-genesis-screenshot-aerial-attack-by-kage.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/6/f/gfs_61956_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/b/f/gfs_61956_1_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/0/f/gfs_61956_1_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/1/f/gfs_61956_1_4.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/4710-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/llEq5o6.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4710.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The arcade smash hit explodes onto Genesis! Select one of eight fighters, then pummel the opposition, either computer or friend, who stand in the way of a showdown with the mysterious Dural!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>oulNdGCcYE8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6780788b-34cc-4c89-8771-dcf44035fc97.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f0dddebe-95a7-4ad1-8311-c2f1879d4e7b.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7568f9f-6452-462b-aa67-47844ab0f6fb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ca453f25-b985-421f-aaf1-81c25bbe5f7d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6b4a4737-08a8-4e94-8565-5c4da4fb2c54.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>