<Game>
	<Name>Vixen 357 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In 2384 AD, a great interstellar war took place. The Earth emerged victorious, thanks to a secretly developed robot weapon called "Serd". After the war, the usage of Serds was not a secret any more, and various nations started using them for military purposes. Several years, a more powerful weapon named Vector was developed. The usage of such highly destructive weapons led to wars between the nations of the world. You control Takuya Murasawa and his comrades, member of a special military force called Slash. Everything begins with an attack of unidentified Vectors on their base..."Vixen 357" is an anim-style strategy/RPG game with mech combat. You control your robots by moving them over the battle map, and fighting enemies with long-ranged or mele attacks. An animated battle sequence is shown when you and enemy robots attack each other. You can switch pilots in the robots and repair them during battles. Your pilots level up by gaining experience points, and you'll be able to acquire new robots and weapons during the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>NCS Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>yGAZU_Ibn8Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20437</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570435-vixen-357</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/vixen-357</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/vixen-357/3030-4111/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20437-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/227847-vixen-357-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/227848-vixen-357-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102415-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102413-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-introducing-other-characters.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102414-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-take-a-good-look-at-that.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102417-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-the-hero-takuya-murasawa.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102416-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102412-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-first-chapter-story.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102418-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-explaining-the-situation.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102419-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-pilot-information.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102420-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-move-attack-or-information-your.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102421-vixen-357-genesis-screenshot-you-are-being-shot-at.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A war with the aliens was ended with victory of the Earth, thanks to secretly developed battle robots named SERDs. Years passed and wounds from this war were healed. Humans once again divided into multiple nations. And, as always, started to make a more powerful weapons. A new and much more powerful battle mech prototypes named VECTOR were developed and subsequently build. And while Takuya and his team were testing them, some unknown enemy VECTORs attacked their base. Vixen 357 is a turn-based strategy RPG game developed by the same team responsible for the Langrisser games. Those who remember and like Langrisser games will feel right at home with this one, but it also has its own distinctive features, so it’s not just “Langrisser IN SPACE!!”. All characters can use different mechs and weapons, and there are special attacks. Many situations require to use some tactical thinking, so you cannot just rush headlong into things for the most part.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eab4fa33-7e7a-4d36-9f2d-905311a71343.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4c5e3873-aab4-4639-9a66-34de1441dfcb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Masaya</Publisher>
</game>