<Game>
	<Name>VR Troopers (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>VR Troopers was a show about fighting evil monsters. The person that made   Power Rangers also made this show. The game was based off of the TV show.  Characters Ryan Steele - The leader in VR troopers. His father is part of the evil side.   Finishing Moves Laser Fist Command -  His hands turn blue like lasers and punches the enemy.Lightning Hand Command - his hands glow blue and slices through enemies. Internal Gyro Command   JB Reese - Tech guy for the VR troopers. He is a computer genius.   Finishing Moves Super saber- two swords and hacked and slashed the enemies.VR techno bazooka- a double barrel rocket launcher.Vortex Command- He made him and the enemy into a virtual world.    Kaitlin Star - A news reporter and photographer. It seemed like she was just put into the show and game for an extra character.    Finishing Moves VR Kaitlin Double Team- she would transform into two of her to fight enemies. VR Double Team- She and JB would combine their two pistols to turn it into a better gun.  Jeb- Jeb is Ryan Steele's dog. Jeb has the ability to talk. He got this ability by accent from a power surge. He only talks to the troopers for advice. In the game he usually tells the player to go kick butt. 	</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Syrox Development</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>DJtDEwXBjnM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4712</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586582-vr-troopers</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/vr-troopers/3030-22161/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4712-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/f/8/gfs_39083_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/2/8/gfs_39083_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/9/8/gfs_39083_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/8/8/gfs_39083_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/3/8/gfs_39083_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/6/5/gfs_39083_2_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/b/5/gfs_39083_2_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/0/5/gfs_39083_2_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/1/5/gfs_39083_2_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/a/5/gfs_39083_2_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4712.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Saban's VR Troopers is based on the TV show of the same name and is made by the same company that produced the Mighty Morphin' Power Rangers. The story has the evil Grimlord transport the VR Troopers into (ironically) a video game and it is up to the player (literally) to save them and bring them back to the real world. The gameplay is the standard fighting game, using one of the three different Troopers to kick, punch and use special abilities to defeat a fighter to advance to the next one. Each Trooper has their own strengths, weaknesses and special moves and each has their own separate stages, depending on which the player chooses. It also has multi player capabilities that lets two friends battle head-to-head in a Duel Mode.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>RACuCZf7zLU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66d8f7ee-e075-4e9e-9bdc-201f14bcca0d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41361401-a3ff-46a7-a06f-ad98af493e5d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9dfb864-904f-4334-b4af-c9b815df0fdd.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>