<Game>
	<Name>Wacky Races (USA) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Dastardly and Muttley are set on winning (or sabotaging) the annual Wacky Races. A racer bearing a strong resemblance to mario kart with the Wacky Racers from the Hanna Barbara cartoon.Might have made a pretty good competitor for Mario Kart if the game had been completed. The known beta lacks the polish of a finished product, but is playable and looks decent enough, the worst bit is the poor sound.http://www.genesisproject-online.com/Genesis/U-w/WackyRaces.htmlCheat: PasswordsAt the password screen, enter one of the following codes for the desired effect:Cheat: UnlockablesUnlockablesCheat: Speed BoostThis speed boost can occur at the beginning of a race. When the count down begins, if you press the Acceleration button when the count down reaches 1, and you hold it until the race starts, you get a boost of speed.</plot>
	<releasedate>Unreleased</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Unreleased</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>Ly8FqQQ2HIQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>9376</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/665695-wacky-races</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/9376-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/9376-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/b/gfs_256395_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/a/b/gfs_256395_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/1/b/gfs_256395_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/0/b/gfs_256395_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/b/b/gfs_256395_2_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/6/b/gfs_256395_2_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/d/b/gfs_256395_2_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/0/a/gfs_256395_2_8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/b/a/gfs_256395_2_9.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/9376-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>Cancelled You take on the role of Dastardly and Mutley from the Hanna-Barbera cartoon series in this action title with superficial racing overtones. Your aim is to complete each course in a particular position, which is achieved either by waiting for them to suffer enough damage to drop out of the race, or by inflicting that damage yourself. Your car is armed with a forward-shooting arrow to impale the opposition cars, and deal with the many hazards the races throw at you, including boulders and rabbits, which can be taken out for points. This game was never officially released on the Genesis.</Notes>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/012c999d-8388-4735-8626-39b693a9d597.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44d1105d-11a6-4f1a-abbb-1303cc377dbb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ead76c0-a56d-4bd7-a69f-a869747b3542.jpg</snapshot11>
	<rating>4</rating>
	<Publisher>Hi-Tech</Publisher>
</game>