<Game>
	<Name>Wani Wani World (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Wani Wani World is a modified conversion of the 1991 Kaneko coin-op The Berlin Wall, itself based on the 1980 coin-op Space Panic. Two small dinosaurs with very large hammers, Charlie and Smiley, make their way through numerous screens of platforms and ladders filled with enemies. Their only method of attack is to bash a hole in the ground, wait for an enemy to fall into it, and then bash the enemy in the head, which causes the enemy to fall and transform into items and delicious food.There are five worlds, each with several screens and large boss at the end, as well as a minigame between worlds where bonus items can be earned. The game can be played alone or two-player cooperatively.Cheat: Spin the SlotsWith the World Select code activated, when in-game, pause the game and press Up, A, Right, A, Down, A, Left. This will spin the casino slots for free items and other rewards.Cheat: Spin the SlotsAt the Title Screen, before pressing Start but after the music starts but press Up, A, B, C, Right, A, B, C, Down, A, B, C, Left, A, and B.  At the Options screen and a new World option will be shown.Cheat: Infinite livesWhen the SEGA logo appears, press the Reset button. Do this twice in a row for infinite lives. Your lives should now be displayed as two question marks instead of a number.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kaneko Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>HYwD3ONpfxw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20433</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/570391-trouble-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/wani-wani-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wani-wani-world/3030-22638/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20433-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/256124-wani-wani-world-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411905-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411906-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-options-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411907-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-the-map-of-wani-wani-world.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411908-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-alright-let-s-get-those.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411909-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-to-destroy-enemies-charlie.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411910-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-area-secure.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411911-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-i-used-a-bomb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411912-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-enemies-will-drop-various.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411913-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-enemies-will-explode-into.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/411914-wani-wani-world-genesis-screenshot-these-techno-looking-platforms.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Wani Wani World (ワニワニＷｏｒｌｄ) is a reskinned Berlin no Kabe released by Kaneko in 1992 exclusively on the Sega Mega Drive. In South Korea, it is known as Ageo Nara (악어나라), which roughly translates to "Crocodile's Land". Gameplay is identical to Berlin no Kabe, except C both breaks and destroys a block and you only need one hit to destroy a block. Special items collected throughout the levels are used with B. Each world has nine normal levels, an autoscrolling level forcing you to climb to the boss's chamber, a boss, and then another bonus round.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63d987f8-f8b6-4136-80e9-807da99e6695.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a80062fe-b8cd-43a3-81bd-020e1631f3f4.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a1db0e0b-c895-47ed-9c84-61f061fe1759.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8d2287d-40cc-4a1f-9750-f5c01e1ea517.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46df2e9c-74f1-4b86-a53e-aa20f141dcb3.jpg</snapshot13>
	<rating>4</rating>
	<Publisher>Kaneko</Publisher>
</game>