<Game>
	<Name>Williams Arcade's Greatest Hits (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Play Defender once again, and navigate your vessel through alien territory! Defender II includes added villains and features not found in the original Defender! Challenge gladiators in a fight to the death in Joust! Once again, Robotron: 2084 lets you clash with a mutant force of robots to save the only remaining human family! With the coolest graphics of its time, SiniStar returns with great outerspace battle action!Cheat: Start a game as normal, and during gameplay, perform the following sequences with the joystick and start buttons:Cheat: 1. Move right, Fire up, and press the Player 1 start button.Cheat: 2. Move up, Fire down, and press the Player 2 start button.Cheat: 3. Move down, Fire up.Cheat: You must do each part of the sequence within a quarter second of one another, but you may hold each part as long as you wish.  When the third part is done, the programmer credits will pop up and remain onscreen as long as the fire joystick is held upward.  Be warned that you will lose your game if you do this trick, and it must be done without dying.Cheat: This is tricky, but very possible to pull off in most if not all versions of Sinistar. With only no lives remaining, when you fly up to a fully build Sinistar, he'll suck you in and eat you. However, if a UFO is around when this animation is occuring and you get shot before being eaten, the lives will be -1, which will loop back around to 255. Have fun!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Compilation, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Williams</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>4726</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586028-williams-arcades-greatest-hits</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/williams-arcade-classics/3030-1956/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4726-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/4/7/33947_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/c/gfs_38805_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/7/c/gfs_38805_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/c/gfs_38805_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/d/c/gfs_38805_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/6/c/gfs_38805_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/b/c/gfs_38805_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/0/c/gfs_38805_1_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/d/d/gfs_38805_1_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/d/gfs_38805_1_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/1/gfs_38805_2_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Williams Arcade Classics is a compilation that includes the following games: Defender Defender II Joust Robotron: 2084 Sinistar</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c9f988fe-79aa-43b7-84ca-35004ddc2d0a.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3940741d-568f-4e92-80f0-28d05f35cc56.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb9afa38-5d87-45e7-b596-581b552abd72.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>