<Game>
	<Name>Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Wonder Boy in Monster World is the fifth Wonder Boy game in Westone's series of platformers, and the first to have originally debuted on the Sega Genesis. In Japan, the game is known as "Wonder Boy V: Monster World III", and is recognized as the third game in the "Monster World" sub-series, the first two being Wonder Boy in Monster Land and Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap. The fourth Monster World game is Monster World IV, which at that point had moved away from the Wonder Boy brand. The Monster World games are distinctive within the Wonder Boy franchise for their more overt RPG trappings, like buying new equipment and increasing the main character's maximum health.Wonder Boy in Monster World was later released in the U.S. on the Sega Genesis in 1992 and also on the European Sega Mega Drive. It also got back-ported to the Sega Master System with a graphical downgrade. There is also a TurboGrafx-CD release and rebranding of the game, which was known as The Dynastic Hero ("Chou Eiyuu Densetsu: Dynastic Hero" on the PC Engine CD-ROM). Lastly, both Wonder Boy in Monster World and The Dynastic Hero blessed the Wii Virtual Console back in 2007.Cheat: Save at any time (Japanese Version only)If you want to save the game, kill yourself and you will be sent back to the last inn you stayed at without being punished. This is much quicker as you don't have to travel all the way back.Cheat: Save at any time (Japanese Version only)Any Inn throughout the game will still let you spend the night, even if you don't have enough gold.  If you're short, they will take whatever you have, even if you don't have any gold at all.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>NF_5JuvmfFo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>729</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586607-wonder-boy-in-monster-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/wonder-boy-in-monster-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wonder-boy-in-monster-world/3030-9245/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/729-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/729-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/50tYdrl.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/117232-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34926-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34927-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-in-a-village.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34928-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-buying-things.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34931-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-equipping.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34932-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-blue-sky-and.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34934-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-get-away-from.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34935-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-castle.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34936-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-looks-like-a.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34937-wonder-boy-in-monster-world-genesis-screenshot-how-to-gain.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/d/c/gfs_2225_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/729-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/729-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DLeQoZS.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Wonder Boy In Monster World puts you in control of Shion in his quest to save Monster World from the evil BioMeka. It controls like your standard platform game: run, jump, and kill enemies. The game is filled with RPG elements such as talking to townsfolk, collecting money to buy items, extending your life bar, and equipping a large variety of armor, weapons and magic. Shion travels through the many interconnected regions of Monster World, all the while collecting increasingly powerful equipment in the form of many different swords, spears, shields, suits of armor, and boots.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd99b3fb-cf8e-435c-8988-375a2705afd2.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/765f8600-92c6-4f43-9094-df08902689ba.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23d7615f-0eb3-41ca-981f-f45e2317269a.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>