<Game>
	<Name>World Series Baseball '95 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>700 MAJOR LEAGUE PLAYERSINCLUDING SANDERS, BONDS, BELLE, GWYNN, BAGWELL, PIAZZA, MCGRIFF, AND PUCKETT.-Improved sound effects, music, and announcers put you in the ballpark.-32 bit technology allows for a gradual zoom to the outfield, for better views of players making diving catches, and climbing the walls to rob home runs.-The power of 32X allows for enhanced colors of all stadiums and logos.-Put together the greatest team in history with 50 all time great Legend players.-Multi-player option allows you and your friends to battle it out!-Mid-season All-Star game with your season's best players.-Track stats for individuals, teams and league leaders.-Play in Exhibition, Full Season, and Playoff modes plus 2 Home Run Derby Modes.-Draft and Trade players to create your own dream squad.Cheat: Debug menu Hold A + B + C + Start when the opening logo starts to fade. Release the buttons when the Bluesky Zone appears. Press Start.Cheat: Debug menu Enter the code for the blue sky team, select the teams you want to play, at the controller screen choose team, hold up, press C 3 timesCheat: Debug menuEnter the DEBUG MODE code, then press START twice.. After that you put in these numbers in order 3,1,3 then hold A+B+C+Start.  Press start two(2) times then put the Bluesky mode on then press start.  Go to a normal game and you will find the Bluesky team.Cheat: Home run celebrationsAfter you hit a home run, try pressing A, B, and/or C. If you do A, he'll do cartwheels. B, points at the pitcher. C, waves his arms, or tips his cap. Take that Mr pitcher!!</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>vrBWwpKOJYY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4738</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/921794-world-series-baseball-95</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/world-series-baseball-95</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/world-series-baseball-95/3030-43821/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4738-1.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325208-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-a-player-takes.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325209-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325210-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325211-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-choosing-which.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325212-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-the-box-score.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325213-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-choosing-a-type.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325214-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-selecting-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325215-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-ball-being-pitched.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325216-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-speed-of-the-pitch.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/325217-world-series-baseball-95-genesis-screenshot-selecting-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zZ9XktI.png</banner1>
	<Notes>World Series Baseball '95 is a follow-up to World Series Baseball. The 1995 edition features updated rosters with 700 players. All 28 teams are present, and the stadiums they play in show digitized players and animations. The game supports battery back-up and the ability to play as baseball legends such as Dizzy Dean, Lou Gehrig and Ty Cobb.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c43b4926-e168-481e-8e8c-e7e4e80a117b.JPG</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7fa867c8-5c0a-4b75-a931-12f8688adb12.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>