<Game>
	<Name>World Heroes (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:World Heroes is a 2D fighting game developed in 1992 by                                         ADK and published by     SNK for the                       Neo Geo. Its premise was that a scientist named Dr. Brown created a time machine and used it to organize a martial arts tournament for various historical fighters. Many of the fighters are based on historical figures and fictional characters. The game was mainly dismissed due to its similarities with                        Street Fighter II, but received a cult following that spawned three sequels. The game also debuts the two ninjas,                      Hanzo and                     Fuuma (who are similar in terms of                    Ryu and                   Ken), who later returned in                  NeoGeo Battle Coliseum.  The game was ported to the                SNES in 1993 by                 SunSoft, which is considered the best version due to the ability to use a five-button configuration instead of three (Two for punches, two for kicks, and either shoulder button for throwing) while improving button response and retaining everything about the original version. The game was also ported to the               Sega Genesis in 1994 by              Sega, which is considered one of the worst Neo Geo conversions of all time. The original version was released for the            Neo Geo CD with an arranged soundtrack in 1995 and the           Wii Virtual Console on September 28, 2007. The game was also included in the          World Heroes Anthology compilation for the         PlayStation 2 and an unlockable game in the        SNK Arcade Classics V.1 compilation for the PlayStation 2,       PlayStation Portable, and      Wii. Gameplay:World Heroes plays like a traditional 2D fighter, using three attack buttons. (one for punches, one for kicks, and one for throws) Holding down the punch or kick button makes the attack stronger while simply tapping the button gives a quick strike.  The game also featured Death Match mode, which significantly changed the arena to include gameplay obstacles. Arenas could have mines or slippery oil covering parts of the arena. The edges of the arenas could even have electric beams or spiked walls. Characters:    Hanzo (based on Hanzo Hattori)    Fuuma (based on Fuma Kotaro)    Kim Dragon (based on    Bruce Lee)    Janne D'Arc (based on    Joan of Arc)                                 Julius Carn (based on                                   Genghis Khan)    Muscle Power (based on    Hulk Hogan)    Brocken    Rasputin (based on Grigori Rasputin)                                         Geegus (boss, based on                                T-1000)Critical Reception   When released for the SNES Electronic Gaming Monthly Assigned scores of 8,6,6 and 6 with Ed Semrad writing, "...The best part of this game is the death match, where anything goes.  It would be nice if there was blood when you hit the spikes though.  The play control is good for most of the fighters and the only down point is that it plays slow.  Fighting fans who can't afford a Neo will be happy with this one".Cheat: See the game designers facesWhen you get a high score, enter JJJ as your initials. You will be presented with a white screen where three of the game designers faces will fly towards the front of the screen. This will repeat infinitely until you reset the game or shut the Sega Genesis off.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>vpH1VxmWAsQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4737</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586612-world-heroes</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/world-heroes</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/world-heroes/3030-18554/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4737-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213625-world-heroes-genesis-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213626-world-heroes-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128178-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128179-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128180-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-unique-and-static-introduction.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128188-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-choose-a-fighter.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128192-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-game-mode-selection-normal.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128193-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-vs-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/467188-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-world-map-with-the-location.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/467189-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-fuuma-vs-rasputin-who-seems.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/467190-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-get-a-grip.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/467191-world-heroes-genesis-screenshot-janne-vs-m-power-in-a-death.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/4737.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Are you ready for a fierce battle in an ultra-deathmatch!? Who is the greatest hero in the world? You will find out today! A scientist has created a time machine that eight heroes will travel through time with to prove who is the greatest fighter of all time!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6849003e-46da-4053-9d9a-1909808498e4.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ae93b6b4-79d3-4d0a-96ba-01cee7294b37.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>