<Game>
	<Name>WWF Raw (World)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:WWF Raw is a wrestling game developed by  Sculptured Software and published by  Acclaim or LJN for multiple platforms. It is named for the TV show WWF Raw which regularly aired matches between WWF (now WWE) wrestlers and wrote stories around those bouts.The game uses a horizontal perspective of the ring and has multiple different modes based on events from the TV show: One-on-One, Tag Team, Bedlam, Survivor Series, Royal Rumble and Raw Endurance. Depending on the system, the player has a roster of up to thirteen WWF wrestlers to choose from. As well as regular attacks and signature moves, wrestlers will frequently get locked into a grapple and the player must mash buttons to escape and use the advantage to throw their opponent.Featured WrestlersSNES, Genesis &amp; 32X Versions 1-2-3 Kid Bam Bam Bigelow Bret Hart DieselDoink the ClownKwang (only 32X Version with a code) Lex LugerLuna Vachon Owen Hart Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaGame Gear Version Bam Bam Bigelow Bret HartCrush Diesel Lex Luger Randy Savage Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaGame Boy Version Bret Hart DieselDoink the Clown Lex Luger Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaCheat: continue in RumbleDuring Royal Rumble, if you are thrown out, hold A, B, &amp; C. If there are any wrestlers left, you will come back as that person. You should hear a single bell ring if done correctly.Cheat: continue in Rumble Enter the CHANGE STATS code for the wrestler you want. When you are asked to change the attributes, hold Start until you hear a strange noise. You can now set all the attributes to 10!Cheat: continue in RumbleDuring a one-on-one match (one fall, brawl, tournament) press A+B+C on controller 2, and a wrestler will come out and help the opponent.Cheat: continue in RumbleIn a one player game choose a tag team match, a bedlam or a survivor series. Start the game, then press A+B+C to turn into your partner.Cheat: continue in RumbleTo play as a fighter that's already been chosen, move to that wrestler's selection screen. To activate your selection, press Up + A + C.Cheat: continue in RumbleNote: this code works with 4-player adapters, but you can only have two of any one wrestler.Cheat: continue in Rumble This code will give you fists of steel. At the copyright screen, hold Start, then press Up, Up, Up, Up. The screen will flash red and you'll hear a crash.Cheat: continue in Rumble At the copyright screen, hold A+B+C+START and rotate the d-pad clockwise. The screen should flash red if done correctly.Cheat: KO the ReferreTo knockout the ref, either punch him three times or run into him. While he\'s unconcious you can perform illegal moves in the ring.Cheat: KO the ReferreIf you knock him out repeatedly, he\'ll run away and your match will become a brawl. This lasts until one of you runs out of energy.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>hY2oqFj-YhE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2222</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/919590-wwf-raw</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/wwf-raw-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wwf-raw/3030-4155/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2222-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2222-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/2222-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/75555-wwf-raw-genesis-screenshot-select-a-fighter.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/75556-wwf-raw-genesis-screenshot-the-commentators-present-the-wrestlers.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/75557-wwf-raw-genesis-screenshot-aggressive-action-outside-the-ring.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/75558-wwf-raw-genesis-screenshot-rumble.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/75559-wwf-raw-genesis-screenshot-make-strategic-tags-and-pin-your.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/f/2/gfs_49348_1_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/2/2/gfs_49348_1_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/2/gfs_49348_1_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/f/gfs_49348_2_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>WWF Raw is a professional wrestling game featuring up to twelve superstars (ten in the GameGear, eight in the GameBoy version) from the World Wrestling Federation: Bret "Hit Man" Hart, Bam Bam Bigelow, 1-2-3 Kid, Diesel, Doink, Lex Luger, Luna Vachon, Owen Hart, Razor Ramon, Shawn Michaels, Undertaker, and Yokozuna. In this game, player-controlled wrestlers attempt to pin the opponents to the mat by reducing their power meter until they can fight no more. There is a large number of moves to perform, including turnbuckle maneuvers and "illegal" acts such as hitting the opponent with a metal folding chair. This game supports up to four simultaneous players, and has the following modes: One-on-One, Tag Team, Bedlam, Survivor Series, Royal Rumble, Raw Endurance Match, and Rematch.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce61b02f-d404-4a42-9b3e-058b7d4b0613.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5e0c136-b0c3-4ead-a31b-4d4d8c9d6aea.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9105535-fdd7-470f-8742-26b9a3eb5d7b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/702d82b2-8e66-4da2-8200-bed2c0eb7b1a.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>