<Game>
	<Name>WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (USA) (Alpha)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:WWF WrestleMania: The Arcade Game is an exaggerated fighting game that uses digitized sprites of the featured professional wrestlers, similar to Mortal Kombat. Players battle through one-on-one, one-on-two, and one-on-three matches to claim either the Intercontinental Championship or WWF Heavyweight Championship. Vince McMahon and Jerry Lawler provided commentary and the game was later ported to home consoles by Acclaim Studios Salt Lake City, which would make the successor title, WWF in Your House.Playable CharactersThe UndertakerShawn MichaelsBret HartRazor RamonLex LugerBam Bam Bigelow (Not playable in the SNES version)Yokozuna (Not playable in the SNES version)Doink The ClownGameplay:Developed by Midway, WWF Wrestlemania plays similarly to Mortal Kombat, with a few exceptions. Characters can move in somewhat 3-D space, in that you can walk up and down, as well as left and right. Combat features 5 buttons, Light Punch, Power Punch, Light Kick, Power Kick and Block. It is also possible to Run by pressing Light Punch and Light Kick together.The main game consists of the player choosing to go after the Intercontinental title or the World Wrestling Federation Title. In the Intercontinental Title challenge, you'll face 4 opponents via 1-on-1 matches, followed by two 2-on-1 matches, and finally a 3-on-1 match. In the WWF Title Challenge, you'll start out with four 2-on-1 matches, moving on to two 3-on-1 matches, and finally the "Wrestlemania Challenge", a gauntlet match against every wrestler in the game. In the final match, however, only 4 people (including yourself) will be in the ring at once. Once you eliminate an opponent, someone will replace them until you've beaten all eight opponents.Each character has a unique ending.The only known "finishing move", similar to a Fatality, is done by the Undertaker. Originally the game was scheduled to have finishing moves for each character, but the WWF shot down the plan.Cheat: Freeze TimerPause game play and press Left, A, Up, Down, B, A, Up, Down. The timer will now freeze.Cheat: Freeze TimerPause game play and press Down, Up Left, Left, Left, Up, A, Up. You will now never lose energy.Cheat: Freeze TimerPause game play and press D, Up, A, Left, C, Left, Up, B. Your opponent will now lose in 2-3 blow.Cheat: Freeze TimerPause game play and press Right, A, Down, B, Left, Up, Right.Cheat: Freeze TimerPause game play and press B, A, Down, B, Up, Left(x2). Both characters may execute unlimited combos. </plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>shsYfKvykwg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>731</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/919593-wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game/3030-8027/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5166/1559062-wwf_wrestlemania_the_arcade_flyer.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/731-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/137239-wwf-wrestlemania-dos-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701304-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-player-select.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701305-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-select-your-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701306-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-fighters-intro-s.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701307-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-next-fight.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701308-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-match-1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701309-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-punch-to-the-head.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701310-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-first-attack.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701311-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-he-grabbed-you.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701312-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-in-a-hold.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/701313-wwf-wrestlemania-arcade-screenshot-kick-to-the-midriff.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QeU8drP.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/731.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>WrestleMania's one-player mode has the player choose one of eight wrestlers - Bam Bam Bigelow, Bret Hart, Doink the Clown, Lex Luger, Razor Ramon, Shawn Michaels, The Undertaker or Yokozuna. One unique feature is that each character can "bleed" his respective objects other than blood upon taking damage from most attacks in the Mortal Kombat sense. Such "bleeding" objects include Yokozuna's food and Bam Bam Bigelow's flames. WWF WrestleMania features two single-player modes: the Intercontinental Championship and the WWF Championship. In the Intercontinental Championship mode, the player must win four one-on-one matches, two two-on-one matches, and one three-on-one match to win the title. In the more difficult WWF Championship mode, the player must win four two-on-one matches, two three-on-one matches, and finally a "WrestleMania Challenge," where the player must defeat every wrestler in the game in a gauntlet, starting with a three-on-one setup, with each eliminated opponent being replaced with another until all eight have been defeated. The game also features two multi-player modes; head to head, a one-on-one match between two players, or cooperative, where the two players team up in a tag team version of the WrestleMania Challenge in which they must defeat the game's eight wrestlers in groups of two to become the Tag Team Champions.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39a7b99d-1ce8-4d3f-b540-b3706843ca4d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fca4b430-a5ca-4746-b673-758c4087dd0a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04e60782-9ef8-4fcd-8dc1-f50668f0f9d8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>