<Game>
	<Name>Yogi Bear - Cartoon Capers (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In this vast multi-level platform game, Yogi is awoken from his winter sleep to discover that work has started on a chemical plant in the heart of Jellystone Park. Yogi's mission to alert Ranger Smith of the danger turns into a true fast-paced hilarious adventure through five different terrains of Jellystone Park!Cheat: Infinite LivesAt the title screen press Down, A, Up, B, A, Left, A, Right, Down ("DAUBALARD"). The short sound will denote correct code entry.Cheat: Infinite LivesAt the title screen press Left, A, Up, Down, A, C, Right, A, B ("LAUDACRAB"). The short sound will denote correct code entry.You will get to some variety of Snake game.Cheat: Infinite LivesAt the title screen press C, Right, Up, Down, A, C, Right, Down ("CRUDACRUD"). The short sound will denote correct code entry.You will be able to jump as high as you want and from any point, even in the air.Cheat: Infinite LivesAt the title screen press Right, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, A, Up, C. The short sound will denote correct code entry.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Blue Turtle</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>rZ3DYU8NzmQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20431</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/942356-yogi-bears-cartoon-capers</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/20431-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/4/4/89944_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/4/d/gfs_94092_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/d/0/gfs_94092_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AucVcE4.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Adventures of Yogi Bear is a multi-platform game released by Cybersoft on October 1, 1994 in North America and later in Japan and Europe. The game is called Yogi Bear in Japan, Yogi Bear's: Cartoon Capers for the European Super NES version, and Yogi Bear Cartoon Capers for the European Sega Mega Drive version. When Yogi Bear catches wind of a plan to turn Jellystone Park into a Chemical plant he sets out on a mission to stop it. Play as Yogi in this side-scrolling Action/Adventure that is fit for all ages. Work your way through the five park areas collecting "Pic-i-nic" baskets by bouncing on top of them. In many cases you bounce from one basket to the next raising you into the air where no "average bear" could ever go. There are a variety of enemies such as weasels and skunks. There are also some action parts where you ride a mine cart or go "beaver surfing".</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d22e706-017f-41e6-94aa-6c44d9ea8fa3.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44e08f71-e5cf-470a-8594-d3698b49b1ab.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>