<Game>
	<Name>Ys III (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Years have passed since the swordsman Adol saved the kingdom of Ys from certain destruction.Joined by his companion, the ex-thief, Dogi, they set out for new adventures.And just in time...Bizarre tales of monsters and demons wreaking havoc throughout the Kenai Region reach our heroes.Dogi's hometown of Sarina is in the middle of the afflicted kingdom.He inspires Adol to help him rid the world of this new evil.Join them as they battle the forces of darkness - Deep in a haunted coal mine in the heart of an active volcano and on top of a blizzard swept peak.All the while uncovering clues to the identity of the malevolent force that is guiding the evil warriors of the Dark World.Cheat: Level UpReset the game while holding Up, A, B and C on controller 2. Start the game with the buttons held down, wait until you can open your status screen. On the status screen, enter the code belowCheat: Level UpHold Up on controller two when the Sega logo is displayed. During game play, enter the status screen and hold C. Press Up, then Down.Cheat: Use the Amulet to max out your Levels, HP, and GoldWhen you are on the verge of raising a level, use the third and final charge of the Amulet on the monster that would've raised your level. The game will freeze for a second, the screen will flash, and your levels, HP, and gold should max out, along with the message that your Amulet is exhausted of it's powers. YOU MUST USE THE THIRD AND FINAL CHARGE of the Amulet for this trick to work! This trick will not work in boss fights. NOTE: This trick does not work on the SNES version of Y's III.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Riot</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>oXT1bwuOa7o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4746</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/563358-ys-iii-wanderers-from-ys</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/4746-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/4746-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/e/7/gfs_66257_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/7/a/gfs_66257_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/a/a/gfs_66257_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/c/e/gfs_66257_3_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6EPzH4X.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games, allowing Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. Beside changing the battle system, the game's perspective switches to a side-scrolling view, as opposed to the top-down one of the previous games. Adol also has the ability to jump now. New to the series is the use of magical rings, which give Adol different powering-up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fb01ad3-909d-4351-94dc-bd27b33fd8bd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bdb60760-f727-44f2-a758-e60a4d8b6b38.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Renovation</Publisher>
</game>