<Game>
	<Name>Zero Wing (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Reception:The gameplay was quite well received upon release. British magazine Mean Machines gave the Japanese version a 91% score, praising the gameplay as well as the intro sequence, though this was before the release of the English-language version...Legacy:Zero Wing is incredibly infamous for the opening sequence of the game in the Engrish-language European version for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis. The dialogue has been remixed several times and has even been sung about by Nirvana. The line: "All Your Base Are Belong to Us" has been used many times in pop culture and parodies.Williams licensed the arcade version for distribution in the US, but the console versions of the game were never released in that territory. The infamous English translation comes from the European Mega Drive version of Zero Wing.Cheat: Test ModePause the game, then press C, Up, B, Down, A, Left, Right, B, C, C, Right, Left, Right, A, Down, Start.Here you can change some options, choose any level or view all the endings.Cheat: Alternative EndingsThere are three different endings depending on how many times you beat this game non-stop. No such thing as Expert Mode. Only Easy and Normal(Hard). Beat the game and your back at NATOLS, keep going for more endings.Cheat: level four weapon power-upThough very difficult to acheive it is possible to obtain a level four power up for the zig fighter.  First use the zig's tractor beam to pull in a smart bomb, hold this bomb in your tractor beam until another item ship carrying another bomb is on screen, use the bomb you are carrying to destroy that ship, the item it will drop should be the level four power up.     </plot>
	<releasedate>31/5/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Toaplan Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>D_WaqY7vMgw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>7392</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/468841-zero-wing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/genesis/zero-wing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zero-wing/3030-20364/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2389679-genesis_zerowing_eu.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/7392-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/48481-zero-wing-genesis-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26957-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-and-it-was-this-damn-line-that.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26958-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-and-little-did-we-know-that-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26959-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-of-the-big-explosion-i-see.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26960-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-now-picture-the-mechanic-talking.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26961-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-signal-say-even-engrish-speak.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26962-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-yes-him.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26963-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-couldn-t-be-better-thanks.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26964-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-don-t-question-the-man-you-zig.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26965-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-oh-no-you-don-t-say.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/26966-zero-wing-genesis-screenshot-i-say-victoly-a-winner-is-cats.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/7392-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/7392-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/H5SETif.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/7392.png</clearlogo1>
</game>