<Game>
	<Name>Zool - Ninja of the 'Nth' Dimension (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Once every year, the games world is rocked by a game so stunning, so fast, so colorful, so big, so demanding, so mega, so awesome, so varied , so incredible, and so full of fabulous features and unexpected treats, that everybody just looks at it and says "THAT'S IT!" This year, ZOOL, THE NINJA FROM THE Nth DIMENSION, is definitely "IT!"Gameplay::Zool is a "Ninja Of The "Nth" Dimension" who is forced to land on Earth. In order to gain ninja ranking he has to pass six lands. Gremlin has asserted that the name "Zool" did not refer to the supernatural entity Zuul from the film Ghostbusters.The game is a pure arcade platform game, relying on smooth, fast moving gameplay, colorful graphics and a popular soundtrack by Patrick Phelan which overlaps with the Lotus 3 soundtrack and has inspired several modern electro/techno remixes. The game also contains a number of embedded minigames, including several arcade games, a scrolling space shooter and a game accessible only by making Zool play a certain tune on an in-game piano.Zool was also ported to the Atari ST, Game Boy, Sega Mega Drive, SNES, Master System, Sega Game Gear, Amiga CD32, PC, Acorn Archimedes and Jaguar. A Zool coin-op was released in 1993 to cash in on the hype surrounding the Amiga release, but was not well distributed and is now not widely remembered. Zool was also ported to the RISC OS platform.Reviews for the Amiga version of the game were extremely positive, possibly partly because the need was felt for the Amiga to have a flagship game to rival Sonic. However some criticism was aimed at the blatant and pervasive product placement in the game for lollipop company Chupa Chups, in the first three levels (known as 'Sweet Zone'). Another frequent criticism of the game was that it was excessively difficult. Some contemporary reviewers complained of not being able to get further than the second level (Music Zone).Hints:- Extra Energy and Time -B, A, Right, Right, A, C, Up, Down, and A- Extra Life -Down, Up, Left, Left, A, Right, and Down - Stage/Level Skip -Pause the game and press C, Right, A, B, B, A, Left, Left, A, Right, and Down. Press Up to skip a stage or Right to skip a level- The "Pause" Screen will now be brighter. -Pause, Hold Start and press Down, Up, Left, Left.- Tons of Extra Energy and Time -Hold Start and press Right, A, Down, A, Right, B, Left, Up, Right, and then press A + B + C at the same time.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zoolhttp://www.gamefaqs.com/console/genesis/data/586627.htmlCheat: Cheat CodesWhen in-game, hold down Start and press A, B, Right, A, C, A, Down, A, B, Right, A (ABRACADABRA). You can now fly anywhere, but if you get hit by an enemy, the affect will be removed.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>Xz99maNBLOM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3128</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/genesis/586627-zool-ninja-of-the-nth-dimension</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/3128-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/3128-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/3/7/gfs_39110_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/7/gfs_39110_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/5/7/gfs_39110_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/7/gfs_39110_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/f/7/gfs_39110_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/2/7/gfs_39110_1_6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/7/gfs_39110_1_7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/4/6/gfs_39110_1_8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/f/6/gfs_39110_1_9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/e/gfs_39110_1_10.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/3128-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DeR7nxZ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/3128.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>His name is Zool. He is a Ninja in the 2345th dimension, 6 worlds each with 3 stages.  In this platformer, you can run, jump, climb walls and shoot the enemies. In the levels are also some power-ups for Zool. There are life-spending hearts, smart bombs, shields, more powerful jump-skill and a twin Zool. This "twin" makes all your motions a few seconds after you do. In the options you can change the difficulty and the game-speed two times, the continues and the background music (Rock or Funk).</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a8bd7a58-31c7-42b0-9bc4-7d426a87e1fa.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f19b3274-67a2-46ff-bd7a-0a115f549560.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c5a96ab-bf96-4b68-a57d-a3c438f425fa.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3635e125-17a9-4b1b-a2f9-4ecf2b98fcd6.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ce9b17b-a364-43e5-8cd5-b55cdc04879f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4ac2f40-dadb-494c-a0b3-6f8bc5a5bdec.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01594b8d-a8c8-41a9-93db-e7fee2998674.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20bade54-bab5-412d-9751-832a39923af5.jpg</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>