<Game>
	<Name>Harobots (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Harobots was first released on the Wonderswan in 1999 and then on the Game Boy Color (as Harobots GB) in 2000. It was developed by anime giant Sunrise's videogame division, and draws on the company's vast library of robot anime series. It follows the formula of many   Pokemon-like RPGs and features a young protagonist who wants to become a "Harobots Battle" Master.  Represented Anime Harobots features more than three dozen robot anime series. Interestingly enough, aside from the Haro itself Mobile Suit Gundam is not represented in any way.  G-BreakerBlue Comet SPT LayznerThe Brave of Gold GoldranGasarakiPanzer World GalientMetal Armor DragonarRound Vernian VifamEnergetic Explosion GanbarugerStrongest Robo DaiojaWhirlwind! Iron LeaguerGiant GorgHeavy Metal L-GaimAura Battler DunbineOutlaw StarAbsolutely Invincible Raijin-OhCombat Mecha XabungleArmored Trooper VotomsFang of the Sun DougramSun Brave FyvardBrave RaideenSuper Robo GalattThe Vision of EscaflowneSpace Runaway IdeonBrave of Legend Da-GarnHot-Blooded Strongest Go-SaurerLord of Lords Ryu KnightSpirit Hero WataruSorcerer King GranzortInvincible Steel Man Daitarn 3Invincible Super Man Zambot 3Invincible Robo Trider G7Brave ExkaiserBrave Police J-DeckerThe Brave Express Might GaineThe King of Braves GaogaigarThe King of Braves Gaogaigar FINALBrain PowerdBettermanThe Big OInfinite Ryvius</plot>
	<releasedate>7/10/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27614</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/harobots/3030-31318/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/27614-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan/Named_Titles/Harobots%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<Notes>Harobots is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Sunrise Interactive, which was released in Japan in 1999.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e019086-3446-4c7e-b821-123fa9a70a53.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/908236c0-2596-4f60-82ae-7bb52e7b8caf.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c27d6b74-c38d-4ba1-862e-c5285029ced4.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d18291f-4e06-49a5-8c8c-54a67ed562ec.PNG</snapshot3>
	<Developer>Sunrise Interactive</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sunrise Interactive</Publisher>
</game>