<Game>
	<Name>Kaze no Klonoa - Moonlight Museum (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In this game, you control a boy named Klonoa. One day he sees a dream in which he learns that somebody has stolen a fragment of the moon. He is told that the thieves are probably some painters who took the moon fragment into a museum. As Klonoa enters the music, he gets teleported into a mysterious world. Now he has to use his wit in order to overcome all the obstacles in this world and retrieve the moon fragment.Kaze no Klonoa: Moonlight Museum is a platform game with an emphasis on puzzle-solving. The enemies you encounter can be inflated with the help of Klonoa's yo-yo, and carried around. You can throw them at other enemies, or use them to jump to higher ledges. In addition, there are various kinds of symbols you have to collect to open locked doors, teleporters, switches, time bombs, and other ingredients for puzzles.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/5/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>27628</thegamesdb_id>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/wonderswan/kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum/3030-2202/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/27628-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/313503-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/313504-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-media.jpg</media1>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan/Named_Titles/Kaze%20no%20Klonoa%20-%20Moonlight%20Museum%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154317-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154316-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154318-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-hey.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154319-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-klonoa.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154320-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-you.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154321-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154322-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154323-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-klonoa.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154324-kaze-no-klonoa-moonlight-museum-wonderswan-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Kaze no Klonoa: Moonlight Museum (風のクロノア ムーンライトミュージアム?, Kaze no Kuronoa Muunraito Myuujiamu, lit. "Klonoa of the Wind: Moonlight Museum") is a video game developed and published by Namco and released exclusively in Japan for the Bandai WonderSwan in 1999. As Klonoa's first handheld adventure, it is the first game in the series to place him in a fully two-dimensional world, and establishes the system that his Game Boy Advance titles will use. Taking place sometime before Klonoa: Door to Phantomile, Klonoa's first game, Kaze no Klonoa: Moonlight Museum stars Klonoa and his friend Huepow as they come across a young crying girl who tells them that the moon has been divided into fragments and stolen by a mysterious group of artists that reside in the nearby Moonlight Museum. Determined to help, the duo rush off to the Museum's entrance, and once they come inside, they are greeted by a painter named Picoo who traps them inside a piece of artwork. Klonoa and Huepow must fight their way through five worlds within the Museum itself before finding the source of all their troubles and restoring the moon to the sky.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6aa7ae55-e532-4d2c-85f6-39cc391ee144.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b838feb-3576-46b8-94ca-6d1b6c71b5c9.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98d11460-35c7-4a13-962a-a673ee23f10a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06387c88-f7f2-427a-a4d3-2f7bc0643cd4.PNG</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>