<Game>
	<Name>Rockman & Forte - Mirai Kara no Chousensha (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The game's title screen.Rockman &amp; Forte: Mirai kara no Ch&#333;sensha (literally translated as Rockman &amp; Forte: Challenger from the Future) was released on October 28, 1999 in Japan for the WonderSwan. The game was developed by  Capcom and published by  Bandai. Rockman &amp; Forte is in the  Mega Man franchise; pertaining more to the games that starring  Mega Man and  Bass (Rockman and Forte in Japan).The DimensionsPlot:It is the year 20XX in Symphony City, where robots and humans can live in harmony and peace. Suddenly, a group of robots calling themselves the Dimensions attacks Symphony City. Their leader is a robot with similar power to Rockman who has dubbed himself Rockman Shadow. Rockman sees this tragedy from  Dr. Light's laboratory, and goes to investigate. At the same time,  Dr. Wily sees the event from his laboratory and sends Forte to investigate.Gameplay:A screenshot of Rockman, early in the game.As in the previous title,  Mega Man &amp; Bass, there are two characters to select: Rockman and Forte. Rockman handles just about the same, with the ability to charge his attacks and slide on the ground. Forte can shoot quickly, but cannot charge, and can dash and double jump as opposed to sliding. A notable difference from previous Mega Man games is the fact that  Robot Masters do not have a period of invincibility after they have been hit, making it possible to continually hit them. A unique stage, Aircon Man's stage, requires that the handheld be tilted so that the game can be played vertically. There are five weapons to be gathered in this game, with only Compass Man not giving up a weapon.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/7/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai</Developer>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rockman-forte-mirai-kara-no-chousensha/3030-24425/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/800248-rockman_fortews.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14761/856583-back_cover.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/libretro/libretro-thumbnails/master/Bandai%20-%20WonderSwan/Named_Titles/Rockman%20%26%20Forte%20-%20Mirai%20Kara%20no%20Chousensha%20(Japan).png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/841330-rockman___forte___mirai_kara_no_chousen_sha.png</snapshot2>
</game>